? ?
? Dexter 7x07 ?
Do the Wrong Thing
Original Air Date on November 11, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Previously
on Dexter...
This blood is
from a defensive wound.
So you got arrested,
there'll be a trial,
you'll go to prison
for a long time.
Does that mean
this is over?
No.
These men
are dangerous.
You should not get involved
with the Koshka brotherhood.
Don't be scared.
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.
Where's Nadia?
Isaak Sirko wants you
to lose the blood evidence
linking him
to the Colombian murders.
If I do this,
Nadia is a free woman.
Deal.
What was Price
doing here?
He heard we dug up
more Wayne Randall victims,
he asked if he could see
the case files.
I fudged
the blood report.
My guy said
the void pattern on this body
indicates a killer
much smaller than Wayne Randall.
Smaller,
like Hannah McKay?
And I think
she kept right on killing.
If that's true,
we're totally fucked.
We gave her immunity.
So how'd he die--
your husband?
Uh
heart attack.
I know she killed
her husband, I can feel it.
Aconite.
Ingesting it
causes heart attack.
Do what you gotta do.
Dexter--
- chemistry.
I've heard
some people have it.
An attraction that can't be
quantified or explained.
Is that the reason
behind this...
Loss of control?
Maybe the desire
to get Hannah on my table
was just a way to deny
the effect she has on me.
So now what?
How do you like it?
Not much.
You do this to all the girls
that you go out with?
Wrap them up in plastic?
I don't actually
go out.
So then, what?
This whole date thing was just
a way to get me alone
so you can kill me?
Why?
It's what I do.
You kill people.
Bad people.
So you think I'm bad.
You
you fit
the general description.
You have no idea.
You know, I didn't plan
to spend the whole evening
talking about
Hannah McKay.
Well, what do you want
to talk about?
The economy?
I don't know.
What kind of music
you like?
Um...
A jailhouse door
slamming shut.
That's my idea of music.
I don't know
what's driving me crazier,
Hannah McKay getting away
with a shitload of murder,
or you chewing
on that straw.
Old habits die hard.
You know, it's gonna be
a real downer for your book
if Hannah gets away.
Now that you mention it,
people who buy true crime stuff
tend to like it
when the bad guy gets caught.
Well, maybe I can help you
rewrite the ending.
So now
you're an editor.
I'm thinking about
Hannah's husband.
40-year-olds don't just
drop dead of a heart attack.
Maybe I could
have the body exhumed,
and we could test it
for aconite.
It's been ten years.
But if it's there,
the tox screen will find it.
And the hard part
is getting permission.
Hannah's
the next of kin,
and I doubt
she's gonna sign off on it.
She's not the only
next of kin.
Hannah's husband
had a sister.
Well, aren't you
a goddamn know-it-all.
It's not
my only virtue.
That remains
to be seen.
Thank you
for dinner.
We should
do it again.
Yeah, why not?
I'll check my notes
on the sister
and get back to you.
Chemistry deals
with the reactions
between elementary
forms of matter.
Separate the elements,
and you negate the reaction.
This can't happen again.
Which part?
The horse tranquilizer?
The sex part.
Yeah, I was thinking
the same thing.
W
why?
We both know
it wouldn't end well.
Just tell me something.
What?
You're not gonna
try and kill me again, right?
Because I feel like
I have the right to know.
No. If I was, we wouldn't be
having this conversation.
Let's just think of it
as a misunderstanding.
One way to put it.
You know, you don't really
seem that shaken up.
You know, for someone
who thought she was gonna die.
Yeah, you're right,
I suppose I should be
a little more
freaked out.
Maybe I never
really believed that
you were gonna do it.
Boy, did he pick
the wrong car.
Oh don't, don't.
It was an interesting night.
That's one way
to put it.
You know, you never
really asked me
why I kill people.
I don't need to.
Price.
The man thrives on stories,
and I've just given him
a great twist.
If he writes
about Hannah and me
my career is a memory.
Clouds parted,
and much was revealed.
And that would be?
Now I know
why the blood work
on the Wayne Randall spree
was so spotty.
You were
protecting someone.
As far
as Price knows,
I'm an innocent lab geek
in over his head.
How long have you
been seeing her?
What do you want
to keep quiet?
It's not in my nature
to keep quiet about anything.
You can't write
about this.
It's nothing personal.
I'm just doing my job.
You'll destroy my job.
Sorry.
No way around that.
You could always
go on the record,
help me
get my facts straight.
I love writing about crimes
from the inside.
What if I give you
something better?
What better than "lab tech
seduced by femme fatale?"
I was the last one
to speak with Wayne Randall.
I could tell you
what his last words were.
How he really felt
about Hannah.
How do I know
you wouldn't be
making something up
to save your ass?
I wouldn't be,
but you'd have to judge
for yourself.
Either way,
I'd be on the record.
I'll give it
some thought.
In the meantime, I'll keep quiet
about you and Hannah McKay.
Show of good faith.
Between you and me,
I'd watch what I eat
around her.
I'll be in touch.
As if I needed another reason
to stay away from Hannah.
At least I've bought myself
some time.
This a good time?
Yes.
My theory
on the barrel girl killers
went nowhere.
I'm on a dead end
on bay harbor butcher.
- Shit.
- I was thinking
we could brainstorm.
I keep wondering
if we haven't missed something.
You know,
some angle, or--
- you know, maybe
we haven't missed anything.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, maybe
we've been sidetracked
by our feelings
about Sergeant Doakes.
I think
we've been objective.
Well, I guess I'm just
not sure, you know?
I know what it's like
to hold on
to an idea of someone,
you know?
To refuse to believe
that they have a dark side,
but everything we've done,
all the evidence,
it still
points to sergeant doakes.
At some point,
we have to face facts.
It's possible that we've been
reaching for leads.
So should we rethink
what we're doing here?
I mean, I just--
I don't know if it's worth it.
Maybe you're right.
I'm fucking
going to hell.
Sal Price made his living
writing about
the dark things
people do,
but he doesn't seem to have
a dark side of his own.
At least nothing
I can use.
You have a minute?
Sure.
- What's this?
- It's your blood spatter report
on the Wayne Randall
victims.
- What about it?
- Well, there's something weird
I was hoping
you could clear it up.
This blood spatter
points to a killer
other than Wayne Randall.
Someone smaller.
And how'd you
come to that?
Sal Price had an outside lab
run an analysis.
They found
the discrepancies.
Did you miss this?
Price strikes again.
Where will he
show up next?
Deb, I didn't miss
anything.
I considered
the same scenario.
And?
Bl
blood spatter
is largely a matter
of interpretation,
but I'm convinced
Wayne was the sole killer.
These blood drops
came from the killer.
You could've tested them
to see if they matched
Wayne Randall's DNA,
just to be sure.
I was sure.
I didn't think the test
was worth the time
or the money.
Especially since the case
had been solved.
You wanna just come out
and say what you want to say?
Hannah McKay
killed this woman
and you're covering
for her.
Why would I want
to do that?
To save her
for your table.
You're wrong, Deb.
If you want,
I'll have the blood tested.
Just say the word,
we can spend the money.
I'll think about it.
You smell that?
- What?
- Sulfur, mixed with shit.
Means Isaak Sirko's attorney
is on his way.
They want to run
their own analysis
on the samples we took
from Mateo's.
Hmm.
Confirm that it's
his client's blood we found.
Masuka's grabbing it now.
I'll have it ready
for them.
That evidence should keep Isaak
locked up for a long time.
One less killer
to worry about.
I just checked
the freezer.
The evidence on Sirko
is gone.
Or not.
How in the hell does the most
crucial piece of evidence
against Isaak Sirko
just disappear
from our own
police station?
I don't know.
I logged the blood samples
into evidence myself.
There's only
one explanation.
The Koshka brotherhood
has a mole inside Miami Metro.
A mole?
You read too many spy novels.
Maybe the evidence
just got misplaced.
Hey, we do not
misplace evidence.
And who reads anymore?
Simmer down, tiger mom,
nobody's blaming you.
Masuka's right.
This is why Sirko's attorney
asked for early discovery.
He knew the evidence
would be missing,
we'd be left there
holding our dicks.
We can find out
who's responsible later.
Right now,
we have 24 hours
to find those blood samples,
or to come up with new evidence.
And if we don't,
Sirko walks.
I'm gonna go
check the evidence room log.
See who's been there
in the last couple of days.
The crime scene at Mateo's
hasn't been released yet.
Maybe we could re-collect
a sample of Sirko's blood.
Fucking haul your ass
over there.
Masuka, Quinn,
go with him.
We let a fish this big slip
through our net,
I'm gonna be
very unhappy.
You and me both.
Angel, what's going on
with the restaurant?
I've been approved
to take over the lease,
but I still need a few thousand
to keep the place running.
What are you
gonna do?
Turn over
all the cushions,
stand in the corner
with a tin cup,
I don't know.
Ugh. Ugh.
Ugh
holy shit.
I don't know
about the holy,
but there's no denying
the shit part.
Fucking Koshkas.
They fucked up
the sewage line
to contaminate
the crime scene.
Which means
Sirko will be free soon.
And I'll have to kill him
before he comes after me.
Need any more proof
that there's a mole
in the department?
I hate to ask,
but would you guys
take a look around,
see if there's any blood
anywhere
that's not mixed
with crap?
I wouldn't get
my hopes up.
They do not
pay us enough for this.
Quinn,
can I talk to you outside?
Yeah, why don't you guys
wait outside
while we're in here
vomiting?
The list of visitors
of the evidence lock-up
in the last 72 hours.
- Your name's on it.
- So?
So what were you
doing in there?
I don't know,
my job, maybe?
I'm a detective,
occasionally I have to go
to the evidence lock-up.
What was the case?
The Dixon murders.
I gotta testify next week.
Just wanted to make sure
I had my ducks in a row.
What the fuck
you insinuating?
You're dating a stripper
that works at a club
that's owned
by the Koshka brotherhood.
So you think I stole evidence
for the Koshkas?
Doesn't look good.
Fuck you.
Hold on.
You're no choirboy,
but I know
you wouldn't sink that low.
Then why the fuck
are we talking about this?
Because
I'm doing my job,
and I needed to hear it
from you.
No, it looks like
it was deliberate, Deb.
We're not gonna find any
new evidence, at least not here.
We're halfway through another
sweep of the evidence room,
and so far
we've got fucking zip.
I don't think
you're gonna find anything.
Neither do I.
Dexter, if this case
falls apart and Isaak walks,
he could be
on the street tonight.
I know.
Just have to
take care of him myself.
Stay the fuck
away from him.
I don't think ignoring Isaak
is the right approach.
I'm not gonna ignore him.
I'm gonna put a tail
on him 24/7
until his travel visa
expires.
He's not gonna be able
to pick the crust out of his eye
without us
knowing about it.
So don't fucking
do anything.
I won't.
Except use the time
to get Sal Price off my back.
The address for the sister
of Hannah's late husband.
Her name's Lori.
Have you ever heard
of this thing called email?
I like interacting
with people face to face.
Especially when their face
looks like yours.
You can cancel that shit
right now.
You got a problem
with compliments?
Yes, I do,
when they're slightly cheesy
and they come
out of the blue, yeah.
I'll try to contact Lori
and get permission
for the exhumation.
Can I tag along,
for the interview?
No.
It's gonna be
awkward enough
without some goofy writer
hovering over us.
Well then, maybe we can
meet later for drinks
and you can fill me in.
I did get you the info.
Come on.
It'll be
totally off the record.
Fair enough.
But I'm buying.
You all right?
I'm okay.
I thought I wasn't
going to see you again.
They hurt you?
No.
They sent me to their club
in Fort Myers.
I was so scared.
I thought for sure
they were
going to send me
back to Kiev.
I'd burn down every one
of their fucking clubs
before I let that happen.
Oh, my God, Joey.
Did you promise them something
to keep me here?
Don't worry
about it.
I warned you
about the Koshkas.
I can take care
of myself.
And I can take care
of the both of us.
Hmm?
Look at me.
Very soon, you're never
gonna have to work
for any of those people
again.
I-I don't understand.
What w--
what have you done?
You're gonna be free.
Trust me.
Touched you wanted
to be part of
my welcome back committee.
More like a parade.
Heat like that's
gotta make
a flight home to Kiev
feel pretty good.
Not yet, George.
Miami is still overcrowded,
by one.
So you said this was
about my brother Jake?
Yes.
This may be
a little upsetting,
but we need your permission
to exhume his body.
Exhume his body?
Why?
Evidence has come to light
that your brother's death
may not have been
an accident.
But Jake died
of a heart attack.
We believe
he may have been poisoned,
and that his wife
was responsible.
Oh, my God.
Hannah?
That's what we're thinking.
Did she and your brother
get along?
Yeah, they seemed to have
a great relationship.
Looked like they were
totally in love.
Especially after they found out
she was expecting.
She was pregnant?
Yeah, she told me
in confidence.
I was surprised.
I didn't think
Hannah wanted kids.
What happened
to the baby?
She lost it.
Right after Jake's death.
It was a miscarriage.
You know, after the funeral,
Hannah cut everyone off.
It was like my whole side
of the family never existed.
No matter how many times
I reached out,
she just
wouldn't reciprocate.
Ms. Kirkwood, I think
we can find out for sure
what happened
to your brother.
We just need your help.
That looks heavy.
Need a hand?
I need you
out of my life.
That can be arranged.
All you have to do
is talk to me.
Well, everything
I have to say to you
can be summed up
in two words--
Let me guess--
"fuck off."
Glad we got that straight.
I want to write
the authorized biography
of Hannah McKay.
It'll go
through the roof.
God knows I haven't had
a decent seller in years.
I need this, Hannah.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I missed the last part over
the sound of my heart breaking.
You don't talk to me,
you'll force me to speculate.
Maybe even
get creative.
It takes brains
to be creative.
"Hannah McKay never lost
her taste for killing.
She just updated her technique
from knives to poison."
Just an excerpt
from the preface.
Along with some material
on one Dexter Morgan--
who's a fan of my work,
by the way,
and how he manipulated evidence
to help the woman he loved.
I'll deny everything.
Which will be
great publicity.
Okay.
Fine, we'll talk.
Just keep Dexter
out of this.
Depends on
what you give me.
My house, tomorrow,
4:00 p.m.
Hello?
It's your
favorite author.
Decided to take you up
on your Wayne Randall offer.
You won't be sorry.
I'll come
to your place.
How's tomorrow night sound?
7:00 p.m.?
7:00 it is.
Price covered a lot of murders
during his career.
The bloodier,
the better.
He likes getting at
his cases from the inside.
You can't get more inside
than becoming a suspect.
Christy Lawson.
Her killer was never found.
Price wrote a book
about her case.
One of his best sellers.
All I need is Price's DNA
to link him to the crime.
You should
throw that away, Dex.
Hannah needs to know
what's going on.
You're looking for an excuse
to see her.
You could just
pick up the phone.
Christ, Joey.
You're here so often,
we gotta get you
your own parking spot.
I did what you wanted.
The evidence
against Sirko is gone.
I want Nadia's passport.
She's done with you,
and your whole
shitty fuckin' organization.
Is she?
Yeah, and so am I.
We've been
working so well together.
Why kill a good thing?
Who do you think
you're fucking with?
Think I'm some
fuckin' asshole,
one of your
little fuckin' bag men?
- Take it easy.
- You know how badly
I could fuck you up?
It goes two ways,
Detective.
You destroyed
police evidence.
That'll get you
thrown off the force.
Hell, you'd probably
do time.
Stay the fuck away
from me.
That's not gonna happen,
Joey.
So you think real hard
about your next move,
and what it means
for your future.
And Nadia's.
You managed to stay away
from me for one whole day.
What happened
to our plan?
Sal Price happened.
Price?
He saw us together
when I dropped you off.
He threatened
to put me in his book.
I can't let that happen.
There's more.
He showed up
at the Flower Mart.
He wants me to go on record
about my time with Wayne,
or he'll say
that I'm a murderer.
I'm going to handle
Price.
Like
the way you handled me?
Not exactly.
I only go after killers.
Like me.
It's the code I live by.
Code, huh?
You know, sometimes
life just has to be taken.
There's no need
to dress it up.
It's more than that.
I think you're just afraid
to admit that you enjoy killing.
And you don't?
No.
Killing for me is just
surrendering
to nature's way.
Nature adds
and subtracts.
Survival of the fittest.
So you're the fittest.
So far.
You ever wonder
what it would be like
if you didn't have
all these rules?
Price doesn't have to die.
I can get him
to back off for good.
I'm used to dealing
with things on my own.
I don't need
somebody to protect me.
I know you don't.
But I have this covered.
Consider it
a good-bye present.
Okay.
Well, I suppose
we're going for a record.
A record?
How many times we can
say good-bye for good.
Goodbye.
She isn't drawn to my darkness
like Lila,
or blind to it
like Rita,
and she doesn't need it
like Lumen.
She accepts both sides of me.
The whole Dexter.
So why am I walking away
from this?
Because
when some chemicals mix
they combust, and explode.
You don't have
to be here.
He's my brother.
I understand.
You okay?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
There's no tissue.
That normal?
It is if the body
wasn't embalmed.
Isn't that
standard procedure?
Unless the next of kin
specifies otherwise.
Can we do the tests?
Not on bones,
Lieutenant.
There's nothing
I can do here.
What is it?
Your brother's remains--
he wasn't embalmed.
Wha
I don't understand.
We can't run the tests.
So you're saying
this was all for nothing?
I'm gonna find out
what happened, Lori.
I'm not gonna give up.
I can see
this was a good idea.
You look like
you need a drink.
Yeah, or five.
Excuse me.
Bottled brew
for the lady.
Uh
actually,
can I get a double scotch,
neat, please?
When do you get
the test results
for the exhumation?
We won't.
The body was more like
a pile of bones.
There was
nothing to test.
Shit.
He wasn't embalmed.
Yeah, and--
big surprise here--
it was all
at the discretion of...
Hannah.
Thank you.
That poor woman had to watch
her dead brother be dug up.
And for what?
I put her
through fuckin' hell.
You couldn't anticipate
this.
It's not your fault.
Well, it doesn't make it
any better.
Sometimes my job
really fuckin' sucks.
Actually,
it always sucks.
Why do you do it?
'Cause I don't know
how to do fuck-all else.
I'm sure
that's not true.
Oh, God, if you are
building up to a compliment
now is really not the time.
Look.
I'm gonna interview
Hannah later.
Maybe I can pull something
out of her.
Gross.
Well, you can tell me
how it went over dinner.
I might even let you pay.
Lemonade?
I'll pass.
Should we get started?
I just want to make sure
that we're clear.
You're going to forget
about Dexter Morgan.
He really got
under your skin, didn't he?
Just tell me
that you understand.
Never heard of him.
We'll start with the couple
from the motel.
I just need
enough of Price's DNA
to plant
at a crime scene.
Traces of blood.
Good for me,
bad for his gums.
The more you linger,
the greater
the chance
of being caught.
Crime scene data,
audio interviews.
It's Price's research
on Hannah.
If I get rid of it,
it'll cripple his book.
Maybe kill it.
You didn't come here
to protect Hannah.
You need to think
about yourself right now.
Wayne gave me
the knife
and told me
to guard the woman.
I figured it'd be easy,
seeing as how scared she was.
What was Wayne doing?
He started
to stab the husband.
Over and over and over.
The woman was screaming
like crazy.
The man she loved
was getting knifed
in front of her eyes.
But he, uh--
he didn't--
he didn't give up.
He grabbed Wayne
and he pulled him toward him.
And--and then the woman
jumped on Wayne.
The woman
you were guarding.
Yeah, she was just
protecting her husband.
I don't blame her, I--
I would've done
the same thing.
Keep going.
Wayne was yelling for me
to get her off him, so I--
I grabbed her by the hair and
I pulled her to the bed,
and she just--
she just kept screaming,
and s--
and screaming.
So I--
I stabbed her.
And she just
kept screaming.
And there was
so much blood.
What did you do?
I stabbed her
until the screaming stopped.
Take a second.
Looks tasty.
Certainly better than the swill
I've choked on of late.
Don't worry,
I haven't come down here
to cause you harm.
Not yet.
Not with
Miami Metro's finest
shadowing
my every move.
Yes, I certainly hope
they are the finest.
For your sake.
What do you want?
Well, so long as
I'm waiting around to kill you
I thought we might
have a little chat.
Mmm.
Good chips.
While I was
incarcerated,
I found myself plagued
with a nagging question.
I mean, I will
move heaven and earth
to snuff out your life
because you killed Viktor--
in fact, I was so blinded
by my desire for vengeance
that you were able to lead me
into a trap.
A mistake I assure you
won't happen again.
We have a cartoon
in America
about a coyote
who chases after a roadrunner.
He keeps thinking that.
He keeps rocket-skating
right off the cliff.
You see, I know
what motivates me.
But what I don't know
is what drove you
to kill my friend.
I told you.
He killed Mike Anderson.
A man you barely knew
for what,
less than
three months?
Oh, it's all
public record.
No.
You didn't kill Viktor
out of vengeance.
I have a feeling
that you're a different
kind of animal.
The question is...
What kind are you,
Dexter Morgan?
The kind who hunted
your friend down
and strapped him
to a board,
and put a plastic bag
on his head,
and crushed his skull
with a fire extinguisher.
The kind who's going to
do the same thing to you,
give or take
the fire extinguisher.
You're going to regret
sharing that with me.
For the chip.
This is
the last load.
- Thanks, Jamie.
- Mm-hmm.
You know,
you're an interesting guy.
Have a seat.
I should do
my next book on you.
Believe me,
I know a good story
when I hear one.
You know,
as a blood spatter analyst,
I'm kind of
a storyteller myself.
Only difference
between us is
your medium's ink,
and mine's blood.
Interesting
observation.
Uh, before we
talk about Wayne,
I have a story idea
of my own.
Uh, mostly non-fiction.
I wanted to get
your take.
I'm all ears.
So new DNA evidence
pops up
in the unsolved murder
of Christy Lawson.
You know, the jogger who was
killed near Matheson Park.
It turns out that the DNA
belongs to
a true crime writer.
You said it was
mostly non-fiction.
Sounds like
it's all bullshit.
Well, the anonymous tip
is real enough.
The one that mentions
Sal Price.
It seems he wrote
a very successful book
about the same case.
Now it turns out
he was her killer.
You have to appreciate
the irony.
How do you plan
to make this happen, exactly?
Let's just say
you're gonna need
a new electric toothbrush.
You broke
into my apartment?
No, I very carefully
picked your lock.
By the way, it's time
to visit the dentist.
You son of a bitch!
Hey, it's nothing
personal.
I just can't have you
messing with my life.
Fuck you!
You're not gonna
get away with this.
I'm gonna ruin your--
Hannah.
God, what happened?
Call 911.
911, what is
your emergency?
I need an ambulance
at 8240 Palm Terrace.
Apartment 10.
So I came in
to see if Dexter was okay,
and I saw that guy
on the floor.
Uh, Dexter told me
to call 911,
and he started CPR.
Did you hear anything
before the crash?
There was some shouting.
Kinda like an argument.
Dexter's voice?
Mm, I didn't
recognize the voice.
I administered CPR
until the paramedics showed up,
but he was unresponsive.
Okay, Dex.
I think it's all here.
Hey, were you and Price
arguing before he collapsed?
The interview might have
gotten a little heated.
How heated?
He accused me
of sloppy work
on the Wayne Randall case.
I might have
raised my voice a little.
That's all.
A contusion
to the head.
The source
of all the blood.
But that's not enough
to kill a man.
Okay, just wait
for the medical examiner
to get here, okay?
Why all the blood, Dex?
His head struck the table
as he fell.
Jesus.
You okay?
No, I'm not okay.
I can't even
have a drink with someone
without them dying.
- You had a drink with him?
- Yeah.
He was nice, you know?
I liked him.
Did Price tell Deb
about me and Hannah?
Doubtful.
Deb would have already
brought it up.
I can't believe--
I'm sorry, Deb.
I wish I could tell you
what happened.
I know what happened.
Hannah McKay.
She killed Price.
- What makes you think that?
- He was convinced that
she stabbed one of the victims
on the spree.
And that she
kept on killing.
Her husband, other people.
All with poison. He was gonna
put it in his book.
She poisoned Price.
It's not a coincidence.
How would she
pull that off?
I don't know.
But I'm gonna pick her up
for questioning.
I'm gonna run a tox screen
on his body.
She's not gonna
get away with it.
Not this time.
Hannah must know
that Price's body
will be tested for poison.
So why isn't she concerned?
Or is she just that good
at hiding it?
Mrs. McKay,
I'm Lieutenant Morgan.
Do you want anything
before we get started?
A water?
Coffee?
Uh, just want to know
what I'm doing here.
Okay.
Sal Price is dead.
Oh, my God.
She is that good.
Uh, what happened?
I was hoping
you could tell me that.
How can I do that?
Ms. McKay,
I was really hoping
that we could
cut through the crap.
Sal Price was
writing a book on you.
You didn't like it,
so you poisoned him.
That's crazy.
You're a killer,
Ms. McKay.
You're a fucking good one,
I'll give you that.
You've gotten away with it
for a long time.
But I have a blood report
on Beverly Grey
that proves she was killed
by a plant
that grows
on your property.
And I have a forensics report
on the Wayne Randall bodies
that prove that you stabbed
one of their victims to death.
I'm not even sure
why we're talking about that.
I have immunity
for the Wayne Randall killings.
Right,
and the Beverly Grey evidence
is circumstantial.
Unless I can tie it to
the poisons that I'm gonna find
in the tox screen that
I just ordered for Sal Price.
That is gonna nail
your fucking ass to the floor.
I didn't do anything
to Sal.
No. He just dropped dead
of a heart attack.
Sometimes
people die.
It doesn't mean
that they were poisoned.
Is that what happened
to your husband?
Did he just die?
Along with
your unborn baby?
What the fuck happened,
Ms. McKay?
Was he pressuring you
to have a family?
Was it making you
feel trapped?
She's not acting.
Charge me with something,
or let me go.
I am trying to give you
an opportunity
to come clean
about Sal Price.
You'll be doing yourself
a big favor
when your case
comes to trial.
- Am I done here?
- Yeah. You're done.
Trust me.
You know, my grandma
has this saying.
"Trust those who
seek the truth,
"but doubt those who say
that they have found it."
My grandma
wasn't ever wrong.
Hannah survived
Deb's questioning,
but she might not make it
through mine.
Price was going
to destroy my life.
I had to do something.
I told you
I would take care of it.
Well, you weren't exactly
giving me progress reports.
I saw a chance
and I took it.
I was doing it
for you too.
For me?
He died in my apartment!
My living room
is a crime scene.
You know who I am, what that
means to someone like me.
I figured it would kick in
while Price was on the road,
a convenient
auto accident.
How'd you do it?
Is it really
important?
Is life in prison
I'm never
going to prison.
Price liked to chew
on his pens.
The last one had
a little something on it,
completely undetectable.
You better hope so.
I know so.
Just wish I could've destroyed
Price's book along with him.
Actually,
I took care of Price's book.
You what?
How?
I was at his apartment,
collecting DNA samples
for my now-defunct plan
to get him to shut up,
and I erased
his research on you.
Thanks.
It only took a minute.
I could feel you watching me
while I was being interrogated.
You saw the whole thing,
didn't you?
Is it true
about your husband?
Did you kill him because you
didn't want a family?
It was the opposite.
I wanted a family,
and he didn't.
He threatened to leave me
unless I got an abortion.
What happened
to the baby?
It was
a miscarriage.
Sometimes life subtracts.
Sometimes it adds.
Do you realize
what happened?
We were looking out
for each other.
That's big
for people like us,
maybe even historic.
What's this?
For your restaurant.
- It's 10 grand.
- You know I got
that inheritance
a while back.
I've been looking for
the right place to invest.
I can't take this.
What are you, crazy?
Why, you too good
for my fucking money?
No, this is
way too generous.
Bullshit.
It's family money.
You're family to me.
Quinn-
Look, you're stuck with it.
I'm not taking it back.
I do expect
a few free meals, though.
This is a loan,
you asshole.
I'm gonna pay you back.
Okay, big guy.
We're good.
Report's back
on the tox screen on Sal Price.
This can't be right.
M.E. ran it twice.
Negative both times.
That fucking bitch is gonna
get away with it again.
Wayne was yelling
for me
to get her off him,
so I grabbed her by the hair
and I pulled her to the bed,
and--and she just--she just
kept screaming and screaming
So I--
I stabbed her,
and she just kept screaming
and there was so much blood.
What did you do?
I stabbed her
until the screaming stopped.
Not only
can't I kill her,
I can't seem
to stay away from her.
Even when I'm not with Hannah,
she's there, in my head.
When some elements
come together,
they create a reaction
that can't be reversed.
They transcend
chemistry.
Is this
what love feels like?
Is this how it begins?
Am I even capable of this?
Hello?
Hannah McKay
killed Sal Price,
and she's gonna walk.
She's gonna
get away with it,
and we both know
she's gonna kill again.
Deb, can we talk about this
in the morning?
He didn't deserve
to die.
I can't
let this happen.
There has to be
some fucking justice.
It's you, Dex.
Me?
You know
what I'm saying?
She deserves it.
I want you
to make it right.
Do what you do.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==