?
? Dexter 7x11 ?
Do You See What I See?
Original Air Date on December 9, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Previously on Dexter...
Our primary suspect
is Sergeant James Doakes.
Doakes?
If Doakes really wasn't
the Bay Harbor Butcher,
the best thing to do is to look
into Doakes's final days.
We should start with the cabin
in the Everglades
where Doakes died.
I was renting the place
to Santos Jimenez.
Jimenez.
He was one
of the three men responsible
for killing Dexter Morgan's
biological mother.
What if Dexter
is the real Bay Harbor Butcher?
If somebody's gonna talk
to Dexter, it's gonna be me.
Tell your boyfriend
who you belong to.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay. Go. Go. Now.
He died
in my apartment.
Figured it would kick in
while Price was on the road.
A convenient auto accident.
How'd you do it?
Price liked to chew
on his pens.
The last one
had a little something on it.
She is a killer.
You will never be safe
with her.
When Hannah
got out of juvie,
she killed a counselor
at a halfway house.
She fed him rat poison.
Her roommate, a little gal
named Arlene Shram,
saw her do it.
He won't be bothering you
again.
I love you.
I think
I love you too.
We need to find a woman
named Arlene Shram.
Sure.
Who's that?
According to a message
I got last night
from Hannah McKay's father,
she's a witness
to a murder.
I've never thought
about the future.
About growing old.
Maybe because the future
has never been kind
to people like me.
Or their loved ones.
Bye, Dad.
Bye, Harrison.
But suddenly my future
seems very possible.
And growing old
is not only a possibility.
It seems appealing.
Hello?
Am I speaking
with Dexter Morgan?
Yeah, that's right.
This is Dade County
Department of Corrections.
Hector Estrada...
Wait. What?
- Is having a parole hearing.
- When?
- This morning
at 10:00 a.m.
I know this is sudden.
Okay, thank you
for letting me know.
You're welcome, sir.
That was the Department
of Corrections.
Hector Estrada is up
for parole.
He thinks there's a good chance
he'll get it.
Estrada?
Remember, I told you
about my mother
and how she died?
Oh, God.
Was he--was he one of the men
that killed her?
He was the leader.
He gave the order.
What about the others?
Dead.
Estrada is the last survivor.
I'm sure you'll have something
to say about that.
Look at it this way.
Maybe it's the universe
giving you a Christmas present.
No one but you
would see it that way.
Maybe killing Estrada will close
this chapter of my life...
and open me up
to a future with Hannah.
The panel has reviewed
all the pertinent data
in this matter.
We find that the prisoner meets
the requirements for parole
under the compassionate release
statute 463.
Have you read the statute?
Do you understand
your obligations?
I understand
what's expected of me.
I won't screw up.
At this time we invite
any victims present
to enter a statement either for
or against the board's decision.
I have no objection.
Nadia, it's me again.
This is my fifth message.
Just want to know
where you are.
Give me a call.
Did you get bad news?
Just trying
to find Nadia.
Hey.
Taking a survey.
Secret Santa this year
or no secret Santa?
I got enough presents
to buy, man.
Man, the Christmas spirit
around here
sucks big reindeer dicks.
Deb.
I found Arlene Shram.
- Oh, fucking amazing.
- She's living out in Hialeah.
Two drug arrests
since juvie.
Has two kids
from different fathers.
Temporarily lost custody
a year ago
due to her drug abuse.
Good to know.
We'll have to
go after her hard.
I might have to threaten
to take away
her mother of the year trophy.
Any luck in locating
Hannah's father?
No.
Zero.
He dropped the dime
on his daughter
and then skipped tn
like it was nothing.
Well, he's a drifter.
He could be anywhere.
Listen, um...
maybe we should let your brother
know what we're doing.
I mean, we're investigating
his girlfriend.
I already told Dexter that
if I found anything on Hannah,
that I'd act on it.
I still don't feel right
about this.
And I'm telling you
that it's my call.
Okay?
Matthews made his choices.
Now he spends Christmas alone
with his boat.
How close was I
to the same fate?
Oh, hand me
one of those zip ties
on the table there,
will you?
Thanks.
Fucking Christmas lights.
Every year I put 'em up,
and every year I wonder
why I bothered.
You said you wanted
to see me.
Yeah.
Yeah, thanks for coming out.
Sit.
I wanted to give you
a heads up on this idea
that Captain LaGuerta's
got into her head.
What?
The Bay Harbor Butcher.
Maria's convinced
that Doakes was innocent
and that the real killer
is still at large.
Actually, she thinks
it might be you.
Me?
I know.
Personally, I think she's had
one too many "mosquitos,"
or whatever they call
that goddamn drink.
But anyway,
here we are.
What makes her think
I'm the Bay Harbor Butcher?
She knows
your life story,
your childhood, what you saw
in that cargo container.
Most people...
that'd screw 'em up for life.
I mean, your brother went
through the same thing you did,
and look what happened to him.
He saw your mother dismembered
before his eyes,
and he went on
to dismember his own victims.
Drink?
No.
The Bay Harbor Butcher
also dismembered his victims.
Of course, your brother
wasn't the butcher.
The murders continued
after his death.
But it's weird, huh?
Another thing that's weird--
that cabin where Doakes died.
What about it?
Was rented
to a man named Jimenez.
He was one of the men
who killed your mother.
I mean,
what are the odds?
He's interrogating me.
You knew my father.
You've known me my whole life.
Do you think
I'm the Bay Harbor Butcher?
Of course not.
But if I don't ask
these questions,
Maria will.
You know, I always had
a bad feeling about Doakes.
He obviously didn't like me
too much
from the get-go.
Hmm.
Not exactly a secret.
But then that whole Bay Harbor
Butcher case came along,
and something happened that I've
never told anyone about.
- What?
- I saw Doakes on his boat.
Doakes had a boat?
Yeah.
I figured he used it
to dispose
of his victims.
He kept it
at the same marina as mine.
I moved my boat
to get away from him.
Why didn't you
ever come forward?
'Cause I didn't know
what he'd do to me
or my sister.
Yeah.
Doakes was
a pretty formidable guy.
Yeah.
I can imagine how scared
you must have been.
Sorry to put you
through all this, Dexter.
I'll talk to Maria.
Get her to move on.
No hard feelings?
None.
I've given them a boat
to search for.
Now I just have to make sure
there's something
for them to find.
Hey, don't splash your sister!
- Oh!
- I'm not gonna tell you again.
Sorry. They are nonstop.
No, I have a nephew
their age,
so I can relate.
Traded one vice
for another.
At least they can't take
your kids away for tobacco.
First Christmas clean and sober,
and it won't be the last.
Knock on wood.
Just want to keep
looking forward, you know?
That's kind of why I'm here,
Arlene.
To keep you looking forward.
To keep you out of jail,
actually.
Why would I be going
to jail?
As an accessory to murder.
He was a counselor
at a halfway house
where you resided
about ten years ago.
Someone spiked his coffee
with rat poison.
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about.
I'm not after you.
I'm after Hannah McKay.
She was your roommate
at the time of the murder.
And I know
it was her idea,
but you had some part in it.
You either helped
or you kept quiet.
What do you want from me?
I want to know
exactly what happened.
And in return I will promise you
immunity from prosecution,
I will keep you out of jail,
and I'll make sure
that your kids have their mother
to put presents
under the tree.
I'd like some time
to think about this.
Okay, do that.
And play with your kids.
'Cause, depending
on what you decide,
you might not get to do that
for a really long time.
?
Turn this way now.
Do you remember
the first and last time
dad took us to see Santa?
You yanked his beard,
and I asked for a gun.
Where the fuck are you,
the North Pole?
You haven't said anything
since we've been here.
What is it?
You sure you want to know?
Oh, Jesus.
Tell me.
LaGuerta's still looking
into the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Shit.
I talked to Matthews.
She's pulled him
into the investigation.
What?
It gets worse.
They think it's me.
You weren't gonna
fucking tell me?
Do they have anything?
I don't know.
I need to put them off this
once and for all.
How?
Give them definitive proof
that Doakes was the butcher.
It'll mean planting evidence.
You can't do that,
not with those two on your case.
I'll just have
to be very careful.
Now were you a good boy?
So what do you want
for Christmas?
Fuck it.
It's too risky for you.
I'll do it.
Deb, no.
I'm not gonna let Harrison
grow up without a father.
I don't want
to argue about it.
I just want this to be the end
once and for all.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Ready?
Say cheese, everyone.
Cheese.
I'm sorry, but I just
don't think Dexter Morgan
has anything to do
with the Bay Harbor Butcher.
You're letting
your personal feelings
for the Morgans completely cloud
your judgment.
And I think you're letting
whatever you had going
with Doakes make you blind
to his guilt.
I've heard of people
fucking their brains out,
Maria, but God almighty.
Well, that's low
even for you, Tom.
Look, let's just follow up
on this boat.
Look, if James had owned
a boat,
I would have known.
Well, call it
a wild guess,
but if he was using it
to dump his victims
into the ocean,
he probably would have tried
to keep its existence
a secret.
I swear, I never told anyone
I saw you poison that man.
I don't get how that stanky
detective could know about it.
Must have been my dad.
Why would he do that?
He needed money,
and I wouldn't give it to him.
You know my dad.
Yeah, unfortunately.
I can't go to jail, Hannah.
Losing my kids again?
I couldn't take it.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Hey, look at me.
When that fucking counselor
was putting his hands on us
and I shut him down for good,
you backed me up.
We always stuck together.
That's not gonna change now,
is it?
But that detective's
gonna come back.
She's not gonna let up.
I'm gonna figure
something out.
You just have
to stay strong, okay?
Not this one.
This one looks like Doakes.
Did you have to get
the biggest tree on the lot?
Well, anything smaller
than this
looks like
a Charlie Brown tree.
By the way, you still doing
Christmas day
with Debra and Harrison?
Yeah.
You can join us.
Not sure if Debra and me
in the same room
would be very Christmasy.
Okay.
Maybe we could start
a new tradition.
Christmas Eve this year
and next year,
the year after that.
I like that.
Except there is one problem.
What?
I haven't got you
a Christmas present yet.
I don't really
need anything.
Suit yourself.
I guess I'm just gonna have
to go out
and buy you
a pair of socks.
Hold up.
Hey. Hey.
That's not the walk
of a dying man.
I guess freedom
was the tonic he needed.
But I'll soon change that.
- Jenna.
- Hey, Quinn.
I'm looking for Nadia.
Do you know where she is?
Hey, pal,
find your own.
I'm sorry.
Does your wife know you're here?
No.
So shut the fuck up.
Nadia's in Vegas.
Vegas?
What are you talking about?
She moved there to work.
Got a job
in one of the casinos.
- When?
- Couple days ago.
She left you a note.
It's in my locker.
I probably shouldn't he
read it.
What did it say?
That she's sorry
but that she needed a new start.
Staying here
was too hard for her.
She was really broken up.
That all?
Oh, that you really
mean a lot to her
and she'll never forget
what you did for her.
I'll be done in a few minutes,
and I can go get it.
Thanks.
Last Christmas,
I was down in the keys.
This Christmas--
your garage.
No one's forcing you
to be here, Tom.
Oh, I'm too afraid
to leave you alone.
You might decide
I'm the Bay Harbor Butcher
and haul me in.
What is it?
Take a look.
It's a tackle box.
These are
deep-sea fishing lures.
Meaning?
Meaning they're the kind
you need a boat to use.
Jeez, what a mess.
Well, it's been empty
for years.
Doakes probably
scrapped his boat
once we were closing in
on him.
We don't know
Doakes used this place.
You're jumping
to conclusions.
This address came
from the tackle box...
Which came from the cabin
where Doakes died.
This isn't jumping
to a conclusion.
This conclusion's
hanging from your ass.
That private
forensics team of yours...
Yeah.
What about 'em?
Get 'em out here.
I think we just struck oil.
The blood's too degraded
to analyze,
but we found one print
on the hilt.
It's a match
for James Doakes.
You're certain?
No question, Captain.
Well, that sews it up.
Tom.
This evidence could have
been planted.
Dexter is a forensics expert
and he has the skills--
- Maria, it's over.
The fat lady isn't singing.
Her song is done.
She's getting dry-humped
in her dressing room.
Jesus Christ, Tom!
What is wrong with you?
Maria, why can't you
let this go?
I guess
because I feel
I owe it to James
to clear his name.
Why?
Because you two were a couple?
Because he was innocent.
You're not an investigator,
Maria.
Your talent's
in playing the game,
and you play a great one.
Hell, you beat me.
But either way...
I'm done here.
Now, I expect you to live up
to your end of the bargain.
40-year pay scale
on my pension.
I remember, Tom.
Don't worry.
You'll get what's coming to you.
I expect to.
Feliz navidad, Maria.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Don't tell me
we're fucking neighbors now.
I'm not here to fight with you
or trade insults.
That's a good thing,
'cause you probably wouldn't
last one round.
Uh, I came here to talk
to you about Dexter.
Dexter.
If you care about him
as much as I do,
you'll listen to what
I have to say.
Just hear me out.
That's all I ask.
I'm all ears.
Dexter is happy, and...
I know him well enough
to understand
that this is
a pretty big deal.
He's been through
a lot of trouble
and a lot of pain.
I can't deny that.
I think for the first time
in a really long time,
he's actually looking forward
to the future.
He talks about it.
About me and him together.
And I think that Dexter
could be a whole lot happier
if he knew that you and I
could find some common ground.
- For Dexter's sake.
- Yeah.
Hmm.
He really does seem to like
having you around.
I love him.
And I know that you do too.
Yeah, you bet I do.
Can't we work out
our issues?
I think we can.
It's because I love Dexter
that I'm willing to do
whatever it takes
to protect him from you.
I'm not gonna give up
until your murdering ass
is behind bars for good.
That's how we're gonna
work out our issues.
But, hey...
Thanks for stopping by.
Okay.
- Son of a bitch.
- You got a dead one.
Yeah.
Well, it's gonna have
to stay dead.
There's only so much
a man can do.
What brings you around?
Merry Christmas.
I noticed you were on empty.
Thanks.
I was also thinking about
the last conversation we had.
I owe you an apology.
I should have come forward
with my suspicion about Doakes.
More people would be alive.
No, if anyone
should apologize, it's me.
I was stupid.
I should never have even
entertained Maria's crazy theory
about you being
the Bay Harbor Butcher.
You think she'll ever
accept the truth?
She already has.
We found Doakes's boathouse.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
What's even more amazing
is what we found
hidden inside it.
I won't go into details
except to say
that it leaves no doubt
as to Doakes's guilt.
Believe me,
you won't have to worry
about LaGuerta anymore.
Well...
I gotta say that's
about the best Christmas present
I could have imagined.
You and me both.
Have a good Christmas
with your boy.
We will.
Christmas just got a lot less
merry for Hector Estrada.
My late-lamented dark passenger
would be very pleased.
If I can break this last strand
from my past,
do I get the future I want?
Yep.
I just went
to see Matthews again.
They're calling off
the investigation.
You sure?
Yeah. They bought it.
Everything.
Well, let's hope
they stay bought.
Thanks, Deb.
You Hector Estrada?
- I know you?
- You do now.
I'm Steve Gaskill.
Come on, man.
You're a legend.
You're gonna be a stain
on my shoe
if you don't crawl back
to where you came from.
Look, I know I'm probably
way outta line here,
but I really gotta tell you
about my situation.
I have this contact in Honduras,
an old army buddy.
He sends me a crate of Sativa
every other month.
I've been trying
to lay it off where I can,
you know, college campuses
and whatnot,
but keeps piling up.
It's just too much
for me to move.
How much
are we talking about?
Enough to make you
shit your pants.
Anyway, I've been trying
to find a way
into the Hispanic market.
Here you are.
It's kismet.
Kiss who?
It's, uh, good luck...
For both of us.
I can show you the stuff.
Let me know
if you're interested.
Maybe we can
work something out.
First, let me hear you say
you're not a cop.
I'm not a cop, man.
Jeez, we know a lot
of the same people--
Tuerto, Pepe Chao.
I've sold plenty
of shit to them.
Fuck!
Long time since I've dealt
with those guys.
Where and when?
35 Quayside Road.
Tonight. 10:00.
Unless you got something else
to do on Christmas Eve.
I'll see you then.
- Yep.
- Dex, it's angel.
Debra's at St. Joseph's
in Hialeah.
She's been
in a car accident.
I'll meet you
at the hospital.
Dex.
How is she?
She's fine.
Her wrist is broken,
and there's lots of bruising,
but she'll be out
by tomorrow.
What happened?
Apparently, she blacked out
or something behind the wheel.
Does Debra have a prescription
for antianxiety medication?
I mean, not that there's
a problem.
Most people do.
Yeah, she does. Why?
The doctor said there was
a lot of that in her system,
almost three times
the normal dose.
Now, maybe she lost track
on how much she took.
You know.
It happens.
Well, why is she here
in Hialeah?
Where was she going?
Um...
Debra drove out here
for an interview,
a second interview with a woman
named Arlene Shram.
Now, look, Dex, maybe I should
have told you this before now,
but...
Deb got a tip
that this woman,
Arlene Shram,
was a possible witness
to a murder...
A murder committed
by Hannah McKay.
Yes, you should have
told me.
Debra has a bug up her ass
with this girl.
Maybe that's why she took
all those antianxiety pills.
Because she's convinced that her
brother is dating a killer.
I don't know what happened.
I was tired.
I was driving.
I kept getting sleepier
and sleepier,
and I don't know,
I must have...
Closed my eyes for a second?
But the next thing I knew,
I was...
Hanging upside down
in a ditch.
Hanging by my seatbelt.
This is the most fucked-est
Christmas ever.
And were gonna spend it
with Arlene Shram.
Hannah told you.
Hannah knew?
She was at my house
yesterday
asking me to back off.
Arlene must have called her
after I left her house--
Hannah was at your house
yesterday?
Yes.
And now I'm here.
Fucking hell, Dexter.
She didn't poison you.
Well, I sure as shit didn't
swallow a handful of pills.
The doctor said
that it's possible
the drugs built up
in your system.
I took one.
One. Last night.
That drug has a short
half-life.
Gotta hand it to her.
That's a really good plan.
Making it look like
I accidentally took
too much of a prescription
that I have?
It's not a hard drug to get.
How would she even know
that you were on it?
- You must have mentioned it.
- I never did. No.
That's the thing about people
that poison people, Dexter--
they're really fucking sneaky.
So...
She, what, poisoned you
while she was at your house
last night?
I didn't let her inside
my house last night.
- Deb--
- I went for a run.
Maybe she broke in
after I left or something.
She broke into your house
and did what?
I don't know how she did it.
- Because she didn't.
- Fuck.
This is exactly what happened
to Sal Price.
As soon as he got close to
knowing the truth about Hannah,
she killed him.
There's no proof
that she killed Sal Price,
and there's certainly no proof
that she poisoned you.
Well, maybe we need
to find the proof.
I think there's another
explanation for what happened.
You took more of those pills
than you think you did.
You've been under
a lot of stress, Deb.
No shit, Sherlock.
So you took one
and you lost track.
You took another.
And another--
it's possible.
It happens.
You have to admit that.
Right?
Deb's more right
than she knows
about what happened
to Sal Price.
But Hannah wouldn't
do that to Debra.
Would she?
I make my living at crime
scenes, proving what happened.
But now can I prove
what didn't happen?
Prove that Hannah
didn't poison Debra?
Is this proof
that Hannah was here?
Did she break in?
Or did she simply walk through
an open door?
Or did this fall off me?
Did I track this in just now?
The drug works quickly.
Deb would have passed out
minutes after ingesting it.
Sorry for your loss.
No. My sister's
doing fine.
Yeah. Can't say the same
thing for this poor baby.
You'll have to go in
through the passenger side.
I'll see what the lab
has to say
about what's in this bottle.
Hannah didn't poison Debra.
All I want for Christmas
is for that to be true.
Merry Christmas Eve.
We're having a noche buena
at the restaurant later.
Auri will be there.
You should come by.
Uh, thank you but, uh...
I'm not up for it.
Holidays, family, cheer...
They're keeping Debra
overnight at the hospital.
I thought you
should know that.
I know.
You wanna tell me
the real reason you're here?
I been thinking about
what's next for me
after all this.
Yeah?
I'm enjoying the restaurant,
even with all the headaches.
It's real.
Straightforward.
You open up,
you feed people,
you clean up,
you close up,
and you go home.
That's it.
That's your day.
You don't carry it with you.
- Not like this job?
- No.
And up until,
I don't know...
Mike's death maybe,
it never got to me.
It's time, isn't it?
You ever think about
what's next?
Sometimes.
I've been looking back
a little too, you know,
wondering about some
choices I've made...
Wishing I'd made
different ones.
Wha-are you, uh...
talking about me?
Are you talking about you,
about us?
You--you--are you wishing
that it would have worked out?
No.
Okay. Just checking.
So...when are you retiring?
Thought about putting
my papers in on the first.
Happy New Year.
- Let's hope.
- Mm-hmm.
Dexter.
Hey.
I was worried about you.
Oh, look who's here!
- Daddy's home.
- Come here, bud.
Yeah.
Thanks for staying over
tonight.
My pleasure.
Ever since
I've gone vegetarian,
the idea of watching my brother
roast a whole pig
grosses me out.
Besides,
you guys are family too.
Yeah. So are you.
- How's Debra?
- Yeah, how's she doing?
She's fine.
She should be out tomorrow.
I'm glad to hear that.
Well, I hope you're hungry,
Dexter.
Look at her.
So beautiful.
But can you ever fully trust
a poisoner?
Mmm...
Okay, Dexter?
Dexter.
Earth to Dexter.
I think your food coma's
hitting way early.
- I think you're right.
- What do you want?
Uh, a little bit
of everything.
Christmas is a time
of expectation.
If you're good,
a red-suited fat man
will break into your house
and leave you presents.
But Santa Claus doesn't exist.
The most wonderful time
of the year celebrates a lie.
Is the future I imagine
with Hannah
nothing more than a vision
dancing in my head?
It's funny how we started off
in Santa's holiday adventure
and here we are,
Christmas Eve together.
A place I never thought
I'd be with anyone...again.
Much less you.
Thanks.
I'm not saying this
quite right.
Um...
All the men
that I've been with--
there was a lot of...
running away.
But when I'm with you,
I don't wanna go anywhere.
Stay with me tonight.
No, I can't.
I have somewhere to be.
Debra?
Estrada?
Good for you.
I know he's somebody that you've
wanted for a long time.
Someone I thought
I'd never get.
I imagine that will be
deeply satisfying.
When Deb had her accident...
She was heading
to Arlene Shram's house.
She was hoping Arlene
would give her a statement
that would let her
arrest you.
But Deb never made it there.
She blacked out
behind the wheel.
Does that sound familiar?
- Familiar?
- Sal Price.
It's what you hoped
would happen to him
before you poisoned him.
Are you--
do you think that I had
something to do
with Debra's accident?
Did you?
I can't believe you would
even think something like that.
Say something.
I know you will always do
whatever it takes
to protect yourself.
That does not include trying
to poison your sister.
You yourself told me
Arlene saw you
poison that counselor's
coffee.
And I can't tell you
how many times
I saw Arlene shoot up.
I was nervous about
what she could do to me,
but then I went to see her
and...she's a mess
that any second-year law student
could discredit.
She's not a threat to me.
But Deb is.
Do you really think
that I would be that stupid
to try and poison
the lieutenant of homicide?
And to think that
you wouldn't figure it out?
Wouldn't exactly bring us
closer together, would it?
You know I love you, right?
Yes.
Do you love me?
I don't know
if I believe you.
You were at her house
last night.
I thought that if she knew
how much I cared about you,
then she would
back down a little.
But she never will.
What happens next week
when Deb has a heart attack?
Do you hear yourself?
If anything
ever happens to Deb,
I'm gonna wonder if you had
something to do with it.
Well, that's your problem--
your lack of trust.
Your inability to trust.
God, it's like...
It's like you have something
deep down inside of you that you
think is undeserving of love.
- Don't turn this back on me.
- You're the one accusing me.
I ju-- I know what
you're capable of!
Okay, I'm not sure
quite how to say this, but...
I've never made a mistake.
If I had poisoned Debra,
then she would be dead,
and if you know me the way
that you say that you do,
then you know
that that's true.
Maybe it all was
just an accident.
I know it must have been
really scary
to see her in the hospital
like that.
It was.
And it's understandable
that you would try
to make sense of a situation
that doesn't make sense,
but you're doing that at the
expense of this relationship.
I'm not trying to.
I--
I don't want to lose you.
I'm sure about you.
I'm 100% sure,
but you need to be able
to say the same thing about me.
I know.
We could have it all.
I think you need to figure out
what it is that you want.
And what type of future
you want to have.
It's right in here.
What the fuck is this?
Huh?
Where's the stuff?
Estrada!
Estrada.
Estrada, it's time.
I guess the Department of
Corrections kept that for you.
That was very thoughtful.
You've changed a lot
in the past 40 years.
So have I.
Three men murdered my mother.
Juan Pablo Aliso
was shot in another deal.
Santos Jimenez.
You remember him.
He testified against you.
I cut him into six roughly equal
pieces with a chain saw...
Just like he did my mother.
Just like I'm gonna
do to you.
Holy fuck!
You're Dickie Moser!
Dexter...Moser.
I am Dexter Moser...
And I'm gonna kill you.
Is that what all this
is about?
I was three years old when you
left me in that container.
Who am I gonna be
when you're dead?
Still some fucking freak,
probably.
We'll see.
Ha. You're working
with her, aren't you?
What?
That fucking cop bitch,
the one who got me out.
Oh, yeah, they said
that there was a big push
for my release
from the captain of Miami Metro.
LaGuerta?
She fucking set me up.
You're not the one
who was set up.
Officer.
We followed him to here,
but we lost him.
Until we heard the gunshot.
That's when we called you.
All right.
Anything else since?
- No, ma'am.
- Show me where.
What the fuck
is going on in this place?
Keep looking for Estrada
and anyone else with him.
Estrada's not alone.
Don't make a fucking sound.
Around this side.
Around the back.
Which side?
It wasn't the universe
giving me a gift.
It was LaGuerta.
I can make sure at least
one member of the Morgan family
has a good Christmas.
Yes.
Dexter, it's Sergio.
You told me to call you when
I ran that water you brought in.
I know it's early.
It's okay. What'd you find?
That water's like
40% Alprazolam.
That's an antianxiety drug.
Someone must have really wanted
to knock themselves out.
But this time of year,
who can blame 'em?
- Thanks.
- You got it.
It was no accident.
Hannah dissolved the pills
into Deb's water
so that she'd pass out
behind the wheel.
A problem
in Hannah's life solved.
Hannah poisoned Debra.
It's not the future
I had wanted with Hannah...
but maybe it's what I deserve.
You barely said two words
on the ride home.
I have something for you.
A present?
A new car, I hope.
I guess it's a present.
It's Sal Price's pen.
If you test it,
you'll find traces
of aconite on the end...
and Hannah's prints.
So that's how she did it.
I found it the next morning.
I kept it out of evidence.
I can't believe
you're gonna turn her in.
As long as she's free,
you're not safe.
Dex, I know how hard
this must be for you.
You're here.
Does that mean
that you know what you want?
Yes.
Hannah...
You have to kiss me,
or it's bad luck.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry--
Hannah McKay,
you're under arrest
for the murder of Sal Price.
You should have killed me.
I should know better
than to count on the future.
All you can ever believe in
is now...
This moment.
Because in a blink...
Everything can change.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==