? ?
? Dexter 7x08 ?
Argentina
Original Air Date on November 18, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
?
Previously on Dexter...
She accepts both sides of me.
The whole Dexter.
How in the hell
does the most
crucial piece
of evidence against
Isaak Sirko just disappear?
I did what you wanted.
The evidence
against Sirko is gone.
I want Nadia's passport.
She's done with you
and your whole shitty
fucking organization.
That's not
gonna happen, Joey,
so you think real hard
about your next move.
I'm at a dead end
on Bay Harbor butcher.
Everything we've done,
all the evidence,
it still points
to Sergeant Doakes.
At some point,
we have to face facts.
Harrison is only going
to Orlando
for a few weeks, Dexter.
He's gonna be fine.
All he'll want to do
is follow Cody around.
Every time the shit
hits the fan, I go to him.
He's your safe place.
You're making it sound
like I want to
be with him or something.
Well, do you?
You didn't kill Viktor
out of vengeance.
I have a feeling that you're
a different kind of animal.
I can't even have
a drink with someone
without them dying.
I'm sorry, Deb.
I wish I could tell you
what happened.
I know what happened.
Hannah McKay.
Sal Price was writing
a book on you.
You didn't like it,
so you poisoned him.
That's crazy.
Report's back on
the tox screen on Sal Price.
M.E. ran it twice.
Negative both times.
That fucking bitch is gonna
get away with it again.
Hannah McKay
killed Sal Price
and she's gonna walk.
I want you
to make it right.
Do what you do.
Was Deb's call
just a bad dream?
Or does she really want me
to kill Hannah?
Morning.
- How did you sleep?
- Okay.
Special herbs
from my garden.
It's my secret ingredient.
How can I help?
Uh, you can dice.
It's, uh, more my style.
I sometimes
lose track of time,
but your calendar
goes beyond that.
Oh, it's not so much
a calendar, but a reminder.
That's the year
you took off with Wayne.
It's not about Wayne.
It's Argentina.
What was so special
about Argentina?
Nothing, really, I just--
I like the picture.
It looks like... nice.
Happy.
A home.
My sister,
who's also my lieutenant,
so I should probably
get to work soon.
Your sister
is the lieutenant?
Yeah,
I didn't mention that.
No, you didn't.
Is this crazy?
"This"?
You and me,
just sitting here,
eating breakfast.
I always eat breakfast.
It's important.
I-I know
that we decided
to never
see each other again,
so I just want you
to know that
if last night was
a one-night thing for you,
then I'm okay with that.
Okay.
But if you want
to never see each other again
tomorrow night,
then I'm okay with that too.
Okay.
You're very agreeable.
Yep.
I need to find some way
to get her out of Debra's head,
even if I can't get her
out of mine.
Hey, come on in.
Do you want coffee?
There's plenty.
I couldn't fucking sleep.
Sure.
Deb?
Yeah?
What you said last night,
you didn't mean it.
Did you?
Yeah, Dex, I meant it.
The good news is
I've already vetted her for you.
She's killed three people
that we know of.
That's not including
what she did with Wayne.
And Price had a tissue sample
and a lab report
on Beverly Grey
that proved she was poisoned
with aconite.
But, go figure, some asshole
broke into his apartment
and disappeared
all the files on Hannah.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
You don't know
she killed Price.
You don't even know Price
was murdered.
You want to know what
he was doing the day he died?
He was recording this.
Then she just
kept screaming,
and there was so much blood.
What did you do?
I stabbed her
until the screaming stopped.
Deb, she was 15.
You want more?
Let's talk about how
she didn't allow
her husband's body
to be embalmed.
She fits your code, Dex.
I'm not killing
Hannah McKay.
You know how hard it was
for me to ask you that?
I have been going around
in my head in circles
trying to come up
with something,
with anything
that I can fucking use,
but I've got nothing.
Sal and I were so close.
If that body
hadn't decomposed...
We'd fucking have her.
She'd be locked up.
He would be alive.
But he's dead,
and Hannah McKay
is walking around,
free to kill again.
And she will
fucking kill again, Dexter.
That's who she is.
And I can't let that happen.
Not after Speltzer.
I wish
there was another way.
You're all I have left.
What's up?
It's Astor.
"Grandpa's kidney stones
are acting up again.
"Grandma's taking him
to the doctor.
Hopefully it's not
too serious."
Deb, you told me you didn't want
to be a part of what I do.
That was before
I realized--
You could hardly
live with yourself
when you lied
to Batista for me.
How do you think
you're gonna live with knowing
that you're responsible
for a murder?
Don't tell me what
I can and can't handle.
Turns out there's
a fuck of a lot
that I can live with
these days.
No, you can't.
Ever since you found out,
you've been teetering
on the edge.
You've covered up evidence,
you've lied--
For you!
Yeah, that's why I can't
let you take it any further.
For your own good.
For my own-
oh, you--please do not
parent me, Dexter.
You sound like dad.
Because that's probably
what he'd say.
This isn't who you are.
Deb, I care about you too much
to let you do something
you're gonna regret.
I'm sorry,
the answer is no.
Well I guess it's
your fucking decision, isn't it?
Even though everything
I just said is true,
it doesn't make me
any less of a liar.
Excellent.
The police will follow Jurg
and your bodyguard
around all afternoon.
And then what?
The cops are dicks,
but they're not morons.
They're gonna figure out
you're not in the car.
Eventually, sure.
But by then, I'll have
taken care of my business.
Business?
What business?
This isn't about Dexter Morgan
again, is it?
You're not thinking
straight here.
He works for Miami Metro.
We take out
one more of theirs,
they shut this place down
for good.
We have inventory to move--
tonight.
Come on, man, just--
just let it go.
You can go home.
Deb's got 24hour police
surveillance on Isaak.
Which means I know where
he is at all times.
He's moved into Viktor's
apartment and hardly gone
anywhere other than the Fox Hole
and a few restaurants.
Hey, Dexter.
The usual?
Yeah, thanks.
Hey, do you have
any Boston cremes?
It's my sister's favorite.
Got some fresh ones
coming out now.
Take just a minute.
Thanks.
Is that your plan
to keep Debra from going over
to the dark side?
Give her a massive
sugar rush?
I don't exactly
have a plan yet.
I can think
of an obvious one.
I'm not gonna
stop seeing Hannah
just because
she's a murderer...
and my sister
wants to kill her.
Do you hear
how that sounds?
- What the hell?
- I don't know.
Those fucking gang kids
are at it again.
- Yeah, I guess so.
- I'm calling the police.
Looks like while you were
playing house with Hannah,
Isaak found a way
to shake the police,
which likely means
he'll come after you again.
Well, if he can get past
Miami Metro homicide, so can I.
Grandpa's gone to surgery.
Grandma says we have
to stay with you in Miami.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
The kids are coming.
"Kids" as in plural?
Grandpa has to have surgery.
I need to send Jamie
to Orlando to pick them up.
It was Isaak, wasn't it?
How the fuck did he get away
from the cops?
Does it matter?
Did you see him?
Yeah.
Then you're a fucking witness.
I can arrest him.
You already
tried that once, Deb.
It didn't work.
You really want
an investigation
into why Isaak Sirko
is trying to kill me?
So what the fuck
am I supposed to do?
Just let me handle it.
It's not like I have
much of a choice.
Just be careful, okay?
There's one other thing.
I got a call
from the kids' grandmother.
- Harrison okay?
- Yeah, he's fine.
But Bill has to have
emergency surgery,
and Maura wants me
to watch Harrison
and Astor and Cody
for a few days.
- Now is not a good time.
- I know, but what could I say?
Jamie's on her way
to pick them up.
Well they can't stay
at your fucking apartment.
Isaak probably has
his own key by now.
Any ideas?
Yeah, they can stay
at my place.
I'll get patrol cars
to cover my house, just in case.
How are you gonna
explain that to LaGuerta?
I'll tell her that I'm afraid
Isaak's gonna come after me
for his arrest.
Your house
isn't exactly kid-friendly.
- What does that mean?
- Well, you have a gun.
I'll lock it up.
And the pay channels.
Cody's 12.
Okay, I'll lock up the remote.
Anything else?
Anything in your kitchen
besides salsa and beer?
I think there was some cheese
when I moved in.
I'll have Jamie
stock the fridge.
This is gonna be great.
I love kids.
I don't love kids in general,
but I love your kids.
And Astor and Cody,
it's been a long time.
I'll give you a heads-up
as soon as I know
when they're getting in.
Thanks.
Yeah.
What's that?
I'm gonna pay Hannah McKay
a visit.
Why?
Just because you're
not gonna do what you do
doesn't mean she gets to live
happily fucking ever after.
I guess it was foolish
to think
Deb would simply
walk away from this.
Hey!
I heard about
your donut shop.
Oh, yeah.
Pretty scary.
Francisco thinks
it was gang-related.
Showdown between
the crullers and the fritters?
Uh, Deb?
If you need me,
I'll be on my cell phone.
Something up?
Just some business
on the other side of town.
Dexter.
Ladies.
If you get a chance,
stop by papa's after work today.
It's under new management.
Shut the fuck up.
You got the restaurant?
The landlord and I came
to an agreement with the lease.
Call me papa.
No, I will not do that.
But I will stop by
for a drink later.
Dex, you're in?
No, I've got the kids
coming into town, so...
It's a family place.
Bring 'em.
Angel...
I'm really happy for you.
1 cubic yard
of cocoa mulch.
25 pounds of--
uh, let me get back to you.
Lieutenant.
You, uh, in the market
for some orchids?
I'm not buying anything
from you.
Look, I think you have
the wrong idea--
Shut up.
I'm not interested in
anything you have to say,
'cause you're a fucking liar.
I know who you are.
I know what you are.
Well, I think
you'd be surprised
at the things that
you don't know about me.
Sal Price
shared everything with me.
So you may think you're safer
because he's dead,
but actually, it's worse.
He was just a writer.
I'm a cop.
Whatever you're hiding,
I'm gonna find out.
Sal Price
was a storyteller.
He wanted to sell books.
He didn't care
if they were true or not.
You admitted to him
on tape
that you killed
with Wayne.
How convenient that he died
before he had a chance
to write about it.
Lieutenant,
what were you doing
when you were 15 years old?
I'm guessing
you were probably
on a soccer team
or something, right?
Me?
I was just some dumb farm girl
who was wakened
in the middle of the night
by an older boy
that I had a crush on
who said, "let's go on a trip."
I was in over my head.
You knew exactly
what you were doing then.
You're in over your head now.
Well, I don't know why I care
so much about what you think,
but somehow I do,
so, I'm sorry.
You haven't even begun
to be sorry.
I'm not suggesting
a coup here.
More like a realignment.
I'd never do anything without
the support of the brotherhood,
but I feel like something
has to be done
or this whole thing's
gonna explode in our faces.
Okay.
Consider it done.
You want to stick around?
Watch your girl?
Drinks on me.
I've got a better idea.
Why don't you
go fuck yourself?
Ah, come on, Joey.
Nah, don't
"come on, Joey" me.
We had a deal,
and you fucked me over.
So we're done.
Look, I'm sorry I couldn't
get you Nadia's passport.
I tried, man,
but the guys in Kiev,
they pull the strings.
What I do have is some cash.
If you do
one more job for me,
you can buy something
for Nadia.
See, I don't want
your fucking cash.
And if you take that
out on her,
I'll have I.C.E. down here
faster than you can count,
checking on the immigration
status of all your employees.
So go fuck yourself.
Bye.
Miami Metro believes
they know where Isaak is
at all times,
but obviously
I can't count on that.
Hope he enjoys his last meal.
When he gets home to Viktor's
apartment, I'll be waiting.
Hey, Jamie.
Hey, Dex.
We just made
a quick pit stop.
I warned Cody
about the Big Gulp,
but we're about
three hours out
depending on traffic.
Great.
Why don't we meet at
your brother's new restaurant?
If he's got macaroni
and cheese, we'll be fine.
Apparently that's all
Harrison's willingly consumed
since he got to Orlando.
It is his favorite.
God, Cody, we don't want
to have to stop again.
But I'm thirsty.
Can't we just leave
him by the side of the road?
No, Astor,
we can't just leave him
by the side of the road.
Sounds like you've got
your hands full.
We'll see you
in Miami, Dexter.
Drive safe.
People always say
they'd like to die at home.
I'll leave his body here
and let the police blame it
on the Colombians.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the building super.
I came to fix the faucet.
I didn't know
anyone was home.
You're not the super.
Sure I am.
Who are you?
I'm the Avon lady.
Well, that's just silly.
You're here for
the same reason I am.
- Which is?
- To kill Sirko.
Look, I don't know
who sent you here,
but I'm not going halvsies
with anyone.
This is my job.
We could have
just gone halvsies.
With all
the people who want
to kill Isaak,
why is it so hard
to get him dead?
Not this guy.
This one either.
Dexter Morgan.
This guy had a slip.
Had?
Meaning he doesn't
have one anymore?
No. He moved
a few years back.
I remember it
because it was odd.
He had, uh, eight months
to go on his lease.
When exactly did he move?
May, 2007.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You're getting heavier.
What did they feed you up there?
Mac and cheese.
And more mac and cheese.
You want to go play
on the beach after we eat?
Oh, I can take him now.
Astor and Cody were fighting
the entire drive down.
I need a break.
- Mojitos on the house.
- All right.
For the grown-ups.
Sodas for the kids.
Sorry, I gotta keep
my liquor license.
Everything good here?
It's perfect.
Thanks, Angel.
Perfect because it has
a built-in security system.
Dexter, check out
my Angry Birds score.
Dexter doesn't want to see
your Angry Birds score, Cody.
Put it away.
I've missed you guys.
We missed you too.
So how's school?
Is math
still kicking your ass?
Butt.
Kicking your butt.
That's what I said.
Is math still kicking your butt?
I'm a year ahead in math now,
and I'm taking A.P. Bio.
Impressive.
She passed out when
they dissected the fetal pig.
Can we not talk about
fetal pigs at dinner?
God, Cody, can we not
get through one dinner
without you doing something
completely disgusting?
Can you stop acting
like miss perfect?
You can't even make it
through a weekend
without smoking pot.
Oh, my God.
You know how many cops are here?
You want to get arrested?
God, what is wrong
with you?
Guess I should go talk to her.
I'll be your backup.
I don't do it
a lot, I swear.
Just when I get
really stressed out.
You want to tell me
what's going on?
It's just pot.
In some states,
it's not even against the law.
It's always against the law
for someone your age,
which is for your own good,
by the way.
Thanks for the public
service announcement.
Dexter's right.
Sometimes the things
that seem
like a good idea
in the moment
are the things you'll
end up regretting later.
Astor...
I know how...
certain vices can be used
to relieve stress.
But sometimes those vices
can cause more problems
than the original stress.
Okay, I get it, pot is evil.
Are we done?
We...sure, we're done.
Kids are all asleep
in your room.
I put Harrison on your bed.
I hope that's okay.
Yeah, sure.
He doesn't wet the bed,
does he?
Not always.
You owe me.
Jamie will be here first thing
in the morning.
Hey, Dex.
Um...
Maybe you were right...
about Hannah.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
If anyone deserves
what you do, she does, but...
It must have been hard
to resist,
and I know
you did it for me.
So...
thanks for caring.
You don't have to thank me.
Thanks for taking
everyone in.
My home is their home.
My family.
All that's left of it is here,
under one roof.
It should feel like home.
So why do I want so badly
to be somewhere else?
Look who's not here again.
Is this a bad time?
Fortunately,
you've managed to catch me
in between gentleman callers.
Well, I guess
it's my lucky night.
What brings you by?
Or is this your version
of a Booty call?
What's a Booty call?
Seriously?
Actually, I just stopped by
because I'm gonna be busy
for the next few days.
So you came by to see me
because you can't see me?
Something like that.
So what's got you so busy?
Nothing, I just--uh...
The head of the Koshka
Brotherhood wants to kill me.
You're not kidding.
Well I don't know what
a Koshka Brotherhood is,
but it sounds bad.
It's kind of a...
Ukrainian Mafia.
Wow.
What did you do
to piss them off?
Not them.
Just Isaak Sirko.
He has this personal vendetta
against me.
Why?
I killed
one of his key guys.
Oh.
Well, it happens.
So what do you know
about this Isaak Sirko?
I know that he wants
to kill me,
and that I need
to kill him first,
and that it's harder
than I thought it would be.
Well, you want my advice?
Uh, sure.
You spent a lot of time
finding out all about me
before you--
Before I tried to kill you.
Right.
This is different.
I had to make sure
that you fit my code.
I already know Isaak's a killer.
Well, still, it seems like
you have a system,
and it's working for you,
right?
Most of the time.
Well, so why don't you try
the same thing on this guy?
Figure out who he is, and why
he really wants to kill you.
Here.
Take my van.
He might know your car.
Besides, it'll give you
a decent excuse to come by
and not see me again.
I have never been able
to talk to anyone
about my kills before.
Not like this.
No judgment,
no fear, no panic.
- That's nice.
- Yeah.
But I'm kind of tired
of talking.
Maybe I can show you
what a Booty call is.
Mm.
Come on, Joey.
It's not that bad.
I only have to work for George
for two more years,
and then I'll have my freedom.
You believe that?
He likes his dancers young.
There are always more girls
who want to come here.
I'm sorry I let you down.
Just promise me you'll never
do anything for them again.
Not even for me.
I promise.
Okay.
I'm gonna take a shower.
How'd I know I'd find
your horny ass here?
I got something to show you.
I'm not interested.
Oh, I think you might be.
But Isaak Sirko,
he wants you to lose
the blood evidence
linking him
to the Colombian murders.
Let me skip to the good part.
If I do this,
Nadia's a free woman.
You give me her fucking
passport, understand?
Deal.
And I'll do you one better.
You can even keep the cash.
Now do we
understand each other?
If I go down,
you're going down with me.
It won't exactly ruin
my reputation.
I got the Koshka Brotherhood
behind me.
You saw how long
Sirko stayed behind bars.
Who's gonna save your ass?
Miami Metro?
What do you want?
Same kind of shit
you used to do for us.
You know, we have some product
that needs to move.
I need a cop around
to make sure nothing goes wrong.
If you help us,
you make some money.
And if you don't, that recording
goes on the fucking cloud.
I'm sorry to twist
your arm, buddy,
but you really left me
no choice.
I'll see you tonight.
No one else here.
Not anymore, anyway.
Do you recognize him?
He's one of George's men.
Sent here to kill me.
George wouldn't make a move
without getting approval
from the boys in Kiev.
So much for brotherhood.
This can be fixed.
We can go home, we can call--
no.
I'm a dead man there.
You've already gone
above and beyond
the call of duty, Jurg.
Your loyalty
could get you killed.
Where you go, I go.
My offshore accounts
should last some time.
But I won't have access
to the corporate accounts.
Bloody hell!
Then there's this.
We're gonna need
another place to stay.
Who do you think
killed him?
Well that's a job
for the police, isn't it?
Why don't you go and give
our friends downstairs a call.
Looks like
the gang's all here.
So you have no idea
what he was doing
in your apartment?
Not a clue.
But I'm sure your trusty
blood spatter analyst
could figure it out.
Mr. Sirko,
the gun that we found
would suggest that he came here
to kill someone.
And since you live here,
that someone
may very well be you.
What a frightening thought.
Then perhaps I need
some sort of police escort.
Oh, I already have that.
Well we'll have to confirm
with the M.E.,
but judging by the lividity
and state of rigor,
I'd estimate
the time of death
as sometime
yesterday afternoon.
Let me see now,
where was I yesterday afternoon?
Perhaps these kind officers
could refresh my memory.
Unis tailed him all day.
He wasn't here.
Seems I have an alibi.
I hope they're trustworthy.
Dex, what have you got?
Yes, please, Dex,
tell us your theory.
I'm so curious.
Well, judging by the photo
found in the victim's pocket,
he way lying in wait
for Mr. Sirko.
Here you go.
These scuff marks indicate
a struggle.
They fell to the floor.
And the killer cut
his carotid artery
with one swipe
of a very sharp knife.
My, my.
You couldn't have described
that better
if you'd been there yourself.
Thanks.
Hey, Vince, I have plans
with the kids today.
You think you can
finish this up?
Fine. But one of these days,
I'm gonna track down
some of my kids so that
I can skip out on work.
Thanks.
Vince is gonna take it
from here.
Keep him occupied
as long as you can.
Kill ya later, Isaak.
Yeah!
Oh, that's gonna be
really good.
See, get it all up in there.
Yeah!
That's a strong castle,
mister.
You're doing so good.
Want that?
He did it all himself.
- That's pretty awesome.
- Yummy.
You know what,
I think you need
a little bit more sunscreen,
Harrison.
Hey, buddy, you know what
this place needs?
A moat!
Keep the bad guys out.
Oh.
I'll be back in a minute.
Can I have some
of that leg?
I miss the beach.
It reminds me of mom.
Yeah, she used to take
you guys here all the time.
Atlanta doesn't feel
like home,
but here doesn't either.
It's like there's no place
I actually belong.
You know what I mean?
Actually, yeah, I do.
If my grandparents
find out about the pot,
they'll think I'm just turning
into my dad or something.
I feel like they're
just waiting for that
to happen anyways.
You know, when I was younger,
someone told me who I was,
and I pretty much took
his word for it.
If I'd taken the time
to decide for myself,
I would have
turned out different.
Different how?
I don't really know,
but I kind of wish I did.
For the record,
you didn't turn out so bad.
For the record, the pot
will stay off the record.
Just give me a sec.
Hey, Hannah.
Hey. I'm sorry
to bother you,
but I accidentally left
my greenhouse keys in the van.
I'm kind of
in the middle of something.
I could bring them by
in a few hours.
Just tell me where you are
and I'll swing by.
Hobie Beach.
Tower one.
Okay, great.
I'll call you when I get there.
- Is this the one?
- Yeah, thanks.
So, what are you
doing out here?
Hey, Dexter!
Look!
Oh, right.
Of course.
I should've seen
that one coming.
No, she's not, um--
She's my nanny.
Your nanny?
Yeah, that little guy
is my son.
Harrison.
He's three.
I told you about his mother,
how she passed away.
The other two
are Astor and Cody.
They're my stepkids.
They live in Orlando
with their grandparents.
Harrison lives with me...
most of the time.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you.
You didn't trust me,
or you were afraid it would
push me away?
Maybe a little of both.
Well I'd love
to meet them sometime.
You're lucky, Dexter.
Lucky?
No matter where I go,
I'm Hannah McKay,
the spree killer's girlfriend.
Nobody has a clue
who you are.
You get to have this
normal life, with kids and...
Is that something you want?
It was, once upon a time.
Wayne and I talked about
having ten of them.
Can you imagine what a train
wreck that would have been?
Then when I
got married to Jake,
I thought, "this is how it's
supposed to be," you know?
But when that whole thing
went to shit,
I just figured it wasn't really
in the cards for me.
That's what
I used to think too.
Dex! Get over here!
Well, I won't intrude.
Enjoy your time with them.
Okay.
Hey.
Everyone asleep?
Yeah, finally.
Dexter, you did not
tell me that bedtime
is, like,
this two hour process.
And that reading
those Dr. Seuss books
out loud
is really fucking hard.
Sorry I missed that.
Teenagers are great, though.
You just tell them what to do.
I mean, my house
has never looked so clean.
I love families.
Does Hannah fit into
my family somewhere?
What's that doing here?
Oh, I borrowed
a car from a friend
so Isaak
wouldn't recognize me.
Does that friend
happen to be Hannah McKay?
I was going to--
Oh, my God.
Are you fucking her?
Deb, I can explain.
I know what fucking is.
No explanation necessary.
Is that why
you wouldn't kill her?
Partially.
I am the biggest asshole
on the planet.
All that bullshit about
you caring about me too much
to let me do something
I would regret?
I fucking bought it.
Deb, everything
I said was true.
Okay, yes,
I didn't kill Hannah
because I have feelings
for her,
but that doesn't make
what I said to you
any less true.
Feelings?
Are you in love with her?
I don't know.
Is it because
she's a serial killer?
Does that turn you on
or something?
What--what do you all do?
Do you sit around
and talk about
who you're gonna
take out next?
Oh, my God.
Price?
Did you fucking
help her with Price?
No!
I don't even know
why I fucking ask you, Dexter.
Every time I think
I know exactly who you are,
you tell me something worse.
Being with Hannah
is worse than being a killer?
Yes!
No. I don't--
I know you're not
gonna stop killing.
I mean, you've made that
very clear.
But you can stop seeing her.
I don't want
to stop seeing her.
Look what happened
to her husband, Dexter.
She doesn't have
the best track record with men.
I don't even want to talk about
the fucking body trail
that you've left
in your love life.
I'm not asking
your permission, Deb.
So you don't care
what it does to me?
I don't want to hurt you.
Well, guess what?
You did.
You picked the one way
that you could hurt me
worse than you could ever
fucking understand.
Wha
You told me you accepted
me being a killer.
I feel like if you love me,
you'll accept this.
If I love you?
If I love you!
I went to the church
that night
that you killed
Travis Marshall
to tell you that
I'm in love with you!
You're...
In love with me?
Fuck!
Oh, my God.
Was.
I don't even know
if I fucking like you.
This is--
oh, forget it.
What do you mean
you're in love with me?
I didn't--
I didn't mean to say that.
I don't--
I know it's weird,
and it's gross,
and it's fucked up, but--
And I know you don't
feel the same.
I don't even know
if feel the same.
I mean, it's one thing to be
in love with your brother,
but it is
a whole 'nother level
to be in love
with your brother
who's a goddamn fucking
serial killer.
You're a serial killer,
and I'm more fucked
up than you are!
Well, aren't you going
to say anything?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
Oh, God, you never do.
Will you please just go?
I really--
I can't look at you.
What are you gonna do,
just keep following Isaak
around all night?
I can really use
a kill tonight.
After what just happened
with your sister?
She's not--
she's not in love with me.
That's insane.
You have to admit,
it explains a lot.
Why she didn't arrest you.
Why she keeps believing
all your lies.
Why she's willing to give up
everything she believes in,
for you.
What am I supposed to do?
I can't feel
what Deb wants me to feel.
You don't even know
how she wants you to feel.
You just left.
She asked me to leave.
Dexter...
Calm down.
Oh, well, you know
what I do to calm myself.
Where is Isaak going?
Looks like a bar.
I'll give him half a dose.
I'll walk out the back
so the police don't see me.
I'll look like a friend walking
his drunk buddy to his car.
He could be leading you
into a trap.
Not to mention, the police
are only 100 feet away.
? ?
What a pleasant surprise.
We both know
you can't kill me here.
Oh, I can.
But I won't.
Has to be some vestige
of civility left,
even in this corner
of the world.
You call shooting at me
in a donut shop "civil"?
Afraid I was short
on time and opportunity.
Barman!
Can I have a beer for my friend,
Dexter Morgan.
Now we can both relax.
Unlike most places
on the planet,
everyone's welcome here.
You thought your enemies
wouldn't follow you
into a gay bar?
No.
I thought I'd feel comfortable
in a gay bar.
Ironic, isn't it?
I always feared
the brotherhood
would learn my secret
and turn against me.
And now they've turned
against me anyway
and none the wiser about this.
Incidentally,
I will have to thank you
for slitting
that assassin's throat.
You might have saved my life.
But you must explain to me
your aversion to guns sometime.
It's complicated.
I can imagine it is.
You should cut your losses,
Isaak.
Go back to Kiev.
There's nothing waiting for me
back in Kiev,
except for a large,
well-staffed house;
an attractive secretary
who occasionally pretends
we're an item
to keep the rumors
from circulating.
The one thing that made
my life worth living in Kiev,
you tossed in the ocean
a few weeks back.
You and Viktor were--
Lovers.
More than that.
You--you took from me
the one thing
that money and power
can't bring back.
And now, thanks to you,
most of the luxuries
are gone too.
Not because of me.
Because of this vendetta
you're holding on to.
And what did you do to the man
who murdered your spouse?
Nothing you wouldn't
have done.
Nothing I wouldn't do
a thousand times over again.
Did it help?
She's still dead.
I can see that Viktor
meant a great deal to you,
but he was a killer,
and he got what he deserved.
My wife was innocent.
And if she weren't,
you'd feel the same.
That's how love is.
It's a powerful weapon.
It can work for us
or against us, can't it?
I don't understand
much about love.
Well, that's because
you're a scientist.
Love defies reason.
Nothing defies reason.
Logically, Viktor and I
shouldn't have been together.
I mean, aside from
the obvious social stigma,
Viktor was impulsive,
foolhardy even.
Always out to prove something.
I suppose the heart
knows something
that we just don't know.
Or maybe the heart
is just wrong.
Oh, I doubt that.
Love can be inconvenient,
perhaps inappropriate.
It can be dangerous.
Make us do things
we wouldn't dream of doing.
But wrong?
That just depends on
where we end up,
doesn't it?
We don't have to do this.
I do have to do this.
And then what?
Then?
Well, I hadn't
really thought about it.
I suppose I'll take my funds
and find some little attractive
corner of the world,
and while away my days
in comfort and anonymity.
Argentina.
Actually, I was
thinking more like Micronesia,
but each to their own.
We're outsiders, you and I.
On the periphery.
Watching everybody else.
Pretending we're just like them,
but knowing we're not.
Best we can hope for
is to find a place
where we don't
have to pretend.
It's a shame, really.
Under different circumstances,
I think we could have been
great friends.
Till next time.
Everyone wants
an Argentina.
A place where the slate
is wiped clean.
Isaak, I'm at
the airport in Miami.
I'll be home soon.
Isaak, I'm at
the airport in Miami.
I'll be home soon.
But the truth is,
Argentina ...
is just Argentina.
No matter where we go,
we take ourselves
and our damage with us.
So is home
the place we run to,
or is it the place
we run from...
Only to hide out in places
where we're accepted,
unconditionally.
Places that feel
more like home to us...
Because we can finally be
who we are.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==