?
? Dexter 7x12 ?
Surprise, Motherfucker
Original Air Date on December 16, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
?
Previously on Dexter.
Dexter, what the fuck?
Maybe we should
just get rid of the body.
We can make it
look like a suicide.
How do we do that?
Gasoline.
There's a station nearby.
I'll go get
a couple gallons.
If Doakes really wasn't
the Bay Harbor Butcher,
the best thing to do
is to look into his final days.
We should start
with the cabin in the Everglades
where Doakes died.
Maria's convinced
that Doakes was innocent
and that the real killer
might be you.
Me?
Do what you gotta do.
That was the Department
of Corrections.
Hector Estrada is up for parole.
Estrada?
Remember I told you about
my mother and how she died?
Was he one of the men
that killed her?
He was the leader.
He gave the order.
Maybe it's the universe
giving you a Christmas present.
No one but you
would see it that way.
Estrada!
You're working with her,
aren't you?
That fucking cop bitch.
The one that got me out.
LaGuerta?
She fucking set me up.
You're not the one
who was set up.
Debra's at St. Joseph's
in Hialeah.
She's been
in a car accident.
Well, I sure as shit
didn't swallow
a handful of pills.
She what,
poisoned you
while she was
at your house last night?
We need to find the proof.
Hannah dissolved
the pills into Deb's water
so that she'd pass out
behind the wheel.
Sal price's pen.
If you test it, you'll find
traces of aconite on the end.
I can't believe
you're gonna turn her in.
As long as she's free,
you're not safe.
You should have killed me.
You look like
you got some sun.
The boat.
They treating you well?
I get
ten minutes outside.
My cellmate seems nice.
She robbed a liquor store
so she could buy some meth.
Look, you have
every right to--
- You said that you loved me.
- I do.
- Then why am I here?
- You poisoned Debra.
Because she was
trying to keep us apart.
And what
was I supposed to do?
I don't know.
But I know you could have
just broken up with me.
And completely free you up
to kill Deb? No.
I'm gonna spend
the rest of my life behind bars.
- You left me no choice.
- You had a choice.
You were supposed
to choose me.
- She's my sister.
- Oh, Jesus.
I never stood a chance.
Don't.
Why are you even here?
I had to see you.
If you're worried I'm gonna
tell people what you are,
then don't worry.
Your secret is safe with me.
Is it?
I would never
do that to you.
I came here
because I wanted--
I needed you to know...
If there was another--
any way
to keep Deb safe,
I would have found it.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too.
You're the only person
in the world
I don't have to hide
anything from.
I don't know
what I'm gonna do without you.
Dexter,
it's not too late.
The only thing they have on me
is that fucking pen.
If the pen disappears,
so can we.
We can go some place
that your sister can't find us.
We can go to Argentina
and be together always.
I can never trust you.
But, you just--
And you know
you can never trust me.
We both knew
it would come to this.
One of us dead
or behind bars.
Yeah.
Except I always thought
it would be you.
Sorry.
Yeah, me too.
Goodbye, Dexter.
I tried to kill Hannah,
but couldn't.
I wanna hate her for what she
did to Deb, but can't.
Hello?
An inmate from the Miami-Dade
Sheriff's Department
is trying to contact you
via collect call.
Do you accept the charges?
- Uh, yeah.
- Connecting.
Arlene, thank God.
Hannah, what is it?
What's wrong?
I can't do this.
I can't spend my life in here.
I need you to help me.
I need this to be over.
No, you're stronger
than that.
You haven't even
had your trial.
I--I can come visit you.
Arlene, you owe me.
I took care of the counselor
for the both of us.
And now I need
your help, okay?
I can't live like this.
Tell me what to do.
I don't know who's worse,
you or him.
It is toy-mageddon
every time I walk in here.
He can't make up his mind
which one he likes the best.
He's a boy.
He wants them all.
I can clean this stuff up.
Go, get ready for work.
I got it.
All right, Harrison.
We're gonna need to let Jamie
pick some things up,
but that doesn't mean
you can't play with Thomas.
I want Hannah.
Sweetie, uh,
Hannah had to go away,
but that doesn't mean
that she doesn't miss you
very, very much. Okay?
Here, let's see if we can
get Thomas to talk.
Captain?
Dexter.
What are you doing here?
It might be best if you take
Harrison to another room.
Because?
Because I'm placing you
under arrest
for the murder
of Hector Estrada.
Dexter?
Maria, this has to be
some sort of mistake.
- I wish it was.
- Who the hell's Hector Estrada?
I need you to stay back.
- You get your hands off of me.
- Stay back.
Jamie, just take Harrison
to his room.
Please.
It's okay.
I'm calling Deb.
Dexter Morgan.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say or do
can be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attorney.
If you cannot afford
an attorney,
one will be
provided for you.
What the hell's going on?
Jesus.
LaGuerta arrested Morgan.
Maria, what are you doing?
Out of my way, Angel.
Why is Dexter in handcuffs?
I have proof
he's the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Doakes
is the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Have you lost your mind?
Dexter, what is this?
- I don't know.
- What the fuck?
She thinks that your brother's
the Bay Harbor Butcher.
How is that even possible?
It's not.
Williams, take those things off
his fucking wrists right now.
- Leave those.
- Maria, what are you doing?
Stand down, Lieutenant.
Dexter's my prisoner.
You're family.
You need to recuse yourself.
Let's go.
- Angel.
- I'm on it.
Just so we're clear then...
Your official statement is that
you went fishing last night
and then went straight home
to be with your son.
I didn't kill
Hector Estrada.
No.
You didn't cut his body
into pieces
and put it into bags,
take it on your boat,
and then throw it
into the ocean?
Why would I do that?
Because Hector Estrada
butchered your mother
in front of you.
So how about you start
telling me the truth?
I'm not
the Bay Harbor Butcher.
He's answered
all of your questions.
You've got nothing here, Maria.
Not all my questions.
These are from
my phone last night.
And that's you carrying plastic
garbage bags onto your boat.
It was ice to keep
any fish I caught cold.
My cooler broke.
But earlier today you said
you didn't catch anything.
What was in the bag?
It was a shirt with
Hector Estrada's blood on it,
and his wallet.
You killed him.
You killed him like you killed
all your other victims.
Admit it--
you're the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Dexter, don't say
another word.
That's enough, Sergeant.
I was throwing away
my dinner.
It was a bag from Franco's.
You can check.
Angel, you gotta believe me.
You framed Doakes.
After I defended you
against him.
You betrayed me,
this department,
everybody around you.
Is that
what this is about?
Your desperate need to believe
the James Doakes you knew,
or thought you knew,
wasn't a cold-blooded killer?
You don't have the right
to speak his name.
You're so hurt.
Angry, scared.
He's dead because of you.
You were his partner.
And his Lieutenant...
his lover.
What if you couldn't see what
was right in front of your eyes?
What does
that say about you?
I swear to God, Dexter,
I'm gonna nail you to the wall
for what you've done.
- Maria.
- To the wall!
Maria, that's enough.
God damn it, Lieutenant.
You can't be in here.
Tell them
what you just told me.
I reran the blood
on the shirt
that Captain LaGuerta
discovered in the trash.
It's definitely
Hector Estrada's,
but after going over it,
I found an evidence number.
What
what evidence number?
The shirt you gave me
with Estrada's blood on it
is the shirt he was wearing
the day he was brought in,
back in '73.
Things got a little rough,
and the arresting officers
broke his nose.
That's impossible.
I checked inventory.
The shirt's missing.
What about his wallet?
Please don't
kill the messenger.
There was a partial print.
And it's yours.
Were you trying
to frame my brother?
Deb.
You son of a bitch.
You set me up.
Maria.
- Can I go now?
- Yes, you can.
He did this!
He's the Bay Harbor Butcher!
He has to be.
This witch hunt of yours
is fucking over.
And if you have a problem
with it, Captain,
we can take it upstairs.
Captain.
Everyone else
may have bought
your little victim routine
in there,
but we both know the truth.
And the truth is
it's been a very long day.
You set me up,
just like you did James.
And I'm sure you've already
managed to kill Estrada,
which leaves me no chance
to prove any of this.
Congratulations.
You've won again.
I just wanna go home
and see my son.
James always knew there was
something wrong with you.
Surprise, motherfucker.
You got my reports?
Hot off the presses.
Headlines.
26 stab wounds.
The first pierced her heart.
Whoever did this--
was making a fucking point.
This is our third vic.
Any suspects?
Walter Munro.
Fucker's crazy.
Thinks he's some kind
of philosopher or some shit.
Always scribbling his fucked up
thoughts in his journals.
Hmm, the victims
are all prostitutes.
The wounds suggest
the same weapon.
It is consistent
with a single killer.
The thing is, he's crazy,
but he's smart too.
I can never get
anything on him.
Hold up.
Sup?
What we...talked about.
Come on, Maria.
Don't you at least
wanna think about it?
I'm sorry, James.
Oh, shit, Morgan.
I didn't even know
you were there.
You're, like, invisible.
If only I had
stayed invisible.
Maria, wait up.
Angel.
- Hey.
- I-I don't wanna hear it.
I just checked with
Estrada's parole officer.
You were behind
his release from prison?
Somehow, Dexter figured out
I was watching him.
Everyone thinks that you're
trying to frame Dexter.
- I--
- Dexter.
I don't care
what everybody else thinks.
Well, you better
start caring.
Do you want
to keep your job?
Of course
I want to keep my job.
Well then,
you better back off
and drop this
whole crazy idea.
Angel, I--I need you
to be on my side.
I am on your side and
that's why I'm telling you this.
But you have to stop.
Okay, it looks pretty bad,
doesn't it?
More than pretty bad.
And you're gonna
have to work
really hard to fix this.
But come on, Maria.
If anyone can work their way out
of a jam like this, it's you.
Thanks for your
advice, Angel.
We need to talk.
Harrison just went to sleep.
I'm glad one of us
will sleep tonight.
How about a heads up
the next time
you're gonna
get yourself arrested?
Or make our Captain
look like a fucking lunatic.
It worked, didn't it?
Everyone thinks
LaGuerta framed me.
She won't be able
to come after me anymore.
And all it cost her
was her career.
How many careers
has LaGuerta destroyed?
It still doesn't
make it right.
Not that I even know
what that is anymore.
I wish it hadn't come to this,
but it was either her or me.
She almost caught me
trying to kill Estrada
in that shipping container
on the docks.
Whose fault was that?
LaGuerta's the one
who set me up.
So you repay the favor?
Would you prefer my normal
method of conflict resolution?
Not fucking funny.
Look, there is a problem
and I solved it
the best way I knew how.
And it's over.
That's what you keep saying.
But what about Hannah?
What about her?
Well, I assume she knows
what you are.
Yeah, but--
Well,
her arraignment's tomorrow.
How do you know
she won't use that
as a bargaining chip
to get a better deal?
- She won't.
- How do you know that.
'Cause she's
in love with me.
Pray to fuck
you're right.
Take tomorrow off,
all right?
At least until the dust settles
with this LaGuerta thing.
You know this isn't over.
Despite what LaGuerta thinks,
Estrada's still out there.
Yeah, I know.
It's been six days
since I let him go.
I haven't found him yet.
If he resurfaces
and LaGuerta gets wind of it--
She'll offer him a deal.
Put him up
in some safe house.
And you're left
having to explain to the D.A.
Why you came after him
with a chainsaw.
I'll find him.
I'll do what I have to do.
You sound like Hannah.
According to
Estrada's parole officer
this is the last known
address of his wife.
Hector has
nowhere else to turn.
He's wanted
by the police, me...
Mrs. Estrada, I'm Arthur Curry,
Hector's parole officer.
Why are you here?
I haven't seen
Hector in years.
- Hey, honey, who's that?
- The neighbor.
Please, don't come here again.
My Tony doesn't like it.
Well, if you haven't
seen Hector,
why are you
still married to him?
I'm Catholic.
Is it that guy again?
You sure
he hasn't been around?
You should go.
It's been 40 years,
but Florencia
hasn't let go of Hector.
Sometimes it only take a moment
to reveal who we really are.
Looks like you spun
a goddamn web.
It's more like a puzzle.
So connect the dots.
Can you pin this
on Munro or not?
The entry wounds
on the victim
are consistent with the puncture
wounds on the previous victims.
Uh, she was standing
when she was attacked.
She stumbled,
her body turning.
And the killer's
behind her now,
stabbing her
in the back repeatedly.
And then she's
down on all fours,
crawling away until the killer
grabs her and flips her over.
He's on top of her now.
He slices
her carotid artery.
She's terrified.
Heart's racing.
It's releasing more blood
in thick arterial spurts
here and here and here.
I've never seen someone
so excited
about a crime scene before.
You like this blood shit
a little too much.
I'm just doing my job.
Then wipe that fucking smile
off your face
and help me
find the creep who did this.
I let my guard down.
For an instant, my real life
bled into my fake life,
and Doakes caught his
first glimpse of the real me.
Thanks for coming, Tom.
Christ sakes, Maria.
It's all over the station.
You tried to frame Dexter.
You know
that's not true.
Do I?
The commissioner's going
to open an investigation
into your recent conduct.
If called to testify
I'll be dragged into this mess
and have no choice
but to tell the truth--
that we found definitive proof
in that boathouse
that Doakes was
the Bay Harbor Butcher,
and that despite me advising
you to cease and desist,
you continued
on this reckless course.
So what's your advice?
Get on your knees
and start kissing anything
that even remotely
resembles an ass.
I'm serious, Tom.
I was hoping
for your support.
And make myself
look as crazy as you?
People still
respect you here.
I need someone
to have my back, Tom.
And you could say
I had reasonable suspicion.
You carried it too far.
Well, then say that.
Say that due to my
overzealous nature
as a police officer, I got
too caught up in the case.
You got too caught up
being an idiot.
I'm already down, Tom.
Stop kicking.
My job is at stake.
Tom.
All right.
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you.
You just keep
your head low.
And for God's sake,
start doing your job
if you have any hope
of keeping it.
Lieutenant.
What brings you here?
I'm the arresting officer.
How's the wrist?
Stronger every day.
How's facing life without
the possibility of parole?
Last time I checked it's
innocent until proven guilty.
Well, this is
your last chance.
You can save yourself
a lot of time and trouble
and confess
what you've done.
I will if you will.
My conscience is clear.
All that Xanax.
My, how you must have trouble
sleeping at night.
You don't know
shit about me.
Can we have a minute?
Except that you're
the lieutenant of homicide
and you wear
a big shiny badge,
and yet you know exactly
what your brother is.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna tell anyone.
They wouldn't believe me
even if I did.
But knowing that you
have to live with it
is, um, punishment enough.
Still, I'm curious.
How do you justify
arresting me and not him?
Or is the law
just something
that you make up
as you go along?
Turning a blind eye
whenever you feel like it,
or whenever
Dexter is involved.
Fuck...you.
You are a liar and a killer.
But not a hypocrite.
Ms. McKay, come on.
Let's go.
Hannah McKay, you are charged
with murder in the first degree
in connection with the death
of Salvador Price.
How do you plead?
My client pleads
not guilty, Your Honor.
Ms. McKay,
you are hereby remanded
to the state of Florida,
and bail is denied.
No!
Hannah.
I'm so sorry.
Listen to me.
It's gonna be fine, okay?
Ma'am, you need
to step back, please.
Thank you.
Good-bye.
Maria, just checking in.
That's nice of you.
Seems everyone else
is avoiding me.
You know how it is.
Everyone is waiting
to see where this lands.
I'm doing everything I can
to make sure
it doesn't land
on my head.
You need to show up
to my party.
I really don't think anyone
wants to see me there.
Of course they do.
It's also an opportunity
for you to apologize to Dexter.
A public act
of contrition.
If you straighten it out
with him,
he can tell
the people upstairs
that it was just
a misunderstanding.
Either way,
show up tonight.
It's not just New Year's Eve.
It's also
my retirement party.
Oh.
It wouldn't feel right
without you.
I'll be there.
1,500 ccs, supercharged...
Shit!
What the fuck?
Seward Memorial
Hospital, now!
She's having
some sort of seizure.
She seems stable.
We're bringing her into Seward
Memorial emergency right now.
We'd better contact
her next of kin.
Hang on, sweetheart.
Go ahead and get her an MRI,
make sure it's with contrast.
Let's hope
my hunch is right.
That the pull
of a long-past romance
is enough to compel
Florencia to help Estrada.
You wanted to talk.
Deb, come in
and have a seat.
What's up?
You were right.
- About?
- Me.
I let my feelings
for Sergeant Doakes
affect my decision-making.
What I put
your brother through
was negligent
and unforgivable.
And I'm sorry.
If it's any consolation,
my career is gonna take a hit.
Suspension,
probably worse.
I hope not.
You don't have to say that.
Either way, in the event
I'm not around much longer,
I wanna leave things
in some kind of order.
I was trying so hard to prove
that the Bay Harbor Butcher
was still active,
I overlooked some loose ends
on Travis Marshall's death.
I was hoping you could
help me with the timeline.
Sure.
Okay, according
to Dexter's statement,
previous to the day we found
Travis Marshall's body
he was doing his final forensics
sweep on the church.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Under your supervision.
No...I mean,
yes, I sent him,
but he was on his own.
He doesn't need
someone to watch him.
You didn't go to the church
that day or evening?
No.
You sure?
Yes.
When I was going through
the mail this morning,
I got a package
from Mike Anderson's widow.
And it seems that
before Mike died,
he ordered security footage
from all gas stations
around the church.
And...somehow this got lumped
into his personal belongings.
It recently
got sent to me, so...
Can you see that?
That's two blocks
from the church.
And there's a timestamp.
It was 22 minutes before
the fire department got the call
on the burning church.
What were you doing there,
Lieutenant?
What it looks like.
I was getting gas.
Then why lie about it?
I didn't lie.
I forgot.
It was a crazy night.
You were certain
about it a moment ago.
No I'm--I'm sorry.
I--
I took some food to Dexter
at the church,
but I was only there for,
like, 30 seconds.
So I didn't think
that it was worth remembering.
- And then you got some gas.
- Yes.
That you put in a gas can?
Yeah.
Why in the world--
Captain,
where is this going?
That's up to you,
Lieutenant.
Debra...
we've known each other
a long time.
Is there something
you wanna get off your chest?
Yes.
I think you've been under
a lot of stress.
You know what I think?
I think I'm not the only one
who made a mistake
trying to protect
someone they care about.
Is there anything else,
Captain?
Not for now.
But this is just the start
of a much larger conversation.
Count on it.
Estrada.
I guess some bonds
are unbreakable.
We never leave behind
the ones we love.
He could be there all day.
And you can keep that,
all right?
Hey!
Hi, Deb.
W--now?
Okay.
Give me 15 minutes.
She's still unconscious,
but the seizures have stopped
and we've got her stabilized.
We're waiting for a doctor.
We could use
your help over here.
Okay.
LaGuerta knew
I was lying, Dex.
Wait, wait,
let me think.
What?
This is bad, Deb.
I don't wanna
fucking hear you say that.
You always say
that you can fix it.
I will.
Just don't know how yet.
Look, it was dangerous enough
when she was focused just on me,
but now that
she's pulled you into this,
well, it's worse.
Tell me about it.
I know I've said this
a hundred times--
But you're sorry
that I got involved in this.
I am.
Are we really that fucked?
Look, all she knows
is that you bought some gas.
That's not a crime.
Yeah, but buying gas
to burn down a church
to cover up the fact that you
killed Travis Marshall is.
And she knows that.
But she can't prove it.
Yet.
I need to know
what else she has,
what her next move is.
If all she's got is that DVD,
I can handle this.
Is this ever gonna end?
Yeah, it will.
Just go back to work.
Try and act normal.
Normal?
What the fuck is normal?
Just do the best you can.
I'll deal with LaGuerta.
What the hell is that?
Estrada.
Oh, shit.
Let's go!
This is Officer Armes
calling for backup.
We need units
at Seward Memorial.
LaGuerta's house.
What is it you're hoping
to find, Dexter?
I don't know.
Not this.
Warrants.
With a judge's signature...
allowing LaGuerta to track
the GPS on my phone and Debra's
the night
the church burned down.
Once this warrant
goes through,
LaGuerta will
have a timeline
for the night
I killed Travis Marshall.
She'll know that Debra
went to the church,
then the gas station.
And then
back to the church...
Proving that we both were at
the church when it burned down,
and proving that Deb
was my accomplice.
I think it's time
to run, Dexter.
But Deb?
I can't leave her behind.
Take her with you.
Debra and Harrison--
just go.
You knew one day
it would come to this.
Deb could never
live like that.
That's always
been the plan, Dexter.
That was before.
It's not just Deb.
I don't wanna run either.
Before?
Before what?
Before everything.
Before I married Rita,
before I had a son,
before Deb knew who I was,
before I fell in love.
What difference
does any of that make?
Somewhere along the line,
the fake life that we created
as a cover for me
to kill became real.
It's not fake to me anymore.
I don't want to lose it.
I'm gonna stand my ground.
I don't see
any other options here, Dexter.
But I do.
No.
Dexter, you have never done
a kill like this.
I'm about to.
No.
LaGuerta's an innocent.
She doesn't even begin
to meet the code.
It's the only option.
I can't let Deb go down
for what I've done.
My God, Dexter.
How did we end up here?
Morning, Dex.
Gonna pick up some steaks
and beer tonight, yeah?
Sounds good.
Hey, Morgan,
the kind of doughnut you choose
says a lot about a man.
You might want
to avoid Doakes.
He's in a bad mood.
First the LT dumps him,
and now
his prostitute killer
seems to have gone missing.
- I love these.
- Thanks.
Get one while they last.
I don't want no fucking
doughnut, Morgan.
Sorry.
Hell, it's not you,
it's LaGuerta.
I should have never gotten
involved with her to begin with.
Never jump the fence
if you're not willing
to face what's
on the other side.
Where the fuck
did you hear that?
A friend said it to me
in a moment of stress.
Bullshit.
You don't have any friends.
This is the journal of that
motherfucking hooker killer,
Walter Munro.
I took it from his place
a couple of weeks ago
while serving a warrant.
It's been locked up
in my drawer ever since.
"Never jump the fence
if you're not willing
to face what's
on the other side."
That's a weird coincidence.
Fuck coincidences.
I don't believe in 'em.
Anyway, I should--
There's something off
about you, Morgan.
I should have
seen it before.
The fake smile,
the doughnuts.
You don't even walk
like a normal person.
You glide.
Like a...
fucking lizard on ice.
It's all a fucking act.
And I ain't buying it.
I think you're overreacting.
You're hiding something.
And one day I'm gonna
figure out what it is.
You are one
creep motherfucker.
It was a mistake to try
to act human in front of Doakes.
All I did was reveal
how fake I was.
Captain LaGuerta.
Oye,
this is Hector Estrada.
You're alive?
I need your help.
I'm back here
at the shipyard.
Same container.
That's good.
Very convincing.
You're gonna
let me go now, right?
No.
You said--
You think I'm a killer
and not a liar?
Now this is a kill
I've been looking forward to
for a long time.
You're the one who started
this all, so many years ago.
Should auld acquaintance
be forgot?
- No, no, but--
- It's a rhetorical question.
Look, I'm sorry I killed
your mother, all right?
Was it hard?
Making the decision
to kill her?
Yes.
Yeah, man.
It was the hardest decision
of my life.
Look, I didn't wanna do it.
You're lying.
She was a snitch.
It was a matter of survival.
It was her or me.
Come on,
this was 40 years ago.
What are we still
talking about this?
Well, when we finish talking,
I kill you.
Okay, okay.
What else
do you want to know?
Did it make you feel bad?
Look, I said I--
it was her or me.
Survival of the fittest?
Yeah, exactly.
Killing you will be easy,
but I have another kill
I have to do
that's not so easy.
So why are
you doing it, man?
To protect myself.
And my sister.
Exactly.
Survival.
Right?
The normal reasons.
I've never killed
for normal reasons.
I used to think
I was special.
I'm a special
kind of killer,
but tonight, I'm not.
I hear you, bro.
I hear you.
So then what are you, man?
What am I?
I'm just a...
Creep motherfucker.
?
- Jamie.
- Hey, Deb.
- Hey, have you seen Dex?
- No, he was supposed to be here
to pick up Harrison.
The little guy was so tired,
I put him down
in the back office.
Well, if you see him
will you let him know
I'm looking for him?
Yeah, of course.
Happy New Year.
What?
Fuck, sorry.
Happy New Year.
Oh, slow down, cowboy.
I'll share.
I heard that you broke up
with your girlfriend.
She dumped me.
So are you gonna get
all sloppy drunk
and make an ass of yourself
like you did
when you broke up with Deb?
I was thinking about it.
You gonna
hit on me again too?
'Cause I'm just saying,
fair warning,
I do not need my brother
to protect me.
And if you don't
show me respect,
I will fuck you up
and serve you balls
in a shot glass.
How do you make that
sound so fucking sexy?
- Everything good here?
- Just fine.
- Yep.
- Good.
Mmhmm.
- Hey, Hermano.
- Hey.
So how's it feel?
Knowing you're putting away
your badge?
Honestly,
a little scary.
All I've been is a cop.
I'm putting it
all behind me, you know?
Unknown territory.
That takes balls, man.
Oh, hey,
it's almost time.
Uh, where can I go
to change?
No, you're not gonna
put on a diaper
and come out
as baby new year.
That's--no.
- Try and stop me.
- No.
You're gonna scare people
is what you're gon--
Great party, Angel.
Thanks.
Is your brother here?
I was just gonna ask you
the same thing.
He said he was gonna be here.
Yeah, Maria too.
Maybe after
what happened yesterday,
they want
to avoid each other.
Yeah. Maybe.
I'm gonna--
I'm gonna call
and make sure he's okay.
Okay.
Dispatch.
Dispatch, this is
Lieutenant Debra Morgan.
I was hoping to get a 20
on Captain LaGuerta's vehicle.
I'll wait.
Her vehicle is heading north
to the Miami port,
by the shipping yards.
The shipping yard?
Are you sure?
- That's correct.
- Thank you.
Dex, it's Deb.
Whatever you're thinking
of doing,
please don't do it.
So what's the plan?
I gave LaGuerta
half a dose of M99
so it won't be found
in her system.
I'll use her gun to shoot
Estrada in his puncture wound.
Destroying any evidence
that he was stabbed.
And then?
Tell me.
I'll use Estrada's gun
to shoot LaGuerta.
So it'll look
like they killed each other.
Yes.
Dexter.
Where will this end?
Shit, Dex,
what have you done?
Deb?
Oh, God.
Dexter.
You shouldn't be here.
Why...shouldn't I be here?
What are you doing?
What needs to be done.
Are you gonna kill her?
You need to leave.
I need to finish this.
Dexter, you can't.
I can.
And I will.
No, fuck, Jesus.
Dexter, you can't do this.
It's the only solution.
The only way to end this.
No, no, no,
I can't let you
go through with this!
Shoot him, Debra.
You have to end this.
Shoot him.
Stop!
Do it, Debra.
Shoot him!
Do it!
This is not who you are.
You're a good cop.
You're a good person.
You're not like him.
Put him down!
It's true.
Everything she said.
You're a good person.
It's okay.
Do what you gotta do.
Dex.
Oh, my God!
We all make rules
for ourselves.
It's these rules that help
define who we are.
So when we break those rules,
we risk losing ourselves
and becoming
something unknown.
Who is Deb now?
Who am I?
Is this a new beginning?
Or the beginning of the end?
?
? should auld acquaintance
be forgot ?
? and days
of auld lang syne ?
? for auld lang syne
my dear ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==