?
? Dexter 7x10 ?
The Dark... Whatever
Original Air Date on December 25, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
? ?
Previously
on Dexter...
Our primary suspect
is Sergeant James Doakes.
Doakes?
He is not your man.
I think the Bay Harbor Butcher
is alive
and still in Miami.
Doakes was the Bay Harbor
Butcher, end of story.
I found a blood slide
at a crime scene
exactly like the ones
we found in Doakes' car,
and Doakes
never had a boat.
Here is a list of Miami Metro
personnel who still do.
Its point of origin--
front center mass
burned upward, downward.
Can we close
the doors?
This void,
it's the same thing
that happened
with the first car victim.
"Bobby"?
Maybe the victim was
letting us know who did this.
You fucked my girl?
You know, you could learn
a thing or two from her.
She takes her job
very seriously.
Have you always been
this afraid of the water?
Ever since
my father thought
that the best way
to teach me how to swim
was to march me down
to the local pond
and throw me in.
That's horrible.
Six years old,
and I already knew
what it felt like
to be dying.
Look, I think you have
the wrong idea.
Shut up.
I know who you are.
I know what you are.
Dexter, you don't have
to save her.
You shouldn't even be
with her.
It's not even like you
will have a fucking future.
All I know is that,
when I'm with you, I feel...
Safe.
I saw him, and he was coming
through the flames.
He was wearing
a silver-colored suit.
That's
our phantom arsonist.
- He looked like an alien.
- Or a monster.
I swear,
he was 7 feet tall.
Monsters,
aliens, phantoms--
none of them
are real.
The thought
that an actual person
could do this
is too awful,
so our imaginations create a way
to make it easier to take.
But even the strongest
of imaginations
can't protect us
once we know the truth.
I called you
last night.
I wanted to go
over the facts of the case.
We can go
over them now.
Where were you?
Oh.
You were with Hannah.
Find anything?
DNA? Prints?
Nope, nada, zip.
Same accelerant as the other
four fires, though--
kerosene.
And he left another "Bobby"
scribbled in the soot.
Fuck, that's five "Bobby"s
in two weeks.
I mean, he's gotta be signing
his name, right?
I mean, it's the only thing
that makes sense.
None of the victims
were named Bobby,
but, I mean,
fuckload of good that does us.
There are thousands of Bobs
and Roberts in Miami.
What do we know
about the latest victim?
Mom took her daughter
to the bathroom.
They both
went up in smoke.
Kid was six years old.
What kind
of sick fuck
does that
to a six-year-old kid?
Maybe the kind
who isn't bothered
by the sight
of a dead child.
Hey.
How you feeling?
You get your stitches out?
Yeah, I'm going to have
a really sexy scar.
How was your day?
It was fine.
You don't sound fine.
The phantom
started another fire today.
It killed
a mother and child.
What?
Why do I get
the feeling
you want to wrap him up
in plastic?
Doesn't matter.
I promised Deb I wouldn't take
any cases from the police.
Well, if you
always listened to Deb,
you wouldn't be here
with me.
I can't kill him,
okay?
Okay, ne.
Sorry.
I'm just frustrated.
As much as I want
to be here with you,
my dark passenger really
wants to be somewhere else.
I'm sorry.
Your dark what?
My dark passenger.
That's what I call
my need to kill.
Why?
Because it's like
this thing living inside me,
telling me what to do,
saying I have to kill,
not leaving me
any choice.
You're not a puppet.
Of course you have a choice.
Actually, I don't.
Come on, Dex.
It's just you.
You're the one
who wants the arsonist dead.
And I don't blame you.
Who wouldn't?
- It's not the same.
- Well, what do you mean?
Ignore that.
I-I want
to understand this.
How is it different?
'Cause a lot of people feel
like they want to kill somebody,
but I have
to follow through.
I follow through,
and I don't have
a...
dark passenger.
You don't get it.
I'm trying to.
But, no,
I don't get it.
There's a man
in the window.
What?
- Hi, Banana!
- Oh, my God.
That's my dad.
I'm sorry
if I surprised you.
I didn't even know
Hannah had a boyfriend.
I don't know
why you would.
I haven't spoken
to you since--
Go ahead
and say it.
Since before I went
to prison.
Clint McKay, convicted felon.
Nice to meet you.
No need
to get nervous.
I was just in
for check kiting,
and I got out early
on good behavior.
Dad,
what are you doing here?
Well, let me just
get to the point.
I don't know what Hannah's
told you about me.
Uh, not a lot.
Just that you almost
let her drown.
Well,
the truth is,
I was real, genuine asshole
of a father.
And I needed to admit that
to you in person.
Dad, can we please not
do this in front of Dexter?
No,
if you two are together,
then I-I want him
to hear this.
I spent a lot of time
with a prison shrink,
working through
my issues.
He said it's important
to take responsibility,
so that's
what I'm here to do.
Okay.
Now, I don't expect you
to forgive me.
I don't see any reason
that you should,
not after everything
I put you through.
But it's important
you know,
no matter what,
I always loved you.
I always will.
I've got something for you
in my truck.
Let me give it to you,
and I'll be on my way.
Surprise.
It's your dollhouse,
repainted and rebuilt.
It was
in your Aunt Cindy's garage.
I figured you loved it
so much as a kid,
you might like
to have it now.
Uh, Dex,
give me a hand?
Well,
I guess I'll be on my way,
let you two
get back
to your dinner.
There's a diner
at the Purple Flamingo,
where I'm staying.
They say they make
a pretty decent burger.
Okay.
I guess
I'll see you around then.
Nice to meet you,
Dexter.
You look good, Banana,
happy.
Glad to see
you're doing okay.
I'm sure
he meant well,
but he could not have given me
a worse gift.
Brings up
so much shit.
What kind of shit?
When I was eight, he took me
to a poker tournament,
lied to my mom and said that
we were going to a county fair,
and stashed me
in a motel room.
Went to play cards and didn't
come back for three days.
That's awful.
When he came back,
he brought the dollhouse,
bragging about a big win,
saying that
he'd never leave me again,
and making promises
that things would get better.
- And did they?
- No.
Of course not.
I don't know.
I'm--
he's trying, right?
Maybe--
maybe this last stint
in lockup did him some good.
Yeah, maybe.
Most likely,
we're looking
for a male suspect.
Egocentric,
manipulative,
possibly in or on the outskirts
of law enforcement.
He's methodical.
Fastidious in his appearance,
poor social skills--
this list is
by no means comprehensive.
But it should give you
a pretty good idea
of what we're looking at.
Bosso's profile
of the phantom--
he may as well be
describing himself.
An arsonist who works
for the fire department.
It's almost too easy.
What else?
Hands-on learner,
prone to self-aggrandizement.
Thank you,
investigator Bosso.
Where are we on tracking
the fireproof suit?
Oh, there's at least 100 sites
that sell that on the Internet.
Almost impossible
to trace.
Are you guys
still interviewing witnesses?
Yeah, but nobody's seen
the guy's face.
We got more people
coming in today though.
Let me know
what you find out.
Simms, Miller, any leads
from the tip line?
None so far.
Mostly girlfriends trying
to get back at their exes.
All right.
Keep at it.
Maybe something
will come through.
In the meantime,
this fuck has killed
seven people
in two weeks.
Let's stop him before he
makes it to number eight.
Hannah's wrong.
Of course I have
a dark passenger.
There's no other way
to explain this compulsion.
I hope she knows
what she's doing.
Who's sending you
hugs and kisses?
No one.
Bullshit.
That was a girl.
Was she sexting you?
You got pictures?
Come on,
I gotta restock my spank bank.
Hey, Angel, do you know anything
about Dexter's new girlfriend?
- Who, Hannah McKay?
- How did you--
Jamie told me.
Ahh, my man.
Hannah McKay!
Yeah,
that is so awesome.
Excuse me, but what
is so fucking awesome
about my brother
dating a killer?
You guys heard
Sal Price's recording.
Hannah confessed
to murder.
Oh, come on, she was only 15
when she did that.
I mean, when I was 15,
my parents still thought
I was retarded.
Hey, hey.
I get it.
Hannah is
an attractive girl.
But you should
probably be careful.
Yeah, you--you should
definitely be careful
of getting burned
because she's so freaking hot.
Can I see you
in my office, please?
I didn't realize
you and Hannah McKay
had gone public.
We hadn't,
until a minute ago.
Well,
that's kind of dangerous.
Don't you think?
Dating someone so notorious
out in the open like that,
when you're trying to stay
under the radar.
Deb, I really don't want
to talk about Hannah right now.
Can you just leave it?
Fine, yeah.
I'll butt out.
I mean, we're all
responsible adults, right?
You live your life,
I'll live mine,
and Hannah
will live Hannah's.
Great.
And you'll leave Hannah alone?
I'm saying that I'll stay
out of your relationship.
I'm not going to let that woman
get away with murder again.
That's not
what I meant.
Dexter,
I am fucking serious.
I have compromised
the shit out of myself for you.
I am sure as fuck not going
to do it for Hannah McKay.
Fine.
I get it.
Why are you
standing here?
We have a phantom
to catch.
She did say "we."
Philip Bosso.
In his last
27 arson investigations,
he found
the fire's origin point.
Either he's great
at his job,
or all he had to do
was look in the mirror.
Okay,
it says here
that you work as a janitor
at the Y in Brickell Bay
where the, uh, phantom
set the first fire.
Mmhmm.
Did you see
anything suspicious
when you were making
your rounds that night?
No, I didn't even
know it happened
until I saw
the fire truck.
It was horrible.
Right.
Right, right, right.
And did you see anyone
in a fireproof suit?
Don't you think
I would've told you if I had?
Bosso's S.U.V.
But where did he go?
Is he
about to strike again?
Electric fuses
and camping fuel.
What are you doing here?
That's not
a fireproof suit.
Dexter, you
a Civil War reenactor too?
You here for the battle?
Uh
yeah.
Which side
you fighting for?
The North.
You Blue Belly.
I should buck and gag you
right here.
Were you there
last weekend
at the Sixth Maine Battery
cannon firings?
No, damn.
I guess I missed that one.
It's
a whole weekend affair.
I was in charge
of special effects--
ground, air bursts,
artillery fire.
Which explains
what's in his car
and gives him an alibi
for Saturday's fire.
- Want to see some pictures?
- You bet.
Wow.
Bosso's not the phantom.
He's just strange.
But if he didn't set
those fires, then who did?
Oh.
Hang on just one sec.
I guess coffee
went better than expected.
After coffee, Hannah wanted
to show me the Flower Mart.
So we're walking around,
and I catch a whiff
of this flower.
It smells
just like licorice.
So I ask Hannah
what it is--
And I tell him
it's anise.
So I tell the lady
in the booth
that her anise
smells delicious.
Except you didn't quite
pronounce it right.
I don't know exactly
what I said,
but she did not
react well.
Well, do you blame her?
Sounds like you had
quite a day.
Yeah, uh--
we, uh, we really did.
So, Clint, how long
are you going to be in town?
Oh, just another day
or so.
And then I'm off
to Louisiana.
Oh, uh,
what's in Louisiana?
A poker tournament?
No.
I am all done with that.
I am looking for an honest way
to make a living.
And I think I found
the perfect thing.
You ready?
Crawfish.
Crawfish?
Yeah, a crawfish farm.
I got a line on one
near Lafayette.
I'm going to call it
"Big Clint's Crawdaddies,"
and I will ship 'em
to you fresh
anywhere in the country.
There's a market
for that?
You bet your balls
there is.
Ain't nothing like
a crawfish boil--
weddings, bachelor parties,
fourth of July.
Everybody
likes crawdads.
Well, I am excited
for you, Dad.
And I'm proud of you.
Well, thank you, honey.
Means a lot.
Well,
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you check out
of that motel
and come and stay with me
while you're here?
You're starting
a new business.
You're going to need
to save your money now.
No, no, no, no.
I couldn't do that.
I-I wouldn't want
to intrude.
- Oh, you're not.
- Yeah, don't worry.
I was going home
tonight anyway.
Why don't I bring you guys
breakfast in the morning?
Best doughnuts
you ever tasted.
Okay.
Aah! Aah! Oh!
Aah!
What the hell
are you doing, man?
Get out of here.
Mmm.
Man, it's like I died
and went to heaven.
I think if I had
one more of those,
I probably will.
I'd like to make
an orange juice toast
to the cutest damn couple
I have ever seen--
outside of me and Bubba
in prison.
That's just a little joke.
Right.
Well,
to you, Dad,
the king of crawfish.
There's
no stopping me.
I just gotta get
the money together.
So where are you
at with that?
Well, actually,
that's something I wanted
to talk to you about.
I figured you might like
to get in on the ground floor.
- What do you mean?
- Well, you know, invest.
I only need
about 20 grand more.
Oh, wow.
No,
it's a great opportunity.
I mean, there's
a guaranteed 10% a year back
on your investment.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I-I can't.
All my money's tied up
in the business.
Aw, come on, now.
Not all your money.
I mean, there's got to be
a little wiggle room
in there somewhere.
I'm sure you could
remortgage your place.
I don't think so.
No, this place has got to be
worth a pretty penny.
Dad, it's not
going to happen.
Well, fine.
Whatever.
Forget it.
I'm sorry.
I just don't have the funds.
What kind of daughter
won't even help out
her own fucking father?
Jesus, Dad.
Look, I need some air.
I'm going to go for a drive.
Dad,
you don't have to go.
You think
I was wrong,
telling him
I couldn't give him the money?
Of course not.
But I feel like
I should help him out.
Why?
Because he's my dad.
The same dad
who almost let you drown?
Who left you alone
in a hotel for three days?
He's trying
to change.
I doubt it.
Look, I know he's done
some bad things,
but there's good
inside of him, as well.
Oh, right,
you've known him for, what,
24 hours, and you think
you understand him?
Well, I have a sense
for this sort of thing.
Oh, yeah,
you and your dark--
whatever--
part of you.
That you
don't think exists.
Because it doesn't.
I gotta go to work.
It's the arsonist again.
Look, I'm just trying
to help here.
I know.
I appreciate it.
I'm sorry.
I'll be fine.
Go.
Okay.
?
Another "Bobby."
"It's Bobby."
He added an "it's."
Like we didn't know
it was Bobby.
Make sure
you get this.
Did you see Bosso?
He was sniffing
the body.
Probably for accelerant.
Still, it was
kind of creepy, right?
I mean, I know it would be
the biggest cliche in the world,
the arson investigator
turned out to be the arsonist,
but does he--
does he set off anything
in your lizard brain?
I don't think
Bosso's the phantom.
He has an alibi.
You vetted him?
I looked into him.
You said
you weren't going to take
any more cases
from the police.
- I didn't take it.
- Fuck, Dexter.
Why would you put yourself
in that situation?
Good question.
Why did I?
Hey, L.T.
We got
the security camera.
I'm going to take the hard drive
back down to the station
and see if we can get eyes
on the phantom.
Good.
We could use a break.
Hey, Hannah.
Wait, hold on.
Slow down.
What happened?
I'll be right there.
?
What happened?
Ii came back
from the Flower Mart,
and it was like this.
Oops.
Well, I had a couple of drinks
to take the edge off,
but I guess I might have
overdone it a little.
You did this
to get back at me
for not giving you the money
that you wanted.
Oh,
talk about paranoid.
But then,
maybe you've got reason to be.
Must be a whole lot
of folks hate you
for all the pain
you've caused.
How can you even
say that to me?
Playing mother nature
in here
with your stupid,
little flowers,
won't even help out
your own fucking father!
Because I don't want
to help you!
You got any idea
what it's like
to be the father
of the infamous Hannah McKay?
You're a goddamn curse,
you ungrateful little shit!
That's enough, Clint.
You stay out of this.
This is family business.
You know you killed
your mother, don't you?
She died
of a broken heart
after your spree
with Wayne Randall.
I'm sorry.
Everybody would have been
a lot better off
if I'd let you drown
that day at the pond.
Get out of here.
Now.
Fine.
I said
what I had to say.
Well, it looks like Hannah's
found herself another winner.
You two
deserve each other.
I can cut a body up
into pieces,
but how do I help Hannah
put herself back together?
Could you have picked
more of a dump?
Come on, Maria.
It's perfect for all this
cloak and dagger bullshit.
It's the kind of place you take
hookers and ugly broads.
And also,
nobody sees you.
You should know,
I followed up
on all the names
you identified on my list.
Yes, the list
of suspicious police employees
who own boats.
Yes.
They were all dead ends.
All except
for Dexter Morgan,
who conveniently
moved his boat
right when we were closing in
on his marina
during the official Bay Harbor
Butcher investigation.
You really think Dexter
is the Bay Harbor Butcher?
It's worth
looking into.
No,
it's a waste of time.
Now, look, you have
to start thinking logically.
If Doakes really wasn't
the Bay Harbor Butcher,
then that means that somebody
probably framed him.
Right.
Which means that same person
probably killed him,
most likely
the real Bay Harbor Butcher.
So the best thing
to do is to look
into Doakes' final days.
We should start with the cabin
in the Everglades.
Where Doakes died.
Makes sense.
First let's eat.
- Okay.
- Waiter.
Oh, wow.
You went all out.
Well,
you had a rough night.
I figured you could use
a pick-me-up.
Sit.
You were right
about my dad.
I'm sorry
I was.
I just--
I feel like such a sucker.
You know, I don't fall
for anybody's bullshit,
but when it comes
to him, I--
I get it.
Fathers can be complicated.
I just don't understand why I
keep holding on to this idea
that, underneath it all,
he's a good person.
Maybe because the idea
that he's not
is just too hard
to take.
Well, I just hope
he's gone for good.
You sure
scared the shit out of him.
That voice--
I hadn't seen that look
on your face
since you took me
to see the snow.
Is that
what you were talking about?
Your dark...
rider?
Dark passenger.
Okay, fine.
It sounds a little silly
when you say it out loud.
No, I-I get
what you mean, you know.
You do seem like
a different person,
so it makes sense that you would
name that part of yourself.
Does it
just take over?
Where do you go?
Does Dexter Morgan
just disappear?
No,
I'm still there.
Do you hear a voice,
or--
Not exactly.
It's more like a need.
So it's just
like a feeling.
Well,
I should get to work.
Unless you need me to--
No, I'm good.
I got pancakes.
Okay, the good news
is that we have
the phantom
entering the bus.
The bad news is
that he never shows his face.
My promise to Deb is getting
harder and harder to keep.
This is more
than just a feeling.
There's no way
to I.D. him?
I didn't say that.
Right there.
He grabs a rail bare-handed.
We might have a print.
Halle-fucking-lujah.
Pull the fucking print
off the rail,
and we might get lucky
and get a match.
All right.
Let's go, bro.
Hey, baby.
What's up?
What?
Whoa, whoa.
Motherfuck.
I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
Fucking Novikov's
sending Nadia
to work at a sex club
in Dubai.
He's holding her
at the Fox Hole.
I gotta get her
out of there.
- You're going alone?
- I got no choice.
He's putting her
on a flight tonight.
You're going to need backup.
Let's go.
Where do you think
you're going?
I'm here
to see George.
Why don't you
stay here?
Hmm?
Well, well,
if it isn't Sir Lancelot.
- Where's Nadia?
- Nadia?
Let me go get her
for you.
She's got something
to tell you.
Get over here.
All right, tell your boyfriend
who you belong to.
Let her go.
- Tell him.
- Fuck you.
You touch her a-fucking-gain,
you're dead.
Oh, what are you going
to do, Mr. Policeman?
You're going to shoot me
in my own club?
Fuck.
Don't move.
Nadia,
get behind George's body.
I want you
to take this gun, Nadia--
I want you to shoot me
in the arm.
Okay, sweetie?
It's okay.
Shoot me in the arm.
What the hell--
are you okay?
I'm fine.
He pulled a gun and shot me.
I had no fucking choice.
He just grazed me.
- Christ.
- Go to the safe.
Get your passport
and the money and go.
What?
She's a witness.
I'm not going to let her
take that money.
She's earned it.
She can't be a witness.
The Koshkas
will kill her.
And she's here
illegally.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Go, go, now.
So did you find
a match?
We'll see.
I'm running the phantom's prints
through A.F.I.S. now.
Nothing.
Fuck me.
So what now?
You hand the whole thing
over to me
and let me take care
of it my way?
I can't stop thinking
about this "Bobby" thing.
You know, that somehow,
that's the key.
It's a kid's name.
Nobody calls an adult Bobby.
He wrote "it's Bobby"
on the bus.
Sounds like Astor and Cody,
blaming each other.
"It's Astor."
"It's Cody."
You think the fires
have something to do
with his childhood?
Could be.
Maybe his urges
started back then.
I wish we could run that print
against the juvie records,
but that shit's sealed.
Back to square one.
Not for me.
?
Government workers
never miss a break.
There's your phantom.
Arrested for burning down
his school's gym at age 12.
Spent some time in detention,
set his roommate's bunk on fire.
Got sent to
a psychiatric facility in 2006.
That explains why the fires
only just started now.
You going to turn that
over to Deb?
Call it in
on the tip line?
I'm not sure I can.
Deb was right.
Now that I have proof,
my urges are beyond my control.
Your dark passenger.
Where did you come up
with that, anyway?
I thought I got it
from you.
I gave you
the code.
The dark passenger
was all yours.
You said it got
into me too early,
in that shipping container.
Like you thought
I was possessed.
I meant you were traumatized,
Dexter.
Not possessed.
I remember the first time
you said it.
You must have been
about 12.
I just let it go.
I couldn't let you blame
yourself for feelings
that were too complicated
for a young boy to understand.
But you're not
a boy anymore.
- You sound like Hannah.
- Maybe she's right.
Maybe the dark passenger
is just a feeling.
- It can't be.
- Why?
Because if there's
no dark passenger,
then I'm responsible
for everything I've done.
It sure is a whole lot simpler
to just pin all the blame
on something else,
isn't it, Dexter?
It's much scarier
to think
that the dark passenger
is no more real than I am.
This is
where the cabin used to be.
Yeah, before it got blown
to smithereens.
Juan Alonso?
I'm Captain Maria LaGuerta
from Miami Metro Homicide.
This is
Thomas Matthews.
What do you want?
Were you the owner
of this property back in 2007?
And did you rent it,
at that time,
to a James Doakes?
The Bay Harbor Butcher.
No, no, no, no, no.
I told the cops back then,
I had nothing to do with that.
Then how did Mr. Doakes
come to be staying here?
I was renting the place
to Santos Jimenez.
Jimenez?
Some kind
of Colombian drug guy.
Not that I knew it
at the time.
I would never rent
to a criminal.
Of course not.
Now, why does that
sound so familiar?
Now I know why the name
Santos Jimenez rang a bell.
He wasn't just
a drug runner.
He was one
of the three men responsible
for killing Dexter Morgan's
biological mother, Laura Moser.
- Moser?
- Yeah.
Some drug lord
put a hit out on her
because he found out
that she was Harry Morgan's C.I.
She was butchered by Jimenez
with a chain saw
right in front of Dexter
and his brother Brian.
Brian Moser?
The Ice Truck killer,
that was Dexter's brother?
Yeah.
So that means
that Dexter
watched his mother
get chopped up,
just like the Bay Harbor Butcher
chopped up his victims?
So what are you saying?
Where's Jimenez now?
He disappeared.
Murdered
by the Bay Harbor Butcher?
Maybe.
So who was more likely
to want Jimenez dead,
Doakes or Dexter?
- Oh, come on, Maria.
- No, Tom.
We can't ignore
the facts.
The Bay Harbor Butcher took
blood slides from his victims.
Dexter is
a blood spatter analyst.
And Doakes
always thought
there was something off
about Dexter.
What if Doakes
was on to him?
Jesus.
What if Dexter is
the real Bay Harbor Butcher?
What if he isn't?
I am going
to go question him.
No, no, no.
You're not going to do that.
Now, I don't think
you're right about this.
Trust me,
I hope I'm not.
If somebody's got
to talk to Dexter,
it's going to be me.
I've known him
since he was a kid.
He trusts me.
What's more, I'm a lot
less likely to fuck it up.
The only thing
that stands between me
and killing
the phantom
is a slightly deflated
water wing.
You sure we can't talk you
into coming for a swim?
Yeah, I'd love to,
but I got something
I gotta take care of.
Here, put your hand
through there.
Boom.
Do this one too.
There you go.
Well, well.
Who's this big fella?
That's my son,
Harrison.
Isn't that fancy?
And who are you?
I'm Jamie,
Harrison's nanny.
Boy.
They didn't have nannies
like you back in my day.
We're going to go
swimming now.
You ready?
Ready, little man?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Whoo.
Boy, the way
they coddle kids today.
You know, they're all going
to be expecting a helping hand.
The world
isn't like that.
It's sink or swim,
Sonny boy.
Have fun.
What do you want?
Well, Dexter, I can tell
that you care about my daughter.
I'm just here
to find out how much.
Get to the point.
I have some information
that could be very damaging
to Hannah.
Now,
I could give
this information
to the police,
or you could pay me
a nice, tidy sum
to keep it to myself.
What are you
talking about?
When Hannah
got out of juvie,
she killed a counselor
at a halfway house.
She fed him
rat poison.
Her roommate,
little gal named Arlene Shram,
saw her do it
with her own two eyes.
I figured the cops
could get her to spill her guts.
You're lying.
I read Sal Price's book
on Hannah.
He mentioned the counselor
but nothing about the roommate.
Because I hadn't told him
about it yet.
What?
Where do you think
he was getting
all those juicy,
little plums?
Price was paying me
to dish dirt on my daughter.
But I was saving the good stuff
for a bigger payday.
Then the son of a bitch
went belly-up,
and...pfft.
There went my meal ticket.
You'd sell
your own daughter out
for a crawfish farm?
Fuck crawfish, man.
I'm up to my ears
in gambling debt.
But you do
what you gotta do.
So you going
to give me my money,
or do I send Hannah
to jail?
Get out of here
before you see my bad side.
You might want to ask Hannah
about Arlene
before you come
to a final decision.
Then we'll talk numbers.
What exactly
were you doing here?
It was
a personal matter.
My girlfriend
works at the club.
Jesus, Quinn.
I came here to talk
to Novikov about Nadia.
The conversation
got heated.
He pulled out a gun
and shot me.
I returned fire.
Self-defense.
Plain and simple.
Well, write up a report.
I want it on my desk
in the morning.
There's a little problem
with your story.
There was a time lag between
the first shot and the second.
I want the truth.
I told you
the truth.
I went down
when George shot me.
He started to beat
the shit out of Nadia.
I reached
for my gun.
He wheeled around,
ready to blow my head off,
and I took him out.
That's what happened.
Okay.
Then we'll go with that.
Minus Nadia.
Hey.
Where's Dexter?
I don't know.
But I'd like
to point out the fact
that I am here,
doing my duty.
- What?
- Nothing.
I feel like
I'm going to be sick.
How can that be
my own father?
I'm sorry to have
to tell you all this,
but I needed to know
that he was telling the truth.
Arlene Shram
is the only person
who can put me in jail.
She saw me put poison
in that counselor's food.
I'm going to have
to pay him.
That's not going
to solve anything.
He's just going
to come back.
Well, I don't see
any other option.
When other people
have threatened you,
you've found
other options.
I can't.
He's my father.
I'm going
to call my bank.
I know
what you're thinking.
I'm not thinking
anything.
Clint McKay
doesn't meet the code.
But Joseph Jensen does.
?
It's not
as much fun
when you're not wearing
your suit, is it?
Who-who are you?
I can't see you.
Maybe I'm a phantom.
Then again,
maybe not.
A phantom
can't hurt you.
Oh, God.
Please don't.
- Who's Bobby?
- Let me go.
Stop whining.
Who's Bobby?
Bobby Hamilton,
my best friend when I was 12.
That's when you set
your first fire.
I didn't set it.
Bobby did.
It was all his idea.
But then he died,
and I got caught.
They sent me to the nuthouse,
like I was crazy.
It's all because of Bobby.
Fucking asshole.
So does he still talk
to you?
Is Bobby the one telling you
to set these fires?
No,
that would make me crazy,
and I'm not
fucking crazy!
But I only hurt people
because of Bobby.
No, you're the one
who's setting those fires.
You're the one
who's burning people alive.
You can't blame it
on something
that happened to you
when you were a kid.
You're not
a kid anymore.
It's time for you
to take responsibility.
Fuck.
?
The caller said
they smelled kerosene.
Looks like we have
the right place.
Holy shit.
That's Joe Jensen.
I interviewed this guy.
Dumb fuck must have
passed out from the fumes.
He's still alive.
I guess
we found our phantom.
Who'd have thought
it would be so easy?
Yeah.
Guys, come on down.
Got your call.
Glad you came
to your senses.
You got my money?
Yeah.
It's right back here.
What's
with all the plastic?
You'll find out soon.
?
What the hell?
I realize
this isn't the best way
to make a good impression
on your girlfriend's father.
But I can't allow you
to hurt Hannah.
Oh, please.
I won't talk to the cops.
I'll leave town.
I promise, I'll never come
near Hannah again.
I wish
I could believe you.
Actually, I don't, 'cause then,
I couldn't kill you.
Oh, please,
you don't have to do this.
That's what I'm realizing.
I don't have to.
But I want to.
Even though
you don't meet my code,
I really,
really want to.
Because, unlike you,
I care about Hannah.
You got the devil
inside you, boy.
No, I think
it's just me.
Sink or swim, daddy.
Hey, Deb.
We arrested the phantom,
thanks to you.
Now I know
why you weren't at the Fox Hole.
Consider it a gift.
Bullshit.
You want something in return.
And I'm guessing it's for me
to lay off your girlfriend.
Well,
now that you mention it.
Forget it.
I always give in to you.
But not anymore.
I understand.
I got the money
for my dad.
I left him a message.
He should be here soon.
- He won't be coming.
- How do you know?
I had a talk
with him.
I made it clear
that I wouldn't allow him
to hurt you anymore.
And I think
he understood.
So he's gone?
He won't be
bothering you again.
Thank you.
The dark passenger
has been with me
ever since
I can remember,
pulling the strings,
running the show.
But as it turns out,
I'm no puppet.
And you should know,
you were right.
About what?
The dark...rider.
He doesn't exist.
Turns out,
maybe you understand me
a little better
than I understand myself.
I love you.
I think
I love you too.
Hey.
I need your help.
We need to find a woman
named Arlene Shram.
Sure.
Who's that?
According to a message
I got last night
from Hannah McKay's father,
she's a witness
to a murder.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==