Henry Winchester.
My father
and his father before him
were both Men of Letters.
If you guys
were such a big deal,
then why haven't we
ever heard of you?
Josie.
No one told me this initiation
was a formal affair.
The hard part's over, right?
We made it.
What do you know about the
Men of Letters massacre of 1958?
My name is Abaddon.
We will march into Hell,
and demonkind will rise up
and sweep over the earth.
Who put Crowley in charge?
The King's dead.
Long live the queen.
You knew about the mark.
You knew about Abaddon and Cain.
You knew all of it.
And you played me.
You owe me!
You make me a junkie.
You keep me stashed away
for months
while my kingdom falls apart?!
So, where is the Blade?
This is the object
of your quest.
Dean!
Drop the Blade.
I'll hang on
to old donkey teeth here
until such time
as you locate Abaddon.
I'll tell you, one of
the things that I really love
about the Tour Angle 144 --
there are a lot of you
out there
that have something
called the chipping yips.
Um, you're not proud
of having them.
A lot of people don't even
want to talk about it.
If you don't have them,
be glad.
But I got to tell you,
this product...
What's
on the menu tonight?
Meatloaf.
Really? Again?
And you're gonna make little
motions back and through...
...just brushing the grass.
I wish
you wouldn't say that.
You know how hard I work all
day, and yet you criticize me.
So, yes.
We're having meatloaf.
With potatoes...
and broccoli...
...and lots
of good things.
? Supernatural 9x17 ?
Mother's Little Helper
Original Air Date on March 25, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey.
You catch any shut-eye
last night?
Nope.
Guess I'm driving, then.
Driving where?
Caught wind
of a case online.
A 1st-grade teacher came home
and killed her husband.
Well,
maybe she snapped.
Ankle biters
can do that to you.
Dude, she pounded him,
into ground chuck.
So,
what are you thinking?
Best guess --
possession.
Why don't you go?
Dean, look.
I want to find Abaddon,
too,
but we've been combing
through this stuff for days.
Well,
maybe we missed something.
And maybe there are better ways
to spend our time
than just spin our --
Maybe we don't have time.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
Yeah?
See, because ever since
you killed Magnus,
you've been acting...
sort of...obsessed.
Well, maybe because I want
an end to all this.
Maybe because
if we find Abaddon,
then Crowley ponies up
the First Blade,
and we kill her
and him both.
So, what you call
being "obsessed,"
I call doing my job.
Okay, um...
I get it, Dean.
I'm just checking in.
I'm fine.
All right.
Hit me up
if you find anything.
It says here
in your report
that you were the first on the scene?
Yes, sir.
I found Mrs. Young sitting next
to her husband covered in his blood.
Now,
was her husband abusive?
Ric?
Oh, no. Not at all.
I mean, he could be a stubborn
S.O.B., but can't we all?
Ah.
Anything else, uh, weird
that maybe you felt
was too odd to include?
Like?
Like,
did you smell sulfur?
Why would I smell sulfur?
Of course. Uh, thank you.
What about Karen's eyes?
You notice anything strange?
Actually, agent, they, uh,
pretty much looked like eyes.
Oh, lord.
I don't get this.
Karen and Ric were
two of the most ordinary people
you'd ever meet.
Did she go anywhere
on the day of the murder?
It was Saturday.
Uh...
A quick trip
to the grocery store.
That's about it.
How's Mrs. Manson doing?
Dead.
Hung herself in her cell.
Lovely.
The demon smoke out?
If it was a demon.
I mean, there was no sulfur,
no EMF anywhere.
And everyone who saw her
just before
she gutted her husband
said she was totally fine.
What are
you still doing there?
This sounds like
a case of the crazies to me.
Well, if nothing kicks up
by morning, I'm out of here.
How's the research going?
It's going.
All right. Well, uh...
Good luck.
I can give you the Mark, Dean,
if it's what you truly want.
Can I use it
to kill that bitch?
Yes.
But you have to know with
the Mark comes a great burden.
Uh-huh.
Yep.
No. I know. I'm sorry.
No, I'll make it up to you.
Look,
I'm trying to get there, babe,
but I got into a fight
with my mom.
Oh,
I think I got a bite.
Yeah, a van is pulling up.
Let me roll.
I love you. Bye.
Oh, hey!
I didn't know this was
your ride, Mr. Richie.
Let's get you
out of the cold.
Thanks.
It's freezing out there.
Hey,
what -- what are you doing?!
Get off me! No!
Order up.
Here you go.
Thanks, R.J.
Can I get you anything else,
honey?
Uh, this is great.
Thank you.
Order up.
Be with you in a minute,
Bill.
Billy, what are you doing?
Your mother raise you in a barn?
Don't talk to me
like that!
Hey.
Take it easy.
She's working hard.
What's eating you?
You. My mom.
Him.
Buddy...Give it a rest.
Billy?
Billy.
I'm gonna call your mom,
have her come fetch you.
No, you're not.
So, tell me
what's happening here.
I was hoping you'd tell me.
You're the one
that mentioned weird.
Now, where did
they all come from?
Oh, they're all locals.
Four of the straightest arrows
you'd ever meet.
Apparently, they've been
acting like this for days.
Do they share anything
in common?
Church? School?
Uh, book club?
Not of my knowledge.
Oh,
I met the kid's girlfriend.
She said he was hitching a ride
when a van picked him up,
and that's the last
she heard of him.
Whatever that's worth.
What are you, Billy?
Clear.
Of?
Everything.
Why are you doing this?
You think there's a "why"?
No.
It's because I want to.
And I can.
Grocery store
surveillance pics.
Great. Thank you.
Hey.
Well, that took forever.
Uh, well, I'm working.
You got anything?
Not sure.
But, um,
a handful of other people
have started acting out,
too.
Acting out how?
Well, same as the woman --
aggressive, violent, impulsive.
Sounds like
you're in a Gold's gym.
Yeah.
Except it's less
steroid-induced,
and more...basic instinct.
It's like the littlest things
can set them off.
Kind of like me.
You've got no instinct.
I mean, you are
seriously messed up.
You?
Yeah, uh, soulless me.
Remember that?
Yeah,
how could I forget?
But you weren't out of control
like these people.
Yeah, well, maybe everyone
has a different reaction
to losing their soul.
Possible.
So, what?
A crossroads demon making deals
and taking people's souls?
No, I don't think so.
I mean, it's not as if these
people are winning the lotto.
Okay.
Uh, well,
that was my best swing.
I hope not, Dean.
I-I could really use
your help down here.
Dean?
Yeah, no, I --
I heard you.
I just, uh...
I'm getting close, Sam.
I can't drop the ball on Abaddon
right now.
All right. Be safe.
You're lying to Sam
like he's your wife,
which kind of makes me
your mistress.
Now,
listen to me, young man.
Those demons are back.
I'm telling you,
it's happening all over again.
Demons?
Yes! Demons.
Are you deaf?
Yes, ma'am.
You know what?
We're gonna take care
of those demons right away.
Now, do you need a ride home
or something?
Don't patronize me,
you little turd.
Hey, you know what? I can take
it from here. Um, agent Leiter.
Please.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Sure.
Now, why don't you, uh,
tell me all about these demons,
Ms. Wilkinson?
Please, call me Julia.
It's very simple, Agent.
They...
...they came to Milton.
And?
I say "demons,"
and you don't bat an eye,
when everyone else around here
thinks I'm nuts on toast.
Maybe I'm just a bit more, uh,
open-minded than most.
Maybe.
You're one of them,
aren't you?
Sorry. One of who?
Men of Letters.
They came here in 1958.
Men of Letters...
came here?
Oh, yes.
It was different then.
I was different.
They were
a lovely couple.
Sister Julia,
please answer the door.
Yes, Mother Superior.
Good evening, sister.
We're here from
the Office of the Inquisition.
What do you want?
You tell me, romeo.
You rang.
Let me guess --
you butt-dialed me?
Whatever the hell
that is.
Either way,
we done here?
Actually, long as I'm here,
last time we chitchatted,
we agreed that you were gonna
line up Carrot Top.
Yep, well...I'm on it.
Unless Abaddon likes
10-cent wings, stale beer,
and the clap,
I doubt that she's here.
Go to hell.
Oh, if only.
What's going on with you,
huh?
You call me,
you hang up.
You want Abaddon,
you don't want Abaddon.
You want the Blade,
you don't want the Blade.
If I didn't know you any better,
I'd say you're stalling.
Just between us girls,
how did you feel
when you sunk the First Blade
into Magnus' head?
Not half as good as I'm gonna
feel when it's yours.
Love it
when you talk dirty.
You know what I think?
I think
you felt powerful...
Virile...
And afraid.
Afraid?
Don't scam a scam artist,
darling.
You're stalling
'cause you're scared.
They gave false names,
but later I learned
that the man's name was Henry.
Henry Winchester?
Never got a last name.
Okay, um, and the woman?
Josie.
Did you know them?
Yes, uh...
Sort of.
It's complicated.
I'm an ex-nun, sweetie.
Complicated
my middle name.
Now, w-what were they here
to investigate?
Sister Mary Catherine.
She killed two people before
jumping from the bell tower.
So I took 'em to see
Mother Superior
and sister Agnes.
Time is of the essence,
Mother...Superior.
The cardinal is meeting
with the holy father
first thing in the morning,
and he wants a report.
Our beloved abbey
is open to you, Father.
Sister Julia here
will be your guide.
Where would
you like to begin?
Sister Mary Catherine's
sleeping quarters, please.
Sister Mary Catherine's room
it is.
I hate nuns.
Why, because she answered me
and not you?
No, because I went
to Catholic school
and I have
a lot of pent-up anger.
We have no time
for such pettiness.
What's got your boxers
all in a bundle?
This.
Why are
we out in the field?
It's called
learning on the job.
And you know damn well
this is the last assignment
before we are full members.
Therein lies
the problem.
As our initiation grows closer,
I...
I worry that this might be
a selfish endeavor on my part.
Selfish. How?
If anything were to happen
to me, what of John? Millie?
They'd be proud to know
that you answered the call.
No. My wife would be a widow,
and my son fatherless.
I don't expect you
to understand.
You don't have a fam--
I'm sorry, Josie.
I didn't mean it that way.
I know, Henry.
You're a good man.
Millie is lucky to have you.
Here we are.
The...blood
wouldn't come off.
So, we're assuming demonic
possession here, correct?
Or a linguist gone mad.
It looks ancient.
Zapoqra or Sanskrit?
No.
It -- it's pre-Enochian.
A crest of some sort.
Kni--
"Knights of Hell"?
What is that?
Trouble.
Knights of Hell?
What were they doing there?
I'm not sure
of anything I saw that night.
We couldn't leave our room
after 10:00.
Mother Superior
forbade it.
Stay still.
I woke up in
a dark place, tied to a chair.
There were others.
They were taken.
I was so scared.
I prayed and prayed, but God
didn't answer my prayers.
Henry and Josie did.
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus...
Ergo, Draco maledicte et omnis
legio diabolica,
adjuramus te.
Et secta diabolica!
Ut ecclesiam tuam secura tibi
facias libertate servire,
te rogamus, audi nos!
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus,
omnis satanica potestas,
omnis incursio
infernalis adversarii,
omnis legio!
Henry!
You hunters are always
sticking your noses in
where they don't belong.
Hunters?
Please.
Then what are you?
Quickly, dear,
before this one pays
for your stubborness!
We are preceptors...
Beholders, chroniclers
of all that which man
does not understand.
A woman
amongst the Men of Letters?
Yes.
Well,
ain't that a blast.
You do know
what we're capable of, demon?
Yes.
I know what you think
you're capable of,
but perhaps I should see
for myself.
Wait.
What are you doing?
I'm trading up from this bag
of bones to Mr. Dreamy here.
Then I can study your kind
real close.
Don't, or I'll --
or what?
Take me, not him.
You're joking.
I could be more useful
to you.
People underestimate
a woman.
No. That's not it.
You love him.
He loves you, too,
you know.
Like a sister.
Please...
Spare him.
Take me.
You have my permission.
You've been very entertaining,
my dear.
But I don't need
your permission.
Abaddon takes
what she wants.
And right now,
she wants everything.
You're going to study
the Men of Letters?
For a moment.
And then
I'll destroy them.
And what of all this?
Keep it going
until I return.
Now play dead.
Henry!
Are you okay?
We did it.
We stopped the demons.
Abaddon.
Did you ever see exactly what
she was doing down there?
No, but whatever it was she was
doing at St. Bonaventure,
it seems
to be happening again.
The convent's name
was St. Bonaventure?
Yes.
Where is it?
On the outskirts of town.
It's been closed
for years.
I love this.
I really do.
Couple of cold ones,
a kind jukebox...
Good and evil,
bro-in down.
Shut your pie hole,
Crowley.
Yeah,
you said that already.
Look, I merely suggested
you might be a bit scared.
Yeah. No, I heard you
the first time.
You still don't know what
the hell you're talking about.
I know that Cain gave you
his Mark for a reason.
And I know that rather
than embracing it,
rather than looking at it
as the gift that it is,
you're sulking like
you lost your knuffle bunny.
Why are you fighting
what you really are?
I'm a hunter.
Who's a chip
off the old Mark of Cain.
No. When I kill,
I kill for a reason.
I'm nothing like Cain.
Nothing like --
who are you talking to?
I know you're not talking to me.
Eat me.
I saw you.
I saw the two of you together.
Nothing like Cain?
What's in that bottle? Delusion?
I'm really starting to worry
about you, Dean.
Yeah, well, why don't you worry
about yourself?
I will.
'Cause like it or not,
we're in this together.
Your problems,
my problems...
Our problems.
Where you going now?
I'm going
to go water the lily.
Care to cross streams?
So serious.
? You're no good,
you're no good, you're no good ?
? baby, you're no good ?
Next time,
it'll be easier.
That's it.
Good.
You'll get used to the feelings,
even welcome them.
? You're no good ?
? baby, you're no good ?
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Easy.
I know what you're thinking.
I'm thinking I'd like
to take a leak, so move.
I'm Dean Winchester. And I know
a hunter when I see one.
You don't want to do
what you're about to do.
And why's that?
Because you're packing a knife
to a demon fight,
and you don't stand
a chance.
Then I'll go down swinging.
Hey, hey, hey.
Listen to me.
Any other day, I'd be
right there with you, brother.
I would, okay?
But you got to trust me
on this one.
Or you could grow a pair
and come with.
You ever
taken on a demon before?
Yeah.
Well, trust me when I say
that when he's done with you,
he's gonna go
after your family.
He's gonna go
after your friends.
Hell, he'll go
after your prom date.
So,
if you want to do that,
if you want to damn anyone
and everyone you've ever loved
in the slightest chance
that you could win,
then by all means, pal.
You go right ahead.
I got a kid sister.
She don't deserve that.
What's your name?
Jake.
Good to meet you, Jake.
Thanks.
I'll see you around.
Come on.
We got to go.
Demons don't take leaks.
Next time
you want to shoot up,
why don't you find
a better excuse?
Guilty as charged.
What happened? I thought
you were cleaning up your act.
Well, I was going to,
but then after
very little soul-searching,
I decided to embrace
my addiction.
What about you?
Takes a junkie
to know a junkie.
You just want to touch
that precious again, don't you?
I want to kill Abaddon.
That's what I want.
So, whatever happens with the
Blade, I can't worry about that.
Sure.
Whatever you got
to tell yourself
so you can sleep better
at night.
Look, what I want, what I fear,
none of that means squat.
Because this is the one chance
that we have to kill Abaddon.
So, I'm all in, no matter
what the consequences.
So the plan
remains the same?
I find her,
you bring the Blade.
It's a date.
For a second there,
I thought he made me.
He has other things
on his mind.
But he did do
exactly what you said he would.
He saved you.
Of course he saved me.
We're besties.
And now he's ready.
Souls are a very precious
and fragile thing.
Break one of those,
and them little buggers fly
right back home.
We can't have that,
now can we?
So,
after all these years,
you're still doing Abaddon's
dirty work, huh, Agnes?
Would you believe
it's gotten even dirtier?
Used to be folks believed
in the church.
Heck, the way they would come
strolling in here,
looking for God.
It was like fish in a barrel,
really.
But times change.
You can blame your perverts
for that.
Now I'm riding shotgun in some
smelly van with a handyman
and tricking any half-wit
I can lay my hands on.
But it's worth it.
Because...
Stealing souls is so noble.
Stealing souls is winning!
Winning what?
Hell's crown, nimrod.
You think Abaddon
is just gonna sit there
while those pantywaisted demons
refuse to pick a side?!
And so she made a plan --
if you can't convince 'em,
make 'em.
She's turning souls
into demons?
Hmm. A demon army, unbeatable,
loyal only to her.
Well, uh...
At this rate...
Should only take
a couple million years.
Have fun with that.
You think
I'm the only one doing this?
We have factories
spread throughout.
Worry not, though.
Victory is nigh.
And we'd like you to be
on our team.
Recruitment is easy.
I just have to rip your soul
out of your body.
Regna terrae,
cantate deo --
Please!
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus
omnis satanica potestas,
omnis incursio
infernalis adversarii,
omnis legio, omnis congregatio
et secta diabolica.
Ergo, Draco maledicte et omnis
legio diabolica,
adjuramus te.
Cessa decipere
humanas creaturas,
eisque aeternae perditionis
venenum propinare.
Vade, satana,
inventor et Magister
omnis fallaciae,
hostis humanae salutis.
Humiliare sub potenti
manu dei --
You know, um,
can I ask you something?
If it's for a date,
I'm sorry.
I never see anyone
under 65.
Too much drama.
Spit it out.
After witnessing
what you did,
why didn't you warn Henry
about Abaddon?
I became a nun
because I wanted to help people.
Make a difference.
But they
never prepare you.
They never tell you how to act
in the face of true evil.
Thank you, sister.
For the safety
of all those involved,
it's important that we keep
what happened here today...
...quiet.
Of course.
Soon after,
I left the order.
Why?
Because I was ashamed.
I had betrayed our flock,
God, myself.
It was
and still is my greatest shame.
Well, what you shared with me
saved lives.
And I couldn't have done that
without you.
Take care.
You too, Sam.
You okay, Henry?
Better.
We saved lives today.
We made a difference.
Hmm.
This -- our work...
It's a noble calling,
isn't it?
I mean, yes, there's risk,
but, gosh.
I feel the fool for doubting it
for even a second.
Hmm.
And you, Josie?
Me?
Well, I feel
like a whole new person.
Still plugging away?
Like a dog with a bone.
You?
You were right.
About what?
Finding Abaddon ASAP.
She's mining souls.
Why?
To create an army.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man