Something's broken here.
I'm not saying
that it's not. I...
We don't...see things
the same way anymore --
Our roles
in this whole thing.
I can't trust you.
We are family.
You say that
like it's some sort of cure-all,
like it can change
the fact
that everything that has
ever gone wrong between us
has been
because we're family.
15, 14, 13, 12...
11, 10, 9...
8, 7...
6, 5...
No chipmunking allowed!
Swallow
or you're disqualified!
...2, 1...
Looks like we got a wiener!
Yeah!
He cheated!
Hey, back off, Skeletor.
I won fair and square.
Like hell you did,
Jabba!
I saw you slip a hot dog
in your pocket!
Well, I hate to break it
to you, pal,
but that's no hot dog.
Ohh!
Mmm.
? Supernatural 9x13 ?
The Purge
Original Air Date on February 4, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey.
You go to bed
last night?
What? Uh, no.
No, "Rudy" was on.
"Unforgiven," and then I was
too jacked to sleep,
so...research.
Gadreel?
And Metatron
and the mark of Cain and...
Crickets.
I did find us a case, though.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, was a strange death
in Stillwater, Minnesota.
A competitive eater died
after a hot dog-eating contest.
So, what? Death by tube steak?
If only.
He got attacked in
his car, but, uh, get this --
he shrunk from 300 pounds
to 90 pounds.
Witchcraft?
Or a heavy-duty laxative.
You game?
Yeah.
Good.
Looks like it's a whore's bath
for me. I'll be ready in five.
You sure
you're okay, Dean?
Why wouldn't I be?
'Cause --
I don't know you...
This isn't about what
I said the other day, is it?
Oh, about that we're
not supposed to be brothers?
No, don't flatter yourself.
I don't break that easy.
Oh, good, 'cause I was
just being honest.
Oh, yeah. No, I got
that loud and clear.
Thanks for
your patience, agents.
Coroner's report
finally came in.
All right,
thank you.
All right, let's see.
Did Wayne McNut
really weigh 300 pounds
just moments
before time of death?
316 to be exact.
And the official cause of death?
Cardiac arrest.
But between you and me,
that's just a guess.
The vic suffered
massive organ damage.
Here you go, Jenny.
Ruptured spleen,
pierced liver, collapsed lung.
Looked like everything
was just
Sucked
right out of him.
Like he'd been hoovered?
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, I got
to be honest, fellas -- hm?
We're stumped.
This type of thing just
doesn't happen in Stillwater.
Now, did Wayne
have any enemies?
Hmm.
More like
an unfriendly rivalry.
A guy named
"Slim Jim" Morgan.
Like Wayne,
he was pretty well-known
in the competitive-eatin'
circuit.
Competitive-eating circuit?
Is that a big thing out here?
Oh, yeah.
You betcha.
Folks take it
real seriously --
train for months.
Eat all sorts of wackadoo stuff,
you know, like, uh...
Baked beans,
buff wings, butter.
Butter?
Yeah.
Sometimes deep-fried.
Hm.
This year alone,
Wayne won the Butter Bowl,
the Wing Ding,
and Shrimptasia.
Anyhoo, point being, Wayne McNut
was the only one Slim Jim
couldn't beat in
the whole Great Lakes region.
So is he a suspect?
We checked him out, but Slim Jim
was in the Hot Doggery
at the time
of Wayne's death,
and we got 15 witnesses
to prove it.
Really?
Yeah.
Training.
When I gear up for
a competition, I eat lettuce --
stretches the stomach.
Yet another reason
to stay away from salads.
How well did you know
Wayne McNut?
Well, well enough to know
he was a weasel and a cheat.
I hate to say it,
but, uh, karma's a bitch.
This is interesting.
Mala's
good-luck charms.
And Mala is...?
My old lady.
Is your old lady
superstitious?
Yeah.
She's Romanichal.
Romanichal?
Gypsy.
But don't call her that.
She says it's reductive.
But I think
it's a compliment.
I mean, gypsies are
all the rage on TV --
"My Big Fat Gypsy Wedding,"
"Gypsy Sisters"...
"Keeping up
with the Kardashians."
Um
you mind if I use your bathroom?
Yeah, go ahead.
But use the one upstairs
at the back.
Mala's taking
a shower in ours.
Right.
Did you really lose
the "Wiener Winner" by one dog?
Yeah.
And what are we talkin'?
Six inches? Foot-long?
Look, agent. Am I a suspect
here or what?
'Cause unless you got
a warrant --
You, uh, ready to go?
Yeah.
Uh, Mr. Morgan,
thank you for your time.
If you remember
anything else,
this is our number and
where we're staying locally.
All right, so, we got what
appears to be Wayne McNut's hair
and...
a bag full of weird.
In Romanichal culture, the pouch
is called a putsi bag.
It's used for hexes.
Okay, so, what?
Mala's putting hexes
on hubby's competition?
I mean, what do
we got ourselves?
A "thinner" sitch here?
Slim Jim
might not even know.
Hm.
Hi.
I believe you have
something of mine.
Kill Wayne?
I loved him!
So...you were...
Yes. Okay?
We were having an affair --
for years, actually.
I don't mean
to be rude, uh...
But how is it that Wayne McNut
is your type?
I mean, you're married to a man
who's barely a buck -- wet.
What can I say?
Sometimes it's nice
to feel a little give.
Oh.
Yeah, I get that -- a little
extra cushion for the, uh...
Help me
understand something.
If you loved Wayne,
why did you put a curse on him?
It wasn't a curse.
Putsi bags are also used
for blessings.
I wanted Wayne to win.
Plan was, take the prize money,
get a quickie divorce,
and then tie the knot
in Orlando.
Wayne used to call me
his "Princess Jasmine."
? Love lifts us up
where we belong ?
? where the eagles cry
? on a mountain high
? Love lifts us up
where we belong ?
? far from the world below
? up where...
I gained weight?
How is that even possible?
Hello?
Anyone there?
Let's try this again.
Any idea what the vic
weighed beforehand?
165.
So...180.
Known fact -- all women lie
about their weight and age.
Wait, you told that waitress
the other day you were 29.
Mm-hmm.
Need anything else,
agents?
Yeah, is
Sheriff Hanscum around?
Sorry. She's out
for the rest of the week.
Hell of a time
to take a vacation, right?
Okay, so,
we have two victims,
with seemingly nothing
in common except, uh --
a love for eclairs.
Check this out.
What is that?
A birthmark?
Huh.
So the weight had to
come off somehow, right?
What if it's a suction mark?
A suction mark?
Okay.
Uh, changeling?
Yeah, but changelings
don't take over kids.
Neither of the vics
had any.
And we don't know if Wayne McNut
had a suction mark.
Unless we missed it.
Yeah.
Well, we should, uh, split up.
One of us should hit the morgue.
The other should stay here
and question the staff.
I'll stay.
Ain't gonna happen.
Why?
Because you're weird
around girls.
What does that mean, weird?
You're awkward. You know,
weird -- Sam Weird.
Sorry, man.
I'm just being honest.
So, you were scheduled
to close the gym last night?
Yeah, but I didn't
exactly lock up.
Carol was still
working out,
and
I had a date.
I didn't want to
shortchange her, you know?
I mean, the poor girl
has been working so hard
to lose weight
for her wedding.
I slipped her the key,
and I told her to lock up
on her way out.
Oh, it's all my fault.
Hey.
Find anything at the morgue?
Yeah.
Uh, so, Wayne was
banged up pretty bad.
But on the back of his neck,
just below his hairline...
suction mark --
identical to Carol's.
Okay, so,
they both had marks,
just like the hot trainer
at Rollz.
But she was skinny...
and alive.
And just recently lost
a ton of weight.
When I asked her
about the mark, she, uh --
she clammed up,
got all embarrassed.
So, uh,
I did some checking.
And it turns out that she took
a couple of "me" days
last month
and, uh, went here.
Canyon Valley?
Hm. Yeah.
When you look in the mirror,
do you recognize the fat person
staring back at you?
Have you tried every fad diet,
every fitness trend out there,
but nothing
seems to work?
Here at Canyon Valley,
we guarantee weight loss
with no surgery...
No extreme dieting...
...and no intensive
workout regimen.
Guaranteed results
in one week!
You can reach
your weight-loss goals.
We did.
But only if you reach
for the phone
and call
Canyon Valley...
Now.
How far away is that place?
Couple of hours.
We were really, really moved
by the online testimonials.
Oh, yeah.
That was some powerful stuff.
And you boys are both
certified personal trainers?
Yeah.
Yeah, personal training brothers.
Kind of like Hans and Franz,
but, uh, less German.
And you're certified in...
Makin' people sweat!
Yeah. Kickin' ass
and takin' names!
That's how we do!
Uh...
Uh, to clarify, uh, what my
brother's trying to say is,
w-w-we both have a passion
for-for fitness
and helping people.
Oh, us too.
Hm.
In fact,
that's how we first met.
I was Maritza's first client
back in Peru.
I was on a student visa --
homesick, stressed,
eating my troubles away.
Oh, he was the size of a casa.
Oh, it's true!
I was one empanada away
from a heart attack.
But then this...
gorgeous godsend
made me the lean, mean,
fighting machine I am today.
Hm.
Ho!
Oh.
But I digress.
Now, the good news is,
we are hiring.
The bad news is, there's only
one trainer position available.
How do you feel about working
in another department?
Huh?
Nice shorts.
Nice hairnet.
Yeah, why do I got to be
the lunch lady?
Since when have you ever complained
about being around food?
- Okay, this is not food.
- Hey, new guy.
Quit flirtin' with the trainer
and keep scoopin', huh?
It's all right.
My, uh...Ashtanga yoga class
starts in five minutes.
How the hell do you know
anything about yoga?
You're not the only one
who's ever dated someone bendy.
Hey, you have
any oatmeal?
Yeah, I wish.
No, but we have, uh, something
that's tofu over there.
I -- what is that?
It's a pancake. It's tofu.
I feel like a baby
asking this, but...
Will the treatment hurt?
Not at all.
The only drawback of cupping is,
it leaves a suction mark.
It can bruise a little.
Cupping?
Yes, ancient Chinese secret.
All the celebrities do it.
It draws out toxins,
boosts metabolism.
You'll feel good.
Who knew?
Oh, excuse me.
It's just so relaxing
in here.
It's the aromatherapy.
The lavender
really packs a punch.
Huh.
Ahh. Geez.
That's wa-a-a-rm.
Flojo.
You got time to lean,
you got time to clean, huh?
I'm starving.
What do we get to eat?
Same as the clients.
They expect us to eat this rabbit food?
It's not rabbit food.
It's super food.
I'm not eating it.
At Canyon Valley, we're supposed
to lead by example.
This is
leading by example?
It's not for us, stupido.
It's for the clients.
They're allowed to have
pudding on their spa day.
It's like a -- a last hurrah
before the real work starts.
Get to work.
- Hey, Frank.
- Yeah?
We need to order more asparagus.
Okay.
Mm.
What do you know?
Looks like
it's my "spa day," too.
Okay, good job, guys.
Go to, uh...
Downward dog.
Hold for five minutes.
Five minutes?
It's usually 30 seconds.
Right. Yeah, 30 seconds.
That's what --
that's what I mean.
Okay, uh,
I'll just come around,
make sure everybody's
form is okay,
make sure you're, uh,
keeping your cores tight,
and, uh, your --
uh, good job. Great.
Straighten that back out.
Mmm.
Mm.
Well done today! Good job!
Good work, guys!
Good work!
Namaste!
Okay. Good work.
See you all soon.
Good job.
How was class?
It was, uh...great.
Yeah.
Agent Frehley?
What are you doing here?
Uh, I-I-I don't know. She must
be pretty out of it, huh?
Oh, excuse me.
Sorry.
I got to get this.
Yeah?
Have a good one.
Sammy.
Dean?
What's wrong with you?
I need your help.
Where are you?
Dean?!
Sweet potatoes.
Sw...
Dean?
Dean!
- Dean!
- Sammy.
Dean! Hey! Hey!
Wake up!
What took you so long?
What the hell happened?!
I was drugged.
Dru-- what?
Pudding.
It was supposed to be
for the clients,
but I couldn't resist.
What, salted caramel?
Yeah, man.
The best of both worlds --
salty and sweet.
Right. Uh...
All right, you stay here.
No, no,
I'm gonna come with you.
Go ahead, man.
I'll catch up.
Hey.
Did you make
the pudding?
Depends.
On what?
Whether you
liked it or not.
What's in it?
Relax, Jack Lalanne.
It's low-cal.
Nonfat milk, sea salt --
No, no.
Not the ingredients.
The something extra.
Chill, man.
Supplements, okay?
- What kind of supplements?
- Here. Hey.
To boost metabolism,
per Larry and Maritza.
These aren't "supplements",
they're roofies.
What? How do you know
what roofies look like?
How do you not know?
You think I want to end up
in a hotel bathtub
with my kidney
carved out?
In Chechnya?
Did you find
anything out in the yoga?
Yeah. Yeah. "Invasion
of the Body Snatchers."
Every single person
in class
had one of those
freaky-ass suction marks.
What the hell's
goin' on here?
You know, I didn't mean
to bail on you fellas,
but I've been waiting
over six months
to get
into Canyon Valley.
And let me tell ya,
it was worth it.
I already lost
10 pounds!
In -- in one day?
No offense, Sheriff --
'cause you look great --
um, but aren't you
the least bit curious
as to how you dropped
10 in a day?
Well, to tell you
the truth, Agent,
I don't really give
a flyin' fudge.
My husband, Doug,
left me last year
'cause he said I loved
cookie-dough milkshakes
more than him.
Sorry to hear that.
Yeah, Doug's a dick.
You deserve better.
Thanks.
But he was right.
That was a dark time
for me.
Whoever said
you eat your pain?
Not me. I guzzled it.
Anyhoo...
I guess I just wanted
to feel pretty again.
And Canyon Valley
did that.
Only question is...
What are you
doing here?
We're, uh, uh...
We're undercover.
Yeah.
Sort of got that.
We think that there's a
connection between Canyon Valley
and the murders in town.
What kind
of connection?
Suction marks.
You mean like this?
Yeah. Where did that come from?
My spa treatment.
Cupping.
Cupping?
Yeah. You know,
I thought it was gonna hurt,
but honestly, I snoozed
through the whole thing.
By the time I woke up,
I was down two dress sizes.
Before the cupping,
did you eat any pudding?
Darn tootin'.
Licked the bowl clean.
Donna, do you remember
who did this treatment?
Oh, yeah.
You betcha.
Evelyn,
you are looking great.
Just 10 more pounds
till your goal weight.
Do you mind if I borrow
my wife for a sec?
I'll be back.
Looking good, ladies.
Thank you.
The new guys aren't
personal trainers.
What are you talking about?
I did a little digging.
I found this
in their glove compartment.
They're Feds?
Worse.
They're hunters.
Why are hunters here?
Maybe because of this.
Oh, my God.
Do you think --
I do.
What are we going to do?
Relax. I'll take care of it.
Just get rid
of the evidence.
Okay, I'm no health nut,
but that...
is just wrong.
All right, talk.
This isn't what you think.
I'm not a killer.
Well, then,
what are you?
I'm a Pishtaco.
A fish taco?
A Pishtaco.
It means
"Peruvian fat sucker".
Never heard of it.
So, what, you're like vamps
with a sweet tooth
for cellulite?
Vampires kill.
We're just...
Parasites.
Oh, well,
in that case --
Look, I would
never hurt anybody!
Okay, this -- this is why Larry
and I started Canyon Valley.
We could help people
lose weight,
and I could feed.
It was a win-win.
Yeah, except for
the two you dysoned to death.
That wasn't me.
Well, then who was it?
Alonso.
The dude
from the cafeteria?
He's my brother.
I knew you were
a lost cause.
Unlike your sister,
you're weak.
Good to see you, too, Larry.
How could you do this to her?
To us?
Do what?
This.
Oh, that.
Oh
yeah, that.
You know what
that means?
Huh?
Now there
are hunters here!
It's your fault,
blanco!
If you didn't starve me, maybe --
Listen, freak!
Your sister and I spent years
building this operation.
And if you think I'm gonna let
your gluttony destroy it,
you got
another thing coming.
I want you out.
Now.
I'm not leaving Maritza.
Well, I got news
for you, pal.
She doesn't want you
here, either.
Either you leave...
or I'll make you.
I brought Alonso here from Peru
to show him a better way,
a more civilized way.
One where
we weren't monsters.
That the secret to coexisting
with humans was just...
eating enough to get by.
Let me guess.
Alonso wasn't a big fan
of portion control, was he?
No.
During a routine treatment,
he almost killed a client.
He sucked out
too much fat.
I demoted him
to kitchen duty --
no human contact,
just fat from a jar.
But he said
the more I deprived him,
the hungrier he got.
And now three people
are dead.
My husband...
Where's Alonso
right now?
The -- the basement?
That's -- that's where he spends
most of his time now.
What about her?
Well, till we figure out
which side she's on,
she stays put.
I am on your side.
Okay.
Then how do we kill him?
You and stupido have no chance.
The fat makes us stronger.
Your sister didn't mention that
when she ratted you out.
You're lying!
I guess after
you killed her husband...
you were too monstrous,
even for her.
We'll let you know if
we need any other information.
Thanks for everything.
Appreciate it.
Hey.
What did you tell
the sheriff?
The usual --
psycho killer on the loose.
They, uh...
usually buy it.
I lost
my whole family today.
I'm so sorry.
I...
Can I steal
you a sec?
Once this place
clears out,
we're gonna make this
a family affair.
Wait, Dean.
We're not gonna
kill Maritza.
She's a monster.
Yeah, who saved our asses.
You said that you wanted to
keep things strictly business.
Well, last I checked,
we were in the business
of killing monsters.
I wanted to keep things
strictly business between us.
But I still have a heart.
What if I had crossed paths
with a hunter
back when I was possessed
by Gadreel?
I could've
ended up dead, too.
Would I have deserved that?
Would I have deserved to die?
So, one-way ticket
to Peru?
I'm hitting it.
Yeah.
Hey.
Yeah?
About what you said
the other day.
I thought it didn't
bother you.
You know, Sam, I saved
your hide back there.
And I saved your hide
at that church...
And the hospital.
I may not think things
all the way through.
Okay?
But what I do,
I do because
it's the right thing.
I'd do it again.
And that...
is the problem.
Y-you think you're my savior,
m-my brother, the hero.
You swoop in,
and even when you mess up,
you think what you're doing
is worth it
because
you've convinced yourself
you're doing
more good than bad...
But you're not.
I mean, Kevin's dead,
Crowley's in the wind, uh...
We're no closer to beating
this angel thing.
Please tell me, what is
the upside of me being alive?
You kidding me?
You and me -- fighting
the good fight together.
Okay.
Just once,
be honest with me.
You didn't save me
for me.
You did it for you.
What are you
talkin' about?
I was ready to die.
I was ready.
I should have died,
but you...
You didn't
want to be alone,
and that's what all this
boils down to.
You can't stand
the thought of being alone.
All right.
I'll give you this much.
You are certainly willing
to do the sacrificing
as long as you're not
the one being hurt.
All right,
you want to be honest?
If the situation were reversed
and I was dying,
you'd do the same thing.
No, Dean.
I wouldn't.
Same circumstances...
I'm gonna get to bed.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man