Reverend Buddy Boyle's
"Goin' For Glory Hour."
When angels come a-knocking,
let 'em on in.
Angles can't possess a human
without permission, right?
Yep.
So, what?
They're using this guy
to find vessels?
It's a willing audience.
Who put Crowley in charge?
He's the king.
He's a salesman.
Right now you and I are gonna
talk about a regime change.
You're ours.
Your demon ass is going to be
a mortal ass pretty damn quick.
Where do I start
to even look for forgiveness?
How 'bout we start with this?
You're human?
Zeke?
Castiel cannot stay here.
He will bring the angels
down on all of us.
He's warded.
He was warded
when April found him.
Castiel is in danger.
And if he is here,
I am in danger.
Wait, you're in danger?
If he stays,
I am afraid I will
have no choice but to leave.
Cass, can we talk?
You can't stay.
Sir?
Sir, can you hear me?
Please --
please just say something.
Are you still there?
Keep talking,
and I can help you through this.
Please, sir, if you can hear me,
stay on the phone.
It may feel hopeless right now,
but you called the hotline
for a reason.
There's some part of you
that still wants to live --
some part that knows suici--
Who are you?
Did the lady from the hotline
send you?
No.
You did.
? Supernatural 9x06 ?
Heaven Can't Wait
Original Air Date on November 12, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I know, and that play
in the second quarter?
I mean, what team
is he playing for?
Not ours.
High-five!
Morning, Steve.
Bill.
High...
Five.
Sorry I'm late.
I had to drop the baby off
at daycare,
then hit every red light
on the way here,
but guess
I shouldn't have worried.
Place looks great.
Coffee urns.
Uh, full.
Dairy case.
Stocked.
Okay, Steve,
last question --
where have you been
all my life?
You're not like
the other sales associates.
There's...something different
about you.
I can assure you
there's -- there's not.
I know these things.
You're...
Mm. You're special.
That's your "big news""
is that you translated
the tablet into...
Doodles?
It's cuneiform.
I-I hit a wall translating
the tablet into English.
But I found
an ancient codex
linking the Angel script
to proto-Elamite cuneiform,
and I was able
to translate the tablet
and the footnotes
into Elamite, which is --
Doodles.
It's extinct.
Well,
can you read it?
No one can.
Scholars have tried
for centuries.
So it's a dead end?
N-not quite.
Now, most proto-Elamite
is abstract,
but I was able
to decipher
one phrase
from Metatron's footnotes.
"Falling angels."
Okay, so, the footnotes
refer to Metatron's spell?
Maybe.
Okay.
Well, maybe if we can
decipher the footnotes,
then we can
reverse the spell and...
Punt those winged dicks
back to heaven.
Where do we start?
Research.
We comb through
the library,
see if we can find
anything else on Elamite.
"Zimmerman's encyclopedia
of extinct languages volume 1:
Adai to Atakapa."
How many volumes
are there?
24.
Don't worry,
we've got them all.
Awesome.
There is a God.
Hello.
I may have a case for you.
Four missing
in Rexford, Idaho.
Presumed dead,
but no bodies have been released
to loved ones.
And there were reports
of a strange substance
at the scenes.
Oh, well,
hello to you too, Cass.
How are you?
I...am busy.
All right. So, how do you
want to do this?
You want to meet up at
the latest scene?
You want me to pick you up?
What?
Um, I've got my hands full
over here.
I just -- um...
Cass? Hello?
...thought you would want
to know about the case.
Hey, are you sure
everything's --
Okay.
So, he said nothing
about where he is
or -- or
what he's been doing?
This is Cass.
In case you forgot,
he's not exactly chatty Cathy.
And you're not even gonna
see him when you're in Idaho?
Well, like I said, as long as
he's catnip for angels,
he's keeping his distance.
So -- then what's
the point, Dean?
I mean,
it's barely even a case.
That's why I'm just gonna
go have a little look-see,
and we're not gonna waste
a whole lot of manpower
on a big pile of nada.
In other words, a perfect excuse
to bail out on research.
You got me.
Hey, Steve?
I found this
in the supply closet.
Do you know whose it is?
Um...
That's mine.
Thanks.
I also found
a rolled-up sleeping bag
behind the tool locker.
Yes, I wanted to be thorough
with inventory,
so I worked late
last week,
and taking a nap here was easier
than going back home to my bed.
Which I-I have, of course --
a bed...and a home.
Wow, Steve.
You're so...
responsible.
I've been afraid to ask.
I-I don't want to take advantage
of you as my employee,
and I certainly don't
want to jeopardize
our working
relationship.
But as a working
single mom,
it's hard enough
to get a date,
let alone
meet a really great guy.
And tomorrow's my night off,
and I know you're off, too,
and I was just wondering
if there's any chance you're...
free tomorrow night?
Um...
Yes?
Yes.
You're the best!
So, uh, four missing?
Four dead.
Just got confirmation.
And, uh, any common threads
you can think of?
Well, Joe in there
had the suicide hotline
on speed dial.
The gal before him
was a shut-in.
Had enough antidepressants
in her medicine cabinet
to stock a pharmacy.
The first victims --
a married couple
out of Sugar City.
Pretty much a walking billboard
for no-fault divorce.
Were they all basket cases?
If you asked me to make a list
of this county's saddest sacks,
these four would've been
right on top.
All right, so,
four unhappy people,
one of them
definitely suicidal.
But you've
ruled out suicide?
You're gonna
want to put these on.
This look like suicide to you?
Blood?
If the tests come back
same as the others,
it's everything.
Blood, skin, hair, nails.
Internal organs.
Even clothing fibers --
like these poor souls
got run through
the world's finest wood-chipper.
What about witnesses?
Same as the rest.
Neighbors reported
some kind of a pink flash.
By the time we got here,
all that was left was...
this.
Yeah, we're almost
through the texts over here.
We got nothing.
Have you tried
Professor Morrison?
Yeah, he's unreachable.
He took a sabbatical
to live amongst the Trobrianders
of Papua New Guinea.
Needless to say,
we're pretty burnt.
Well,
there's one guy there
who is nothing
notifl-rested.
Crowley?
I'm just saying.
We're not keeping him chained up
for the one-liners.
It's worth a shot,
I guess.
Just be careful,
all right?
Don't fall for any of his
"quid pro quo" crap.
Noted.
So, what about you?
How's Cass' lead
panning out?
Four victims
suddenly exploded.
I tried EMF.
I've looked for hex bags,
sulfur -- nada.
Spontaneous combustion?
Maybe the Thules?
No, no, no. I already
ruled them out.
The bodies were vaporized.
They weren't burned.
That sounds
like a real case.
Dean,
I should be there.
No, man. That's -- that's
uh...not necessary.
No, I, uh --
I got this one covered.
He dumped me, Jace.
In the cafeteria.
In front of everyone.
It's just like...
Who does that, you know?
Like, why couldn't he
just dump me on Facebook
like a normal person?
I've been destroyed.
Socially and romantically
totaled.
I know.
Just so embarrassed, Jace.
I could just die.
I can help with that.
What?
Thanks.
Good day, ma'am.
And good luck!
I'll have some beef jerky
and a pack of menthols.
What are you doing here?
Gee, it's nice
to see you, too, Cass.
It's Steve now.
And...you --
you surprised me.
Well, the feeling is mutual.
I mean, I knew you had to
lay low from the angel threat,
but, uh, wow!
This is some cover.
My Grace is gone.
What did you expect?
Do you have any idea
how hard it was?
When I fell to earth,
I didn't just lose my powers.
I --
I had nothing.
Now...
I'm a sales associate.
A sales associate?
Hey, Steve. Sign here?
I'm responsible for inventory,
sales, customer service.
I keep this place --
thank you --
thank you.
Clean and presentable.
And when my manager's busy,
I even prepare the food.
Wow.
So you went from fighting
heavenly battles
to nuking taquitos?
Nachos too.
I've been politely asking
for reading material for weeks,
and this is
what you bring me?
Pass.
Can you read Elamite
or not?
It's by no means my favorite
of the ancient tongues,
but yes.
Will you help us read it?
Why on earth would I?
Because I was there
that night.
I saw what humanity
did to you.
Like it or not,
there's a little part of you
that's not a douche.
Sorry, moose.
To the last drop.
Crowley, the only reason
you're alive
is because my brother
thought you would be useful.
So far,
you've done Jack.
Back to plan "B," I guess.
Which is?
Give you up to Abaddon.
You think you can
threaten me with that hack?!
She's all fury,
no finesse.
I'm not so sure.
Our last encounter with Abaddon,
she was, uh --
she was pretty terrifying.
Scarier than you've been
in years.
Bring that to me.
This is not you, man.
You are above this.
Come on.
No, Dean.
I'm not.
I failed
at being an angel.
Everything I ever attempted
came out wrong.
But here, at least I have a shot
at getting things right.
I guess
you can't see it,
but there's a real dignity
in what I do --
a human dignity.
Hate to interrupt
you guys, but, Steve?
Customer had an accident
in the men's room.
I'm on it.
Oh, and tonight --
7:00 at my place
work for you?
Great.
You're the best!
That's what
this is about!
What?
The girl.
No, Dean.
It's not.
Nora --
she's a very nice woman,
I'm pretty sure she's not
a reaper intent on killing me,
and she's asked me out.
Going on dates --
that's something
humans do, right?
Yeah. I mean,
my dates usually end
when I run out
of singles,
but, uh, yeah.
Yeah, that's something
that humans do.
This is Agent Lee Ermey.
I'll be right there.
There was another kill --
over at the high school.
You comin'?
I wouldn't be much use.
I don't have my powers.
So?
I've never had powers.
You are a hunter.
And you're a hunter
in training, remember?
Yeah, I remember.
You said I sucked.
I didn't say that.
I said that there was, uh,
uh, you know,
"room for improvement."
Come on.
All right, my shift's over
in five minutes,
and my date's
not until later, so...
Attaboy!
I'll go get the car.
Not just yet.
I have to clean
the bathroom.
One second we're talking,
and the next, she just...stops.
And then everyone
in the cafeteria freaks,
rushing and pointing
out the window, at --
Could -- could that
really be her?
And nobody saw anybody else
at the scene --
a man, woman,
anything unusual?
Your friend,
was she, uh, depressed?
Depressed?
Any thoughts of suicide?
Ew. No.
I mean,
she was kind of bummed
that dick-bag Travis
broke up with her
in front of the whole school.
Kind of bummed?
Yeah.
Like more bummed than when
she got a "C" on a quiz,
and...
less bummed
than when her parents split up.
Kind of...bummed.
Excuse me.
Cass, what's wrong?
I've seen this before.
What? Where?
In heaven.
What, you're saying
an angel did this?
It's no ordinary angel.
Dean, this is bad.
This is very bad.
On the battlefields
of Heaven,
there was a special class
of angel, the Rit Zien.
It's Enochian
for "Hands of Mercy."
They functioned
like medics.
They tended to the wounded.
They healed those
who could be healed,
but for the mortally wounded,
those who were past saving,
the Rit Zien's job
was to put them down.
But the granulated bodies?
This was
their special ability.
They had this way of smiting
that was so quick and so total
that it rendered death
virtually painless.
Yeah, but these
aren't wounded angels
that they're vaporizing,
they're people.
Right.
I don't know.
The Rit Zien home in on pain,
it's like a beacon to them.
So, when this angel
fell to earth,
he heard the victims' cries,
their anguish,
same as he'd hear an angel's
in heaven.
He's continuing
his heavenly work down here.
One suffering human
at a time.
Yeah, but this last victim
was not suffering.
She was just a normal,
moody kid.
But he just got here.
The ebb and flow
of human emotion --
Dean, I've been on earth
for a few years,
and I've only begun
to grasp it.
To him,
pain is pain.
So everybody's fair game?
All right, well,
we got to stop him.
You have to stop him.
You're scared.
It's different now, Dean.
Everything feels different.
You're right.
All right, I'll track down
this, uh, Kevorkian wannabe,
and I'll put him down.
Okay.
You stay safe.
Go on that date,
all right?
Go live a normal life.
Okay.
Well?
I need a ride.
Right.
I'll do it.
But I want something in return.
Yeah, what's that?
A telephone call.
Come on, moose.
Even Dahmer
got one telephone call.
Seriously?
You want to let Crowley
communicate with Abaddon?
A king and a power-mad knight
of hell isn't enough for you?
Want to throw a demonic team-up
into the mix?
I don't think so.
I mean,
I don't trust Crowley, either.
But I can't honestly see him
working with Abaddon.
He hates her too much.
You said it.
You can't trust him.
We don't have to.
Look, Crowley's bound.
We can end the call
whenever we want.
Even if he wanted
to give Abaddon information,
he has none
to give her.
He doesn't even know
where the bunker is.
He says he can decrypt
the translation?
What if he's lying?
You're right.
We're gonna need proof.
What are these?
Ingredients.
More specific.
Ingredients for a spell.
Heart of a Nephilim.
Cupid's bow.
Grace of an angel.
And the rest of them.
Phone call.
You'll get the rest
when I get paid.
Now, who's gonna be a dear
and open up a vein?
Okay.
Thanks, Dean.
Cass.
Wait.
I can't let you
do this.
What?
You're gonna wear that
on a date?
This is all I have, Dean.
Okay.
Uh, lose the vest.
What are you --
Lose the vest.
Come on.
That's a little better.
All right.
There we go.
And now your buttons --
why don't you
unbutton it?
Okay.
Th-that's far enough,
Tony Manero.
Um...
Yeah. Good. All right.
Listen to me.
Always open the door
for her, okay?
Ask a lot of
questions.
They like that.
And, uh...oh, if she says
she's happy to go Dutch,
she's lying.
All right?
Go get 'em, tiger.
Nice touch.
What are you doing,
jackass?
Hey!
Steve!
I'm so glad you're here.
Come in.
I thought
I was gonna be late!
Late for what?
My date.
Bowling,
would you believe it?
But damned if I'm not
dressing fancy,
even for bowling.
Haven't had an excuse
to doll up since Tanya was born.
And there she is,
my little angel.
Now,
she's already been fed,
she'll probably sleep
the whole time,
and I'll only be gone
a couple of hours.
I just couldn't get
my usual sitter,
and I needed somebody here
just in case she wakes up
and starts crying,
which she won't, I promise.
Baby Tanya never cries.
Wish me luck.
Oh, and thank you.
You really are the best.
Babysitting.
A-bup-bup-bup.
What?
Not yours. His.
What difference
does it make?
I've had yours.
Stuck in here,
you can't fault me
for wanting a little variety.
No way!
What's wrong,
Short Round?
Afraid of needles?
No, I just have a policy
of not giving blood
to anyone
who's murdered my mother.
I have nothing
but time.
You're a dick.
Good luck
with that translation.
Inferni sectatores,
nunc audite regem.
This is Crowley.
Connect me to --
Crowley.
Bad connection.
Your king.
If you don't connect me
to Abaddon right away,
I will be forced to --
What? What happened?
I've been placed on hold.
Hello?
Um...
Please -- please don't.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
How 'bout --
how 'bout a lullaby?
Um...
Okay. Shh. Shh!
? Look at what's happenin'
to me ?
? I can't believe it myself
? suddenly I'm up on top
of the world ?
? it should've been
somebody else ?
? oh, believe it or not
? I'm walkin' on air
? I never thought
I would feel so free-e-e ?
? flyin' away
on a wing and a prayer ?
? who could it be?
? Believe it or not,
it's just me ?
? believe it or not,
Shh.
I know, I know.
Sheriff?
Now, here's a wrinkle.
Our first crime scene,
married couple?
Full analysis of the spray
came in from the lab.
Turns out it only contains
the wife's DNA.
The husband's
still out there.
Nobody told you.
Nobody explained.
You're just shoved out
kicking and screaming
into this human life,
without any idea why any of it
feels the way it feels,
or why this confusion,
which feels like
it's a hair's breadth
from terror or pain.
You know, just when
you think you do understand,
it'll turn out you're wrong.
You didn't
understand anything at all.
Guess that's just how it is
when you're new at this.
You know,
it wasn't that long ago
when all I'd need to do to
ease your pain was touch you.
You're very warm.
Is that normal?
Oh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
He was already a bit screwy,
but then he found religion.
She was a hard-line atheist,
no peach herself.
When he got himself obsessed
with this Buddy Boyle whack job,
an already bad marriage
got worse.
Kept telling her
to "Let God in."
Buddy Boyle.
That explains it.
Explains what?
Never mind.
Let's see.
Is that his truck?
Yep.
Cass.
Nora, she's hot.
She's really hot.
Please just call -- call me.
Call -- call back.
If I don't hear back,
I'm taking her to the hospital.
Okay, Tanya,
we're taking a little walk.
Hello, Castiel.
Squalid little dump.
No wonder she cries.
It's a fever, Ephraim.
It will pass.
You remember my name?
I was just a nobody
when we met,
but you --
you were a legend.
You've been here before.
This is my first time,
and it's...
Intense.
You know, there's a lot
you don't understand
about humanity
at first.
If you would just stop --
Stop?
I won't stop
until I wash the planet clean
of all suffering.
Allow me.
Don't...touch...her.
You think I came for her?
No, Castiel.
I came for you.
How long's it take to transfer
a demonic phone call?
Can it, moose.
Crowley, you got your call.
Yeah, it's time.
It's time when I bloody well
say it's time!
Hello, Abaddon.
Crowley,
how in the hell are you?
So much pain and despair,
so many voices
begging out for relief.
How'd you find me?
Because you're warded?
The same way
I find all my patients --
I just followed
the sound of your pain.
You have no idea
how loud it is.
I could hear you
for miles.
Do you really think you're doing
Heaven's work down here?
I know I am.
You're wrong.
Earth can be a hard place.
But these humans,
they can get better.
They're just doing
the best they can.
Is that what you think
you're doing, Castiel --
the best you can?
Well, I'm sorry.
But if this is the best
that the famed Castiel can do,
you're a more urgent case
than I thought.
I used to admire you.
You failed more often
than you succeeded.
But at least
you played big.
Now what are you doing?
Burying your head
in the sand.
Right when your kind
needs you the most.
How are the numbers?
You mean souls?
I've managed to double
on your projections.
Now, how did I ever
pull off such a feat?
You're taking souls
before their time.
Voiding my contracts.
That's right.
I'm taking it all down,
brick by brick.
It's over.
The days of Crowley, the king
of bureaucrats, are done.
Shhh.
It'll be over soon.
I'll take the pain away.
I want to live.
But as what, Castiel?
As an angel or a man?
You...
Ganky...
Putrescent...
Skanger.
It may look like
bean-counting to you,
it may lack a certain
adolescent flair,
but my way...
Works!
You think you can control Hell
with chaos alone,
without the support of those
who are still loyal to me?!
No one's seen you in weeks,
and last I saw you,
Howdy and Doody had you tied up
nice and tight.
Seems to reason, they've
turned you into a kennel dog.
How does it feel, Crowley,
to be the Winchesters' bitch?
It's been fun
indulging in your bluffs,
but we both know
you have no real authority left,
no leverage,
you have nothing to offer me.
You have nothing.
Your way will backfire.
You will burn.
I can't wait.
Crowley?
Bring me the translations.
I keep my agreements.
"Obtain the ingredients --
heart, bow, Grace."
Blah, blah, blah.
"Mix until the smoke
shall rise from the ashes
casting the angels
from heaven."
Blah, blah -- oh.
Hm.
It's irreversible.
What?
The spell can't be undone.
The new world order --
we're stuck with it.
You say you want to live.
But you can't see
what I see.
By choosing a human life,
you've already given up.
You chose death.
Well, there's no way.
Crowley's lying.
No, Dean,
not this time.
Look, Metatron
built the spell
to withstand any attempt
to reverse it.
There is no putting the angels
back in Heaven.
It's done.
Are you gonna tell Cass?
I'm, uh,
sorry I overreacted.
My friend gave me a tip.
A low dose of acetaminophen
brought the fever right down.
Oh, that's okay.
Date was a bust anyway.
Steve?
The part of you
that overreacted,
that cares so much?
That's what
makes you special.
I got to go.
Where to, Cass?
Listen, Cass,
back at the bunker,
I, uh...
Sorry I told you to go.
I know it's been hard on you,
you know, on your own.
Somehow you're adapting.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you, Dean.
But there's something
Ephraim said.
The angels --
they need help.
Can I really
sit this out?
Shouldn't I be searching
for a way to get them home?
Me and Sam, we'll take care
of the angels.
You're human now.
It's not
your problem anymore.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
It's been weeks
since the massive meteor storm,
yet Idaho falls astronomers
still have
unanswered questions.
NASA and Washington
are both continuing to study
the phenomenon.