Take your brother outside
as fast as you can!
Now, Dean! Go!
What else do you remember?
Nothing.
I was a kid, all right?
And most important --
Watch out for Sammy.
Watching out for you --
it's kinda who I am.
I got this brother, right?
And he's always telling me how
he's gonna watch out for me.
Now eat your dinner.
Don't forget your vegetables.
Don't you dare think
that there is anything
that I would put
in front of you!
Sammy's hurt.
He's hurt real bad.
I heal Sam
while healing myself.
Every time I use my power,
it weakens me.
You went through the trials.
I just think it's better
if you took it easy,
you know,
and didn't act like you were --
Possessed by an angel.
Aah!
Wait up!
Hurry!
He's right behind us.
Come on, come on!
Hurry!
Go, go, go -- it's open!
Come on, guys.
The barn is a no-fly zone
during hide-and-go-seek.
Boys?
Come on, you delinquents.
Time for bed!
All right!
Game is over, boys!
Let's bring it in!
Lights out was 10 minutes ago!
You little bastards.
Okay, I'm gonna...
You got till the count of 10,
and you'd better come out
or the belt's coming off!
1...
Come on!
Boys?
This isn't funny.
? Supernatural 9x07 ?
Bad Boys
Original Air Date on November 19, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Dean?
Kevin?
Hello?
I'm sorry, there's no, uh --
there's no Dee-dawg, uh...
I got it.
Sonny, hey.
So, what's up?
Okay.
All right. Yeah, just sit tight.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Yeah.
So, what was that all about,
Dee-dawg?
You remember
when we were kids
that spring
in upstate New York?
Dad was on a rugaru hunt.
We, uh --
we crashed at the, uh...
the bungalow colony
with the ping-pong table.
Yeah. Uh, y-you disappeared.
Dad came back. You were gone.
He shipped me off to Bobby's
for a couple months
and went and found you.
You were lost on a hunt
or something.
That's what we told you.
Right.
I'm sorry.
That's what you told me?
Truth is, um...
I lost the food money that
dad left for us in a card game.
I knew you'd get hungry,
so I tried taking
the five-finger discount
at the local market
and got busted.
I wasn't on a hunt.
They sent me to a boys' home.
A boys' home,
like a reform school?
Yeah, more or less.
It was a farm, and the guy
who ran it -- Sonny --
he, uh --
you know, he looked after me.
Wait. Does Sonny know
what we do?
Yeah. He's good people.
I gave him the number
to the bat phone,
and sounds like he's got
something in our wheelhouse.
So...
Hey, you gonna be cool to do
this, or are you too tired?
Uh, no. Yeah, I'm just, uh...
I'll be fine.
And everybody's okay with
heading out to the Catskills?
I am everybody.
Yeah.
Right. All right.
Grab your stuff,
and we'll head out.
Hey, Dean...
I mean, why didn't you
just tell me you went
to a boys' home?
I don't know.
Uh, it was dad's idea.
And then it just -- you know,
the story became the story.
I was 16.
You were here for two months
and dad couldn't find you?
Oh, no. He found me.
He found me quick.
But he left me here
'cause I lost our money.
You were 16.
You made a mistake.
Yeah.
I made the mistake.
Look, I know how you think.
None of this was dad's fault.
Hi.
What can I do
for you boys?
I'm Dean.
This is my brother, Sam.
We're old buddies
of Sonny's.
Prison buddies?
No. Uh, you mind telling him
that we're here?
I'll go get him.
I just mopped this floor, so you
take off those roach stompers.
Sonny's an ex-con, huh?
What,
and we're such angels?
Trust me,
he's more than made up for it.
Steven Hewlett
caught him red-handed
- stealing up at his store.
- So, what did he take?
Get this --
peanut butter and bread.
Okay.
And how about family?
Well, his old man called.
Once he found out what happened,
he said let him rot in jail.
Judge is off
on a fishing trip.
The boy's too young
to leave in county.
So we thought it best
he stay here till arraignment.
I don't see why not, man.
Appreciate it, Sonny.
Where'd you get the shiner?
You think that's funny?
I think you're slow.
You sucker punched me!
You wish!
Come on, now!
Billy, I got this, buddy.
It's all right.
You shouldn't do that,
kid.
Yeah? Why?
Because he's a cop?
Because when you make him mad,
he leaves with the key.
Eh, don't sweat it.
Deputy do that?
What, your old man?
Well, then,
how'd you get it?
Werewolf.
Okay.
So, how do you know
I won't just run away?
Because you're hungry.
No, I'm not.
Well, then, why'd you steal
bread and peanut butter?
So, what is this place,
anyway?
It's for boys like you.
You work the land.
Teaches you some discipline
and responsibility.
Keeps you out of trouble.
That's lame.
Beats jail.
Come on.
I'll fix you something to eat.
Dee-dawg!
Sonny, good to see you.
Hey, you, too, brother.
Oh, and this must be Sam.
Good to meet you.
Back at you, brother.
So, farm looks,
uh, nice.
Oh, please, man.
It's barely standing.
Only got a handful of kids
working around here now.
Why's that?
Because these days,
the system
would rather incarcerate a boy
than redeem him.
Hey, Sonny, uh, y-you mind
if we talk alone?
Hey, Ruth, would you,
uh, please go check on the boys,
make sure their morning chores
are getting done?
All right.
So, what's happening?
Well, you remember Jack,
don't you?
Yeah. The, uh,
tough, old leatherneck.
Mm-hmm.
Well, somehow, that ancient,
rusty, broken-down tractor
just roared to life and
ran him over the other night.
Maybe -- maybe it just,
uh, slipped out of park
or something.
Couldn't have.
You know, I never --
I never believed
any of this mumbo-jumbo stuff
you boys are into,
but...
something ain't right.
What do you mean?
Well, just things
started happening --
you know,
lights flickering on and off,
strange scratching sounds
coming from inside the walls,
windows and doors slamming.
All right.
You think you can round up
the boys while we take a look around?
Well, that shouldn't be a problem.
Most are home on break --
well, except those
with no home worth going to.
Mm.
All right.
Why don't you take the house?
I'll check out the barn.
Yeah.
Hey. I am so sorry.
I-I-I thought I...
saw something in, uh --
Like a ghost?
Sonny told me
you were old friends,
but I know why
you're really here.
That's why
I was praying for us.
Praying for what?
For the ghost that haunts
this farm to leave.
All right, Casper...
Where are you at?
Hello?
Anybody here?
Hey, kid, what are you doing
in here by yourself?
Fighting monsters.
What kind of monsters?
All sorts
with Bruce the monster smasher.
Hmm.
Is that a cape?
Little impractical
for smashing monsters, huh?
You know,
you could choke.
I clobber evil!
I bet you do.
I'm Dean.
Timmy.
Let's try that again.
If you're gonna be a man,
you got to learn how to shake
like one, okay?
So give me
your best Kung Fu grip.
Good. Now look me
straight in the eye.
Let me know
that you mean business.
Shake as hard as you can.
That's it.
You shake like that,
you'll be all right.
Hey, Timmy, did you know
Jack who worked here?
Mm-hmm.
What can you tell me
about him?
He yelled a lot.
He was yelling
when he had his accident.
How do you know that?
'Cause me and the other boys
were playing here
when it happened.
Did you see anything?
Is there anything else
about that night
that you can remember,
anything at all?
It suddenly got
really cold.
Can I go?
I have to finish my chores
before Ms. Ruth gets mad.
That Ruth --
she runs a tight ship, huh?
Yeah, you better roll.
I grew up in this town.
I used to come up here
as a little girl.
The Wasserlaufs,
Howard and Doreen --
they used to own this farm
back then.
My co-worker, Jack,
may he rest in peace,
he worked here
as a farmhand.
Howard was a nice man,
but...
Well, he'd get
into that corn liquor.
And one night he got it
into his thick skull
that Jack and his wife, Doreen,
were rolling around in the hay.
It wasn't true, but --
but Howard's paranoia
got the better of him.
He tried to kill them both.
Jack got away,
but Doreen...
He killed her?
With a meat cleaver.
Got life in jail...
which for Howard
ended a year ago.
He always swore he'd get
his revenge on poor, old Jack,
and...looks like
he finally got it.
Is Howard
buried here in town?
So
Dad didn't want you
to tell me.
How come?
Was this place
really so bad?
I don't really remember.
I mean,
look, nobody bad touched me.
Nobody burned me
with their smokes
or beat me
with a metal hanger.
I call that a win.
Hey.
All right. Let's
barbecue old MacDonald here,
get the hell out
of Dodge.
Help! Help!
Ruth, you okay?
What's wrong?
Open up!
Ruth!
? Ave Maria
That's okay.
Dean, you know I'm fine just grabbing
a burger to go somewhere, right?
What, and miss out on the best
banana pancakes you ever had?
Thanks.
No problem.
I do this for all the boys after they've
been here for a month.
I meant for getting
the charges against me dropped.
Well, being hungry's
not a crime.
It's the stealing
that is.
But I feel
if you only do that once,
you don't deserve
a record.
And seeing as how we can't find
your pops anywhere,
you can stay here
as long as you want, Dean.
You're doing good in school.
You're making friends.
You made
the wrestling team.
I'm proud of you.
Let me ask you something,
and I want you to be straight
with me.
Are you into
the whole heavy-metal,
devil-worshiping stuff?
What?
No.
Hey, I'm not --
I'm not judging.
It's just I found
a few occult-looking symbols
carved into your bedpost.
It's...
It's a very long story.
That story have anything to do
with why you put the salt
in front of your bunk door
every night before bed?
Well, it's a family thing,
so I can't really talk about it.
Same family
that left you here?
What are you --
what are you,
in the mob or something?
More like something.
I was part of this gang,
right?
They were my family.
I lived, breathed,
I would have even died for them.
You know
where it got me?
15 years
in a correctional facility.
And for what?
Being loyal?
To who?
I should have been loyal
to myself.
Because you get one shot
at this game, Dean,
and when you look
in the mirror,
you want the guy looking back
at you to be his own man.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Robin.
How are you?
I'm good. How are you?
Good.
Meet my new
ranch foreman here, Dean.
Hi. Welcome to Cus's.
What can I get you two?
Bet you never thought
you'd see me here, huh?
Uh, look, I'm a little bit
slammed right now.
Do you guys want to hear
the specials?
Robin...
Dean Winchester.
Um...
I used to live up at Sonny's.
Oh, oh.
Uh, look, sorry.
There's just --
there's so many boys
that pass through there,
it's -- it's hard to remember
every -- every name and face.
Yeah. Uh, no.
Sorry, I just --
I remember you coming up there
with your mom.
She'd give guitar lessons.
It's, uh --
it was a long time ago.
Yeah. Mom --
she loved helping out the boys.
I guess that's why I kept giving
lessons after she passed.
Hey, Robin?
Um, would you excuse me?
I'll be right back.
Dude...
Let's go.
W--
what was that?
Nothing.
Nothing? Well, obviously
it was something.
Who was that waitress?
Said it was nothing, all right?
Drop it.
Sonny.
What?!
I tried to get in to save her,
but the damn door wouldn't open.
Locked?
There's no locks
on the farm.
That means our little field trip
to the cemetery was a bust.
Sonny, is there anything else
weird you can remember?
What, 'cause we're not chest-deep
in weird already, boys?
I know, I know.
I mean anything --
really.
There was one thing.
Ruth always had
her rosary beads with her,
but now I can't find them
anywhere.
All right. Um, let's start
with the vics, okay?
I mean,
both lived in the house.
They both, uh, worked closely
with the boys.
All right, why don't I go have a
chat with the rug rats, see what's up?
Yeah.
Sonny, you got any
employee records on the victims?
In my office.
Let's do it.
Come on, whatcha gonna do
about it? You gonna cry?
Timmy,
you're such a little weirdo.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Come here. Huh?
Nothing.
Timmy, what's going on?
All right, you two.
Where were you this morning
when Ruth had her accident?
Unless you're a cop, we don't
need to tell you anything.
Oh, okay.
Well...how about that?
We weren't even here
this morning.
Sonny sent us into town to get
some chicken feed -- we swear.
What about Ruth?
What can you tell me about her?
Uh, we used to call her
the warden.
She was a real
Bible-thumping hard-ass.
Obviously. What else?
Anything different or weird
you can think of?
You mean besides Timmy?
Hey.
Either of you touch him
ever again,
I'm gonna go all Guant?namo
on you.
Understand me?
Get the hell out of here.
Go on! Get.
Hey.
You and Bruce okay?
Yeah.
Listen to me.
Guys like that --
they're cowards, okay?
All you got to do is stand up
to them one time
and they'll stop,
I promise.
Okay.
Sonny, wait.
Um...
W-what is all this?
It's our hall of fame.
We had some pretty great
athletes come through here,
including your brother.
He was Sullivan county
135-pound wrestling champion.
Hey, guys!
She could give me a lesson
anytime.
Gross.
She's like ancient.
What the hell?
What's this doing
in here?
Kid's gonna need about 8,000
stitches, but he'll be fine.
That kid was bullying Timmy
before the accident, right?
Yeah. Why?
Check this out.
Timmy was found
in an abandoned building
about a year ago
all by himself.
No one was sure how long
he had been there.
And what
about his parents?
Well, they posted a picture
on the Internet,
but no one ever showed up.
Well, then,
what's he doing here?
Shouldn't he be
in an orphanage?
He kept running away
from Child Services.
So about three months ago,
Sonny offered to take him in.
All right,
so hard-ass counselors,
bullies all bite the dust,
but Timmy's still standing.
So, what are we talking?
We got ourselves a Damien
on our hands?
No.
EMF rules out a demon.
So...
probably ghost possession.
Meaning what, we find Timmy
and shove a fistful of salt
down his throat,
forced ejection?
You're taking the barn
this time.
So, you've been
a lot of places?
Yeah. My, uh...
My dad likes
to move around a lot.
What's your dad do?
Boring stuff.
Do you like it?
No, not really.
But my dad expects me
to follow in his footsteps.
So I've kind of
gotten used to it.
Yeah. I-I get it.
My pops wants me to
take over the diner,
but that's
not happening.
So, what do you
really want to do?
I want to be a photographer
and see the world,
go to strange lands,
eat crazy food.
I want to be a rock star,
but...
I also really like cars.
Being a mechanic
seems rough.
What?
No, no. Not at all.
Cars are
freaking cool as hell.
Fixing them
is like a puzzle,
and the best part is
when you're done, they leave,
and you're not responsible
for them anymore.
Have you kissed
many girls?
What?
Yeah. Of course.
Lots.
Really?
Well, I guess we'll
just have to keep practicing.
Oh. Hey.
Uh, what happened to you
at the diner?
I turned around to take your
order, and you were just gone.
Long story.
Um, have you seen Timmy?
No, not yet, but he should be here
any minute for his guitar lesson.
Yeah, we're gonna cancel that.
What?
We got to get out of here, okay?
I don't have time to explain.
You just got to trust me.
T-trust you?
And why
would I do that again?
You do remember me.
How could I forget?
? I do recall
? those were the best times,
most of all ?
? In the heat
with a blue-Jean girl ?
What's wrong?
? Burnin' love comes
once in a lifetime ?
I just hope this lasts.
I'm not going anywhere,
Robin.
Yeah, says you.
Well, I can't.
? Those summer nights
are callin' ?
Who else would take you
to the school dance?
? Stone in love
Is this your way of asking me
to be your date,
Dean Winchester?
Yeah.
How am I doing so far?
? Stone in love
There were -- there were reasons
why I had to leave.
I don't have time to explain
them to you right now.
I got to get you out
of here.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry.
Sorry about what,
Timmy?
I can't stop it.
Go, go, go!
Sam, go!
Locked.
Damn it!
Circle.
Dean, what --
what just happened in there?
Okay, listen to me.
Whatever happens,
you stay inside this circle.
Understood?
All right. Dean...
I can't control her.
Can't control who?
Your mom, right?
Timmy, listen.
We need you to tell us
about the fire, okay?
It was late,
and we were driving home
when we crashed in the woods.
Everything was on fire.
But she saved me,
pushed me out...
Before the car blew up...
With her in it.
But that's not all,
was it?
I ran through the woods.
I found an empty building,
where I hid.
I was scared.
It was dark and cold.
So I cried.
I cried for my mom.
And then she came.
But she had changed,
right?
I'll bet she gave you
that cool action figure, huh?
Yeah. When I turned 9.
Timmy...
...I'm gonna need
that action figure.
No!
I clobber evil!
I clobber  evil!
I...clobber...evil!
It looks like it wasn't the action figure
that was anchoring her here, Dean.
Well, then, what is?!
Him.
You know what?
I think maybe
his mom can't let go
and she's still protecting him
from the grave.
Protecting him from what?
What, from us?
Maybe she doesn't know what
threats are real and what's not,
so she just attacks
all of them.
Great. So, what, unless we waste
the kid, we're sitting ducks?
This is -- this is crazy.
Robin. Robin!
Damn it.
Robin, wait!
Who are you?
Right now I'm the only thing
that's keeping you safe.
Timmy, we're gonna need
your help, okay?
Listen to me.
I need you to focus, okay?
Look, we are not here
to hurt you.
Sammy!
I can't stop her.
Timmy, you have to try!
She came to you
when you cried out for her.
Now you have to tell her
to stop and go away!
She's my mom.
She's a ghost.
Timmy, because she can't
move on, she's going crazy.
Okay? You got to let her go.
You'll be okay.
Listen to me.
Sometimes you got to do
what's best for you,
even if it's gonna hurt
the ones you love.
Mommy...
Stop it.
Timmy, Kung Fu grip!
Mommy, stop it!
Stop hurting people!
You have to go.
Never come back.
I'll be okay.
I promise.
I love you, too.
So, then,
this is the family business?
Told you it was boring.
Yeah, right.
Well, as you can see,
I did not run off
to become a rock star.
Mm...
I don't know about that.
You look pretty rockin' to me,
Dean Winchester.
And what about you?
I mean, I always thought
that I would hate
being in the same little town
my whole life,
and, you know, taking over
the diner
like dad always wanted,
but...I don't.
I just -- I love it.
I guess we didn't know
everything we thought we did
at 16, huh?
Not everything.
Just some things.
Sounds like Timmy's
gonna need some help adjusting.
Yeah,
but he's got you.
I always hate to see you go,
Dee-dawg.
Can't thank you enough
for this one, man.
Sonny,
we'll see you around.
You can bet on that,
boys.
Take it easy, man.
Hey, h-how did you know
Timmy asking his mom to leave
was gonna work?
I didn't. Total hail Mary.
Got lucky.
You just got lucky?
Kind of like you did
with this place.
I mean,
here I was thinking
this was the worst part
of your life,
and it turns out
it was the best.
Why'd you ever leave?
Never felt right.
Really?
It was two months, Sam,
okay,
and I couldn't wait
to get out of here.
I don't know what to tell you.
It wasn't me.
Oh, look at you.
You clean up good!
Thank you.
You know, uh...
I've never actually been
to one of these school dances
before.
Yeah.
Look, about that, Dean,
your old man's outside,
and, man,
he's really something.
I tried to tell him what a big
night it was for you, Dean,
and ask him if he
could come back later,
but he just said to tell you
he had a job,
said you'd know
what that means.
You know,
after I got out of jail,
this place gave me
a second chance,
and it's done the same
for you, too.
So if you want,
I'll stick my neck out for you,
and I'll fight
for you to stay.
Sonny...
...thank you --
for everything.
But I have to go.
Dean...
Thank you.
For what?
For always being there,
for having my back.
Look, I know
it always hasn't been easy.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man