You lied to me.
Again.
You decide to trick me
into being possessed
by some...psycho angel?
And now...
Kevin's blood
is on my hands.
But I'll find Gadreel.
And I will end
that son of a bitch.
But I'll do it alone.
What's that supposed to mean?
Sam, people get close to me,
they get killed...or worse.
Just go.
I'm not gonna stop you.
It's the bloody mark of Cain.
The mark and the blade
work together.
I can give you the mark, Dean,
if it's what you truly want.
The mark can be transferred.
I called a friend of ours --
Garth.
He does what we do...
In his own way.
Stop being a idjit!
Now, you know
what's coming next, right?
Man, this is good.
Oh, Marmaduke, you're crazy!
Where's Garth?
On a case or --
or the dentist.
I don't know.
I haven't heard from him.
Garth still M.I.A.?
Hey!
? Supernatural 9x12 ?
Sharp Teeth
Original Air Date on January 28, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Afternoon.
I'm looking for a John Doe
that was admitted here
a few days ago.
He's a, uh...
skinny...Ichabod Crane-looking
kind of guy.
I know just who you mean.
Room 113, agent.
All right, thanks.
Sure is a popular fella.
Saw Garth's John Doe
on the police wire.
You?
Yeah.
Where you comin' from?
New Mexico.
Well, that's a haul.
Especially considering
that I got this, uh...
pretty much covered,
so if you want to...
You spoken to him yet?
No.
Assload of painkillers.
He's been out
since I got here.
What's
he being charged with?
Killing a cow.
Why?
I was about to see
if I could find out.
Lock the door.
Whoa. Hey.
What is that? Adrenaline?
Yes, sir.
You trying to jump-start him
or kill him?
I want some answers.
He walked out on Kevin.
He walked out on us.
So if you got
a better idea...
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Dean?
Sam?
What is this?
A hospital?
Wait.
Am I in Heaven?
All right, take it easy, Garth.
You're in Wisconsin.
You were hit by a car.
Do you remember anything?
I, uh...
Vaguely.
What's with the hardware?
You tell us.
And while you're at it, why
don't you give us the lowdown
on why you went AWOL
for the past six months?
Only way we tracked you down
is that you offed a cow.
Offed a...what?
I -- I --
I was on a hunt.
Hunt for what?
I --
oh, no.
Oh, get back.
Ohh. Oh, God.
Good thing I didn't give him
the adrenaline.
Anything on Gadreel?
Actually, uh, yeah.
Turns out he, uh,
he left some Grace in me
before he bolted.
You know how wrong
that sounds, right?
Wouldn't worry about it.
Cass took care of it.
Hmm.
What?
Nothing.
I'm gone for two weeks,
and you're like an episode
of "Teen Mom."
Just breathe, Garth.
Work it out.
What happened
to your arm?
Oh.
It's a...
Gift from Cain.
Like...the wrestler?
I wish.
That would be awesome.
Uh, no. The, uh...
The old testament dude.
He got all biblical on me
and gave me his mark.
What does it even mean?
How -- how did that happen?
Crowley and I found him,
and he gave me this
so that I could eighty-six
Abaddon once and for all.
You worked a job
with Crowley?
The devil you know...
Garth?
What?
Son of a bitch.
Why would Garth run
from us?
Why haven't we heard from him
for the last six months?
Did you test him?
He was unconscious.
No, I --
he steal a car?
Did he...
steal a car naked?
I'll see what I can find
on those cameras.
Why don't you go talk
to farmer Brown,
see about that cow?
Yeah.
Last week,
it was a couple of chickens.
Goat the week before that.
So when I saw that boy
tearing out of my barn,
hell yeah,
I was gonna ask questions later.
Now, the animals -- were they
all killed in the same manner?
More like sacrificed.
What do you mean by that?
Their organs
was ripped clean out.
Only the organs.
If this wasn't some kind
of devil-worship thing,
I don't know what.
Mm.
Well, thanks.
Yeah.
So,
the cow wasn't just killed.
It was eviscerated.
Well,
why was Garth there?
He said he was on a hunt,
right?
Maybe he was hunting
whatever killed it.
Why would he run?
This whole thing's starting
to stink. You know that, right?
Yeah.
What about you?
Any luck?
Uh, nada.
Cameras were pointing
in the wrong direction.
You're kidding.
Wish I was.
Hmm. So --
so Garth's a hunter. If he wants
to stay gone, he's gone.
We got nothing?
Well, what can I say, Sammy?
We lost this one.
Send me a postcard.
Wow.
Make, model, license plate.
Really, Dean?
I told you
we can't hunt together.
It's for your own good.
I hear you.
And after we find Garth and get
to the bottom of this, I'm gone.
But until then,
no more games.
Ride belongs
to a girl named Bess Meyers.
She lives
in the next town over.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
Hey, guys.
I can explain.
Everything's cool.
Just a simple misunderstanding.
Who you talking to?
What?
The girl?
What -- what girl?
What the --
what, now?
All right, all right.
Guys, everyone
needs to take a chill pill
and put their guns down.
You see?
Let's all be grown-ups here
and have an adult conversation.
No!
Sam!
Sam, please --
don't hurt her.
What are you doing?!
She's a werewolf!
So am I.
It's okay, baby.
Hold it like that.
What are they doing here,
Garth?
They're friends.
I promise.
They're hunters.
All right. We've all gotten off
on the wrong foot here.
So let's do things right.
Boys...this is Bess...
My beloved.
And, Bess, that's Dean.
Now, he could start a fight
in an empty house,
but deep down inside,
he's just
a big ol' Teddy bear.
And Sam here -- Sam can be
a bit insecure at times,
but for good reason.
Bless his heart.
That's sweet.
Werewolf?
All right, guys, look --
about six months ago,
I was outside Portland, Maine,
hunting this big bad wolf.
I took him down, but...
He bit me in the process.
And you didn't call
one of us?
And tell you what?
That I messed up?
No, I-I knew the deal.
There's no cure,
so I accepted my fate.
Ate my favorite dish
of egg fu Yung,
watched the world's
greatest movie, "Rocky III""
and then...
was ready to eat a bullet,
when Bess here found me.
And how'd she do that?
Smelled him.
How else?
Yeah.
She talked the gun
out of my mouth,
and, as they say,
the rest is history.
We've been married
for four months now.
You're married?
To a werewolf.
Yes.
And my pack has taken him in
as one of our own.
Guys,
it's not what you think.
We don't hurt people.
No, you just go all Wolverine
on cattle.
Yeah.
At least
he's not eating human hearts.
Do you have any idea
how hard it is for a bitten
to control his instincts,
like Garth does?
How well he's doing?
Thank you, baby.
Well, it's the truth,
honey bunny.
Wait. A -- a "bitten"?
You're all bitten.
Not at all.
You're either born to it,
like I was,
or you're bitten,
like Garth.
Hold on.
You said you were --
you were born a werewolf?
Second generation.
Garth, can we talk to you
for a sec? Alone?
Honey, why don't you go find
some ointment for that arm?
Okay?
What the hell?
Look, I know
you guys want to shoot first
and ask questions later,
but I checked everything out.
This pack is clean.
Everything's Kosher.
Right. Uh, minus the part
where your wife attacked me.
Yeah, because you two came busting
in here like a house on fire.
Guns waving,
the jawlines and the hair --
it's very intimidating.
What'd you expect?
Dean, no one wants
any trouble.
You got my word on that.
Oh, no.
That ship has sailed.
We're gonna need a hell of a lot
more than your word.
Okay. Okay.
Tell you what.
You want proof?
Come pray with us.
You there?
Yeah, just pulled up.
Nothing too sketchy yet.
That's a good thing,
right?
Not betting on it.
Or are we
just that jaded?
I mean,
maybe Garth's right.
Well, ain't you
a glass half full.
Any luck with the cops?
Uh, sheriff should be rolling up
any second.
Be careful.
Yeah.
? Bringing in the sheaves
We need to come
in strong on the second verse.
Let's try it again.
Garth, play it from here.
And...
? bringing in the sheaves
You must be Dean.
I'm Joy,
Garth's mother-in-law.
Uh, stepmother-in-law,
which I always thought
sounded so silly.
Please, come in.
We're just finishing up.
Why don't you just tell Garth
I'm here?
Dean, you have my word --
you're safe under my roof.
I only ask the same
in return.
After all...
I'm not the one
carrying silver.
? Bringing in the sheaves
? bringing in the sheaves
? we shall come rejoicing
Uh...Thank you,
brother Garth.
Wonderful accompaniment,
as usual.
And I'll see the rest of you
in the pews -- 9:00 a.m., sharp.
No stragglers...Sister Amelia.
Oh. Hi.
So, what'd I tell you?
It's all good, right?
Everyone here's a wolf?
Yeah.
Yeah, not all good.
Oh, come on, Dean.
You just got to meet them.
That's Russ and Joba,
Bess' first cousins
on sister Joy's side.
That's reverend Jim,
Bess' dad --
leader of the pack
and a good man.
"Dean," isn't it?
Welcome.
Jim Meyers.
Folks usually call me...
Reverend Jim.
Yeah, I got it.
Oh.
Uh, my bad.
Dean's got
this crazy fear of germs.
I understand
your apprehension, Dean.
Hunters and our kind don't have
the best history together.
But I think you'll find we're
not much different from you.
Oh, sister,
I highly doubt it.
Why don't we break bread
and see?
Why would I do that?
Dean.
What?
Now, everybody eat up.
But make sure
you leave room for pie.
Sister Joy's pies are famous
throughout the badger state.
Mm. Dean loves pie.
Mmm.
Don't you guys say some sort
of a Grace or something?
We're more spiritual
than we are religious.
We believe, much like
the American Indians did,
that nature and man
are one.
Yeah, really worked out well
for them.
So, why are
a bunch of werewolves
wearing silver bullets
around their necks?
Sorry, Dean, but we don't use
the "W" word around here.
We prefer the term
"lycanthrope."
"We"?
He's entitled
to his opinion, Garth.
Many of our kind see themselves
as indestructible.
This is
a constant reminder
of how precious
our lives truly are.
Yeah, but it's silver.
I mean, doesn't it burn?
Yeah, it does a bit,
but that's kind of the point.
It reminds us
of our fragility.
My daughter, Bess,
was born a lycanthrope.
It was one of the proudest days
of my life.
Which soon turned tragic...
When a hunter
killed my wife.
Believe me when I tell you,
I wanted to make someone pay.
Then I looked at Bess,
and I realized
the road to revenge
is a dark and lonely one,
which you never get off.
And that hole
in the pit of your stomach,
you never fill it -- ever.
Hey, no, I get it.
So I chose to look forward,
not backwards.
And the minute I did that,
the powers that be brought
this beautiful, compassionate,
amazing woman into my life.
And she helped me raise
a little baby girl
as if Bess were her own.
I can't take all the credit.
Daddy had a hand in it,
too.
He saw your potential.
Daddy?
My father --
bless his soul --
was the previous reverend
of our church,
the third generation
in our family to serve.
So, you're
fourth-generation werewolf?
Yes.
Look, the good reverend Jim
and his family
are all a little new-agey
and hippie-dippy like,
but they're clean as a whistle
and pillars of our community.
Why is the FBI
even interested in them?
I just go
where they send me, sheriff.
Truth be told,
I'm more interested in, uh...
Murders
and "X-files"-y stuff.
Anything of that variety
around here?
No, sir.
We're just a small town.
Not much crime of any
to speak of.
I'm sorry, agent.
I wish I could be more help.
Ah, that's all right.
But if you do think
of something, give me a call.
Will do.
Still hungry?
Yeah, I was just, uh...
seeing if you had any beer.
The sooner you realize
that all is good here,
the sooner you can go.
Don't you two have a chew toy
or something to go play with?
Hey, guys.
You mind if I grab a second
with Dean, here?
Why are you being so hard
on everyone?
Because there's no way
that all of this
is what it looks like.
No way.
Why not?
Come on, man.
I know you drank the kool-aid,
okay? But come on.
Look, amigo...
I know this is all looks nuts,
but I found it.
Love and a family?
Who cares
where that comes from?
I do.
I get it.
When I first got here,
I couldn't let go, either.
I kept waiting
for the other shoe to drop.
But when it didn't,
I had to accept the truth.
Well, I got another truth
for you --
we were all left in the dark
when you went AWOL.
I didn't know
whether you were dead or worse.
You should have reached out
and sent someone a message.
And said what, Dean?
That I was a werewolf?
I was embarrassed.
I thought it best for everyone
if I just stayed away.
But that doesn't mean
that I didn't think about
and miss you and Sam, Kevin.
Kevin's gone.
What?
Gone for good.
What happened?
When he needed me,
I wasn't there. That's what.
Okay, Dean,
they gave you lunch,
they gave you pie.
Why are we still here?
Uh, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, Garth's good.
You want to hit the road,
it's square by me.
Look, I'm just saying,
this wouldn't be the first time
we came across
a friendly monster.
Or a-a family
of friendly monsters --
w-whatever this is.
Agent Perry.
Sheriff.
How can I help you?
Really?
Okay.
Well,
you wanted weird, agent.
You tell me
what tore up that deer.
Nothing that runs
in these parts.
Fresh blood.
Yes, it is.
Still warm.
That means it died
after we got the call.
Couldn't just accept
that all was good
and move on, could you?
You have no idea
what you've walked into, do you?
No matter.
You won't be walking out.
Unh!
Hey.
Look at this.
I've seen that before.
Yeah, that is
a favorite accessory
of the good reverend
and his flock.
"Ragnarok"?
Yeah, that's, uh,
Thor, Loki, Odin stuff, right?
Yeah, it's Norse mythology's
end of days.
But why is it
etched onto a bullet?
Who cares?
We got all the answers we need.
I don't know, Dean.
I think we need more.
Oh, what? Sheriff Andy Taylor
here wasn't good enough for you?
Enough to kill Garth?
Come on, man.
Let's do this right.
All right, fine.
Clean this up,
grab Garth,
lock him up
until we figure out what's what.
I'm gonna go
check out that church.
Garth?
Seriously?
Hey. Did you find
the lovebirds?
No.
Place is a wreck.
No Garth, no Bess.
What, they were taken?
Well,
that's fan-friggin'-tastic.
Tell me you got something.
Well, this, uh...Ragnarok,
end-of-days crap --
star of the story
is a wolf named Fenris,
who kills the God Odin
before the world ends.
Okay.
And that helps us how?
There are cults that
consider Fenris a wolf deity
and worship him.
They call themselves
the maw of Fenris.
A cult of werewolves?
What do they want?
Well, Ragnarok is not just
a Bible story to these nutjobs.
It's an action plan --
human extinction,
total and complete
werewolf domination.
And...what?
This is the -- the ground-zero
for their movement?
Freakin' Wisconsin, man.
Well, time for reverend Jim
to go down.
Yeah.
Need any help?
No, no, no, I got it.
You just, uh, you find Garth.
All right.
Unh!
It's no use, Dean.
I can hear your heartbeat.
You must've done this
countless times,
yet you still get nervous.
Nothing wrong
with a little fear.
It's what makes us human.
Fear is not
a purely human instinct.
Even monsters know fear.
I came to work
on my sermon.
Well, why don't you start
by preaching to me
about the maw of Fenris?
Yeah, that's right.
I know all about you
and your pack's little plan.
I assure you,
we are planning nothing.
No? Well, then, why did I
read about it in your good book?
Because generations ago,
that hate and misplaced anger
was part of our beliefs.
But ever since
I took over here,
I have eradicated it
from our congregation.
Yeah, well, apparently, some of
them didn't get the word --
like the good sheriff, who just
tried to off me and my brother.
Sheriff Pat?
Let me see your bullet.
Where is it?
Where's what?
"Ragnarok."
What?!
It was etched into
the sheriff's bullet.
That's impossible.
The maw is dead.
Yeah, well, tell that
to Garth and your daughter,
who are missing.
No.
Bess.
Sam.
What are you two doing?
Russ?
Joba?!
Mom?
What is going on?
Hey!
First off,
I'm not your mother.
You leave her alone!
You hear me?!
You want to hurt somebody,
you hurt me!
Oh, that is so sweet.
But I am
going to hurt her.
And him.
But especially you,
for bringing
these hunters here.
I'm gonna hurt all of you.
I'm sorry.
Sam, pick up, damn it!
Unh!
Please --
don't do this.
Not to Bess.
She's your daughter --
Unh!
How many times
do I have to say this?
"Stepdaughter"!
I'm the last
of my bloodline,
thanks to you and your kind
out there.
He's awake.
Well, don't you just look
good enough to eat.
Why are you doing this?
I mean,
me, I can understand,
but these people
are your family.
Your pack.
Last winter,
my little brother, Charlie,
was killed by a hunter.
My husband counseled patience,
restraint.
Just as when he took over
our beloved church,
he preached
a new direction --
lycanthropes and man
would co-exist.
Peace was more important
than dominance.
I tried so hard
to make his way work...
to be a preacher's wife.
But then...
Charlie was murdered.
And I couldn't help
remembering my daddy's sermons.
And, by golly,
turns out he was right.
As long as there is a man,
there can be no peace.
Because man destroys.
And I, for one,
am sick of it.
Unh!
I get it now.
Why co-exist
when you can rule?
Bingo.
But my husband
doesn't see it that way.
See, he was bitten,
not born into it, like I was.
He still holds on
to his humanity.
Which is why
I am so pleased
it will be his claws
that start Ragnarok, not mine.
You and your brother
coming here
was a blessing
from Fenris above.
The two of you
cornered Garth here,
and then
when Bess came running in
to see
what the fuss was about...
You killed her.
No!
Here.
Silver to the heart.
You're gonna frame
their murders on me.
My husband
turned his cheek once.
I don't think
he can do it again.
Hey! Get away from her!
Killing you
gives me no joy,
but Ragnarok --
it's bigger than all of us.
You're sick.
You're just dying for me to get
my claws dirty, aren't you?
Wearing Russ' coat
to hide your scent -- smart.
Oh,
I'm full of surprises.
As am I.
Be good. Hear me?
I will.
Thanks, Sam.
How's he doing?
It's gonna be okay.
He's taking it
pretty hard.
Feels like he should have
seen the signs earlier.
Yeah, well,
maybe you were right.
Yeah, he seems like
a good man...considering.
Yeah.
And you were right.
Everything around here
wasn't copacetic.
I screwed up again.
First Kevin, now this.
Hey. Kevin?
That's on me.
I'm the one
that pulled him into all this.
I'm the one that should've
been there to protect him.
Well...
I guess there's enough of
that blame to go around, then.
Dean.
Yeah?
Um...
I know this may sound
a little crazy, but...
Maybe I could come back
and hunt with you.
I mean, with my werewolf mojo,
we'd have an advantage.
Yeah, look, Garth --
No, Dean.
I want to make this right.
I never should've left you guys,
especially Kevin.
Kevin was my friend.
Friends don't do that.
Well, hey, you said it --
you know, who cares
where happiness comes from?
Look, we're all a little weird,
we're all a little wacky --
some more than others --
but...if it works,
it works.
You got something here.
Okay? Even though
they are werewolves.
Lycanthropes -- whatever.
Don't let that go.
Okay?
You'll never
forgive yourself.
Besides, somebody's got to live
to tell this damn story someday,
and who better than you?
Now shut up
and come here.
Really?
Hurry up
before I change my mind.
I'll send you
that postcard.
Yeah.
Hey.
Uh, listen,
that night that, uh...
You know, we went our --
our separate ways --
you mean
the night you split?
Fair enough.
I was messed up, man.
Kevin was dead,
and I...
I don't know what I was.
Okay.
Hell,
maybe I still don't.
But, uh...
I know I took a piece of you
in the process,
and for that...
Somebody changed the playbook,
man, you know?
It's like what -- what --
what's right is wrong
and what's wrong
is more wrong, and...
I just know that when...
When we rode together...
We split the crappiness.
Yeah.
So...
Okay.
But something's broken here,
Dean.
I'm not saying
that it's not. I...
I just think maybe we need
to put a couple W's on the board
and we get past all this.
I don't think so.
No, I-I wish, but...
We don't...see things
the same way anymore --
our roles
in this whole thing.
Back in that church,
talking me out of
boarding up hell?
Or -- or tricking me into
letting Gadreel possess me?
I can't trust you --
not the way I thought I could,
not the way
I should be able to.
Okay, look.
Whatever happened...
We are family, okay?
You say that
like it's some sort of cure-all,
like it can change
the fact
that everything that has
ever gone wrong between us
has been
because we're family.
So, what --
we're not family now?
I'm saying,
you want to work?
Let's work.
If you want
to be brothers...
Those are my terms.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man