I'm trying to fix heaven.
Metatron is trying
to fix heaven.
Metatron isn't trying
to fix anything.
He's trying to break it.
Angels.
They're falling.
Metatron -- he took my Grace.
That means you're human.
Cass, listen to me.
There are angels out there.
They're looking for you,
and they're pissed.
Until their last breath,
they will seek revenge
on the angel that did this,
who destroyed heaven.
Stop.
That was beautiful,
Clarence.
We're dealing with a reaper.
I can find you anywhere!
Sammy's hurt.
He's hurt real bad.
This one goes out to any angel.
This is Dean Winchester,
and I need your help.
Start with a name.
Ezekiel.
There is a chance I can fix
your brother from the inside.
What, possession?
It's the best
of a bad situation.
How will it work?
I heal Sam
while healing myself.
Sam can eject me
at any time,
and if Sam does eject me,
he will die.
Then we keep it a secret
for now.
Monsignor Cassidy will join us
for dinner on Saturday.
And mass, of course.
He can be a pain,
so let's have everybody
on their toes.
Gentlemen.
We're looking for a man
we believe you may know.
His name is Castiel.
Hey, Clarence.
How much longer
you gonna be with us?
I'll be moving on tonight
after work.
It's time.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Do you ever tire
of urinating?
I'll never get used to it.
Yeah, I got some more bags
for you.
? Supernatural 9x03 ?
I'm No Angel
Original Air Date on October 22, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Sam!
You here?
Hey. Morning.
You been outside already?
Yeah.
Woke up, went for a run.
Beautiful sunrise.
Anyways, cleaned up.
Went and got breakfast.
Grabbed you real bacon and eggs,
extra grease.
Not even gonna argue.
Mm, perfect.
Wait.
You went running?
What?
Why do you look so worried?
Let's see.
There's Cass,
who I told
to haul ass here.
That was days ago.
He's still out there.
Um, there's you.
Me?
I feel great.
I'm sure you do, but, Sam,
you went through the trials.
Okay, that put
a big strain on you.
I just think it's better
if you took it easy,
you know,
and didn't act like you were --
possessed by an angel.
And he does feel better.
A work in progress, of course,
but I am slowly healing him.
That's great.
Um, but --
I have news.
I've picked up chatter
among the angels.
Not all are wandering around
in confusion.
Yeah, some of 'em
are after Cass.
There is a faction
that is rapidly organizing
and finding human vessels
to contain them.
Led by Naomi?
I have not heard
that name, no.
But it is this faction's
leadership
who want Castiel found.
You see, Dean,
I can be useful.
So can my brother.
So, why don't you go
check your e-mail,
and if I need your help,
I'll let you know.
Dean.
I said I'll let you know.
I mean, you know,
Cass is human now.
It's gonna take him
a lot longer to travel.
I'm gonna get whiplash.
What?
Nothing.
Um, all right,
so, I was thinking
that if the angels
are organizing,
then that makes them a lot more
dangerous than we thought.
Why do you think
they're organizing?
It makes sense.
My point is, is that the more
of them that are after Cass,
the worse it is,
so...We got to find him.
Folks,
like I've been telling you,
we're in that most sacred
of times.
A legion of angels
reaches out for us.
Can you feel
their divine presence?
And if you do,
there's nothing to fear.
Heck no.
If the angels
come a-knocking,
you just let 'em on in
and fill yourself up
with their Grace.
This is
the Reverend Buddy Boyle
in the "goin' for glory hour"
wishing you a most blessed day.
Amen.
And we're clear.
Beautiful, buddy.
One of your best.
Oh, well,
that is high praise, sir,
seeing as how you're an emissary
of the man upstairs himself.
Thank you, Bart.
It's Bartholomew,
and I have to say,
God has
personally assured me
that he is highly pleased
with your work.
He prepareth
a special reward
for helping him populate
a true heaven on earth.
Well, between you and me,
it's practically reward enough
being one of the few humans
of all time to get orders
from an actual angel.
But if he prepareth
I am honored.
Terrific.
Sir? I'm ready.
Oh?
Let me be a vessel
for the divine.
I give myself over to you.
Oh. Hallelujah.
Yes.
Well...
If you're certain.
Aah! Oh!
Bart!
What the hell?
Buddy...
The simple truth is,
not all who are willing
are designed
to contain heaven's Grace.
We have to expect a casualty
now and then.
It's a small price to pay
when you think about it.
Like the lamb
of the sacrifice.
Sure.
All right, so this is where
Cass called from on Tuesday --
Longmont, Colorado.
Each circle is how far
he might have gotten
in one, two,
and three days out.
Okay.
Here we go.
The same day he called
from Longmont,
weird murder, same town.
Cops said it was like the girl
was blasted from the inside out.
Angel kill.
They might have
just missed Cass.
Unless they got him.
You got an Emory Park, Iowa?
Emory Park, Emory Park.
I just saw that.
Yeah, a couple days outside
of Longmont.
Okay, because two priests
were murdered there Thursday.
Eyes blown out,
evidence of torture.
They were impaled on posts.
Torture?
Yeah.
Angels are looking
for info.
Man, if they get to him
before we do...
Yeah.
Thank you.
I was so hungry.
Very kind of you to share.
It's okay.
You know,
I'm finding that often
people with the least to give
are the most generous.
Anyway...
I've got to plan better.
I ran out of food
very quickly today.
You're new at this,
aren't you?
Food.
Sleep or passing gas,
it's all very strange.
And it's occurred to me
that one day I'm gonna die.
Well...
I better try
falling asleep.
It's quite a process,
isn't it?
Try counting sheep.
Thanks once again.
What sheep?
Aah! Ah.
You're human?
Yeah. Yeah, I think I know
this guy you're talking about.
Sounds like Clarence.
Clarence?
The church --
it runs a shelter in town,
and we work here.
We earn our keep.
Clarence spent a couple nights,
and then had to move on.
And he left the day the bodies
were found?
Matter of fact.
Oh, man, those poor guys
were a mess.
They must have suffered bad.
But at least now they're
with the angels.
I sure as hell hope not.
Clarence happen to mention
where he was headed?
No.
He just said he always
had to keep going.
All right.
Well, he's definitely been here.
Good news is
he's getting cagey.
He's using a fake name --
Clarence.
That's what Meg
used to call him.
Of course, he doesn't get
that's the name
of a pretty famous angel.
What?
"It's A Wonderful Life."
Dude, seriously?
What'd you come up with?
Another angel kill,
outside a town
called Lafayette
about a day's travel
east of here.
What is that, Indiana?
Yeah. Body was found
in a homeless camp.
Insides barbecued,
the whole nine.
Homeless guy?
No, a pharmacist
from Dayton.
Huh.
Reverend Boyle's influence
is astonishing.
I'll never understand
these people.
Our fallen
brothers and sisters
are finding vessels
faster than we'd even hoped.
They better.
And then they need to help us
find Castiel.
You know, the one you let slip
through your fingers.
Our Dayton operative
is tracking him.
Good, because frankly,
you're hanging by a thread.
What?
Our operative did manage
to find Castiel,
but Castiel was somehow
able to kill him.
What?
He's a madman, sir,
and very dangerous.
No.
I'm very dangerous.
Now you will find this madman,
and you will destroy him.
Do you understand?
That may not be possible,
sir.
I'm getting a little tired
of you.
Castiel has vanished.
We're unable to track him.
He must have found a way
to ward himself against us.
Please, Lord.
Mike is such a good man.
Please send your angels
to heal him.
Thank you for hearing me.
Amen.
Mike is your husband?
He's very sick.
Yes.
Humans -- so fragile.
I never -- never realized
how fragile until recently.
I guess that's why we pray.
When you get dealt
such a bad hand sometimes,
you need something stronger
than yourself.
That's a wonderful idea,
but...
What?
What if you
were to find out
that no one is listening?
That God
had pretty much left,
that Heaven
had gone out of business?
What would you do?
But that's not possible.
I think
it's completely possible.
You're missing the point.
It's not possible
because I have my faith.
But when I tell you
the truth --
Your truth, not mine.
Your lack of faith
doesn't cancel what I believe.
That's not how it works.
You know...
I think you might feel better
if you tried it my way.
Someone is listening.
The issue is,
he somehow managed to ward
himself against us.
Our ability to track him
has been jammed,
which brings us to you.
My kind, we always get what
we're looking for, chief.
Yes, reapers.
But some of you
have taken your skill set
to a whole new level...
That's the rumor.
...and are willing
to freelance.
For a price.
That's the rumor.
Jump start me.
How do I start looking
for this...Castiel?
I got one word for you.
Winchester.
Damnedest thing I ever saw.
Vic had a stab wound,
but it's not what killed him.
It's like his insides were --
Vaporized?
It's been going around.
So, this guy was a pharmacist
from Ohio?
Apparently.
Total family man, religious.
One day, just hops
in the S.U.V., takes off,
dies under a bridge here
from God knows what.
This is his stuff.
Help yourselves.
Thanks.
Anything?
Nothing weird.
Crappy music, a lot of podcasts,
all the same one.
Reverend Buddy Boyle's
"Goin' For Glory Hour."
Cop said he was religious.
Join me in a heapin' helpin'
of glory, friends.
When you're in the presence of
the divine, you'll know it.
And if you let yourself,
you'll hear it.
So, remember, when angels come
a-knocking, let 'em on in.
Angels can't possess a human
without permission, right?
Yep.
So, what, they're using this guy
to find vessels?
It's a willing audience.
They're all religious types
like our pharmacist here.
Buddy Boyle was telling them to
let the angels take them over.
Like body snatchers.
How big a reach
does this Boyle guy have?
Pretty much
the entire planet.
I'm not stealing.
And I'm not a cop.
It's a shame, isn't it?
So much is wasted
when there's so many hungry.
I never knew.
Peanut butter and jelly?
It's pretty good.
No, I can't take your food.
You're not.
I'm giving it to you.
Look, I've had
hard times myself.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Look,
for the billionth time,
we're just looking
for some information, okay?
We're not cops.
I mean,
do we look like cops?
Yes.
Well, we're not cops.
We just need to find a friend
who's in it deep.
Look, he might have been here
the night that guy was killed.
Were any of you here then?
Maybe.
Oh, okay.
Uh, he's --
he's got dark hair,
blue eyes,
a little out of it.
He maybe called himself
Clarence?
Clarence, yeah.
You two talk?
Not much.
And...?
I think he was on the run.
You see him with the vic?
Uh, victim?
No.
Okay.
He went off to sleep
in another part of the resort.
Where?
He's not there now.
Where'd he go?
I saw him running from under
the bridge to the highway.
You gonna pay us
for all this teeth pulling?
Where was he headed?
He flagged a truck
heading north.
Detroit, probably.
Why Detroit?
Truck was marked
"Motor City Meats."
Whoo!
Wow, it's beautiful.
If you say so.
Uh, just so you know,
I don't usually bring home
strange men.
Am I strange?
No, I mean...
Men I don't know.
But you look like you been
to hell and back.
Yeah, a few times.
April, by the way.
April Kelly.
Um, Castiel.
One name?
Yeah, like God.
Or Cher?
Uh, not to raise
any red flags,
but do you know your shirt's
soaked in blood?
Look at these chemicals.
Do you even read the label?
No. I read "pie."
The rest is just
"blah, blah, blah."
Listen,
when we hit Detroit,
we start with
the homeless shelters.
Right, then go to the
encampments, soup kitchens.
Check out places that he might
have gone looking for work.
Yeah, and I can -- I can check
for vagrancy arrests.
Yeah, and, you know...
Odd deaths.
Who are you?!
Why are you trailing us?
You call this rag
a bandage?
You're lucky
this wasn't infected.
What happened to the guy
who attacked you?
Oh, I stabbed him.
He exploded.
Funny.
You don't look like
the knife-fight type.
Or the homeless type,
actually.
Yes. Well...I guess
I trusted the wrong person.
Bad investment advice?
No, vanity.
I thought I was more important,
more effective than I am,
that I could...
Fix everything.
And now all I can do
is keep running.
Well, all patched up,
but, God,
your delts are in knots.
You got to relax.
Ah, it's all new to me.
Hunger.
Cold.
This feeling,
being all alone.
You're not alone tonight.
So, Maurice.
You bounty hunters are like
Delta Force reapers.
Why would they sic you
on Cass?
He warded himself.
Naomi hire you?
You really are
out of the loop.
Naomi's dead.
Resting in pieces.
So then who's running
things now?
Answer!
Her prot?g?, Bartholomew.
He's an up-and-comer.
So he figured
we'd lead you to Cass.
This Bartholomew,
he organizing the angels?
That's all I know.
You can kill me.
It won't matter.
If I don't find Castiel,
there are others that will.
But do what you want.
Sure.
Well, say something.
There aren't words.
So, that was okay?
Very much so.
Um...
What I did,
that was, uh...
...correct?
Very much so.
Good.
Castiel...
I can't help thinking
all that stuff you said earlier,
blame and guilt?
It seems like
you're taking on a heavy load
for such a sweet guy.
Believe me, I've done a lot
of foolish, unwise things.
I'm no angel.
Well,
whoever you trusted...
Can't they help undo this?
We're not in contact.
So what happens next
for you?
More of this, I hope.
Oh.
I washed your stuff.
Find everything okay?
As a matter of fact,
something is missing.
Oh?
It was with my jacket.
It's hard to describe.
Oh, you mean this?
What's up?
We been chasing our tails
all night.
No Cass.
"What's up?"
I'm fried.
I think it's time
for plan "B."
I'm not following.
I'm letting you know.
O-okay.
Um, letting me know what?
I'm letting you know.
What is it, Dean?
I need your help.
That is flattering.
We've been through this.
I cannot be making
public appearances.
Oh, I understand that.
I'm not asking you to walk
the red carpet, Zeke, okay?
I need your help
finding Cass.
It cannot be done.
He is warded.
I know that,
but maybe you can use
your intergalactic, hyperspace,
X-ray eyeballs
to find someone else.
There might be a reaper
for rent on his ass.
Could you find them?
I could try.
It's probably pointless,
washing the blood out
of your shirt, really.
It's the kind of thing
the real April would have done.
Mm. I miss being her.
Very sweet.
Didn't mind me
entering her one bit.
Why didn't you just attack me
right away?
My briefing said you were
dangerous and powerful.
And you did arrive armed,
so...
I needed information,
so I had to gain your trust.
And that required
intercourse?
Well, I am allowed some leeway
for executive decisions.
And I can't say
I didn't find you attractive.
Who hired you?
I assumed with Naomi gone,
things were in chaos.
New sheriff in town, Cass.
He hired a bunch of us.
I got lucky.
Enough questions from you.
I have several of my own.
Let's talk about your buddy
Metatron.
All right,
let's try this again,
and one of these times,
we'll get it right.
I knew nothing
about Metatron's spell.
I didn't know he was gonna cast
the angels out of Heaven.
I was cast out, too.
Oh, dear.
Nothing but reruns
on this channel.
These blades are marvelous,
aren't they?
They really do a number
on humans, too.
I told you last night,
and I meant it.
I was naive.
I had no idea
what he was planning.
You're lying.
It's known you helped Metatron
enter Heaven,
collaborated with him.
'Cause we were going
to restore Heaven,
bring the factions
together.
He lied to me.
You were with him
when he unleashed the spell.
You know how the angels
were cast down!
I didn't know
he was assembling a spell.
I only knew that I was
the final ingredient.
You?
My Grace.
That's why I'm human.
He took my Grace
for the spell.
Or you gave it.
It may be unwise
to kill me.
If my Grace were the key
to empowering the spell,
I may be key
to countering it.
Are you negotiating with me,
Castiel?
Cass!
This girl's popular
with all the boys.
Cass. Cass.
Cass!
No.
Sam, he's gone.
Dean.
Hey.
Hey! Yeah.
And Sam.
Cass. You okay?
Never do that again!
All right.
But I'm confused.
I know she stabbed me,
but I'm -- well,
I don't appear to be dead.
Well, you got dinged.
And, uh, you.
I made a deal with her.
Said she wouldn't get kabobed
if she brought you back.
She brought you back.
You lied.
I did.
I do that.
You know, you never answered
my question.
How did you know
where to find Cass?
I told you.
I went through
Maurice's pockets.
I found an address
and took a shot.
I never saw you go through
Maurice's pockets.
What are you
talking about?
I don't see half of
the nerdy stuff that you do.
It doesn't mean that
you don't do nerdy stuff.
I am really
enjoying this place.
Plentiful food.
Good water pressure.
Things I never even
considered before.
There really is a lot
to being human, isn't there?
It ain't all just burritos
and strippers, my friend.
Yeah.
I understand
what you're saying.
You do?
Yes, there's more to humanity
than survival.
You...look for purpose,
and you must not be defeated
by anger or despair.
Or hedonism,
for that matter.
Where does hedonism
come into it?
Well, my time with April
was very educational.
Yeah. I mean,
I would think that getting
killed is something.
And having sex.
You had sex with April?
Yeah, that would be
where the hedonism comes in.
Shh.
So...
Did you have protection?
I had my angel blade.
Oh --
oh, he had the Angel blade.
Um...
In any event, I --
I do now see how difficult
life can be
and how well you two
have led it.
And I think
you'll be great teachers.
Thanks. Cass.
Are there
any more burritos?
Uh, yes.
Our little Cass.
He gave it up to a reaper.
That is --
Castiel cannot stay here.
He will bring the angels down
on all of us.
No, no, he's got
the Enochian tattoo.
He's warded.
He was warded
when April found him,
and she killed him.
Yes,
and you brought him back,
and I thank you for that,
but this is Cass,
okay, who vouched for you
when I didn't know you
from Jack.
The bunker is safe.
Bartholomew is massing
a force.
We cannot stand
an incursion.
Castiel is in danger,
and if he is here,
I am in danger.
You're in danger?
From who, the angels?
If he stays,
I am afraid I will have
no choice but to leave.
Oh, no, you can't do that.
Sam's not well enough.
If you leave his body...
I know.
I am sorry.
Epic food.
I can't get enough.
Cass, uh, can we talk?
Of course.
Dean, you know I always
appreciate our talks,
our time together.
Listen, buddy.
Um...
You can't stay.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man