Sam: Ed and Harry --
the Ghostfacers.
[ Both grunting ]
[ Both sigh ]
What the hell
are you doing here?
[ Chuckles ] Uh,
we belong here.
We're professionals.
Professional what?
Paranormal investigators.
This stuff right here -- this
is our ticket to the big time --
Fame, money, sex...
with girls.
We are family.
Everything that has ever
gone wrong between us
has been
because we're family.
So, what?
We're not family now?
I'm saying you want to work,
let's work.
You said that you wanted to
keep things strictly business.
I wanted to keep things
strictly business between us.
About what you said
the other day...
I thought
it didn't bother you.
I may not think things
all the way through,
but what I do, I do
because it's the right thing.
You didn't save me
for me.
You did it for you.
? House is a hotel
? I won't stay long
[ camera shutter clicking ]
? I'd rather be at church
? unless the holy water works
[ Door closes ]
? I won't come around anymore
[ volume decreases ]
Mom?
Mom, are you home?
? Set fire to your worries
? let fear burn to the ground
[ lock clicks ]
? When the storms
are rolling in ?
? and you're filled up
to the brim ?
? they won't
come around anymore ?
[ Gasping ]
[ Dialing, ringing ]
Operator: 911.
What is your emergency?
There's someone
in my room.
What is your location?
Can you give us
a location, ma'am?
Are you still there?
Ma'am, please do not
hang up.
I've begun tracing your call,
but I need you to stay
on the line for me.
[ Screaming ]
[ Knife slashes ]
Stay on the line.
We'll send out an officer...
? Supernatural 9x15 ?
Thinman
Original Air Date on March 4, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ sighs ]
All right.
I'll be back.
Wait.
Where you headed?
Washington.
I caught a case.
You want me to come with?
Do you want to come?
On a hunt?
Why wouldn't I?
I don't know, man.
'Cause lately with you,
up is down
and down is sideways,
you know?
I-I -- I don't know
what you want.
[ Sighs ]
Okay. You want in?
Fine.
Sure thing.
Photo leaked
from the crime scene.
Girl was murdered
in her room,
doors were locked,
the windows were locked.
Who's the wallflower?
Exactly.
Best guest --
ghost caught on film.
[ Sighs ]
So, you're coming.
Does it look
like I'm staying?
Betty:
I scrubbed for hours.
I'll have to rip up
the carpet.
My daughter, Casey...
She picked out
the color herself.
We're...very sorry
for your loss, Mrs. Miles.
You mentioned Casey
had no known enemies.
What about at home?
Anything unusual
you may have noticed?
Uh...Electricity acting up
or lights...flickering,
TV on the Fritz?
[ Warbling ]
No, no fritzing.
No cold spots, either.
Sorry.
Out of curiosity, uh...
Why do you mention
cold spots?
I'm sorry.
That must sound strange, but...
...it's been three days since...
And the police
have found nothing.
I'd h--
I'd have to sell my house
to afford a private
investigator,
so when
the Supernaturalists called --
Dean:
Whoa, uh, sorry, the...
Um...
Supernaturalists?
I know to the FBI
it's not exactly orthodox.
But these men had answers
that no one else had, and I --
I owe it to Casey...
to listen.
Now, they -- they brought up
cold spots in relation to...?
Signs of the paranormal,
I suppose.
They're coming by today
to take a look.
And did these Supernaturalists
give you a name?
? Ghostfacers ?
Son of a bitch.
Oh, wow, look.
We got two more followers.
Mm.
Yeah. Harry,
I think it's from
that library interview we did.
Nice.
Hey, pal.
Hmm?
[ Whistles ]
What did Dana post?
No, it's just --
she changed her profile pic,
and it's cropped,
but you can clearly see
a guy's arm around her.
And she's smiling
like the dickens.
Yeah.
Uh, it --
it could a platonic...
arm that's touching her.
[ Clears throat ]
Ah, the Winchesters.
Yay.
Says nobody.
Ever.
All right, shut up and listen.
This is how it's gonna go.
You two clowns
are gonna get into
that mystery machine outside,
and you're gonna leave town
or I'm gonna put holes
in your knees.
[ Chuckles ]
Waiter: Can I get you guys
anything? Something, uh...
Uh, we're ready
for the bill.
Trey: Hey.
There's still crud
on this plate.
Now, hit the sinks
and do it right.
Sorry, Trey.
[ Slurps ]
Ahh, first of all,
you guys
don't scare us.
Not at all.
Say, "hola"
to my little pistola.
Am I supposed to be impressed
with that treasure trail
or the lady gun you got hiding
in your, uh, pants there?
Uh...Both?
Look, whether you like it
or not,
we are handling
this situation.
Yup.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
'Cause I see
a couple of fame whores
who are pointing their camera
at a mom who just lost her kid.
Ed: Guys,
we are investigators,
and we have
every right --
No. No, you don't.
You know why?
'Cause you're just gonna get
in our way.
Or you're gonna get
somebody else killed.
That's right. So, you can
either walk out of here...
...or crawl.
Up to you.
[ Chuckles ] Oh, my God, Menudo.
Will you guys relax?
We know what we're going.
Yup.
Really?
And what about the rest
of the Bad News Bears, huh?
Where's the --
where's the fat one?
And -- and the girl?
There was a girl, right?
They -- we dropped them. They were --
they were dead weight.
Well, t-they're still alive.
They're -- no, they're totally alive.
I see. So, it's just the,
uh, the dumpy duo, then.
Well, that's great.
So, here's the deal.
A ghost...
Will land you two dead
in five seconds flat.
A ghost?
Oh. [ Chuckles ]
They think it's a ghost.
[ Both chuckle ]
It's so not a ghost.
No.
Okay. We'll bite.
What do you think it is?
Can I --
can I do it this time?
You got it.
Okay.
I've waited all my life for this.
Amazon me, bitches.
I will shoot you...
Bitches.
Like we were saying, you were
just going, right? Great.
[ Grunts ]
Good talk.
50 shades
of way too much protein.
Uh...Dean?
Yeah?
Ed and Harry wrote a book.
What?
Yeah.
Uh,
"The Skinny on Thinman",
by America's foremost
Supernaturalists.
What the hell's a Thinman?
I don't know. Um...
Whoa.
Check that out, though.
That does
kind of look like
whatever was behind
Casey Miles, right?
Or Garth if somebody
shaved his face off.
Big whoop.
Here we go.
Uh, "Thinman --
"an urban legend started
on the world wide web --
"lurks in the background
of his victims' lives
until he's ready
to kill them."
Yeah, because everything started
on the Internet is true.
Like, uh, oh, the shark
attacking a helicopter --
they write the book
on that one, too?
Dude, real or not,
thousands of people
have posted to the site.
It's like Thinman is
the new Bigfoot or something.
Or Thinman is just a ghost
with a brand name.
You saying that
'cause you really think
it's a ghost or because
you don't like the Ghostfacers?
Hey, don't forget --
we hit EMF in Casey's room.
Right, but the house was
next door to power lines,
which can affect the read.
A girl died
in a locked room, Sam --
spells "ghost"
right there.
Maybe it got in there
before it was locked up.
Who knows, Dean?
But how can people all over
the world see the same ghost?
Spirits don't exactly
hop around.
I know that.
But right now, the veil is
all kinds of screwed, okay?
Ghosts could be
popping up anywhere.
Yeah, but, Dean,
Thinman sightings
date back a couple years.
The veil's only been a problem
for, what, the last six months?
Well, you know, people still see
Elvis all over the damn place.
Look, all I'm saying
is those douchewheels
ain't experts on crap.
What are you doing?
I'm checking the local deaths
to see if there's any candidates
for ghosts.
[ Sighs ]
The closet -- the setting
of the sunset of Casey's life.
Harry.
Yeah.
Come on, man,
would you please stop
Facebook stalking
your ex-girlfriend?
I was right.
Hmm.
She changed her relationship
status to "it's complicated."
What does that
even mean?
Who cares?
You broke up with her.
Everything about that girl
is complicated.
Okay, I mean,
she gets the cream puffs,
she tells you
to take out the filling.
They're just puffs.
Yeah, that was
some pretty messed-up stuff.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, okay.
I'm -- I'm sorry.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Mm. Okay.
I'm good.
Okay?
Back on game. Yeah.
[ Inhales deeply ]
We're so close
to finding Thinman, Ed.
Mm-hmm.
I can smell him.
[ Sniffs ]
I can smell his musk.
Mm-hmm.
[ Sniffs ]
Closer than ever.
This is really serious, Harry.
Yeah.
I mean, the Winchesters
are here, and, you know,
I don't want my knees blown off
by Sam and Dean.
[ Sniffs ]
Have you ever thought
that we might just,
you know, bail on this?
What?
What the -- what the hell
is wrong with you?!
We can't let those
jockstraps steal our glory.
No one cares what they think.
They don't even have a Twitter.
We're gonna find Thinman, Ed,
for our families, for Dana.
Oh, so, it's about
your ex eating her words?
It's about making
all the haters eat their words.
Maggie and Spruce --
the just -- deserters.
They want
to lead a "normal life".
I mean, what is that?
Screw them.
Right?
When we find Thinman,
are they gonna be on "Dr. Phil".
No.
We're gonna be
on "Dr. Phil."
Hell, yeah.
Press "record," buddy.
You got it.
Wait for it.
You ready?
Yep.
The bedroom of a teenage girl
is meant for two things --
giggles and joy.
Until one night, Thinman
turned the giggles into blood.
[ Chuckles ] Oh!
You are so money right now.
You like that?
This is good stuff.
And it's gonna pay off
in ladies, Ed -- lots of ladies.
We're gonna need --
we're gonna need snorkels,
'cause we're gonna be
swimming around in so much --
[ ice clinking in glasses ]
Thought you boys
might be thirsty.
Please.
That sounds delicious.
Okay. All right,
over the past six months,
there have been three
unnatural deaths in Springdale,
none of them connected
to Casey Miles,
and none of them
violent.
Okay, that's not exactly
a recipe for a vengeful spirit.
There have been
a bunch of unexplained deaths
pinned on Thinman.
Um, a vic dies,
then, a couple weeks later,
a photo pops up of the vic
with Thinman photobombing.
So, Thinman's
stalking folks?
According to the lore.
According to the idiots.
How come none of these
vics pinged our radar?
I'm pretty sure
the mysterious deaths
can be chalked up
to non-supernatural causes.
That and, honestly,
most of these photos
look pretty fake.
Even Casey's?
Except Casey's.
Casey's photo...
wasn't doctored.
Whatever was behind her...
Was really there.
Okay, well,
that doesn't make any sense.
I mean,
how could something be
both real and fake
at the same time?
Well, a girl is dead, and that's
about as real as it gets.
All right, so,
the last thing she did
was she took a photo
on her phone.
How did that photo
end up online?
No clue.
It was originally posted
to a Thinman fan forum,
but the I.P. address
was blocked.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
This thing has fans?
Of course it does.
Okay, well, then somebody wanted
this photo on the Internet,
and I'm guessing that the ghost
didn't hop online to post it.
[ Grunting ]
Is the, uh,
sheriff around?
There's a couple questions
we'd like to ask him.
Uh,
sorry to disappoint.
Sheriff's
on a hunting trip.
But, uh, I appreciate
you agents being here.
I could use
all the help I can get.
Wait a second. Was this cracked
when you found it?
Yeah, man.
Maybe she dropped it?
911 call
went dead at 11:59.
Wait, what time
was the photo posted?
Around 2:00 a.m.
But the coroner has
the death at midnight.
How could she have posted
the photo from her phone?
That --
that's impossible.
Or...supernatural.
What?
Why would you
say that?
A couple fellas came by,
uh, asking questions
about the girl's death,
suggested they might
be able to help.
They, uh, gave me a book
they wrote about, um...
Thinman?
Yeah.
[ Clears throat ]
Just...
Not a fan?
[ Tapping ]
Agents,
thanks for coming.
[ Scoffs ] What are these
two crapshoots doing here?
I figured it wouldn't hurt to go
a little "medium," you know?
Uh...two counties over,
folks were combing the place
for a poor little dead boy
back in August.
The cops let a psychic
do her thing.
Shish, bang, boom --
found a body a day later.
Uh-huh. Excuse me.
Is there any, uh,
security-cam footage.
Uh, yeah, just...
Hey.
Aah!
I thought
I told you to beat it.
Oh, well, what are you gonna do.
You gonna out me, "agent"?
Okay, look, playing paparazzi
at a crime scene --
who does that help
but yourselves?
The bloggers, Dean,
the believers --
everyone who needs
just a little proof
to know that Thinman
is out there.
Wait, so, you're saying
there's a lot of folks online
that are pretty die-hard
about this thing?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Uh-huh.
You throw the right
Tibetan symbol into the mix,
you dumb asses ever think
the Thinman comes to life
as a Tulpa?
Because
thousands of people
can agree that Thinman
is any one thing?
The lore changes
blog to blog.
He's not a Tulpa.
Okay, all right.
All right.
Right here, right now,
cut the crap.
Do either of you actually
know what Thinman is?
No. We just play
Supernaturalists on TV.
We have no idea
what we're doing.
[ Laughs ]
Of course we do.
Thinman, is  part man,
part tree.
Some people believe
that he emerged
from the nightmare
of an autistic boy.
All right,
so you have no idea.
Norwood: Fellas,
you want to see this.
All right,
check it out.
Whoa.
Harry: Whoa.
Dean: All right,
so, how did he jump
from the parking lot
to the diner.
The doors were locked?
The footage shows Trey
locked them 10 minutes before.
Locked, not locked,
it doesn't matter.
Everyone knows
Thinman can teleport.
I didn't even
get a blip on my EMF.
So, maybe
it's not a ghost.
You Feds believers now?
Okay, uh...
We're gonna go.
Uh, good work, deputy, agent.
Harry: Let's go. Let's go, man.
See it again.
Holy wow.
[ Chuckles ]
Someone posted
the diner footage of Thinman
in the comments section
of our blog.
Who?
Who cares?
Maintain
current velocity.
[ Grunting ]
Hey, wh-why are you
putting your ninja outfit on?
I'm not gonna wait
for someone else to die.
I'm gonna
find Thinman tonight.
Where?
The woods, obvi.
Uh, that's
kind of general.
Well, the lore says that
Thinman hangs out by trees,
and the woods
is where trees hang out.
Two kills in town --
local woods is the best bet.
Two people are dead --
really dead.
And I just keep thinking
that, you know,
maybe Sam and Dean
should just take over.
First of all, hell no.
And -- and quit raining
on my rainbow.
Rainbows can't happen
without rain.
Don't try to use
science with me.
This is
about a-a feeling.
And we can't quit
when we're so close
to finding Thinman
and finally making up
for everything we've lost
because of...what we do.
Okay, it wouldn't be the worst
idea, though, you know,
if we leave it
to the professionals.
[ Laughs ] We are
the professionals, Ed.
[ Goggles whirring ]
So, the woods?
Any woods, Ed.
Any woods.
Okay.
Just grasping at straws here,
but when I think "teleport,"
I think
"Crossroads Demon."
Mm.
Demon that likes to stab
and watch YouTube. Why not?
Oh, by the way, speaking
of which,
the video of,
uh, Trey getting knifed --
it's already online.
It has, like,
2,000 views.
It's like somebody wants people
to see Thinman in action.
It's 'cause people will watch,
'cause people are sick.
And when did "viral" go
from that baby chimp
falling out of a tree
to killer "Candid Camera"?
[ Snaps fingers ]
You know what video would have
gone viral, if we still had it?
When you were five
and you got dressed up as Batman
and you jumped off the shed
'cause you thought
you could fly.
After
you jumped first.
Hey, I was nine, and I was
dressed up like superman, okay?
Everybody knows
that Batman can't fly.
Well, I didn't know that.
I broke my arm.
[ Chuckling ]
I know you did.
Man, I drove you to the E.R.
on my handlebars.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, good times.
Yeah, they were.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Knock on door ]
Come on in.
[ Breathing heavily ]
I got to tell you guys
something important,
and then the case is yours.
Harry here, solo Ghostfacer,
investigating a possible
Thinman habitat...
in the woods.
All alone, deep in the woods,
a man could lose his marbles
being so close
to the blade of doom.
Lucky for us,
I'm really good at marbles.
All right, either you bleed
Ghostfacers red or you don't.
If Spruce wanted to start
a startup
and Maggie's heart
was in the roller derby,
who am I to stop them?
But Harry -- I-I couldn't
let him give in to his girl.
I mean, she -- she called
the Ghostfacers stupid.
Stupid! Can you --
can you believe that?
You know, I-I don't care
how much money
her daddy's hedge fund has.
I just couldn't watch Harry
become a corporate stooge.
Okay, this all sounds like
sad times at Bitchmont High.
What does this
have to do with the case?
Harry was gonna leave,
so I needed to give him
a reason to stay.
I-I made up Thinman.
Harry:
Thinman stalks his victims,
but the tables have turned,
my friends.
The stalker is now the stalkee.
So you're saying that
this crap is actually crap?
One old photo of a butler,
a lot of Photoshop later,
and I posted on one of those
horror forums under "anonymous".
And it blew up.
Yeah.
I only faked one case for us, and
then we're packing up to go home
when somebody posted
a sighting of Thinman,
so...we went after it,
and that's how the Thinman
became
a crowdsourced legend.
Look, we were
at the front of it.
It felt like something.
It -- it was so awesome
to have a following,
and Harry -- he was just --
he was so into it.
Ed,
you have to tell him.
You don't get it.
We were
the Thinman guys.
Without the Thinman,
we're just...guys --
just --
we're just puffs.
What?
If I tell Harry, he's gonna
leave the Ghostfacers.
Listen, if you don't tell him,
he's gonna leave anyway.
Trust me here.
Secrets
ruin relationships.
Okay, well, I'll just tell him
when the time is right.
Time's right now,
chief.
Well, he's --
he's not here.
Uh, he's --
he's out in the woods,
uh, searching
for Thinman.
Okay, because Thinman, or
whatever the hell this thing is,
has killed two people, and now
Harry is in the woods alone.
Well, actually,
it's more like "wood," um,
'cause I dropped him off by some trees
behind a grocery store.
[ Chuckles ] Guys, come on.
He's gonna be fine.
Guys?
Harry: All right, what we have
here is a, uh, -- it's a --
it looks like a formation
of sticks
in the shape of a pile.
Could have been
left here for us by Thinman.
[ Rustling ]
What was that?
Oh!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Oh, my God.
We are not alone.
[ Screams ]
[ Vehicle approaching ]
[ Tires screech ]
[ Thud ]
Sam: Too tight?
Nope. No, I'm good.
I'm good.
Yeah?
I'm good. All right.
I think I'm just gonna
have to staple it
when we get back
to the motel.
We were right, Ed!
Thinman's real.
Yeah.
Some fresh tires tracks
back over there.
I took some photos.
What for?
Because that car might belong
to whoever knifed you.
Well, whoever cut me
was Thinman,
and Thinman doesn't drive.
[ Chuckles ]
It was Thinman, jackass!
I mean, I shouldn't have to
connect the dots for you guys.
I figured, you know, you're
both intelligent, m-maybe.
Um, Harry.
What?
Why didn't you tell me
that before?
Because --
I-I don't know --
I thought you were
gonna get mad.
Oh, good guess, Ed.
I am mad.
I'm really, really mad
at you right now.
I-I can see that.
You crashed the Jenga Tower
of our lives.
I was gonna get married.
I left her to run around
with you, living some lie.
Well, at least we were
living it together.
Seriously?
[ Chuckles ] Seriously?
If I hadn't struck gold
with Thinman,
you'd be doing a boring job,
doing boring numbers,
answering to Dana's dad.
Okay? I saved you, bud.
Saved me? From what?!
From living a nice life?
From not getting stabbed?
How selfish can you be?
Well, maybe it's
not too late, you know?
You could
call her and see.
That's not gonna work.
Well, maybe -- maybe it will.
No, it's not.
You want to know why?
'Cause she's got some guy's arm
wrapped around her neck,
and it's "complicated",
okay?
Look, Harry, we didn't know
from the start
if Thinman
was real or not.
I -- okay, look, maybe I had
some inside knowledge,
okay, but does it
really make a difference
if we keep it going
for the fans?
They'll never know.
I'll know.
You made a chump
out of me, Ed.
Harry, we can
get through this.
We just debunk Thinman
and then we go back
to Ghostfacers.
I can't.
I can't trust you
anymore, Ed.
Oh, come on, Harry.
[ Sighs ]
I get it.
You're pissed, okay?
And -- and you don't mean
what you say.
But, Harry, just tell me
what you need.
I'll go
get some coffee, and --
and you can
stay here and chill.
[ Door opens ]
Hey.
How did it go?
[ Sighs ]
It, um,
went, uh...Um...
Hey.
You okay?
I just got punched
right in the feels.
Um...
None of it was real, Sam.
Ed was just pretending,
and now he wants me to pretend,
like this is just something
I could get past.
I know what you mean.
Look, there are things
you can forgive,
and there are things
you can't.
So, which one is this?
That's something you got
to figure out for yourself.
[ Knock on door ]
Hey.
Uh...
I got a bead on those
tire treads, if you want to...
What's up?
So, the tires were only made
for one kind of car.
It's a 1989 Geo Metro.
Town this small -- there's only
one registered here.
Deputy says it belongs
to a guy named Roger
who works night security
down at the mill
on the north side of town.
So, this thing teleported,
but it has a job and car.
What are we dealing with?
Let's go find out.
[ Sighs ] Oh.
Sam and Dean
caught something,
so they're gonna clean up
your mess.
You're right.
It is my mess.
I should be the one out there
cleaning it up.
You'd just make it worse.
Oh, what?
You were fine leaving Sam
and Dean before. Why not now?
I don't want to be a
jellyfish spine anymore, Harry.
Jellyfish
don't have spines.
Exactly.
Before the heartache,
before the lies,
we set out
to help people, right?
Yeah.
Mostly.
So, there's no reason
not to get out there
and do what we
mostly set out to do.
Harry, I-I can make this right
for the both of us.
[ Sighs ]
We can make it right.
Y-you mean you want
to come with me?
I thought we said my partner
and I would take care of this.
Look, guys,
my boss is AWOL.
We don't have a warrant.
My ass is on the line
if this thing goes sideways.
All right.
Just stay back.
[ Gun cocks ]
[ Electricity crackles ]
Always wanted
to use these things.
[ Humming "Camptown Races" ]
[ Groans ]
So, you're Thinman,
huh?
[ Humming continues ]
That would make sense
if it didn't look
like you just ate
a fat camp.
Oh, God, Sam,
make him stop.
Hey, so, what's the deal?
What are you, Norwood?
You a demon?
I mean, how did you teleport
back at the diner?
Team effort.
So, there was
no teleporting --
just a couple of douche bags
doing the "scream" thing.
Wait,
I know who you are.
You're the busboy
from the diner.
So, what, you just wanted
to kill your boss?
Trey was a dick.
[ Chuckles ]
And what about Casey?
What did she do?
She wouldn't go out with me,
so I set her up
with someone else --
my knife.
[ Norwood laughs ]
Good one, Rog.
I see the sheriff
didn't make it out of town.
Well, he really should
have given me
the time off I asked for.
So, you killed him?!
I didn't kill anyone.
Roger did.
He's the psycho.
I'm the visionary.
I don't blame you
for underestimating me.
Everybody does.
Fancy Fed, coming in here,
treating me like a paper monkey
from the get-go.
But I was Thinman
the whole time.
Do you have any idea
how good that felt?
No, sicko,
I can't say that I do.
Yeah,
pretty boy doesn't know
what it's like
to feel invisible --
to grow up in a town of
300 people and nobody sees you.
They didn't see us.
So,
how did you two meet?
Wackjob.com?
[ Chuckles ] No.
Just a couple of schmoes
in an empty bar.
We hit it off.
Turns out me and Rog --
we're both total
conspiracy-theory junkies.
And then we found Thinman,
and, bam,
we blew up all over
the message boards.
So, what is this, then?
Some sort of a twisted cosplay?
Cosreal.
You know,
blogging was fun, but...
But, let me guess,
you wanted something more.
You realize
what you two jackasses
are doing
doesn't make you Thinman.
It makes you
copycat killers.
It makes me Thinman.
And you're not
telling anyone I'm not,
'cause you'll be
too dead to talk.
Show time.
You two are lucky ducks.
You're the stars
of our best video yet.
And when it goes viral,
everyone will know
Thinman's real.
And...Action!
Sam: Wait, no, no, no. Don't!
[ Thud ]
[ Tape ripping ]
Harry...
[ Groans ]
Oh, he got me!
He got me back!
It's Scooby-Doo time,
douche bag.
Take off the mask.
I know
you're not Thinman.
You're just a "me-me".
Ed,
it's pronounced meme.
It's spelled m-e-m-e,
though.
The second "e"
is silent. Yeah.
You're a me-me -- a-a man-meme,
and I invented you.
Oh!
Good to know.
Oh, sh--
[ breathing heavily ]
I'm a lover
of the classics, Ed.
And what we have here
is a "Frankenstein" situation.
I'm a lover
I mean, wow, the creator.
I mean, we -- we were
gonna let one of you guys
live to tell our story
[chuckles] but now,
once you two are dead,
there'll be no proof
that Thinman was your brainchilc.
No.
[ Gun cocks ]
Wait, no! No! No!
No, look. Look at me.
This is all my fault.
Okay?
It's all my fault.
I got enough bullets
for both of you.
[ Gunshot ]
So, are we good in there?
Yeah.
[ Groans ]
With the Thinman footage
and the way I set the bodies,
there should be enough
breadcrumbs to make it look
like those two psychos
offed each other.
They were
just people, man.
They weren't...demons.
They weren't monsters.
They...were
just frickin' people.
Yeah, well, like I said,
people are sick.
S-so...Are we cool?
[ Scoffs ]
I don't think
we ever will be.
[ Chuckles ]
I mean, you know,
we made it right.
We, uh --
we beat the guys.
This could be our shot to start
the old Ghostfacers again.
I came here with you to finish
this thing with Thinman.
I wasn't just
closing a chapter, Ed.
It was
the whole dang book.
But you saved my life
back there.
I killed a guy, Ed.
He was a bad guy, Harry.
He was a guy, Ed.
Too many people have died
'cause of your crap.
I've done
all this crap for us.
I-I don't know why
you don't see that.
No.
[ Chuckles ] No.
You did this for you.
Ed, there's a lot of things
I can forgive,
so, what does this mean
about us?
It means...
It's complicated.
Can I get a ride
from you guys?
Yeah, sure.
[ Car door opens ]
[ Engine turns over ]
Harry, you okay?
Yeah.
I mean, no.
You roll with a guy
so many years,
you start to think he's always
gonna be next to you.
Like, when you're old and
you're drinking on the porch,
he'll be in
that other rocking chair.
And then something happens,
and you realize that other chair
has gone empty.
You know what I mean?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man