You're dying, sam.
Shut up.
Ezekiel, he's a good soldier.
There is a chance I can fix
your brother from the inside.
I'm trusting you, Zeke.
Metatron tricked me.
He took my Grace.
It's why I'm human.
There's no putting
the angels back in Heaven.
Heaven is locked.
Damn it, Cass! There's a war on,
and it's on you.
I know who you are,
and it isn't Ezekiel.
Gadreel.
You intend to be the ruler
of this new heaven.
I will join you
as second in command.
Here's the first name
on your to-do list.
My name is Abaddon.
War is what I do. It's my job.
I can get you new bodies,
and we will march into hell,
and all the humans and all
the angels will bow to me!
Angels are slaughtering
one another.
It's open warfare.
No one will survive this war.
I did what I had to.
I got my Grace back.
No! No, no!
Kevin.
? Think in terms
of bridges burned ?
? think of seasons
that must end ?
? see the rivers
rise and fall ?
? they will rise
and fall again ?
? everything must have an end
? like an ocean to a shore
? like a river to a stream
? as the light fades
from the screen ?
? from the famous final scene
? Supernatural 9x10 ?
Road Trip
Original Air Date on January 14, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Corey! Corey! Corey! Corey!
Corey! Corey!
You're on in 10.
The label wants to open
with "Baby, Be My Baby."
Then you can roll
right on into "Babycakes,"
and then the clean version
of "Babymaker."
Oh, and, Corey?
Let's try to take it easy
with the groupies tonight, huh?
Yeah, whatever.
The hell -- security!
It's fine, Margey.
You can go.
What? Corey --
Bitch, did I stutter?!
Hello, Gadreel.
Thaddeus.
That's a new look,
I must say.
Well, what can I say,
you know?
We all got booted
out of the penthouse,
and I just kind of figured...
Why be an angel
when you can be a God?
How are you, old friend?
I am not your friend.
Well, I think you're being
a little bit mean there,
considering all the quality time
we spent together.
I was imprisoned,
and you tortured me.
Heaven has rules.
Do the crime, do the time.
That's it.
I made a mistake.
I was a guard.
I was doing my job.
What you did to Abner,
was that was your job?
Your boyfriend?
Now, that, mnh --
that was just fun.
Is that what you're here for --
the big payback?
Fine.
If you want to get
a little bloody,
uh, I have no problem
kicking your ass -- again.
You know, w-we'll say
for old time's sa--
Looking for this?
Gadreel...
...I'm sorry.
Dean.
Cass.
Now, look at you, all suited up
and back in the game.
I, um...
I came as soon
as you called.
I wa--
Dean, what happened?
What's wrong?
Sammy was dying.
What was I supposed to do?
You let an angel possess him?
He said it was the only way,
and I believed him.
Now Sam's gone.
Kevin's...
Dean, I'm sorry.
Yeah, well...
Sorry don't pay the bills,
does it?
It sure as hell
ain't gonna bring Kevin back.
We got to find
that son of a bitch.
Dean.
If the angel possessing Sam
isn't Ezekiel, then who is it?
A dead man walking.
What,
you're gonna destroy him?
Damn right.
You kill an angel,
its vessel dies, too.
Think I don't know that?
If I don't end Sam
and that halo burns him out
and I...
God, I was so damn stupid.
You were stupid
for the right reasons.
Yeah, like that matters.
It does.
Sometimes that's all
that matters.
Listen to me.
Sam is strong.
If he knew an angel was
possessing him, he could fight.
He could cast
the angel out.
Maybe.
But as far as I know,
he's in the dark.
I don't know
how we clue him in.
Do you remember Alfie?
The kid angel?
Yeah. Why?
Before he died,
he told me the demons
were able to dig into his mind,
access his coding.
We might be able
to do that here.
Might be able to --
to bypass the angel
and talk directly to Sam.
And you think
that would work?
I don't know,
but I think we should try.
Okay.
Um, where do we start?
Hello, boys.
Here's the deal --
you're gonna tell us
how to hack an angel,
and I'm gonna give you
some of the good stuff.
Human blood,
fresh from the tap.
Word is you're
jonesing for it.
Please. I'll pass.
What do you want, then?
Well, for starters...
A massage.
Between the sitting
and the shackles,
a body gets
a little stiff.
Yeah, I ain't rubbing you.
God, no.
Get Kevin.
His tiny fists can really work wonder--
Kevin is dead.
Oh.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Don't pretend you care.
You tried to kill him.
I told him
this was gonna happen.
I was the only person
who tried to warn him.
I told him to run.
From what?
You.
How many times
am I gonna have to say this?
People in your
general vicinity
don't have much in the way
of a life-span.
Now, I can't teach you
how to crack open an angel.
It's more...
art than science.
But I can do it for you.
All I ask in return
is a little field trip.
Dying for some fresh air.
Chains on, naturally.
No
No? Of course not.
Because if I'm plan "A,"
I'm sure you have a totally
viable, much better plan "B."
You can't be
considering this.
With the chains on,
he can't do anything.
It's Crowley.
He can always do something.
Looks like we need
a tiebreaker.
Go get moose, squirrel.
Unless...
Unless, of course,
you can't.
That's why you're here,
isn't it?
The poor giant baby's
in trouble again, isn't he?
Are you done?
Depends.
Do we have a deal?
Yeah.
Excellent.
When do we leave?
Soon as I can scrounge up
a ride.
Well, I have a vehicle.
It stopped a few miles
from here, inexplicably.
Really?
What are you, a pimp?
I like it.
Yeah, it's out of gas.
Riddle me this, boy wonder.
Why do you need the wheels?
When you betray us, I'll be
the one to carve out your heart.
Oh, Cass, such a flirt.
All right. Let's go.
Shotgun.
Uh, wrong.
You're in the back.
Hey -- you, too.
Keep an eye on him.
Hey.
Watch the leg.
You're on my side.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Get you anything else?
I'm good, thanks.
Welcome home, sweethearts.
Strange seeing an old vessel,
isn't it?
Like looking
in a funhouse mirror.
But first things first -- the
tasks I gave you, any hiccups?
Killing Thaddeus was easy.
He had it coming.
I know all about your history.
Why do you think
I gave you his name?
Consider it
your signing bonus.
And the kid?
That was...
less easy.
He was a threat,
but I flipped
a switch upstairs,
and now that Kevin is gone,
there will be no more Prophets.
And what about
Dean Winchester?
You never gave me his name,
Metatron.
Not much for seizing
the initiative, are we?
Gadreel, we are writing
our own epic story here.
To make that work, sometimes
you have to kill your darlings.
It's not like you haven't done
worse before.
Sorry. Sorry.
Onto new business.
Your next target.
How many more lives
do I have to take?
It's not your place
to ask questions.
It is your place
to obey.
You want to be
my second in command?
Prove you're ready.
Prove you're loyal.
Or don't.
Walk away.
Go back to being Gadreel
the traitor, the sap,
heaven's
longest-running joke.
Inferni clamavi ad te regem.
Abaddon?
I found him.
Crowley is on the move.
AbnerYour source is in here?
And she can track
anything you need,
even our little
lost Samantha.
How?
Well, this place
isn't really...this.
It's a front
for an N.S.A. listening post.
What are they listening for?
Everything.
The U.S. government
is quite the voyeur these days.
So I planted one of my best
and let her go to work.
Looking for terrorists?
Looking for marks,
slow boat.
Mr. Crowley?
She'll see you now.
Uh, just Mr. Crowley.
I'll be listening
to every word you say.
Promise?
Cecily.
How are you?
Better than you.
That was Dean Winchester,
and...Castiel?
Yes, I know.
Without the tie,
he's barely recognizable.
It's so --
hot.
I mean, human Castiel?
Eh.
But feathered Castiel?
Human Castiel?
You heard what happened
to him, right?
I've been tied up.
Pray, do tell.
Hear anything?
No.
The room Crowley's in
has been warded.
Awesome.
That's friggin' awesome.
So captain sexy out there
totally cuts
another angel's throat,
yoinks his Grace, and now?
He's got his mojo back --
minus the broken wings.
Well, that explains
the hooptie.
And we know all this how?
I tuned one of our satellites
to pick up angel radio.
Impressive.
Yeah.
Not just a pretty face.
What about Hell?
No one's doing their job.
I send oodles of data
down there every week,
but does Hell give a damn?
No.
Well. Of course.
With Abaddon in charge, you...?
Oh, that "b" with an "itch"
ain't the boss.
I mean, she's got a few of the
more aggro types on her side.
But most are just waiting
to see who takes the belt --
you or her.
They're still afraid of me.
Probably 'cause they don't know
you're in cuffs.
Speaking of which...
Do they come off?
Not without the key.
Fine.
I need you to do me a favor.
Can you find this car
for me?
Easy-peasy.
Nice to know
someone's still loyal.
Uh-huh.
That is, of course, if you're
not playing both sides?
Wouldn't you?
Your phallus on wheels
just ran a red light
in Somerset, Pennsylvania,
10 minutes ago.
Let's go.
The three amigos ride again.
He's not my amigo.
Alexander Sarver?
Yeah?
Gadreel?
Abner?
I thought you were dead.
W-what happened?
W-what are you doing here?
I --
What are you doing here?
Daddy! Daddy!
Hey.
Delilah,
this is daddy's best friend.
Can you say hi?
Hi.
You have a child?
I have family, Gadreel.
Look, my wife and the niblet
are going to a movie.
Swing back in a few hours
so we can catch up. Okay?
Okay. Sure.
So, um, you have a job?
Customer support --
computers mostly.
It's like answering prayers,
but they pay you for it.
You have changed, Abner.
Yeah, well,
I was a crappy angel.
I was petulant.
I deserted my post.
I spent 700 years
in heaven's lockup. I...
No.
Doesn't matter.
We're a long way
from Thaddeus now.
I killed him, Abner.
I got our revenge.
I w-- I wish
you hadn't done that.
But why?
He tortured us --
you most of all.
I remember.
And I remember you were always
there to put me back together.
We were friends.
We are friends.
And the fall,
it's our second chance.
We can forget our old hates,
who we were.
It's not that easy.
Yes, it is.
Look at me.
I'm happy.
And your vessel --
is he happy?
He was an abusive ass.
But I love my family,
and they love me.
I'm not a wise man,
Gadreel.
But I know this.
The key to happiness?
It's getting the one thing
you want most
and never letting it go.
And what if there's a price?
There's always a price.
But it's worth paying.
You should not
have come here, Dean.
You kill my friend,
then you take my brother,
and you think I'm gonna
let that stand?
I allowed you to live.
Mistake.
AbnerSo Crowley was here.
Yeah, um,
I thought you'd want to know.
You thought right.
And now? Any idea
where he scampered off to?
Somerset, Pennsylvania,
with Dean Winchester
and the angel Castiel.
And you know this how?
They're chasing an Impala.
I helped them track it.
You helped Crowley?
Yeah.
I'm kind of playing both sides
until someone w--
until you win.
Hm.
Smart, right?
No.
Sort of the opposite.
Welcome to the party, pal.
Cass, how we lookin'?
Most of Sam's internal
burns have healed.
I should be able
to fix the rest.
What's your name?
I thought I knew every angel in
heaven, but I've never seen you.
Why would I tell
you anything?
Well, I don't give a damn
who you are.
You need to get out --
now!
And if I don't?
Then you and I will have
a lovely little playdate.
Even bound,
I can rip this body apart.
Tell them, Castiel.
You do, you die.
You want this to end?
Go ahead.
Put a blade through
your brother's heart.
If it makes you feel better,
I have Sam locked away
in a dream.
As far as he knows,
the two of you are
working a case right now --
something with ghouls
and cheerleaders.
Why are you doing this,
huh?
We fought together.
And I trusted you.
I thought you were
one of the good guys!
I am doing
what I have to do.
Well, so am I.
So am I.
Hey.
I can't watch that
anymore.
I understand.
It's not Sam, but...
It's still Sam.
Pretty much, yeah.
How are you doing?
You want to talk
about me now?
I want to talk about anything
that's not a demon sticking
needles into my brother's brain.
Yeah, humor me, man.
How you doing?
Uh...
I'm okay.
Good. Good.
That's, uh...
So, what, you just change the
batteries out, power back up?
It's that easy?
It wasn't easy,
but I didn't have a choice.
Yeah.
Well, that's usually
how it goes.
Cass...
I'm sorry.
About what?
Kickin' you
out of the bunker.
That's, uh...
You know,
not telling you about Sam.
You thought his life
was at stake.
Yeah, I got played.
I thought
I was saving Heaven.
I got played, too.
So you're sayin' we're
both a couple of dumbasses?
I prefer
the word "trusting."
Less dumb. Less ass.
Laverne! Shirley!
Get in here!
Pinhead's out cold,
but watch this.
Zir noco iad Gadreel.
What's he saying?
His name. Gadreel.
Does that mean
something to you?
Well, it's why
I've never seen him.
He's been imprisoned
since the dawn of time.
Gadreel was the sentry who
allowed Lucifer into the garden.
My, my. A celebrity.
Wait, the garden?
Like eden?
Adam and Eve?
Fig-leaves garden?
It's his fault --
all of it.
The corruption of man,
demons, hell.
God left because of him.
The archangels --
the apocalypse.
If he hadn't been so weak,
none of it would have happened.
You ruined the universe,
you damn son of a bitch!
Cass! Cass! Hey!
Dean, he --
I get it.
But you got to chill.
What's taking so long?
Other than the fact
that I'm trying to unravel
a living, multidimensional
knot of pure energy,
not much.
It won't work.
You will never
find your brother.
Go ahead. Poke and prod.
I can sit in this chair
for years
and watch you fail
over and over again.
I've endured
much worse than this, Dean.
So...much...worse.
And I have all the time
in the world.
Shut up!
All right. Plan "B."
Cass,
you got to possess him.
What?
Do it now!
Get in there,
tell Sam what's going on,
and help him kick
that lying son of a bitch out!
It might work.
But I can't possess
a vessel without permission.
No. Not happening.
Don't be daft.
Demons can take
what they want.
I can burrow
into that rat's nest of a head.
I can wake Sam up.
Just call me plan "C."
You can't --
you got a better idea?
What about the angel?
I'll work fast.
And if he finds you?
I'll run.
I'm not dying
for you lot.
Of course, if I do this,
you're gonna have to...
Take off the leash.
Yeah, I know.
And it stays off.
I save Sam,
I leave here a free man.
Do we have a deal?
Cass,
burn off Sam's tattoo.
Dean.
Do it.
If you mess with Sam,
if you try anything --
I keep my bargains.
Besides, I don't want
to be inside your brother
any longer than I have to.
I'm not one
for sloppy seconds.
When you find him,
say "Poughkeepsie."
It's our go word. It means
"drop everything and run."
Fine.
While I'm gone,
hands off the suit.
I will destroy you.
Eat me.
AbnerA demon and an angel
walk into my brother.
Sounds like a bad joke.
Dean,
if this doesn't work...
It'll work.
I mean, it just doesn't make
any sense.
Why is this ghoul only
chomping on dead cheerleaders?
Hey, you want a beer?!
No, I'm fine.
Not bad.
Dean? Dean!
Poughkeepsie.
How do you know that word?
Because Dean's sent me,
Bullwinkle, the real Dean.
I'll make this quick -- you've
been possessed by an angel.
He's got you packed away in some
dusty corner of your own mind,
and I'm here to break you out.
Seriously?
Fine.
We'll do this the fun way.
See?
Not real. Like I said.
I know how possession works,
Sam.
You've seen
everything that he's seen,
even if you can't remember.
That's what I need you to do.
I need you to remember.
Did I kill Kevin?
No, you didn't.
He did.
You need to take control,
Sam.
Blow it up and cast
that punk-ass holy roller out!
What?
Oh, bollocks.
Hello, Sam.
Who are you?
His name is Gadreel,
the original chump.
Was a chump.
And now?
I'm going to be the one that
leads my kind back to heaven.
I'm going to be a hero.
But you, demon,
for all your chatter,
you will always
be a coward.
You should be running.
Aah!
Give up, boy.
You're not strong enough.
Take control, Sam!
Cast him out!
Get out of my --
you sure you want me
to go?
Maybe I'm the only thing
holding you together.
I leave, you might die.
I said get...
the hell...
Out!
Waiting for someone?
I am, and he's late.
Yes.
Let me guess.
Winchester trouble?
Sam! Cass?
I'm fine.
Thanks for asking.
Sam, are you okay?
Cass?
It's Abaddon.
Go. The back door.
I'll handle this.
Oh, 'cause you're
such a good guy?
Right now,
I'm the goodest guy you got.
This don't make us square.
I see you again --
I'm dead. Yes, I know.
I love you, too.
Pleasure doing business
with you boys, as always.
Hello, darling.
AbnerCrowley.
Bring me his head.
See, that's the thing
about demons.
They're only obedient
to a point.
Right.
Let's have a chat.
I'm not here to talk.
And I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to them,
the average demon,
because I feel their pain.
It must have been difficult,
with your loving king
so cruelly taken from you.
I imagine you felt
all at sea.
And then along came...
The brute.
She's strong...and a knight
and immortal --
at the moment.
So I'm not surprised that
some of my more idiotic subjects
bought her line.
But now?
Good news, fellas.
Daddy's home.
Hell doesn't want you,
Crowley.
It's mine.
Is it?
Not what I hear.
Not while I'm still kicking.
Well, then,
let's settle it.
You and me. Right here.
Winner takes the crown.
See, that's your problem,
love.
You think this is a fight.
It's not?
It's a campaign.
Hearts and minds,
that's what's important.
See, the demons
have a choice --
take orders from
the world's angriest ginger --
and that's
saying something --
or join my team,
where everyone gets
a say, a virgin,
and all the entrails
they can eat.
So, think on this, lads.
Spread the word --
vote Crowley.
You feel better?
A little, yeah.
It'll take time
to fully heal you.
We'll have to do it
in stages.
All right.
Let me hear it.
What you do want me to say --
that I'm pissed?
Okay. I am.
I'm pissed.
You lied to me.
Again.
I didn't have a choice.
I was ready to die, Dean!
I know.
But I wouldn't let you,
because that's not in me.
So, what?
You decide to trick me
into being possessed
by some...psycho angel?
He saved your life.
So what?
I was willing to die.
And now...
Kevin...
No. That is not on you.
Kevin's blood
is on my hands,
and that ain't ever
getting clean.
I'll burn for that.
I will.
But I'll find Gadreel.
And I will end
that son of a bitch.
But I'll do it alone.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Come on, man.
Can't you see? I'm...
I'm poison, Sam.
People get close to me,
they get killed...or worse.
You know,
I tell myself that I-I --
I help more people
than I hurt.
And I tell myself
that I'm --
I'm doing it all
for the right reasons,
and I -- I believe that.
But I can't -- I won't...
Drag anybody through the muck
with me. Not anymore.
Go.
I'm not gonna stop you.
But don't go thinking
that's the problem,
'cause it's not.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Just go.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man