Dead man's blood --
it's poison to vampires.
And most of the vampires lore
is crap.
The only way to kill them
is by beheading.
Hey, Dean.
Jody Mills.
Jody, are you sure you're, uh,
ready to jump back in the fray?
This wackadoo stuff
keeps coming.
More I know,
better armed I'll be.
Did you...Get --
Born again?
Yeah.
I don't make promises
I can't keep.
I enjoy church.
I mean, after my son
and my husband...
...I needed something
that made sense to me.
All right, Missy,
calm down!
Let me go!
Calm down!
Let me out!
Hey, Frank, someone
smashed the front window
over at Dawson's Hardware --
possible B&E.
Need you to check it out.
Yeah, copy that,
but the bullpen's empty,
and I got someone
in holding.
Sheriff's heading
to the station now.
They won't be alone long.
Roger that.
I'm heading out.
Hey, don't leave me.
Please.
Cody.
There you are, girl.
How did you find me?
Come on.
You don't really need
to ask that, do you?
A-are the others with you?
Everyone was off on a hunt when
I'd realized you'd run away.
Figured I'd do you
and them a favor
and come take care of this
before they even know
we're gone.
You can't get me in here.
Cop sure was in a hurry to
check out that "B&E" I faked.
Barely even saw me coming.
I keep telling you --
you can run and you can hide,
but we will always find you.
? Supernatural 9x19 ?
Alex Annie Alexis Ann
Original Air Date on April 22, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You boys are a sight.
Jody.
How's the shoulder?
Eh, only aches when it rains.
How you boys been?
Peachy.
Touch and go.
I know the feeling.
So, what you got for us?
Yeah, uh, that's a vamp,
all right.
I don't know, Sammy.
Looks like Jody might not need
our help anymore.
Oh, they grow up too fast.
Don't they?
Yeah,
joke all you want.
There's more
where this came from.
More?
My men brought in a runaway
last night.
There's no I.D. on her --
nothing on her, actually,
except for a bus ticket
out of Nebraska.
Total Jane Doe.
She won't even give me her name.
Girl's basically feral.
She's got zero manners,
didn't even thank me
for saving her.
Anyhow, this thing went to
plenty of trouble to get at her.
And to hear him tell it,
the "others" will want her
at least as bad as he did.
Sounds like a nest.
Yeah.
Nest?
I'm guessing that's not half
as cute and cozy as it sounds.
Oh, I'm afraid not.
Wilson and Fisher?
You two are FBI,
then I'm Taylor Swift.
That wasn't a dental I.D.
It was a fang check.
You're hunters.
And you're alive because, uh,
hunters trained the sheriff.
I think the first words
out of your mouth
should be a thank you.
So, who were you
to this vamp, anyway?
Hmm?
What's so special about you?
Is there a nest?
Sorry to interrupt.
We got a match on her DNA.
Annie Jones.
Reported abducted
outside of Kenosha in '06.
Raised by
an elderly grandparent.
No living kin.
You think the vamps are the ones
who took her?
Eight years is a long time for
a human to live with vampires
without getting killed
or turned.
You're the experts,
but there was something...
familiar about the way
this vamp talked to her.
Jody's right.
And she had scars on her neck,
feeding scars.
Uh...
They're layered,
as if they'd been built on
for years.
So she's a blood slave.
We've seen it before --
vampires keeping people as pets,
human feedbags.
Sometimes these slaves...
Stay loyal to their captors.
Yeah.
Right.
So...This girl's not talking
'cause she's got a case
of...what?
Vampiric Stockholm syndrome?
She's protecting the nest.
So, you feel a debt.
They gave you a home,
raised you.
Annie, we get it.
Loyalty is
a very powerful thing.
My name is Alex.
No, it's not.
Your name is Annie Jones.
Those vampires stole you.
They're monsters, Annie.
Alex.
And they didn't love you.
They loved your blood.
They fed on you.
I fed them.
My choice.
My brothers --
they brought me food
when I was hungry.
So when they struck out
on a hunt, I fed them.
They're my family.
Okay, you care about them,
but, Alex...
There's a reason
you decided to run away.
It was time...
to move on
and get out on my own.
And how do you think
that decision
is gonna sit with the rest
of the nest?
One of them
already pursued you.
You think when the rest of them
find out that you left
that they're just gonna shrug
and cut their losses?
You lived with them
for years.
They've tasted your blood.
They have your scent
down cold.
I mean, how far can you run
and for how long?
You didn't think this out,
did you?
What would happen,
who might get hurt --
your, uh, "brother," for one.
His name's Cody.
And she killed him.
Because of a choice
you made.
These are the consequences.
You got two options --
them or you.
And we can help you.
We can keep you safe.
But you have to help us.
Where's the nest?
I can't.
After what's happened...
...mama finds me,
she'll kill me.
Mills, you okay?
No wonder
she didn't thank me.
That creep was her brother.
I'm fine.
You know, mostly, I'm just --
I'm hung up on the name.
Alex and Annie --
they're so close already.
Why'd they change it?
Okay, so, we know
from her ticket
that Alex hopped a bus out
of O'Neill, Nebraska, right?
Mm-hmm.
Obviously, it'd be better
to go in with a firm location,
but the town
ain't that big.
There are no caves
or other natural hiding places.
All right,
so go in, canvass it cold.
Well, I worked together
a short list
of possible
nest locations.
Uh, there's an empty
fire station,
four or five
derelict homes.
Nothing we couldn't hit
in a day.
Okay.
You sure you're all right
to babysit by yourself?
Oh, well,
girl's a flight risk,
not exactly friendly,
but I think I can handle
babysitting detail.
The station's been made.
It might be worth heading upwind
for a while.
I mean, vamps are trackers.
Terrific.
Yeah.
Well, I've got an old
family cabin outside of town.
That'll work.
Okay.
Well, shouldn't raise
too many eyebrows,
me being gone for a day.
Maybe, but you, uh,
sure you don't want backup?
You want me to enlist my men
in a protection detail
against vampires?
Frank's still in the dark
about what hit him last night.
The guy still has nightmares
about the barn episode
of "Walking Dead""
They're good cops.
They're not ready for this.
Jody, in your
late-night reading,
did you ever come across
anything about Dead Man's blood?
Mnh-mnh.
It takes vamps down
like a horse tranq.
I would not say no
to some of that.
I mean,
not that I'll need it.
You guys are gonna get the jump
on these vamps
and be back here
before they even realize
their kin's missing, right?
Well, it's not my fault.
Well, Ralph didn't show up
for work today.
I had to pull a double shift.
I'll be home soon.
Connor, you scared the --
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
snuck up on you like that.
It's just, you haven't seen Alex
around, have you?
Uh, your sister.
No, I can't say I have. Sorry.
Huh.
So you didn't sell her
a bus ticket out of town?
Did I help
your shut-in kid sister
get away from her weird,
scary-ass squatter family?
Answer's still "no".
So you're saying
Ralph lied to us?
'Cause he said...that you
sold her a ticket...
...right before
we killed him.
You calling my family weird?
Oh, honey,
you have no idea.
What?
Too rustic for your taste?
Well, I have a lot
of great memories.
Used to come up here
all the time --
first as a kid with my parents
and then with my...
Anyhow, it's a lot nicer
than it looks from the outside.
F.Y.I. --
The woods around here --
really easy to get lost in if
you don't know your way around.
Me --
I know them
like the back of my hand.
I got it.
"Don't try running.
You won't get far".
You know this doesn't work,
right?
- On vampires?
- It's useless.
That's not why I have it.
Mm.
This your family?
Yes.
Where are they?
Oh. Dead.
You know, there are about
a thousand more polite ways
you could say that.
I'll give you a pass
on account of the whole
raised-by-monsters thing.
How'd they die?
Horribly.
You must be exhausted.
I know for a fact
you didn't sleep last night.
I'm fine.
It's no problem.
I can make up a bed.
I'm fine.
Suit yourself.
This place is a foreclosure,
right?
Yep.
It is, just like
the rest of them.
Well, somebody's
squatting here.
Blackout windows.
Hey!
Hey, you need
a hand with that?
Oh.
I guess not.
You go out with the family,
bring home a nice dinner.
How did you get stuck
doing the dishes?
We all have our roles
to play.
Yours being destroying
the evidence, yeah?
Nice job.
Ralph Hedges. Stacy Kepler.
Any reason
you targeted them?
Yeah. Hunger.
And, so, the family's what?
Out taking a nice
after-dinner stroll?
Oh, I'm sure they'll be back
real soon.
What I asked was...
Where are they?
Nice shiner.
Can I help you all
with something?
As a matter of fact...
I think you can.
You don't want to talk.
No skin off my back.
'Cause you see, a blood-sucking,
body-chipping vamp --
that's bad enough,
but vamps...
that kidnap kids...
Well, I'm going to enjoy
putting you down.
Of course.
Oh, I knew this
was about Alexis.
I warned mama
that girl would screw
everything up for us one day.
"Mama"?
As in one vamp
turned you all?
Well, all of us
but little sis.
She was, uh,
"too good to turn".
Mama couldn't bring herself to,
no matter what we said,
no matter how bad
Alexis got.
Bad?
Let me guess.
You never had a teenage sister.
Dragging her heels,
whining, near constant,
about everything,
but more and more
about the blood,
like she's somehow above it,
like she's better than us
'cause she don't feed on people.
She is better than you,
dumbass.
Her moping?
That teenage
crisis-of-conscience crap?
It's annoying as hell,
but it's just an act.
When the chips are down,
she'll always choose us
over humans.
I mean, how do you think
we stayed off your radar
all these years?
Pretty, young,
lost-looking thing like her?
Irresistible,
especially to the kind of man
few people would miss.
? I never read it in a book ?
? I never saw it on a show ?
? but I heard it in the alley
on a weird radio ?
? if you want a drink of water ?
? you got to get it
from a well ?
? if you want to get to heaven ?
? you got to raise
a little hell ?
I mean, sure, we hunt sometimes
for sport,
but it's a lot easier and a lot
safer to get delivery.
Come on, sweetie.
Aren't you gonna
give me a name?
It's...Ann.
Mm. Sweet Ann.
You got any idea
what I'm about to do to you?
Yeah. I do.
Nothing.
What the...
Is this a party?
She's your lure.
Best a vamp could ask for.
And you better believe
you don't get that good at it
unless you enjoy it.
In her own sweet way...
Girl's as bloodthirsty
as any vampire.
Jody.
Alex?
Alex!
Whoa!
Easy.
Sorry.
I made you a sandwich.
It's out there if you want it.
Sheriff.
My grandma?
I'm so sorry.
No, it's -- it's fine.
I figured -- it's been years,
and she was old.
You got it.
Thank you.
She's not answering.
I just ran the victims' names
through local P.D.
They both worked
at the O'Neill bus station.
So they killed them
for Alex's location.
Jody?
Dean, what's up?
Listen to me.
The vamps knew that Alex
went to Sioux Falls, okay?
They're probably
already there.
We're on our way
there next.
But there's something else.
There's something about Alex.
It can wait.
They're here.
What?
At the cabin. Now.
We're on our way.
Hurry.
She hung up.
We moving?
Yeah.
Meet you outside.
Alex?
Alex, come on.
We got to go.
Jody, help!
Alex?!
Alex!
Help me! Help!
Let me go!
Come on, let's go!
Move it!
Jody?
Hey, you okay?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where's Alex?
You tell us.
They came
and I tried to stop them.
And you got knocked out.
Well, happens
to the best of us.
Just lucky you're alive.
You think they went back
to the nest?
Of course they did.
Why wouldn't they?
Question is --
what are they gonna do
when they find
their brother dead?
So we go back now.
Okay. I'm coming.
Uh, Jody? Hey, hey.
Whoa.
Hold on. You're hurt.
I'm coming.
Jody, we can handle the nest
on our own.
I don't give a fig
about the nest.
That girl was under
my protection.
Okay, that "girl" can't be
trusted. She's a lure.
She's a-a honey trap.
She's been feeding people
to those vamps!
I don't care.
Whatever she did,
she did because they made her.
Oh, and that's a reason?
She's a kid!
Yeah, a kid who's been playing
vampire murder
since before
she was in braces.
Jody, he's right.
A-at best,
her loyalties are...
Screwed.
And how do you even know
she wants to be saved?
For the past eight years,
she has been baiting the hook
for an entire nest.
She's got more blood
on her hands
than most monsters we kill.
Are you saying
she's on your list?
No, we're not saying that.
Well, not yet.
Look, it sucks, okay?
It does.
But with hunting monsters
comes harsh truths.
This is a clean-up mission.
It's not a rescue.
What is this
even really about?
You barely know the girl.
I'm coming.
And if either one of you lays
so much as a hand on Alex...
You'll have to go through me.
Put up quite a struggle
with Connor.
Says you nearly
took his eye out.
Maybe that was just his excuse
for knocking you out.
You have any idea
the mess you made?
Hunters raided the place
while we were out,
tortured and killed Dale.
Our home's been made.
We're gonna have
to move again.
Mama, I-I never meant --
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh!
We will all find our way.
Things got screwy...
...but you're back now.
Why?
After everything,
I thought that you --
You thought what?
That I'd hurt you?
Kill you?
I would never hurt you.
Not my baby girl,
not my sweet Alex.
How could you even
think that?
Baby, why did you do it?
Why did you run from us?
I love you, mama.
I do. I just --
I couldn't
take it anymore.
The blood and the death,
the sounds of their screams.
I just...
I can't do it anymore.
And the way
I feel afterwards,
the guilt...
I'd rather die
than feel that way again.
It's my fault.
What?
All of it.
This is my fault.
I should've turned you
years ago.
Well, their truck's
in the driveway.
So we're walking
right into it.
Well,
we've faced worse odds.
Yeah.
Jody.
This is a raid,
so tread lightly,
stay close.
Priority is
clearing the nest.
Alex comes second.
You got it?
Got it.
It was so selfish.
I wanted to
watch you grow up.
I kept putting it off.
Don't you see?
These things
you've been feeling --
all the guilt and suffering --
those are human feelings.
It ain't too late.
I can take the pain away.
And then
we can stay together,
as a family.
Like none of this
ever happened.
Wouldn't you like that?
Drop it.
Alex, come on.
Come on, honey. We got to go.
Go away!
We got to go!
What did they do to you?
I'm sorry, Jody.
I made my choice.
She chose me.
No, no, no.
No. Unh-unh-unh-unh.
Hell of a sight
to come home to...
Brother lying dead
on the floor.
No idea it was a Winchester
that had done it.
So...Which one of you
was it?
Which one of you took off
my brother's head?!
Was it you?
Was it him?
Pretty fitting --
brother for a brother.
This place has been
a good home to us.
But since you two had
to come around and ruin it,
we're gonna have to to hit
the road and find a new one.
And when we hit the road...
...we like to pack a lunch.
Can't say you
didn't come prepared.
Alex.
Hey. Don't be
bothering my girl.
She's going through something,
a process.
What did you do to her?
Fed her my blood.
She's on her way now.
All that's left is to feed.
Please, mama.
Let her go.
I already drank from you.
Made an impression on my girl,
I see.
Baby, this is the human
half of you talking.
After the change, this human --
she ain't nothing to you.
Clearly, Sheriff,
you got issues,
some hole in your life
you're using my Alex to fill.
I would say go and get a family
of your own,
but, well...you know.
Wow. That's pretty rich
coming from the woman
who stole Alex to begin with.
I have fed her,
clothed her, loved her
going on nine years.
You think motherhood's
just about blood?
You don't know the first thing
about it.
Maybe not,
but I know what it isn't.
And it ain't about forcing her
to be like you
the second she becomes
inconvenient.
Don't you see
what she is trying to do?
This hunter cop bitch
is trying
to turn you against me
to save her own hide.
Don't believe a word
she says.
Ha!
Ow!
She ain't your mother.
Tapped this keg.
Get the short-hair one ready.
Time to finish this.
Alex!
Was that her name?
You named her
after someone.
Was it your daughter?
I couldn't figure out
why you changed her name.
I thought maybe you were ashamed
of your theft,
but you have no shame.
You said that I was using her
to fill a hole in my life,
and you're right.
I am.
You are, too.
Mama?
I guess it takes one
to know one.
That Alex...
She died a long time ago.
And it still hurts.
You still feel it, the loss,
the pain --
like a stone in your gut.
It hurts just a little bit less
whenever she's near.
You bitch.
Look at me.
Look at me, bitch!
Dean.
Yeah, I know.
You wouldn't have done
the same for me.
No. Jody.
Good news, lady cop.
Whoever you lost...
You're gonna see them again
real soon.
Alex?
How could you?
You were my girl.
I'm sorry, mama.
Don't watch this, sweetheart.
Nice work back there.
"Look at me, bitch"?
Well, hey, you got another
snappy one-liner, I'm all ears.
What I'm saying is --
it looked to me like
you were enjoying it.
Maybe too much.
And?
Well, sorry for not putting on
a hair shirt.
Killing things that need killing
is kind of our job.
Last I checked, taking pleasure
in that is not a crime.
Right, but...
How's things
back at the station?
Well,
they beat Frank up pretty bad,
but at least
they left him alive.
He kept apologizing for spilling
the beans about the cabin,
but I told him
that one's on me.
Well, speaking of apologies,
um...We owe you a big one.
We were wrong
about the girl.
No. You were right --
about me.
My judgment was clouded.
You know, working this case,
it brought...feelings back.
Feelings I've been trying
to bury for years,
you know,
buried it under work,
religion...even dating.
We know how that worked out.
But, you know, it was still
there, you know, underneath.
The grief.
Don't know what that means
for me,
just that I've been --
I've been fooling myself to
think that I could ignore it.
Anyway, thank you --
for coming out,
for curing Alex.
You don't need to thank us.
I mean, you're the one
who killed her sire,
got her blood.
Sure it'll work?
Well,
speaking from experience,
it'll be a rough
couple of days, but...
She should pull through.
You sure
you don't want us to stay?
I'm good.
After it's done,
you know what to do
with her?
Don't get up
on account of me.
I'm -- I'm hot.
Should I grab a --
I'll just be cold again
in a second.
It's part of the cure,
I guess.
You want something to eat?
No, I'll just throw it up.
But, uh, thank you.
I want you to know that...
When mama offered,
I just...
I couldn't
disappoint her again.
I had enough to be ashamed of
as it is.
Jody, I-I've done things.
You don't have to explain.
I know.
Whatever you want from me,
I'll give it.
If you want, I'm here.
But what you've been through
the last 48 alone,
losing your entire family,
everything you've ever known
or loved --
no one can understand that.
You can.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man