? Carry on, my wayward son ?
? there'll be peace
when you are done ?
? lay your weary head to rest ?
? don't you cry no more ?
I heard your prayer.
The angel lied to me.
He's not who he said he was.
His name. Gadreel.
Gadreel is working
for Metatron?
Metatron made Gadreel
kill Kevin?
I was the one who caused
all the angels to fall.
He took my Grace
for the spell.
That means you're human.
Long live the queen.
? Once I rose above
the noise and confusion ?
It's the bloody mark of Cain.
? just to get a glimpse
beyond this illusion ?
Without the mark,
the blade is useless.
? I was soaring ever higher ?
You're supposed
to lead the angels, Castiel.
? But I flew too high ?
I'm just trying
to get my people home.
? Though my eyes could see,
I still was a blind man ?
You are not the hero.
? Though my mind could think,
I still was a mad man ?
I'm the hero.
? I hear the voices
when I'm dreaming ?
You don't know
what it's like to be human!
? Carry on, my wayward son ?
I'm starting to think
the blade is doing
something to you.
? There'll be peace
when you are done ?
Have you told them about
your stolen Grace, Castiel?
? Lay your weary head to rest ?
Punish him.
I can't.
You just gave up
an entire army for one guy.
? Don't you cry no more ?
He's powering up
with the angel tablet.
Metatron's "secret portal""
from here on out,
I'm calling the shots. Capisce?
I'm not here to fight.
At least give me a chance.
Drop the blade, Dean.
Move.
Dean. Look at me.
Sam! Move!
Aah!
Let it go!
Let it go.
The hell if you think I'm riding
the pine on this one, guys.
Something is wrong
with you, Dean.
And until we figure out what,
this is where you have to stay.
And you two
are gonna do what?
Take on Metatron
yourselves?
That's smart.
Oh, no, wait. No, you --
you lost your Angel army.
And you -- now you're trying
to lock up the one guy
who has a shot at killing
the son of a bitch!
Hell of a plan, fellas!
Look, hey, guys.
Sam.
Sammy.
Yeah?
Dean...wasn't wrong.
My followers
have abandoned us.
Yeah, and Gadreel says
he can help us.
From where I sit,
that's more than an even trade.
? Supernatural 9x23 ?
Do You Believe in Miracles
Original Air Date on May 20, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
So, uh, Metatron.
Metatron.
God?
Just a second.
Is that
the new Angel handbook
you're working on,
or, uh...?
No, no,
this is a story, Neil,
a marvelous story,
full of love
and heartbreak
and...love.
Sort of like
"The Notebook."
Uh...
I love "The Notebook".
No.
Quick.
Which makes me look
more pathetic?
Why do you want to look
pathetic?
You've just reunited
all the angels
under the banner of heaven.
I mean, that's like...
Winning
a People's Choice Award?
Not quite the real deal,
now, is it?
All set?
Uh, yes, sir.
Uh, flip the switch...
Uh-huh.
...wait for the light,
and bingo.
And every angel in heaven
and on earth will hear me?
You and only you.
The signal blocks out
all other voices on angel radio.
Come on.
Hello?
This is Metatron.
More reverb.
Because I'm Lou Gehrig?
Sorry.
Don't do that.
I'd like to take a moment
to welcome you all back.
I want you to know
how moved I am
that you've accepted me
as your new God.
My heart, as they say, is full,
which is why I want to share
some wonderful news with you.
I'm going on a short trip.
Heaven's door
will be temporarily closed
pending my return,
but rest assured
all will be explained.
And it will be...Glorious.
Where are you going?
To tell
the rest of the story.
Please.
I'll leave you alone,
I swear.
We're not here to hurt you.
No. Your Grace.
Healing me
will only weaken you.
Did you hear him?
Metatron. Yes.
Where is he going?
What does he want?
I'm afraid...humanity.
Ohh...God!
I would have thought
you'd be more relaxed...
Having defeated Abaddon.
What can I say?
I wear my stress.
You know...
With so many demons having
rallied back to your side,
well, it's only natural that
they would look to their...King
for some...direction.
Love, if I wanted a soapy
massage from Dr. Phil,
I would have hit 3
on the speed dial, all right?
I'm sorry, sir.
Sir, I believe
you're being summoned.
It's a Winchester.
What's that smell?
What the hell's happening to me,
you son of a bitch?
Liquor before beer,
bad taco?
How should I know?
I can't turn it off!
Ever since I killed Abaddon,
it's -- it's like
this whole...other thing.
I get this high,
and I-I-I need to kill.
I mean, I really, really need
to kill.
And if I don't --
you yak your guts out.
It's the mark.
Meaning?
It wants you to kill.
The more you kill,
the better you feel.
The less you kill,
the less better you feel.
How much less better?
One would imagine
the least-best better.
So dead?
Well, Cain had the mark.
He didn't die.
Cain was a demon.
Your body's not strong enough
to contain the blade's power.
What if I got rid of it?
You want to get rid of it?
What I want is Metatron.
Go on.
But I have to get through
that door,
and I have to get
to the blade.
And you're gonna help me.
Oh, no.
What's that smell?
Sulfur.
Dean, pick up the phone.
Call me back.
I'm not kidding, all right?
Don't do this.
Not like this.
Are you sure
it was Crowley?
Who else would he summon?
I mean, he and Crowley
have been bromancing
over the Blade ever since
Dean got the mark.
The mark?
The mark of Cain.
So that's what Dean
cut me with -- the First Blade.
In a way,
that could be useful.
What?
Well, Metatron is
more powerful than ever,
but if Dean has the First Blade
and the mark,
that might give us
our best chance.
You're joking, right?
An hour ago, we were ready to
throw Dean into a padded cell,
and now you say
he's our best chance?
Hear him out, Sam.
Oh, right. Excuse me.
Sorry, guys.
Uh, sorry I'm a little less
than eager
to hear
that our best chance is --
is arming the warhead
and hoping it hits the mark.
This is not a bomb
we're talking about.
This is my brother.
And your brother would not be
in this alone.
We can help.
How?
I believe Metatron
has found a way
to tap into the Angel tablet,
harnessing its power to give him
powers equivalent to --
God, right?
I mean, that's what this is
all about, isn't it?
Metatron wants to be God.
Great, well, that basically
makes him unstoppable.
Not if we can break
the connection
between Metatron
and the tablet.
That would make him
just an ordinary Angel.
Where's the tablet?
Metatron's office.
In heaven?
I can get us to the door.
And then what?
I mean,
why would they let you in?
I-if Metatron's number two
shows up
with heaven's most wanted,
the gig is up.
Sam, we have to try.
Damn it, Al, I don't care what
you've got going on tonight.
He's your kid, too,
and I'm telling you
he's on drugs.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
She's dead, man!
She's dead.
I'm not so sure
about that.
What can I get
you fellas?
Coffee. Black.
Are you serious?
You take this girl's table,
her time,
you spread out like
an overgrown teenager,
and for what?
What's the tip on a single cup
of Joe? A nickel?
Double cheeseburger --
everything, heavy on the onions.
You got it.
So this is what you
and moose do, eh?
Crisscross the country,
searching for evil,
order your nitrates,
partake
of the local attraction.
Yep.
You never get tired
of the rat race?
Never get the urge
to just...bugger off
and howl at the moon?
Never ask yourself,
"is this it?
Is this all there is?"
I kicked human blood,
you know.
Oh, so you're
full-metal douche again.
Well, that's fantastic.
Would you like a stuffed bear?
Just trying to make
conversation.
How's hell, Crowley?
Hell's fine.
Hell's like
a Swiss watch.
Don't worry about hell.
Hell's complicated.
"Game of Thrones"
is complicated.
Shower sex --
that's complicated.
Hell ain't complicated.
Your problem ain't hell.
It's you.
Fair enough.
What's your problem, then?
My problem is Metatron.
Right now there's nothing.
There's no angel smitings,
no crazy acts of God,
no vermin, hail.
If Metatron's making his move
on earth,
he is taking
his sweet-ass time.
Never fear.
Cavalry's here.
And?
Apparently...
Your angel
has gone viral.
And that, America,
is perfection.
Yo, dude, that's your sister.
Oh, my God!
She's dead, man!
She's dead.
I'm not so sure
about that.
Is he ser--
is he freaking serious?!
Did you see that?!
Holy...
Tell me
you just got that.
Dude, what's your name?
Marv.
When was this taken?
A couple of hours ago.
Muncie, Indiana.
What did he whisper
in her ear?
Exactly.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're not gonna
eat your food?
Not hungry.
The door to heaven
is in a playground?
Guarded by two of Metatron's
most loyal.
I recruited them myself.
So, you said
you had a plan...
How we might convince them
to let us pass.
Wookiee.
Brother, I have no idea
what that means.
It's a reference to a very
popular film that --
never mind.
Asariel.
Asariel, Purah, make way.
The door's closed, Gadreel,
by orders of Metatron.
And who do you think gave
the order to capture Castiel?
Unless you think Metatron
isn't interested
in questioning the leader
of the rebellion?
The spell must be redrawn.
As quickly as possible, then.
I got this.
I guess one of us
doesn't need a demon
to help follow
a clue trail.
You're looking
for miracle lady, right?
Yeah, she's gone.
I had a nice chat with her,
though.
Sam, whatever kind of
intervention you think this is,
trust me, it ain't.
I'm not gonna
explain myself to you.
Yeah, I sort of got that.
I just thought
you might like to know
that while you two have been
playing, uh, odd couple,
your real friends,
like Cass,
like the angel you stabbed --
Gadreel --
they're out there right now
risking their asses
to help you win this fight.
What the hell
are you talking about?
A fight, I might add,
you made
that much more complicated
when you decided to stab
the one angel
who could actually get us
to Metatron.
You mean the angel that took you
for a joy ride?
The angel that slaughtered
Kevin? That angel?
Who you let in the front door
in the first place.
You tricked me, Dean.
And now I'm the one who wakes up
in the middle of the night
seeing my hands killing Kevin,
not you.
So, please, when you say
you don't want to explain
anything to me, don't.
I get it.
And I also get
that Metatron has to go.
And I know you're our best shot
to do that.
I'm gonna take my shot,
for better or worse.
I know.
No matter the consequences.
But if this is it,
we're gonna do it together.
You want to know what he
whispered to her, right,
in the video?
His next stop.
So what are we all
gollywagging on about?
Chop-chop.
Excuse me.
I'm not exactly
demon Minion number three here.
As the kids say,
I've got mad skills.
Look, I don't know
what you expected here, okay.
I don't really care,
but you wanted off
the hamster wheel.
Get off.
Well, I guess I've been
Winchestered.
I'd wish you boys good luck...
If I thought it would help.
Well done.
We've sent word
to Metatron.
He'll be back shortly.
You can wait inside.
Thank you, Ingrid.
What's going on?
No, no, no, no!
Not here!
Did you really think
your little ruse would work?
Please.
Please!
Welcome to heaven's jail,
Castiel.
I believe Gadreel
can give you the tour.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry,
but are you...Marv?
This is my friend George.
I hear
you perform miracles.
It is a burden I accept.
A little single malt?
George.
What?
How about we take care
of that diabetes?
Left you a little something
to celebrate with.
Thank you.
He's a fraud!
I'm afraid I don't know
what you mean, good sir.
How can one be a fraud
when one offers nothing?
A little love,
a little hope,
the occasional miracle --
nothing more.
You know exactly
what I mean...Metatron.
Excuse me?
His name is Metatron.
And much as he'd
like you to think...
He's not one of you.
He's an angel.
We both are.
An angel?
Okay.
Somebody's been drinking
out of George's canteen.
So you deny you're
the former scribe of God...
Sir.
...a petty, unliked,
unloved angel...
These people
don't want to hear --
...driven by the relentless pursuit of
power and nothing more...
This has really gone
too far.
...who's already brought the rest
of the angels under his iron thumb.
As I will you, brother,
if you don't --
Shut your mouth!
Angel? Scribe of God?
Please.
It's true.
What is true is what I can see
with my own two eyes.
You want to call him
pathetic, common?
Be my guest.
Who here isn't?
But who here has the gift
that this man has?
Do you know what he did?
And I'm afraid
if you'd seen what I've seen,
you'd think of him as nothing
more than an abomination.
Abomination?!
Try "Miracle Worker"!
Try "Messiah."
Better.
I am sorry
you don't believe me.
But I must do
what my mission demands.
I must protect you.
Yeah,
that's not gonna, uh...
They love me.
They really, really love me.
Anything?
Uh, yeah.
He's up there.
About a mile up the road.
There's
a homeless encampment.
The way the folks are talking,
he's got them convinced
he's some kind of new Jesus
or something.
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Listen, Sammy,
about, um,
you know,
the last couple of months...
I know.
So, before we find something
else to fight about...
...tell me...
Are you ready
to gut this bitch?
Ohh!
Sorry, little brother.
It's not your fight.
Okay, so you're telling me
that Metatron set you up,
arranged
those suicide bombers
to make himself
look like the victim.
Gadreel was
his second in command.
For what other reason
than the truth
would he turn against
Metatron?
So now I'm expected to trust
the word of an angel
who's only ever thought
of himself since the Garden,
and you?
You told us
not a single angel more
would die in this fight.
What do you think
I have been trying to do?
Trying?
By killing Metatron?
He is the reason
for all of our suffering.
Nothing you say matters.
Would you rather
I not try at all?
Not if you can't prove it.
So give us a chance.
Let us out, Hannah.
Please.
Can I help you?
Take it easy, Chief.
You're Dean Winchester.
Now,
how did you know that?
He said you were coming.
Well, here I am.
Where's Metatron?
Marv.
Sure.
In there...
praying
for our forgiveness.
Forgiveness for what?
Is he, now?
I sat in this hole
for thousands of years,
thinking of nothing
but redemption,
of reclaiming my good name.
I thought of nobody, no cause,
other than my own.
You've been redeemed,
my friend.
The only thing that matters
in the end is the mission --
protecting those
who would not
and cannot
protect themselves --
the humans.
None of us
is bigger than that.
And we will not let our fears,
our self-absorption
prevent us
from seeing it through.
Not anymore.
No. Of course not.
Move to the other side
of your cell, Castiel,
and keep your head down.
What are you doing?
When they say my name,
perhaps I won't just be the one
who let the serpent in.
Perhaps I will be known
as one of the many...
Gadreel.
...who gave heaven
a second chance.
Run, sister.
Gadreel.
Do you believe him now?
You can save
the humble-pie Jesus routine
for somebody
who gives a damn.
The problem with you, Dean,
is the cynicism.
Always with the cynicism.
But most people --
even the real belly crawlers
living in filth...
Or Brentwood...
They don't want
to be cynical.
They just want something
to believe in.
And that'd be you.
Why not me?
You've been working those people
outside for, what, a day?
They've already spilled blood
in your name.
You are nothing
but Bernie Madoff with wings.
So I'm a fake.
Do you have any idea
how much pan-cake makeup
and soft lighting it took
to get God
to work a rope line?
He hated it.
And, you know,
humans sense that.
So they prayed
harder and longer
and fought more wars
in his name.
And for what?!
So they could die
of malaria?
Leukemia?
And all the while,
blaming themselves!
"Oh, if only I'd been
more prayerful,
"God would have loved me!
God would have saved me!"
You know what?!
God didn't even know
their name!
But I do.
Because I've walked
among them.
And I can save them.
Sure, you can.
So long as your mug
is in every Bible
and "What would Metatron do?"
is on every bumper.
And?
What, are you blaming me
for giving them what they want,
giving them a brand
they can believe in?
I'm blaming you for Kevin!
I'm blaming you
for taking Cass' Grace.
Hell, I'm blaming you
for the cubs not winning
the world series
in the last
100 freaking years.
Whatever it is...
I'm blaming you.
The First Blade.
Nasty piece of work,
isn't she?
Okay,
let's say you win, Dean,
and I die.
What's the world
left with then, hmm?
A herd of panty-waisted angels
and you?
Half out of your mind
with lord knows what
pumping through those veins?
Yeah, you see,
the only thing you've said
that went into my ear
was that you die.
Ohh.
Fine. We'll fight.
I don't know what you expect
is gonna come of all this.
Unless...
That's why
you're stalling.
Because you know
nothing's gonna come of this
unless your pals succeed
upstairs.
Well,
here's a news flash --
humpty and dumpty
are starring
in their very own version
of "locked up abroad: Heaven"
right now.
Wow, that big blade
and that...
douchy tribal tat
sure gave you
some super juice.
Whoo!
Okay.
Aah!
Where is it?
Remove her.
Aah!
So, you took
Abaddon's scalp,
then you figured you'd take on
little old nebbishy me.
What could go wrong?
And you're powered by the bone
of a jackass,
and it is just awesome,
right?
Here's a tip --
next time, try to be powered
by the word of God.
Stay back.
Stay back!
Where's Metatron?!
No-o-o!
Hey. Hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Well played, Castiel.
Obviously,
you and Gadreel
managed to turn a few
dead enders against me.
Gadreel is dead.
Ah.
So Gadreel
bites the dust.
And the Angel tablet --
arguably the most powerful
instrument
in the history
of the universe --
is in pieces,
and for what again?
Oh, that's right --
to save Dean Winchester.
That was your goal,
right?
I mean, you draped yourself
in the flag of heaven,
but ultimately, it was all about
saving one human, right?
Well, guess what.
He's dead, too.
And your sitting in my chair.
Sammy, you got to get out
of here before he comes back.
Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
Shut up. Shut up.
Just save your energy,
all right?
Oh, man.
We'll stop the bleeding.
We'll -- we'll get you a doctor
or -- or I'll find a spell.
You're gonna be okay.
Listen to me.
It's better this way.
What?
The Mark.
It's making me into something
I don't want to be.
Don't worry about the Mark.
We'll figure out the Mark later.
Just hold on, okay?
Get you some help.
Aah!
You will never
get away with this.
Get away with what?
You told a silly story
to a group
of less-than-believers.
I'll clean up your mess
in an hour.
You give our brothers
and sisters
far too little credit.
They will soon learn that you
have been playing them.
And then?
They will do nothing
because they are
frightened little sheep
following my crook
wherever it leads.
And where I'm taking them,
back to our rightful place
atop this mountain
of human shame
and excrement --
when that happens,
trust me,
they're not gonna care
how they got there.
What happened with you
being okay with this?
I lied.
Ain't that a bitch?
You know,
while you could never
quite pull it together,
Castiel,
while you're sitting here
with Your Grace
slowly burning away
and your reputation
long extinguished?
No curiosity.
You didn't read enough.
You never learned
how to tell a good story.
But you did.
Sam. Hold up.
Hold up.
I got to say something
to you.
What?
I'm proud of us.
No, no. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, wake up, buddy.
Hey.
Dean.
Dean!
You're doing
the right thing --
letting him live.
It's what a leader
would do.
I'm no leader, Hannah.
I never was.
I just want to be an angel.
And Your Grace?
What will you do
about that?
You will die
if you don't replenish it.
? Come down off your throne ?
? and leave your body alone ?
? somebody must change ?
? you are the reason
I've been waiting so long ?
? somebody holds the key ?
? but I'm near the end ?
? And I just ain't got
the time ?
? and I'm wasted,
and I can't find my way home ?
Damn it, Crowley.
You got him into this mess.
You will get him out...
or so help me, God.
? Mm, mm, mm, mm ?
? but I can't find my way home ?
? mm, mm, mm ?
Your brother,
bless his soul,
is summoning me
as I speak.
Make a deal,
bring you back.
It's exactly what I was
talking about, isn't it?
It's all become so...
expected.
You have to believe me.
When I suggested
you take on the Mark of Cain,
I didn't know
this was going to happen.
Not really.
I mean, I might not have
told you the entire truth.
But I never lied.
I never lied, Dean.
That's important.
It's fundamental.
But...there is one story
about Cain
that I might have...
forgotten to tell you.
Apparently, he, too,
was willing to accept death,
rather than becoming the killer
the Mark wanted him to be.
So he took his own life
with the Blade.
He died.
Except,
as rumor has it,
the Mark
never quite let go.
You can understand
why I never spoke of this.
Why set hearts aflutter
at mere speculation?
It wasn't
until you summoned me...
No, it wasn't truly
until you left
that cheeseburger uneaten...
...that I began
to let myself believe.
Maybe miracles do come true.
Listen to me,
Dean Winchester,
what you're feeling right now --
it's not death.
It's life --
a new kind of life.
Open your eyes, Dean.
See what I see.
Feel what I feel.
And let's go take a howl
at that moon.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man