Henry Winchester.
That's
our grandfather.
You're Men of Letters,
correct?
Our father
taught us how to be hunters.
You're legacies.
Preceptors, beholders,
chroniclers of all that which
man does not understand.
Larry Ganem and Albert Magnus --
all deceased.
Albertus Magnus --
his was the alias we'd use
when going incognito.
Here's the deal --
you're gonna tell us
how to hack an angel,
and I'm gonna give you
some human blood.
Word is you're
jonesing for it.
The Knights of Hell
aren't exactly the dying kind.
But there is something
that can kill a knight.
The First Blade.
It's the bloody mark
of Cain.
Without the Mark,
the blade is useless.
The Mark can be transferred
to someone who's worthy.
But you have to know, with
the mark comes a great burden.
So, where is The Blade?
I threw it to the bottom
of the deepest ocean.
You can't search the
bottom of the ocean, but I can.
So, I'll find it and
bring it to its new owner.
Come on, Crowley.
Pick up!
Where the hell is he?
It's not like
he's got a social life.
Uh, are you
actually worried?
Too busy
inflicting pain to answer.
Leave a message.
Guy's got one job --
find the First Blade,
bring it back. How hard is that?
It's Crowley.
He's not exactly a team player.
Yeah, but his ass
is on the line, too.
He goes missing for weeks on end
without a peep?
Well, not one
that makes sense, anyway.
Listen to this.
Dean. Um...
Wait a second.
Did he...Drunk-dial you?
Come on.
Lola?
My King?
My apr?s-consummation
treat.
On it, sire.
Pantry's almost empty.
We'll need
another volunteer.
You should add that
to your "to do" list.
Ahh.
Lola, pet?
I do believe I'm ravenous.
...And a weakling.
No.
Oh, Richard,
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but -- but you --
you are our last hope.
If you don't
help us...
...Victor Laszlo
will die in Casablanca.
What of it?
I'm gonna die in Casablanca.
It's a good spot for it.
Now if you --
? Supernatural 9x16 ?
Blade Runners
Original Air Date on March 18, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
My name is Aldo.
My intel is
for Abaddon...
Minion.
And she appreciates
the work you've been doing.
At great peril.
But she is tied up
securing her place
as new leader
of the Kingdom.
She assures you that
all relevant information
can be conveyed to me.
So...Update?
The King
is off his game.
Except for sex,
pizza,
and human blood,
he has no interests.
He can't function
without me.
Well played.
I should mention
he keeps getting phone calls
from
those Winchesters.
They leave
voicemails for him.
Saying?
Mostly, they're rude.
One mentioned something
called the First Blade.
Interesting.
Follow how this develops
and report in.
Oh, I will.
And when I do,
I expect to report directly
to the next Queen of Hell.
Capiche?
All right, do it.
Daemon, esto subiecto
voluntati meae.
Winchesters.
I-is that, uh...?
Well,
that explains a lot.
Okay, uh, look...
Snooki --
can I call you
"Snooki"?
No.
It's Nicole now.
Okay, then.
Nicole...
We can do this
one of two ways.
The easy way --
you talk.
Or...
The easier way --
you still talk.
I vote for number two.
We just want some basic
information on Crowley. That's it.
Google him. Are we done?
Whoa! Not the face!
Are you crazy?
Listen, guys, what happens
in Hell stays in Hell.
I got nothin'.
But you do have a pretty sweet
deal with Crowley in charge.
If Abaddon wins,
you can kiss all that goodbye --
all the fancy cars,
the book deals.
Show biz can be tough.
I'm doing fine.
Thanks.
Oh. Well, good luck
landing your next gig
inside a Devil's Trap.
What do you
want to know?
Where is Crowley?
Last time I heard, he was somewhere
in the western Pacific.
Makes sense.
Really?
Floating around in the ocean while
his kingdom goes up in flames?
Meaning?
Hell's gettin' crazy.
Even the loyalists
want to sign on with Abaddon.
She's gonna make
her move.
Are we done?
I got a thing.
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus...
Seriously?
An exorcism?
We had a deal!
See ya, Snooks.
Honey, I'm home.
Hello, pumpkin.
Did you have
a nice day?
Lola did some shopping.
Looks like Lola did
a lot of shopping.
But not all of it's
for me.
Looky, looky.
I hope
it's a good vintage.
Well, you look like you
could use a little pick-me-up.
I just love
what it does for you.
Do you?
Unh!
You tried
to play me?
I play the tune!
Everyone else
dances to it.
Got it?
Yes!
I -- I'm your slave.
You're my rodent --
my little rodent
who went scurrying off
to Abaddon
to rat on me.
No! No.
Do you really think
some other lowlife
wouldn't sell you out?
I thought
you were a smart girl --
a girl I could've helped.
You're joking, right?
You help me?
Look at yourself.
You couldn't help anyone.
? But I'm
Hmm.
? Gonna try for the kingdom
? if I can, 'cause it makes
me feel like I'm a man ?
? when I put a spike
into my vein ?
? and I'll tell ya,
things aren't quite the same ?
? when I'm rushing on my run
? and I feel
just like Jesus' son ?
? and I guess
that I just don't know ?
Hey.
So...Cain said
the First Blade was tossed
in the deepest ocean,
right?
That's the Mariana Trench.
Maybe Crowley found it,
and it's a double-cross.
That doesn't make sense.
He wants me to power it up and
kill the ginger. He set it up.
Okay. A-assuming
he does show up with it,
Crowley is only useful to us
until we have the Blade.
Yeah. So?
So...
There's nothing stopping us
from using it on him, right?
Nothing at all.
Speak of the devil.
Did you find
the First Blade?
Not exactly.
Well, then, what,
exactly?
I'm in...
a jam of sorts.
Thought you might help.
Hello, boys.
And what
do you call this?
Refreshments?
What's in the bag, Crowley?
Nothing.
Really?
Maybe I can, uh...
What, are you knocking over
blood banks?
Come on, guys.
Look at you.
You're a mess.
You know, we were counting
on you. You let us down.
Your slimy followers were
counting on you to kill Abaddon,
and you let them down.
The man with all the mojo --
Captain Evil.
Oh, it's pathetic.
What is this?
An intervention?
You need to focus,
Crowley.
Get a grip!
What, you just gonna
let Hell go to Hell?
You don't know
what it's like to be human!
It's your DNA.
It's my addiction,
my cross, my burden!
All right,
take it easy.
I see the darkness of it now,
the Anthony Weiner of it.
It makes you needy.
I needed her.
Lola used me.
She reported everything I did
back to Abaddon.
Crowley...
Did you tell her
about the First Blade?
I don't know.
Things get a trifle blurry
when I'm medicated.
Great.
If he told Lola,
she definitely told Abaddon.
Which means that Abaddon's
in the hunt for this thing, too.
All right, you know what?
This crap ends now.
You're cut off.
Okay?
Kicking it.
Cold turkey.
Back in this fetid pit.
Could at least have added
some throw pillows.
Focus.
Okay.
You swept the Mariana Trench.
And...?
And the First Blade was not,
as hoped, in the Trench.
It had, in fact, been scooped up
by an unmanned sub,
from whom it was stolen
by a research assistant,
who reportedly sold it
to Portuguese smugglers who,
in turn, lost it to Moroccan
pirates in a poker game.
What?
Poor moose.
It's always a little tricky
keeping up, isn't it?
What are you doing?
I'm still a little tainted
by humanity.
Makes me sentimental.
Well, stop.
You and I both know we shared
a mo back in that church.
And on some level,
we are bonded.
Crowley,
the only reason you are alive
is that we need your help
to deal with Abaddon
'cause she is an even worse
pile of crap than you are.
And that is the extent
of my concern for you.
Got it?
Okay. What happened
after the pirates?
What is Crowley doing?
Stealing candy.
He is -- he's --
he's stealing candy.
You know, at least
when Cass was human,
he was an okay guy.
Should've known Crowley
would be a douche version.
Hey. Hey!
Cut it out, man!
Image!
You're the king of rotten.
Act like it.
You really think
this guy's gonna show up?
I mean,
this isn't exactly a place
where million-dollar deals
go down.
Look, word is,
this Andr? Develin character
bought the Blade
from the pirates,
and he's been
shopping it around.
That's all I know.
Hey, heads up.
Mr. Develin,
we spoke on the phone.
You said you represent
a serious collector
with an interest
in a private transaction.
Did he?
Oh. Well, what he meant
to say was,
is that we are with...
The FBI.
Then good evening.
Wait a second.
We just want some answers.
Read Sartre.
Jean-Paul Sartre.
I'm merely
a facilitator
between the buyer
and the seller -- a conduit.
So, unless
I'm being detained --
So, am I?
Being detained?
Not at the...moment.
No, but we've got
our eyes on you.
National Institute
of Antiquities.
Gin.
Again.
Brought you guys something
for your shift.
What's going on?
I don't have much
for you guys.
The guards
were good men.
They'd been here for years --
vetted, honest.
But...
But?
Security camera shows
a research assistant
caught them breaking into
vault number one.
That's her?
Gets weirder.
Like I said.
Anything special about the
particular vault they opened?
Vault number one is where
they keep rare, new acquisitions
while they're
being examined.
So what
was stolen?
That's the kicker --
nothing.
The curator,
Dr. McElroy,
said the vault's
been empty for weeks.
Excuse me.
Detective?
Okay, so, just connecting
the dots here --
the Blade was likely put
in there when it first got here.
The guards were
obviously demons, so...
What? When the vault
turned out to be empty,
they killed
their guard meat-suits
and smoked out?
And reported back to who?
Abaddon?
She's closing in.
So, the First Blade
was never on display?
No authenticated item
by that name
was ever
on these premises.
"Authenticated."
Dr. McElroy,
this Blade was stolen
and smuggled
into the U.S.
In violation of treaties
with several governments.
We can compel you
to speak.
"Compel"?
And what might that
involve?
All right, look, I did acquire
the so-called First Blade.
And carbon dating did peg it
to biblical times,
but the authentication
proved unreliable.
So it was in the vault.
I removed it myself.
The guards didn't know.
And where is it now?
Several weeks ago,
a confidential offer
was made to purchase it.
I was afraid we would never
authenticate the thing, so --
Who was the buyer?
Sorry.
The buyer insisted on
absolute secrecy.
Well...federal statutes
trump your little deal.
So...the buyer?
And you'll get it out of me
one way or another,
won't you, Agent?
Hmm.
I never did know
his real identity.
He called himself
"Magnus."
Don't ask me where he lives.
I have no idea.
But I do have
a meeting.
So, here is my number,
should you need anything else.
What?
Did you catch that?
"Magnus"?
"Albert Magnus"?
The name the Men of Letters used
when they want to be incognito?
Yeah, but we know that all of
the Men of Letters are dead.
Do we?
Turndown service?
I'd like a mint on my pillow.
What do you know about the Men
of Letters massacre of 1958?
We know Abaddon missed our
grandfather and Larry Ganem.
Was there anybody else?
Let me get this straight.
You keep me locked up
in this closet,
ignore my suffering,
and then come barging in here
and demand my help?
More or less, yeah.
Did I or did I not keep my end
of the bargain the other night?
Quite brilliantly, I might add.
We are partners!
And you owe me!
"Owe" you?
I wouldn't be in this mess
if it wasn't for you two.
You shoot me up.
You make me a junkie.
You keep me stashed away
for months
while my kingdom falls apart?!
What do you want?
It's not a very good scotch,
is it?
Okay, Crowley, we have gone
through the records
for the entire membership
in 1958.
Every single name matches
the men who were killed.
That would be the active
membership, correct?
Were you two dropped
on your heads a great deal?
Like I told you,
rumor has it
that a rogue member
was tossed out on his arse.
Does that
make him "active"?
Seriously, boys, how did you
ever function without me?
Well, hello,
Miss Ichigatsu.
"Infamati et obliterati."
"Dishonored
and forgotten."
Wow.
This guy was something.
Tough name.
Yeah, Cuthbert Sinclair.
I'd have just gone
with "Magnus."
Looks like he designed
most of the warding
that keeps the bunker safe.
Says here he was named
"Master of Spell",
right after he initiated.
I guess his work
got a little crazy.
The leadership called it
"eccentric" and "irresponsible""
good. So these are the projects
that he proposed
the last two years
he was here.
Look at this --
"rejected."
"Rejected." "Rejected""
So difficult --
brilliant, ahead of your time,
despised for it.
Trust me, I know.
"Formal separation
from Men of Letters --
April 1956."
He missed the massacre.
I never knew his name,
but I heard someone was out.
Did my damndest
to find him.
Thought he might be
my way inside this joint.
So where'd you look?
So this is where
your demons tracked him to?
Exact spot.
My boys
never could find him.
I'm sensing nothing,
so if he's here,
he's warded up
to the gills.
Well, he was
a genius at it, right?
Sure as hell ain't gonna be
found by a bunch of demons.
Oh, like he's gonna
open his heart to you lot,
because
you're such prizes?
Better --
we're legacies.
All right, if he's so bent
on hiding, maybe he's watching.
Give it a shot.
Cuthbert Sinclair --
uh, Magnus -- whatever.
We're Sam and Dean Winchester,
Henry Winchester's grandsons.
And Men of Letters,
ourselves.
We know what happened
back in the day.
We don't necessarily agree
with it.
We figured...
Maybe you want to tell
your side of the story.
Which way?
Bravo!
Well done.
Sorry about
all the theatricality.
I just wanted to see
what you two were made of.
So, what,
are we underground?
No.
No, my fortress is right where
you were standing.
But it's invisible.
Then you must be
Cuthbert Sinclair.
Ugh.
I haven't gone by that moniker
in, oh...57 years now.
Well, you're looking good
for a guy pushing...90?
Well, thanks, sport.
There's a spell
for damn near everything.
I am impressed, though.
You did exactly
what you should've done.
Though I am gonna miss
those two from my zoo.
Your zoo?
Oh, gentlemen,
you are in the midst
of the greatest collection
of supernatural rarities
and antiquities on the planet.
I'm sorry.
Did you say
that you were Men of Letters?
I thought that whole thing
died out after '58.
Well, we are --
we are legacies.
But actually, uh...
We're hunters.
Hunters?
Wow!
Hunters.
With the key
to the kingdom!
The boys must be spinning
in their graves.
Damn snobs.
Bunch of librarians,
if you ask me.
Although I was
always fond of Henry.
I was his mentor,
you know?
Yeah, till the squares
gave me the boot.
Yeah.
'Course, he came here
to visit me, in secret.
Called out to me,
same as you did.
Oh, yes.
Quite the wild hair,
your grandfather was.
Listen, Magnus, uh...
We got ourselves
a little situation.
Abaddon,
the last Knight of Hell,
is looking to up her pay grade
and take over the place.
Things never change,
do they?
I kept telling the boys
over and over again --
I would say,
"we could stop all this.
"We could rid the world
of monsters
once and for all
if we just put our minds to it",
but,
"oh, no," they said.
"No, no, no.
It's not our place.
We're here to study.
We're here to catalog""
yeah, yeah, no, we get it.
They're, uh...geeks.
Mm.
But she can be stopped.
But we need something
that we hear you have --
the First Blade.
Hmm. I see.
Interesting.
But if you'd really
done your homework,
you would know
that it's absolutely useless,
unless, of course,
you're possessing the Mark --
the Mark of Cain.
Oh, my.
How did you come by that?
Listen,
if Abaddon takes over,
the one thing she wants
more than anything
is to make hell on earth.
Not even you
can escape that.
And they say
all hunters are morons.
It's right there behind you,
gentlemen.
Listen, if you're serious
about taking action,
this --
this is taking action.
You loan us that Blade,
and we will stop the bitch.
Hmm.
Let me think about it.
All right,
I've thought about it.
Abi, ab oculis meis!
Magnus has Dean.
What did you do
with my brother?
Don't worry.
He's fine.
But I did what any
good collector would do --
I separated the ordinary
from the extraordinary.
I had the First Blade.
And now I have the Mark of Cain
to complete the set.
Yeah, well, problem is,
it's attached.
So how about
you loan me the Blade
and I take care
of business?
Dean, I am offering you
the moon here --
to be part of the greatest
collection of all time,
to be young forever.
Let me teach you
my secrets. Hmm?
Be my companion.
I have to be honest
with you,
it has gotten lonely here
over the years.
When you were
saying any of that,
did it feel
at all creepy?
Yeah.
I'm just gonna
grab the Blade and go.
One little design flaw
to the place --
no windows, no doors.
Well, in that case...
I'll just make my own.
Shen ti r?n shao!
Hey.
Aah!
Eh?
Tricky little spell,
that first one, right?
Chinese. Ah.
Cheap magician's trick on
that one -- picked your pocket.
Nice gun.
Welcome
to the collection, Dean.
You mind?
Who would have thunk it,
eh, moose --
you and me, same team,
in the trenches.
When this is over,
we can get matching tattoos.
Just to be clear, Crowley,
we are not
on the same anything.
By the way,
since the place is warded,
your powers are useless,
which means you are useless,
even more so than usual.
You're gonna need another set
of hands when you get in there,
unless you have
other volunteers in mind.
Thanks. Pass.
If memory serves me,
I'm the one
who helped your brother
find Cain so that we could
find the Blade,
so that Dean
could receive the Mark.
I'm the one who flushed
that lout Gadreel
out of your noggin.
So, lately, big boy, I've seen
mo playing time than you.
Crowley, will you please
shut the hell up?
Oh, you're a really sorry
piece of work. You know that?
Holed up in here,
doing nothing.
You bitch
about the Men of Letters.
You're way worse.
Should we fire it up?
What do you say?
Go to hell.
Oh, come on, Dean.
This is the object
of your quest.
Tell me
Henry Winchester's grandson
isn't curious
to see if it works.
Give me your hand.
Give me...your hand.
That's it.
Good.
Next time,
it'll be easier.
You'll get used to the feelings,
even welcome them.
Here's something.
Apparently,
he wanted to make the entire
Men of Letters bunker
invisible.
All physical points of entry
were to be eliminated,
"and entrance
would only be gained...
By spell."
Oh.
We're gonna need
some things.
You actually might turn out
to be useful, Crowley.
You'll come to understand,
Dean -- nothing can stop us.
Anything, anyone we want
to own or destroy is ours.
Well,
how about this, Magnus?
How about I take a knee?
Then what are you
gonna do?
Huh? You gonna kill me?
'Cause without this thing
on my arm,
that Blade's nothing
but a hunk of bone with teeth.
Hmm.
Well, I'm not asking you
for your cooperation.
I'm just taking it.
Mentem tuam
ac voluntatem adsumo.
Interesting effect, huh?
All thought,
all will just...
Drained out of you.
I do this enough,
you'll be ready
for whatever I have in mind.
I did good, eh, moose?
Everything on the list.
You're welcome.
Remember --
stay close, do what I say,
and shut the hell up.
I'm growing on you,
aren't I?
Ingressum domi
dona mihi.
Love what he's done
with the place.
Take me to my brother.
Sam! No!
Unh!
Shape-shifter.
You see? There are benefits
to keeping a zoo.
You know, I discarded you
far too quickly, Sam.
You're way more valuable
than I thought you were.
Why would I knock myself out
trying to sap your will?
I think Sam here will get you
to see things my way.
Magnus,
I swear to God...
What?
What are you gonna do?
What is he gonna do?
Huh?
Unh!
Yeah, look, look, Sam,
I'm not gonna kill you.
Of course not.
But I am gonna make you suffer
unimaginably, all right?
Dean?
Dean.
Hey, it's over.
He's dead.
Drop the Blade, Dean.
Dean!
Drop the Blade.
Brilliant, I must say.
I'm speaking
of myself, of course.
All you two managed
to do was get trussed up.
Combine a little derring-do
on my part,
a little dumb muscle
from squirrel,
a little bleeding from moose...
Happy ending.
Roll credits.
No, no!
Come on.
What the hell?
That's sulfur --
demons.
Abaddon's.
Well, she's just
one jump behind us.
Guess she couldn't find
Magnus' joint, either.
What about the trunk?
Safe.
Warding kept them out.
Demon mitts
all over my baby.
Oh, come on!
Oh, now
they're keying cars?!
What language is that?
It's Enochian.
The message isn't for you.
It's for me.
"Be afraid. Your Queen."
Abaddon's
getting more brazen.
She thinks
I'm losing my grip.
Dean.
Listen, you said
Crowley was only useful
till we got the Blade.
We got the Blade.
You know, boys,
I'm in debt to you.
You forced sobriety
on me,
and now I can see the situation
for what it is.
Dean, you are quite
the killing machine.
And it occurs to me
that Abaddon
is not the only name
on your list.
My name must be up there,
as well.
It's no good
to you without me.
Yes, but as long as I have it,
it's no good to you.
Now, this is the way
it's going to go --
I'll hang on
to old donkey teeth here
until such time
as you locate Abaddon.
Then you'll destroy her.
You're right, moose.
You can't trust me.
But, sadly,
I can't trust you, either.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man