First time I touched that Blade,
I knew
that I wouldn't be stopped,
and that I would
take down Abaddon,
and anything else
if I had to.
I'm glad the Blade gives you
strength or calm or whatever.
I got to say,
I'm starting to think
the Blade is doing
something else, too.
So, this war between angels
is really gonna happen, huh?
Not if I can find
a diplomatic option.
I know you truly believe
it's for the greater good.
Your mistaken trust in Metatron
will bring you down again.
The gates are sealed.
No one can get in.
Who said
anything about gates?
You don't need gates
when you have a private portal.
You can't hide
something like that.
You can if it moves around
from place to place,
if it's wherever
the boss wants it to be.
How's that stolen Grace
inside you working out?
It's fine.
No, it's not.
Dean.
Do I know you?
We go way back.
Tessa.
I know something
they don't know --
the ending.
How I get there
doesn't matter
as long as everybody
plays their part.
Yeah...
Give me one scoop of the no-fat,
non-dairy vanilla,
with a quarter teaspoon
of the sugar-free caramel,
and 10 -- not 9,
not 11 -- blueberries.
Got it?
Good.
What do you want, honey?
That.
Excuse me.
I-I know this is
none of my business, but --
You're right.
It's not. Go away.
Where are your parents?
I don't have parents.
I'm an Angel.
Yeah, you're a little Angel.
Does your mother know
you're sitting here,
eating diabetes?
You need to run.
What?
Now!
? Supernatural 9x22 ?
Stairway to Heaven
Original Air Date on May 13, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Nice reflexes.
Better hair.
What's wrong with you?
I could have shot you.
Why aren't you sleeping?
We got in like two hours ago.
Not tired.
And we got work to do,
so put on your dancing shoes,
and let's boogie.
All right.
What's up?
I called Cass.
He said there's something
going down in Missouri.
What kind of something?
He said he couldn't talk
about it over the phone.
Why?
Because he is a weird guy,
okay?
He's a weird, dorky,
little guy.
But he happens to have an army
of Angels behind him,
and, even though
I hate to say it,
if we're gonna take a shot
at Metatron,
they might be useful.
Well, do you think we need
the First Blade?
Why don't we just
leave that here?
We talked about this,
and we decided that --
No.
In all fairness,
we didn't decide.
You did.
Okay, I decided
that a hockey stick
that can kill anything
might come in handy,
so sue me.
How many times have we
been around this block?
Magic that powerful comes
at a price,
and right now we don't know
what that price is.
I'm fine.
I'm fan-friggin'-tastic.
And I'm glad, honestly.
I-I'm not saying
we bury the thing.
I'm saying we just save it
for when we really need it.
Crowley. Metatron.
The big boss fights.
You don't have to have it
with you all the time, right?
I mean, just leave it.
Please.
No problem.
Thank you.
Agents Spears
and Aguilera? FBI?
Uh-huh.
Your partner said
you'd be along.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Spears and Aguilera?
I've noticed your aliases
are usually the names
of popular musicians.
Wow.
Come here.
Take a look at this.
Look.
And the other bodies
are the same --
burnt-out husks.
Okay, so, what is this,
some sort of mass smiting?
I don't know
what this was.
Never seen
anything like it.
Six humans died here...
And one angel.
One of yours?
Was a good soldier.
This attack...
I knew he wanted a war,
but this...
This is abhorrent,
even for him.
Uh...just a second!
I gave you a second.
You are such an...
angel sometimes.
What do you want?
To talk about tonight.
We'll be fine.
No, we --
we're losing, Metatron.
Castiel's followers
outnumber us.
And while they haven't gone
on offense,
they have proven capable.
They stopped you
from killing him,
and me, for example.
I told you, we had our shot
with operation Lee Harvey,
and we took it.
I gave the orders.
You weren't to be harmed.
You had me followed.
Yeah, and you met
with the enemy...
In secret.
What is that old line
about sins and stones?
He spoke. He lied.
And I listened.
That's it.
But I serve heaven.
I serve you.
Good.
Don't forget it.
I mean, I-I don't get this
whole Cass lovefest, either.
I'm offering our people
a way home,
and still -- still,
they're choosing him over me.
I mean, sure, he's cute.
And Castiel has
this simple...charm.
He's like
a mentally deficient puppy.
But I'm lovable.
And funny.
I made God laugh --
twice!
You're the one who asked him
to lead an army.
Well, I didn't think
he'd be good at it.
Your meeting tonight --
Tyrus --
he controls
the largest independent faction
of angels left, and --
And I have to make
a good impression. I know.
I've got a plan.
It's not that, is it?
Shut up!
Commander.
Oh,
it's just creepy.
Sam, Dean,
this is Hannah.
The Winchesters --
I've heard so much about you.
What can I say?
Cass is a fan.
I'll start
to examine this evidence.
Y-- oh, um...
Sir, this morning,
Josiah wasn't at roll call.
Uh, roll call?
You hold, uh, roll call?
They like to hear me
say their names.
I know a couple of women
like that.
No one's seen Josiah
since Ezra was murdered.
We think that --
You think Josiah's the killer,
that he is the mole?
Well, who else?
We searched the grounds,
but he's vanished.
Not without wings.
He's an angel, but he's still got
to travel like he's a human,
which means walk, drive --
means he's gonna leave a trail.
All right.
What was
his vessel's name?
Sean Flynn from Omaha.
This the guy?
Yeah, that's him.
All right.
Looks like someone
just used his credit card
at a Gas-n-Sip
in Colorado.
And that's how we do things
in the pros.
Commander.
I have something.
This phone's memory chip
has a video time-stamped
just before the explosion.
And now the moment you've all
been waiting for.
- What?
- No!
I do this for Castiel!
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
I didn't --
I would never ask an angel
to sacrifice himself
to kill innocents.
I'm gonna be sick.
Cass, why would an angel blow up
a Colonel Scoop's in your name?
That's not
what he was doing.
Roll it back.
There.
That was an angel --
Esther.
She's one of Metatron's.
So, this was some kind of hit?
I don't know.
Stop saying
you don't know.
You can't think I would
allow something like this.
Cass, I know you try
to be a good guy, okay?
I do. You try.
But what you got here,
this is a a freakin' cult.
Dean. And the last time
you had this kind of juice,
you did kill humans and angels,
and you did nothing
but lie to me and Sam
about it the whole damn time!
Can we, uh -- can we take this
somewhere else, guys?
Will you
stow the baggage, Dean.
Look, we've got a case.
Let's work it.
Cass, did you know
the angel in that video?
Yes. His name was Oren.
He was a new recruit.
He worked in community outreach.
And what does that mean?
Some of my troops are stationed
at a local hospital.
They help where they can.
Minor miracles -- it's nothing
that would attention.
So, what was he doing in
that video, with the stabbing?
The Enochian runes
that were carved in his chest --
I...I think that they
were meant to focus energy.
When he stabbed himself,
it unleashed all that power.
So, what about the girl?
What happened to her?
If she was the target,
if the blast was focused on her,
then more likely than not,
she -- she was atomized.
So, what do we do now?
Well,
you don't do jack.
Me and Sam will head
to the hospital,
see if we can find somebody
who knew this...walking nuke.
Hold on. These are my people.
I can help.
Well,
that's sort of the problem.
I mean, the Manson girls aren't
gonna give us a straight answer
with Charlie in the room,
so just hang back.
So, I should just sit here?
Pretty much.
No.
If you don't want
my help,
then I will follow
Josiah's trail to Colorado.
I have to do something,
Dean.
All right, fine.
But Sam's coming with you.
What?
Because you don't trust me?
To help.
Abaddon is dead.
And then some.
Oh, no.
Okay. Um...
Ominous.
Does Dean
seem different to you?
Yeah.
Lately, he seems to be...
Amped up --
you know, on edge.
Effects of the mark?
What else?
He does seem angry.
I mean,
he's always a little angry,
but now it seems like...
More.
I think a part of him
actually believed
that I ordered those angels
to, you know...
Sam, you don't, do you?
No, man. Cass, listen.
You got a weird thing
going on back there.
Those other angels,
the way they stare at you,
I-it's like you're part
rock star, part L. Ron.
They've put
their faith in me.
And maybe
that's the problem.
I mean, people have been
doing messed up crap
in the name of faith --
in the name of God --
since forever.
Well...
I'm not trying to...
play God.
I'm just trying
to get my people home.
Yes!
Well done!
It's such
a simple game.
And boy, you got to love
the sound of those pins.
Beautiful --
a symphony of wood.
So,
you've heard our offer.
Yeah,
I sign on the dotted line,
and, well, my people,
they get a ticket upstairs.
What if
we don't want to go?
But it's home.
It's boring.
I mean, you -- there's nothing
like this in heaven.
I could whip you up
a bowling alley.
Eh, but it wouldn't...
I mean,
just smell that.
Mmm.
Old shoes and...
Alcoholism? I...
Authenticity.
So, wait.
You're turning me down
because of...bowling?
And I like being
an independent operator.
And I hear you're losing.
And I hate your face.
Well,
I could get a new face.
You'd still be you --
a nerd trying to be
one of the popular kids.
Mnh-mnh.
Okay.
Time for the hard sell.
Please.
You knife me, and all my guys
will go running to Castiel.
Even you're
not that stupid.
But tell you what,
huh?
You out-bowl me,
we'll talk?
Ma yeah,
I saw him, officer.
He filled up some old,
uh, woody station wagon.
Don't suppose you, uh, got
the license plate number?
No.
But he was headed to an address
in Pray, Montana.
How do you know that?
Guy asked
for directions.
Oh.
Uh, you want me
to write that down?
Yes.
Now. Please.
What do I call you?
My angelic name
is 18 syllables long.
Let's stick
with Flagstaff.
Copy.
So, you knew
this Oren guy?
We worked together
at the hospital.
He was a joy --
bright, full of life.
Yeah, I hear he had
a real explosive personality.
Do you think
this is a joke?
Do you see me laughing?
Is there anything else
you can tell me about him?
For example,
why he'd light his own fuse.
No.
Can I go?
I have lives to save.
Welcome to the club.
Something funny?
Not funny "ha ha."
But you
thinking you help people --
it's amusing.
I help people.
A clogged artery here,
a tumor there.
I do good in this world.
You -- you believe every problem
can be solved with a gun.
You play the hero,
but underneath the hype,
you're a killer with oceans
of blood on his hands.
I hate men like you.
Honey, there ain't
no other men like me.
Don't...please.
Oren. Friends?
Constantine...
And Tessa.
Tessa?
The reaper, Tessa?
You know her?
That looks like the car
the guy at the gas station
was talking about, right?
Maybe
Josiah's still around.
Sam, this place is...
radiating power.
I haven't felt anything
like this since...
since heaven.
We have to get in here.
All right.
Step aside.
I got this.
I don't got this.
Howdy, Tessa.
You're supposed to be working
at the hospital tonight,
but when I stopped by,
you were gone.
So was an ambulance.
Pro tip --
they all have GPS.
Good to know.
So, you're here. Why?
You just
love musical theater?
Only if it's "Fiddler."
We need to talk.
Can't. Sorta got a date.
Not happening.
Where's the other one?
Where's Constantine?
Better luck next time.
Thanks.
Metatron!
I do this for Castiel.
I checked all the windows
and doors. No luck.
What about you?
You find anything?
I think so.
It's Enochian.
I believe
it's some sort of riddle.
"Why is six afraid
of seven?"
Now, I assume it's
because seven is a prime number,
and prime numbers
can be intimidating.
It's because seven eight nine.
It's wordplay.
And the answer
is the key,
like the doors of Durin
in "Lord of the Rings."
Wait a second.
You know about
"The Lord of the Rings?"
I'm very
pop-culture savvy now.
Hey.
How is he?
He's, uh...
He's Cass.
What about you? How's it going?
Great.
Went out, got some air.
Met an old friend.
Say hi to Sam, Tessa.
Your brother's a psycho,
Sam.
Stop.
What's going on?
You first.
I know
he's the commander's friend,
and I know we're supposed
to pretend we like him,
but that ape put a knife
to my throat.
Tessa?
What are you doing?
You want to tell her?
Oh, God.
There's no God.
There's only Castiel.
Oh, and you're done.
You wounded her.
More like "defused,"
okay?
I cut up
that old testament graffiti
she carved into herself.
I figured
that would break the spell.
And now...
What will you do to her?
Guess.
Torture. Predictable.
We need to know if there
are other bombers out there.
No.
I won't allow it.
I know
what Tessa was planning.
It's horrible, but there's only
one person who can punish her.
Let me guess.
Yea big, trench coat,
sensible shoes?
You have to understand
that Castiel
is the only thing
holding us together.
A month ago,
half the angels in this place
were trying
to kill the other half.
Castiel has given us
a purpose.
But more than that, he has
given us a way to live in peace.
We have rules. Order.
If I let you take matters
into your own hands,
what's to stop one of them
from doing the same?
You can talk to her.
You should talk to her.
But leave
the Blade outside.
Are you asking
or telling?
We're not asking.
You sure you don't want
to go back, Cass?
Look, if Dean
is right about Tessa...
No,
I, uh...I do.
I just...
give me a second.
"Only the penitent man
shall pass"?
Cass, wait!
"The Last Crusade."
Okay.
Well, let's start
with an easy one.
Who are you working for?
Castiel.
Liar.
People like you,
they never understand.
Sacrifices
have to be made.
So you go after
one of the bad guys,
and if a few humans
get microwaved,
no big deal, right?
In the grand scheme,
they don't matter.
Oh, Tessa,
you are so wrong.
When Castiel came to me
and told me what I had to do,
he said I was chosen
because I was strong.
Others...
They couldn't handle this.
They're too weak.
Settle down!
Is -- do you think
she's telling the truth?
She thinks she is.
Sam.
We found it.
What?
It's the door to heaven.
Seriously?
What else would Metatron
go to such great lengths
to protect?
I can hear it.
It's calling to me,
Sam.
If we control this door,
we can take the fight
to Metatron.
We may not even need
to fight at all.
Cass, wait.
? Heaven
? I'm in heaven ?
What the hell?
? and my heart beats so
? that I can hardly speak
? and I seem to find
? the happiness I seek
"Welcome to your own personal
heaven, Castiel.
Good luck finding the real one."
? When we're out together ?
but...Why?
? Dancing cheek to cheek
It's Josiah.
He reeks of holy oil.
Yeah.
Looks like he got
"Home Alone"-ed.
So, all of this --
it was a a lie.
Supposed to be here...
Gate...
He told me...
After Ezra, he told me
that I should come to him.
Metatron told me
that I could go home.
I just wanted to go home.
Here. Let me --
No!
I would rather die than owe
my life to you, Castiel.
You play at being noble.
You play
at being one of us.
But I look
into your eyes...
And I don't see
an angel staring back at me.
Where's your friend?
Just you and me now.
Let's talk about us.
I mean,
we got history, yeah?
Sure.
I still remember
our meet-cute.
You were dying.
Good times.
Here's the deal.
I like you, Tess, okay?
For an angel.
But tell me,
why are you doing this?
Castiel.
No, forget Cass.
Why are you doing this?
What would make a person want
to pop their top, huh?
I mean, look,
I've been in bad shape.
I have. But I have never been
that damn low.
I guess I just
can't take the screaming.
Who's screaming?
All of them.
The lost souls.
The ones that can't get
into heaven
now that it's been
boarded up.
I hear them.
They are so confused.
They're in so much pain.
All I want to do
is help them.
It's what I do.
It's my job.
But I can't.
So I suffered...
Until death,
nothingness.
Suddenly,
it didn't seem so bad.
It seemed quiet.
So, why don't you
just jam an angel blade
in your throat
and call it a day?
I thought about it...
But I was too weak...
Till Castiel gave me
a reason to die.
Yeah.
See, that just doesn't sound
like the Cass I know.
But doesn't it, though?
And the Cass you know,
would he raise
an army of angels
without telling you?
'Cause this Cass did.
I'll tell you a secret.
There's more out there...
Like me.
So many more.
You got names?
That would
ruin all the fun.
No.
No, see...
...the fun's just
getting started.
Dean,
what have you done?
What I had to.
Welcome to the club.
Thank you.
He put up a fight.
Get out.
You should have seen
the other 10 guys.
They said
you killed Tessa?
Not so much.
She knifed herself.
Yeah? Why would she
do that, Dean?
I don't know, Sam.
She was saying
all kinds of crap.
So that's why you brought out
the First Blade?
They told you
about that, huh?
We had a deal.
Yeah, well, it was a stupid deal.
Really?
'Cause if you'd stuck to it,
Tessa would still be alive.
Without her,
we ain't got jack.
Yeah, you think
I don't know that?
You think I wanted
that to happen?
I don't know, Dean.
Did you?
All right, that's enough.
Stop it.
Commander,
I'm sorry, but...
You have a call...
From Metatron.
Castiel.
Bet you're not happy to see me.
Is anyone ever?
Dean, always with the B-grade
'80s-action-movie wit.
What do you want,
Metatron?
Just to tell ass-tiel, there,
that I'm still alive.
His bomber failed.
My bomber?
The crazy guy.
Big knife. Kablooey.
I'm fine, thanks for asking,
but Gadreel is wounded,
- and Tyrus...
- R.I.P.
His followers are not
your biggest fans, by the way.
They've all come over
to my team.
I didn't send anyone
to kill you.
Oh, stop lying, Castiel.
Who are you to lecture me
on lying?
Your deception led
to the fall.
I did what I had to do.
I have always done
what I have to do,
for God and for the angels.
Sure. Yeah, you're mother Teresa
with neck beard.
What I did was
neither good nor bad.
It was necessary --
a small hardship to...
Make us all stronger,
to make us a family again.
Yeah, except for the angels
you had Gadreel kill.
Okay, yes.
Maybe I got
a little carried away at first,
but those days are over.
A near-death experience
makes you re-evaluate.
So, one time only,
I'm offering amnesty.
Every angel,
no matter what their sin,
may join me
and return to heaven.
I will be their God,
and they can be
my heavenly host.
Why would we follow you?
Well, look around.
You've seen earth.
You've had a taste of free will.
I got to ask you --
do you like it?
I mean, the way you've flocked
off to follow Castiel
tells me you need
to follow someone.
It's in your DNA.
But Cass --
he's not what you think he is.
He sends angels out to die.
Have you told them about
your stolen Grace, Castiel?
How it's fading away,
and when it burns out,
so will you?
So...
No, then.
I'm not the best,
but I'm the best you've got.
You want to stay
with Castiel, fine,
but he's playing you,
because at the end of the day,
the only thing he cares about
is himself
and the Hardy boys there.
You've got a choice to make.
Make the right one.
He's lying.
About the Grace?
It's complicated.
So he wasn't lying.
He was about
everything else. He...
You believe me,
don't you?
I want to believe you,
but I...
We need proof.
Name it.
Punish him.
What?
He murdered Tessa.
He broke our rules.
Y'all can all go to hell.
Dean.
Hey, wait a sec--
You gave us order, Castiel,
and we gave you our trust.
Don't lose it
over one man.
This is justice.
No. I can't.
Goodbye, Castiel.
You're right.
There is no other side.
Well, welcome aboard.
Well...
The first of Castiel's flock
has come around.
The rest will follow.
You should have told me
what our elite unit was for.
Why? It was none
of your business.
Tessa, Constantine --
I recruited them,
and you...
Brainwashed them
into blowing themselves up.
So?
Well, that's an old
writer's trick --
flipping the script.
You start by building up
a seemingly unbeatable enemy,
like the death star,
or a rival angel
with a bigger army.
That way,
I look like the underdog.
But then, oh, no!
The competition
gets greedy.
He starts pushing things
too much...
With the help
of my combustible double agents.
And then,
after a rousing speech,
his true weakness
is revealed.
He's in love
with humanity.
And now...
I'm inevitable.
What about Josiah?
Mm.
He was a loose end.
I -- I told him
where the gate was...
Before we moved it.
I just wish Cass had walked
into one of those traps.
Anyway, point is --
while everyone else
is playing checkers,
I'm playing monopoly,
and I always build a hotel
on Boardwalk.
And I always win.
So, Dean, uh...
Are we gonna talk about this,
or what?
About what?
Yeah, I lied,
but you were being an infant.
Wow.
Even for you,
that apology sucked.
Oh,
I'm not apologizing.
I'm telling you
how it's gonna be.
Dean, that Blade --
That Blade's the only thing
that can kill Metatron,
and I am the only one
who can use it...
...so from here on out,
I'm calling the shots.
Capisce?
Look, until I jam that Blade
through that douchebag's heart,
we are not a team.
This is a dictatorship.
Now, you don't have to like it,
but that's how it's gonna be.
So, batteries...
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
How long you got?
Long enough
to destroy Metatron, I hope.
But without an army...
Well, hey,
you still got us.
Dean.
Those bombers --
you don't really think that I --
Cass, you just gave up
an entire army for one guy.
No, there's no way
that you blew those people away.
You really believe
we three will be enough?
We always have been.
Guys!
I'm not here to fight.
I thought
about what you said.
You're right.
Metatron, he's...
...something
needs to be done.
And we should
trust you why?
Because I can give him
to you.
I know where Metatron is.
I know everything.
I know the bombers.
They...
They were his agents,
not yours.
You don't trust me, fine.
I understand. I've...
...Made mistakes.
But haven't you?
Haven't we all?
At least give me a chance.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man