Telling you, Will,
you got a real winner here.
She's just gonna love it.
Stacy, box her up.
Oh. Just the box.
I'm sure it's prettier
than the paper.
One tiny rock.
So many other cool things I
could have bought for myself.
Sam, Stacy, it's been a pleasure
being ripped off by you.
Such a nice boy.
Too bad he's a handicap.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
You all right, man?
Take it easy, man!
It's okay. It's okay.
? House 8x14 ?
Love Is Blind
Original air date on February 27, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
?
Kid's a blind diabetic.
He's hyperglycemic
hyperosmolar.
Which is what we thought until
his blood tests showed
a controlled sugar level
and no ketones.
It could be caused by
drug abuse.
His tox screens were clean.
You lying sack of crap.
I have them right
in front of me.
Not you.
This time.
My former BFF.
He's S-M-I-T-B-A-W-A.
Stabbing me in
the back as we speak.
Where exactly are you?
If anyone should happen to ask,
I'm in an out-of-state
medical conference
until further notice.
Why would any--
and...Don't really care.
Auditory hallucinations
and disorientation could be
signs of schizophrenia.
They did a psych consult.
Mental status is normal.
Seizure,
noise-induced epilepsy--
the sound of rush hour traffic
could have set it off.
Run an E.E.G.
Blast his brain with harmonics
to find out.
Also, if anyone should further
happen to ask,
I spent the whole last year
in Africa
with Doctors Without
Boundaries.
Who are you hiding from?
Evil.
Where's House?
Uh, he's at an out-of-state
medical conference.
In Baltimore.
I think.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Blythe, his mother.
Do you want me to pick up
the braille writer
and laptop
from your apartment?
I don't plan on being here
that long.
I didn't eat lunch yesterday.
I probably just fainted.
Or had an epileptic seizure.
Which is
only one possibility.
I'm Doctor Chase.
Uh, we'd like to discuss your
case with you privately.
I'm his girlfriend.
Is it all right
if I stay for this?
Melissa can stay.
And I've never had a seizure
before in my life.
They can be mild.
Like a loss of concentration
or a muscle tremor.
A lot of times a family member
notices before the patient does.
I'm Doctor Park, by the way.
I'm 5'2", Asian,
and I'm totally cool with it
if you wanna feel my face.
Blind people only
do that in movies.
But you sound nice,
so if you want me to...
Her point was,
you may not have realized
you were having a seizure, that
maybe your girlfriend has?
No.
But I--I haven't seen him
for the last five months.
We were on a break.
Like Rachel
and Ross on Friends.
Never seen the show myself,
but I hear it's good.
That joke usually kills
my blind friends.
Will, this is serious.
No, it's not.
Since I don't have epilepsy.
I have to pay attention
to every signal
my body sends or receives.
Or I end up taking a dirt nap.
You don't think I'd know
if I was having seizures?
It's probably just
low blood sugar.
If that's true,
then you shouldn't have
a problem passing our test.
How is he, James, really?
He's better than I've seen him
in a long time.
Is he happy?
Uh...
It's okay.
He's always been
a complicated child.
Were you in
the hospital recently?
Oh, nothing serious.
I just had a few moles
removed yesterday
and forgot I even had it on.
Look, if Greg happens to get
back early from the conference,
I'm staying at a hotel in town
for the next three days.
I would like him to call me.
I will pass it on.
Thank you.
Um, do you think that
they would mind
if I got a refill
for the road?
Not at all.
Good.
Not seeing
any seizure activity
in response
to low frequency sounds.
I'm starting him
on mid-range.
Have you seen his girlfriend?
Extremely hot.
Blind people can't have
attractive girlfriends?
Not my point.
He actually convinced her
to go for
the whole relationship
break thing.
How do you know
it wasn't her idea?
Because she's back with him.
Women suggest a break
when they wanna break up.
Men do it because
they wanna have sex
with other women
before they settle down.
They're a little young to get
married, don't you think?
I was their age when I did.
I see your point.
He's seizing.
Sound frequency's at 300 hertz.
It's not a seizure.
He's not spiking on his E.E.G.
He's not moving air.
I I think
he's choking on something.
Blood.
I don't see any blockage.
Help me move him.
Just relax and breathe.
What--what are these?
Three teeth detached
from his jawbone
and lodged in his throat.
He almost choked to death
on them.
Environmental?
Could be heavy metal
poisoning
or radiation exposure.
Then he wouldn't
be the only one.
He's an accountant
who works
on the same floor
with 50 other people.
Maybe his girlfriend
poisoned him.
House usually thinks
that's a good guess.
And she's gotta be pissed off
and have low self-esteem.
Why else would she
give him a free pass to pork
other women?
Because he's handicapped.
Women feel sorry for us.
This cane is tail bait.
Where are you now?
Expect an actual answer
this time?
Hi, guys.
Was wondering if House's
mother left yet.
He won't let me go to a hos--
It's not environmental,
it's periodontitis.
An oral infection doesn't
explain his disorientation
and auditory hallucinations.
They're laughing
because they know
diabetes exacerbates
the condition.
It could progress
to a systemic disease.
The bacteria spread
and affect other organs.
Like his brain.
Start him on broad spectrum
antibiotics
and book him an appointment
with a periodontist.
He has fake children now,
too?
You think I'm not good enough
for your mother.
Not in front of the kids,
Honey.
Hey, add a couple of flies,
toss in a dead goat or two,
we might have a winner.
She gone?
Yeah.
We really need to talk.
Okay.
Crayons down.
Line up if you wanna get paid.
It's the only time I ever
successfully lie to my mom;
is through the elaborate
preparations
and props.
Hey, hey, hey.
I said no Transformers,
Slick.
Stay here until
the coast is clear.
Fine.
But you sleep on couch
tonight.
You sleeping with her now?
Just in case an I.N.S. guy
comes in through the window.
Oh.
Yeah,
she didn't buy it either.
You need to talk
to your mother.
When I'm ready.
Still need to get
a fake passport,
doctored photos,
maybe a case of Aids.
She's sick, House.
Did she say that?
She was wearing a hospital
admission bracelet
and carrying around a book on
dealing with terminal cancer.
I'm sorry.
She's staying at the Grand
for the next three days.
The antibiotics will stop
the infection
from spreading further.
And I'll spare you
the lecture you'll get
from the periodontist
tomorrow,
but you need to practice
better oral hygiene.
So are you guys saying this is
happening because, what,
- I didn't floss enough?
-  Probably didn't help,
but diabetics are prone
to this type of infection.
Half the time,
he doesn't even bother
getting undressed
before he goes to bed.
Can only imagine how many times
you've skipped
brushing your teeth since we--
sorry.
I don't mean to lecture you,
babe.
Well, I guess you're right.
Look, you haven't eaten
anything all day.
Why don't you go grab a bite?
I'll be fine.
All right, well, I'll see you
in an hour, okay?
Not if I see you first.
I was wondering if I could
ask you guys for a favor.
I really need my laptop
and braille writer,
and I can't ask Melissa
to get them for me.
Why not?
Because...
I want you to put this
someplace safe.
It's beautiful.
People always say
diamonds are beautiful.
But to me they just feel cold.
They have really sharp edges.
I guess convincing her to take
a break was a good thing.
Well, the break was her idea.
Melissa's the only girl
I've ever dated.
She wanted me to be sure
before we...
took the next step.
Wow.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
We're here.
We might as well
search the place
in case we're wrong about
periodontitis.
What are you doing?
We're here.
Might as well eat.
You're stealing food
from a blind man?
We're doing him a favor.
He owes me.
I take it from your
low self-esteem theory
you have some experience
with relationship breaks?
What happened?
He talked me
in it, then...
Slept with three
of my friends.
Then dumped my ass.
College boyfriend.
Thought he was the love
of my life.
Then why agree to a break?
My self-esteem wasn't
as high back then.
No one's is.
Oh!
Sugar free!
Ugh. Disgusting.
I'll check the bathroom.
You keep checking the snacks,
Greg.
Sorry I didn't call first.
I just flew back
from my conference.
Um, this--this
really isn't, uh--
I need your medical records
and the name of your
primary physician.
Well,
you remember Mr. Bell.
Well, if I didn't,
I will now.
You're not dying?
I, uh...I may have
mislead James
by letting him see
a book on cancer.
We did, however,
have some expectations
that you might call first.
Yeah.
This isn't how I envisioned
you finding out.
Mr. Bell and I, we're...
Having sex, got it.
Getting married.
Also.
We wanted you to be
the first to know.
I need 10 milligrams
of benzodiazepine.
Help me hold him down.
I'm putting epilepsy back
on the table.
And I'm taking it off
because
it doesn't explain
losing his teeth.
The kid's diabetic.
The periodontitis could be real
but completely unrelated.
Coincidence.
Buying that, House?
Until I hear something
that takes my mind off
the Jurassic schlong that I was
traumatized by this afternoon.
I know what's wrong
with the patient.
Illegal drugs.
Some kind of acid.
His tox screens
were clean.
His apartment wasn't.
We didn't find any drugs.
Then why am I completely
tripping balls right now?
I'm seriously freaking out
here, guys.
Can't you tell?
You pretty much look the same
as you always do.
Take your glasses off.
Pupils dilated...
Pulse elevated.
Hallucinating?
I think so, because...
He's a rabbit.
Oh, I get it.
Because she's his wife.
They flirt a lot.
I've seen things.
Mm, Taub--
Taub is either...
A tooth fairy or...
Rainbow Brite.
And you...
You're just House.
She ate ice cream
and Gummi Bears
at the patient's apartment.
One of 'em must have
been dosed with it.
Go back and find the drugs.
You two,
find out where
he bought them,
and then MRI his brain.
Check for infections,
masses, and plaques.
Am I gonna die?
We'll get back to you
on that.
I've been blind since birth.
I thought maybe
if I tried LSD,
I might, you know...
Colors...a shape.
I just--
I just wanted
to see something.
How many times?
Maybe five or six.
We need to know
where you bought it
so we can find out
what was in it.
My girlfriend gave it to me.
I'll find her.
No, don't.
It--it wasn't Melissa.
I met someone else.
When were you planning
on telling her that,
before or after
you ask her to marry you?
The ring isn't for her.
We were on a break.
She wanted me to see
what else was out there,
and I did.
I was gonna tell her
the other night,
but I ended up here
instead.
We just need to talk to the one
who supplied the drugs.
She's on vacation
with her parents.
This is her cell.
I don't want her to know
I'm in the hospital.
She'll only freak out.
That's very considerate
of you.
You think this is easy
for me.
I know I have to
tell Melissa.
Well, what's stopping you?
She's still one
of my best friends.
And I don't want to be
alone in here.
Have you seen
your mother yet?
She's not dying.
She was having sex
with my father.
Ignore her.
She's on acid.
Your father's dead,
House.
Not the dead dad,
the biological dad.
The one I pointed out to you
at fake father's funeral.
Huh.
Are you sure?
Your only evidence is
that birthmark you saw
when you were 12.
Well, now I've seen two.
Good news is I won't
technically be a bastard
much longer.
We're gonna be one big
crappy family.
Well, that's--
that's great news.
Your mother won't
be alone anymore,
and you can finally
get to know the guy.
Yes, that is one option.
Are you saying you're
not even curious?
You want to know
what I think?
I think you know the answer
to that question.
You avoid your mother
because she's the one person
whose opinion
you actually care about.
If that was true, you'd have
every reason to shut up.
I avoid my mother
because she's boring.
That's why you've been
so open and honest
about prison and marrying
a complete stranger.
Even if I care
what she thinks,
why would I care
what some sperm donor does?
You read the guy's book
about three times.
Years ago.
It took three times because
it was so badly written.
Oh, I get it.
The second birthmark
was on his penis, right?
He's a dick.
You've been working
for House for months
and just now realized
that disabled people
can also be dicks?
What he's doing now
to that girl isn't fair.
The break was her idea.
And now she thinks
they're back together.
He's a scared, sick, blind kid
who doesn't want to be alone.
You really don't get that?
I do, but...
What is it?
Not good news for him...
Or Park.
Where's Park?
Wilson's babysitting her.
Talking about the fact
that she could have
permanent brain damage might
bum her trip out a little bit.
A dark spot doesn't necessarily
equal brain damage.
It could be
a congenital malformation
connected with his blindness
or a tumor.
A clot.
Exactly.
We need to do another scan,
but inject dye and figure out--
I said "a clot,"
not "or a clot."
It's a clot.
Cerebral venous
sinus thrombosis.
Good news for Park.
I've never seen one
present this large before.
It fits.
When it was smaller,
it caused his initial
disorientation
and hallucinations.
As it grew larger,
the seizures.
If left untreated, it leads
to cerebral edema and death.
But what causes that
and tooth loss?
Any hyper-coagulable state.
Lupus?
I counter your lupus
with Behcet's syndrome.
No, he doesn't have
any of the earlier symptoms--
color blindness,
abnormal visual fields or--
we've been ignoring his eyes
because he's blind.
Well, if he wasn't before,
he would be by now.
Confirm with an eye exam,
start treatment with heparin
for the clot.
Interferon and steroids
for the Behcet's.
No, no!
Give me back my teeth!
Park, listen. Park--
You're a tooth thief!
No, no, no.
Stop it, stop it!
Ki-ki-ki!
Back on the couch.
What are you doing
to this poor girl?
It's not what it looks like.
She--oh!
She's tripping on acid.
Good lord, man,
that's no way
to treat a bad trip.
Put the chair down.
You'll end up hurting
the poor wee thing.
There you are.
Hello, darlin'.
I'm Thomas,
and this beautiful
creature here is Blythe.
Is there anything
we can do to help you?
That rabbit
stole my teeth.
Of course he did, but I'll
tell you what he's done.
He's put them back again,
and they're twice as nice
as they used to be.
You can feel them
if you like.
See?
Now, why don't we sit
on this nice comfy couch,
have a nice cool drink
and talk all about it.
Would you like that?
He's had some experience
with things like this,
back in the day.
As I recall, both of us--
Uh, not the time
or the place, dear.
There you are.
See? There you are.
There's no way
that guy's related to you.
There's fresh scarring
and swelling in both fundi,
and a bleed on the left.
House was right.
It's Behcet's syndrome.
Give it to me straight, Doc.
Am I ever gonna see again?
That's a little out
of our jurisdiction.
We need to wrap a dressing
over your eyes
to keep the light out.
Not really a problem
for me.
You might not see it,
but your tissue does.
It'll also help
with the swelling.
I'll leave you in Dr. Adams'
capable hands.
You think I'm an ass,
don't you?
I can tell
by your breathing.
Either you're angry
or fat.
I think it's unfair that
you're leading on a woman
who obviously loves
and cares about you.
I love and care
about her too.
But we just don't
work together as a couple.
You need to tell her that.
I'm going to.
But I just want to do it
the right way.
I don't want her
to hate me.
When she finds out
you bought an engagement ring
for another woman,
that option is out the window.
It was gonna be for her.
What changed?
She told me we were
going on a break.
I didn't even get a say
in the matter.
She wanted you to be sure
about your relationship.
I can see how that
would be annoying.
I think I liked it better when
you were just breathing angrily.
She still sees me
as the same sheltered,
blind geek
she met in college.
Most of the time
she acts more like my mother
than my girlfriend.
I asked her to marry me.
She tells me I need
to date somebody else first.
I'd rather
she just dumped me.
At least that
I can understand.
So you were hurt
so much
you had to marry
the next woman you met?
Julie doesn't see me
as I was,
but for who I am now.
She trusts me to make
my own decisions
and to help her with hers.
For the first time
in my life,
I have somebody
who needs me...
Instead of
the other way around.
Ah, she finally
fell asleep.
I think she'll be fine
in a couple of hours.
How do you know about
handling a bad acid trip?
Friends in your gardening club
been experimenting again?
I was young once.
A little scrapbook
that Thomas threw together.
He even has a couple
of pictures of you as a child.
And I've known Greg almost
since he was born, you know.
His father and I were
like brothers.
I was a Navy chaplain
in those days.
I left the service
in the late '60s.
I don't think his dad
ever forgave me
for protesting the war.
Of course, if he knew
I'd got Blythe involved...
You protested the war?
When?
You were a child.
I didn't share
my entire schedule with you.
We knew if we told you,
you'd tell him,
and he'd kill us both.
He was a marine.
It was the ultimate betrayal.
Penultimate.
Sweetheart, I think we need
to get back to the hotel.
Wilson, it's been
a real pleasure.
You're right.
Much too formal.
Come here, lad.
We're practically family now.
We'll see you boys tonight.
8:00 sharp.
I invited them
out to dinner.
Told them it was
your idea.
Straw.
I know we agreed that
whatever happened on break
would stay on break,
and I don't expect you
to talk about yours.
But I just want you to know
that there was no one else.
I missed you so much,
I barely even saw
my own friends.
I'm just so glad
it's finally over.
Are you okay?
What's happening
to him?
Is he going to be okay?
I'm going to need to discuss
that with my colleagues.
We have to talk.
No, you need to rest.
I have to tell you about...
About what happened on break.
Later. You just
lie back and relax--
stop it, Melissa!
Just stop telling me
what I need,
and listen for once,
okay?
How are you feeling?
Embarrassed.
I'm still not sure
what was real
or what I hallucinated.
Did you try to kiss me?
What about you?
He's stabilized
for the moment.
Coughing up blood.
That doesn't really
change anything.
Hemoptysis is a symptom
of Behcet's.
Except our treatment should
make him better, not worse.
It could be doing both.
Our treatment breaks down
his clot in his head,
like it's supposed to,
except a piece broke off
and traveled to one
of his arteries in his lungs.
If anything, we need
to increase the heparin
to prevent further clots
from forming.
If we do that
and he starts hemorrhaging,
we won't be able
to stop the bleeding.
If we don't do that,
the next clot
could cause a heart attack
or a stroke.
Park's way, he at least
has a shot at living.
CT his lungs to confirm,
and up the dose.
She's young and hot.
She'll bounce back.
82 pounds.
How much weight I put on when
my break ended the same way.
People were calling me
Park-ing-lot.
Hmm...Almost 9:00.
I think your boy
is gonna stand us up.
No, no, he'll be here.
Practically walked in
on us having sex.
God, if I saw my mother
doing that,
I'd claw my own eyes out.
Of course, she was nowhere
near as attractive as you.
Horribly fat,
as a matter of fact.
Mother...
Guy sleeping
with my mother,
this is Dominika, my wife.
It's so nice
to be meeting you.
Gregory tells me that you were
born in Richmond, Virginia,
and your father was a tailor
who stole from his clients.
James has persuaded me
of the value
of openness and honesty
in relationships.
We see people with disabilities
all the time, but...
Seeing and understanding aren't
always the same thing.
Are you talking to me
or writing a Facebook post?
I'm saying we should have
picked up on the degeneration
in his eyes sooner.
We ignored them
because we assumed
they weren't even part
of the equation.
I also realized,
intellectually,
I may understand what it means
to be disabled,
but emotionally,
I didn't have a clue.
Apparently, his girlfriend
didn't either.
So you're back
on his side?
It's not a side.
It's a perspective.
He just wants to be treated
like an adult,
make his own decisions.
I may not agree
with all of them,
but how the hell
can I judge him?
I'm sure that's exactly
what disabled people want,
to be treated like
completely foreign entities,
incapable of being judged
and understood.
Park was right
about the clot.
Hopefully the anticoagulants
keep it from killing him.
So...She gets the couch
on the odd nights,
and I get the bed
on evens.
In exchange for
a federal felony,
she gets a green card,
and I get a live-in maid.
Good for you.
The immigration policy
in this country is a travesty.
It forces people to lie just
so nice people can stay here.
Thank you...Dad.
I'm grateful you approve.
You should also know that
I was not in Africa
the last year.
You were in jail.
I've been reading
the Princeton police blotter
ever since you moved here.
And I'm afraid I haven't
been truthful with you either.
And I've wanted to tell you this
for a very long time.
Thomas and I...
We got married two months
after your father passed away.
Uh-huh.
You understand,
we didn't want you to think
we were disrespecting
the memory of your father.
And...Is there
another secret
that you want to share
with me?
No.
There's nothing you think
might be relevant
to my life?
Like...What?
I don't know.
Just off the top
of my head,
something like I DNA-tested
my dad and found that
he was not
my biological father--
you are.
That's impossible.
People lie.
Birthmarks don't.
Oh, my God!
You told me
he was a premie.
This bloody lunatic
is my son!
He's not a lunatic.
All those years
you could have told me.
I could have done things.
That could have made
a difference in the boy's life.
I think we should all
just calm down.
Look at him sitting there--
a pill-popping sociopath!
If you wanted
to screw up his life,
you couldn't have
done it better.
He's got you there, mom.
He's one of the most
well-respected doctors
in the world.
He's saved more lives
than you can count.
Now, you apologize to him,
or I swear,
you will never
see me again, Thomas.
I can't deal with this
anymore.
He's my son?
I'm having a bloody breath
of fresh air,
that's what I'm doing.
So, who's for dessert?
Somebody help me!
Uhh! Somebody--
Will? It's Dr. Adams
and Dr. Chase.
We just need to know--
My eyes! My eyes!
It feels like
it's on fire!
It's not behcet's.
It doesn't necrotize tissue
like this.
I think it's
streptococcus pyogenes.
Except we've already
treated him
with broad spectrum
antibiotics.
It shouldn't be spreading.
It should be dying.
Just means
it's drug-resistant.
We need to remove
what's left of his eyes
before
the gangrene sets in.
It's something that looks
and acts like a bacteria
but isn't one.
Could be viral.
No, it couldn't.
There's no evidence
of viral markers
in the necrotized tissue.
Let me see that image
you took last night
of the clot in his lung.
That's not a piece of the clot
from his brain.
That's the point
of infection.
Mucormycosis.
He breathed in the spores,
it's been growing
and spreading ever since.
A fungal infection
spreading this fast?
Kid's a diabetic.
He already has
a compromised immune system.
He's right.
This sample from his eyes
is crawling with it.
Treat with amphotericin b.
We treated him
with gentamicin
when we thought
it was bacterial,
which means the dose
of amphotericin b we'll need
to cure him will probably
leave him deaf.
Sorry, I stopped listening
after you said
"the dose we'll need
to cure him."
Blind and deaf?
I'd rather be dead.
You will be.
I can live with that.
You never did get
my humor.
There's a chance your hearing
won't be completely gone.
How much of a chance?
A small one.
But a chance.
I'm--I'm refusing treatment.
You don't know how hard
things are already for me.
I can't handle any more.
I can't.
Oh, hi.
I'm here to apologize.
I could have handled
the news with more...
Aplomb?
I have a son.
That's great news.
What else did she
tell you to say?
You're not a lunatic,
you're not a mistake.
I never liked your friend...
My father.
Well, he could be
a bit intense at times.
But unlike you,
I did respect him.
Do you respect your mother?
Well, we do have that
in common.
And we all love her.
So we don't have
much choice, do we?
Son, see you
at dinner.
Will, it's me.
Let me guess.
The doctor who thinks
I'm an ass
wants you to convince me
to live.
Yes.
It won't work.
I know.
So I won't.
Wow.
You're that angry?
I've made enough decisions
for you.
This is your life.
Why'd you come back?
Because I love you.
And I want to be with you
for as long as I can.
Melissa, I'm so scared.
Me too.
I'll always love you.
Even if I was deaf?
Even if anything.
Is it working?
He's still very ill,
but if he keeps responding
the way he has been,
he should be fine.
And his hearing?
It's gone.
We don't know yet
if it'll be permanent.
Melissa?
Is that you?
We've been squeezing
his hand,
once for yes,
twice for no.
Can I ask you something?
I completely understand
if you squeeze no.
Will you marry me?
Don't leave me hanging,
now.
Yes.
Yes! Of course, yes!
I--I heard that.
You said yes, right?
Yes!
You said y--
How long are you gonna wait
until you tell me?
I thought we already had
the Santa Claus talk.
You don't think
I saw you steal Thomas' fork
from the restaurant?
Why would I do that?
For his DNA.
That's...That's...
Very observant of you.
See, you're more me
than you pretend.
You had to know for sure.
So you needed proof.
The fact that
you haven't told me
can only mean...
He isn't your father either.
I'm sorry.
You know what that means.
Your mom's a slut.
That...
And...she's not as boring
as I thought she was.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==