Why today?
Do you want to hear me say it?
18 months since our last appointment.
You read the papers?
Sometimes... And you watch telly?
You know why I'm here.
I'm here because...
What happened, John?
Sherl...
You need to get it out.
My best friend... Sherlock Holmes...
..is dead.
Sherlock 2x03
"The Reichenbach Fall"
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
Falls Of The Reichenbach.
Turner's masterpiece.
Thankfully recovered,
owing to the prodigious talent
of Mr Sherlock Holmes.
A small token of our gratitude.
Diamond cufflinks...
All my cuffs have buttons.
He means thank you. Do I?
Just say it. Thank you.
Hang on.
Back together with my family,
after my terrifying ordeal.
And we have one person to thank
for my deliverance...
Sherlock Holmes.
Tie pin. I don't wear ties. Shhh.
Peter Ricoletti... Number one on
Interpol's most wanted list since 1982.
We got him, and there's one person we have
to thank for giving us the decisive leads.
With all his customary diplomacy and tact.
Sarcasm. Yes.
We all chipped in.
Oh... Put the hat on. Put the hat on.
Yes, Sherlock, put it on.
Just get it over with.
"Boffin!"
"Boffin Sherlock Holmes!"
Everybody gets one.
One what? Tabloid nickname.
SuBo, Nasty Nick.
I'll probably get one soon.
Page five, column six, first sentence.
Why is it always the hat photograph?!
"Bachelor John Watson.
" What kind of hat is it?
What are they implying?!
Is it a cap? Why has it
got two fronts? It's a deerstalker.
"Frequently seen in the company
of bachelor John Watson.
" What are you going to do, throw it?
"Confirmed bachelor John Watson."
A death frisbee! This is too much,
we need to be more careful. It's got flaps.
Ear flaps, it's an ear hat, John.
What do you mean, more careful?
I mean, this isn't a deerstalker
now, it's a Sherlock Holmes hat.
I mean, you're not exactly
a private detective any more.
You're this far from famous.
Oh, it'll pass.
It better pass.
The press will turn, Sherlock,
they always turn and they'll turn on you.
It really bothers you.
What? What people say. Yes.
About me? why would it upset YOU?
Just try to keep a low profile. Find
yourself a little case this week.
Stay out of the news.
That's your phone.
Hmm, it keeps doing that.
So, did you just talk to him
for a really long time?
Oh, Henry Fishguard
never committed suicide.
Bow Street runners missed everything.
Pressing case, is it? They're all
pressing until they're solved.
Put your key back please.
Thank you.
Excuse me, sir.
Any metal objects, keys, mobile phones?
You can go through.
Thank you.
Fancy a cuppa then, mate?
Yeah, why not?
Gilts at seven.
Dutch Telecoms in free-fall.
Thank you, Harvey.
What are you saying?
Refuse them all parole
and bring back the rope?
Let's begin.
This is an emergency. Please leave.
Sir, I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
Sir, there's been a break-in.
Not our division.
You'll want it.
The vault!
Hacked into the Tower of bloody
London's security?! How?!
Tell them we're on our way!
There's been another one, another break-in.
Bank of England!
Sir! Security's down, sir.
It's failing.
What is it now?
Pentonville Prison.
Oh no!
No rush.
I'll get it, shall I?
Here. Not now, I'm busy.
Sherlock... Not now! He's back.
That glass is tougher than anything.
Not tougher than crystallised
carbon. He used a diamond.
# Oh, sinnerman, where you gonna run to?
# Sinnerman, where you gonna run to?
# Where you gonna run to?
# All on that day
# Well, I run to the rock... #
Ready? Yes.
Stand back. Stand back.
Mr Holmes. Mr Holmes.
Let them through.
Thank you. Get in.
# Oh, Lord... # Please help me, Lord
# Don't you see me praying
# Don't you see me down here praying
# But the Lord said
# Go to the devil The Lord said
# Go to the devil
# He said Go to the devil
# All on that day
# So I ran to the devil
# He was waiting... #
Remember... Yes.
Remember what they told you.
Don't try to be clever. No.
Please, keep it simple and brief.
God forbid the
star witness at the trial
should appear intelligent.
Intelligent, fine. Let's give
"smart-arse" a wide berth.
I'll just be myself.
Are you listening to me?
Today, outside the Old Bailey...
This is the trial of the century...
The trial of James Moriarty...
James Moriarty, earlier today accused of...
..attempting to steal
the Crown Jewels.
At the Old Bailey we have
Reichenbach hero Sherlock Holmes...
Would you mind slipping your hand
into my pocket?
Thanks.
# It was boiling, I ran to the sea
# It was boiling
I ran to the sea... #
Crown v Moriarty,
please proceed to Court 10.
You're him.
Wrong toilet. I'm a big fan.
Evidently.
I read your cases, follow them all.
Sign my shirt, would you?
There are two types of fans. Oh?
Catch me before I kill again,
Type A. Uh-huh.
What's Type B? Your bedroom's
just a taxi ride away. Hmm.
Guess which one I am?
Neither. Really?
No, you're not a fan at all.
Those marks on your forearm,
edge of a desk.
You've been typing in a hurry, probably,
pressure on, facing a deadline.
That all?
There's an ink smudge on your wrist,
a bulge in your jacket pocket.
Bit of a giveaway? The smudge is deliberate,
to see if I'm as good as they say I am.
Hmm. Oil-based,
used in newspaper print.
But drawn on with an index finger,
your finger. Hmm.
Journalist. Unlikely you
get your hands dirty at the press.
You put that there to test me.
Wow! I'm liking you.
I'd make a great feature, "Sherlock
Holmes, the man beneath the hat".
Kitty... Riley. Pleased to meet you.
I'm saving you the job of asking.
I won't give you an interview.
No, I don't want the money.
You and John Watson, just platonic?
Can I put you down for
a "no" there as well
There's all sorts of gossip
in the press about you.
Sooner or later, you're going
to need someone on your side.
Someone to set the record straight.
You think you're
the girl for that job, do you?
I'm smart and you can trust me...
..totally.
Smart? OK, investigative
journalist.
Good. Well, look at me
and tell me what you see.
If you're that skilful,
you don't need an interview,
you can just read what you need.
No? OK, my turn.
I see someone who's waiting for their first
scoop, so their editor will notice them.
You're wearing an expensive
skirt, that's been
rehemmed twice. Only posh skirt you've got.
Your nails, you can't afford
to do them that often.
I see someone who's hungry,
I don't see smart. I don't see trustworthy.
I'll give you a quote.
if you like. Three little words.
You repel me.
"A consulting criminal." Yes.
Your words.
Can you expand on that answer?
James Moriarty is for hire.
A tradesman?
Yes. But not the sort
who'd fix your heating?
No, the sort who'd plant a bomb
or stage an assassination.
But I'm sure he'd make a decent job
of your boiler.
Would you describe him as...
Leading. What?
You're leading the witness.
He'll object and the judge'll
uphold. Mr Holmes.
Ask me how, HOW would I describe him?
What opinion have I formed of him?
Do they not teach you this?
Mr Holmes, we are fine without your help.
HOW would you describe this man,
his character?
First mistake.
James Moriarty isn't a man at all.
He's a spider.
A spider at the centre of a web, a
criminal web with a thousand threads
and he knows precisely how each
and every single one of them dances.
And how long...?
No, no. Don't, don't do that.
That's really not a good question.
Mr Holmes!
How long have I known him?
Not your best line of enquiry.
We met twice, five minutes in total.
I pulled a gun, he tried to blow me up.
I felt we had a special something.
Miss Sorrel, are you seriously
claiming this man is an expert?
After knowing the accused
for just five minutes?
Two minutes would have made me
an expert, five was ample.
Mr Holmes, that's a matter
for the jury. Oh, really?
One librarian, two teachers,
two high-pressure jobs,
probably the City.
The foreman's a medical secretary, trained
abroad, judging by her shorthand. Mr Holmes?
Seven are married, two are having
an affair with each other.
Oh, they've just had tea and biscuits.
Would you like to know who ate the wafer?
Mr Holmes!
You've been called here
to answer Miss Sorrel's questions,
not to give us a display
of your intellectual prowess.
Keep your answers brief and to the point.
Anything else will be treated as contempt.
Do you think you could survive
for just a few minutes...
What did I say?
I said don't get clever.
I can't just turn it on and off
like a tap. Well? Well, what?
You were there for the whole thing,
up in the gallery, start to finish.
Like you said it would be - sat
on his backside, never even stirred.
Moriarty is not mounting any defence.
Bank of England, Tower of London,
Pentonville.
Three of the most secure places
in the country
and six weeks ago, Moriarty breaks in,
no-one knows how or why.
All we know is...
He ended up in custody.
Don't do that. Do what?
The look. Look? You're doing the look again.
Well, I can't see it, can I?
It's my face.
Yes and you're doing a "We both know
what's really going on here" face.
We do. No, I don't, which is why
I find the face so annoying.
If Moriarty wanted the jewels,
he'd have them.
If he wanted the prisoners freed,
they'd be on the streets.
The reason he's still in a prison
cell is cos he chose to be there.
Somehow this is part of his scheme.
Mr Crayhill,
can we have your first witness?
Your Honour,
we're not calling any witnesses.
I don't follow.
You've entered a plea of not guilty.
Nevertheless,
my client is offering no evidence.
The defence...rests.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
James Moriarty stands accused...
of several counts of attempted burglary.
Crimes which, if he's found guilty,
will elicit a very long custodial sentence,
and yet...his legal team...
has chosen to offer no evidence whatsoever
to support their plea.
I find myself in the unusual position
of recommending a verdict wholeheartedly.
You must find him guilty.
Guilty.
They're coming back.
That's six minutes.
Surprised it took them
that long, to be honest.
There's a queue for the loo!
Have you reached a verdict
on which you all agree?
Not guilty, they found him not guilty.
No defence and Moriarty's walked free.
Sherlock?
Are you listening? He's out, you know
he'll be coming after you. Sherl...
Most people knock.
But then, you're not most people,
I suppose.
Kettle's just boiled.
Johann Sebastian would be appalled.
May I? Please.
You know when he was on his deathbed, Bach,
he heard his son at the piano
playing one of his...pieces.
The boy stopped before he got to the end.
The dying man jumped out of bed,
ran to the piano and finished it.
Couldn't cope with an unfinished melody.
Neither can you, that's why you've come.
Be honest, you're a tiny bit
pleased. What, with the verdict?
With me, back on the streets.
Every fairy tale needs
a good old-fashioned villain.
You need me or you're nothing.
Because we're just alike, you and I,
except you're boring.
You're on the side of the angels.
You got to the jury, of course.
I got into the Tower of London,
you think I can't worm my way
into 12 hotel rooms?
Cable network.
Every hotel bedroom
has a personalised TV screen.
And every person has their pressure point.
Someone that they want
to protect from harm.
Easy peasy.
So how are you going to do it?
Burn me?
Ah, that's the problem, the final problem.
Have you worked out what it is yet?
What's the final problem?
I did tell you...
but did you listen?
How hard do you find it,
having to say "I don't know"?
I don't know. Oh, that's clever,
very clever, awfully clever.
Speaking of clever, have you
told your little friends yet?
Told them what?
Why I broke into all those places
and never took anything? No.
But you understand? Obviously.
Off you go, then.
Tell you what you already know?
No, prove that you know it.
You didn't take anything
because you don't need to. Good.
You'll never need to take anything
ever again. Very good, because?
Because nothing in the Bank of England,
the Tower of London or Pentonville
Prison could possibly match
the value of the key
that could get you into all three.
I can open any door anywhere with
a few tiny lines of computer code.
No such thing as a private bank
account now, they're all mine.
No such thing as secrecy, I OWN secrecy.
Nuclear codes?
I could blow up NATO in alphabetical order.
In a world of locked rooms,
the man with the key is king.
And honey, you should see me in a crown.
You were advertising all through the trial,
you were showing the world what you can do.
And you were helping.
Big client list - rogue governments,
intelligence communities,
terrorist cells.
They all want me.
Suddenly, I'm Mr Sex.
If you can break any bank, what do
you care about the highest bidder?
I don't, I just like to watch them
all competing.
"Daddy loves me the best."
Aren't ordinary people adorable?
Well, you know, you've got John.
I should get myself a live-in one.
Why are you doing all of this?
It must be so funny.
You don't want money or power, not really.
What is it all for?
I want to solve the problem.
Our problem.
The final problem.
It's going to start
very soon, Sherlock...the fall.
But don't be scared,
falling is just like flying,
except there's a more
permanent destination.
Never liked riddles.
Learn to.
Because I owe you a fall, Sherlock.
I...owe...you.
Er, excuse me,
I'm looking for Mycroft Holmes?
Would you happen to know
if he's around at all?
Can you not hear me?
Yes, all right. Anyone?
Anyone at all know...
where Mycroft Holmes is,
I've been asked to meet him here?
No takers, right. Am I invisible,
can you actually see me?
Ah, thanks, gents. I've been asked to
meet Mycroft Holmes. What the hell?!
Tradition, John, our traditions define us.
So total silence is traditional, is it?
You can't even say pass the sugar?
Three-quarters
of the diplomatic service
and half the government front bench
all sharing one tea trolley,
it's for the best, believe me.
We don't want a repeat of...1972.
But we can talk in here.
You read this stuff?
Caught my eye. Mm-hm.
Saturday, they're doing a big expose.
I'd love to know
where she got her information.
Someone called Brook.
Recognise the name?
School friend, maybe?
Of Sherlock's?
But that's not why I asked you here.
Who's that? Don't know? No.
Never seen his face before?
Um... He's taken a flat in Baker
Street, two doors down from you.
Hm, I was thinking of doing
a drinks thing for the neighbours.
I'm not sure you'll want to.
Sulejmani, Albanian hit squad,
expertly trained killer,
living less than 20 feet
from your front door.
Well, it's a great location.
Jubilee line's handy.
John... What's it got to do with me?
Dyachenko. Ludmila.
Oh...
Actually, I think I have seen her.
Russian killer.
She's taken the flat opposite.
OK.
I'm sensing a pattern here.
In fact, four top
international assassins relocate
to within spitting distance of 221b.
Anything you'd care to share with me?
I'm moving? It's not hard to guess
the common denominator, is it?
You think this is Moriarty?
He promised Sherlock he'd come back.
If this was Moriarty, we'd be dead
already. If not Moriarty, then who?
Why don't you talk to Sherlock,
if you're so concerned about him?
Oh, God, don't tell me.
Too much history between us, John.
Old scores, resentments.
Nicked all his Smurfs?
Broke his Action Man?
Finished.
We both know what's coming, John.
Moriarty is obsessed, he's sworn
to destroy his only rival.
So you want me to watch out for your
brother because he won't accept your help?
If it's not too much trouble?
Excuse me. Sorry.
Sherlock, something weird... What's
going on? Kidnapping. Rufus Bruhl.
The ambassador to the US.
He's in Washington, isn't he?
Not him, his children. Max
and Claudette, age seven and nine.
They're at St Aldates.
Posh boarding place in Surrey.
School broke up, the boarders went home.
A few kids remained, including those two.
The kids have vanished.
The ambassador's asked for you
personally. The Reichenbach hero.
Isn't it great
to be working with a celebrity?
We shouldn't need to keep you
for much longer. Thank you.
It's all right. Miss Mackenzie,
House Mistress. Go easy.
Miss Mackenzie,
you're in charge of pupil welfare,
yet you left this place
wide open last night.
What are you, an idiot, a drunk or
a criminal?! Quickly, tell me!
All the doors and windows
were properly bolted.
No-one, not even me,
went into their room last night.
You have to believe me! I do,
I just wanted you to speak quickly.
Miss Mackenzie will need
to breath into a bag now.
Six grand a term, you'd expect them
to keep the kids safe for you.
You said the other kids
had all left on their holidays.
They were the only two
sleeping on this floor.
There's absolutely
no sign of a break-in.
The intruder must have been
hidden inside some place.
Show me where the brother slept.
The boy sleeps there every night.
Gazing at the only light source
outside in the corridor.
He'd recognise every shape, every outline,
the silhouette of everyone
who came to the door.
OK, so? So if someone approaches
the door who he doesn't recognise,
an intruder, maybe he can even see
the outline of a weapon.
What would he do?
In the precious few seconds
before they came into the room,
how would he use them if not to cry out?
This little boy,
this particular little boy,
who reads all of those spy books,
what would he do?
He'd leave a sign?
Get Anderson!
Linseed oil.
Not much use, it doesn't lead us to
the kidnapper. Brilliant, Anderson.
Really? Yes, brilliant
impression of an idiot.
Floor.
He...made a trail for us. The boy
was made to walk ahead of them.
On what, tiptoe? Indicates anxiety.
Gun held to his head.
The girl was pulled beside him,
dragged sideways.
He had his left arm cradled about her neck.
That's the end of it, we don't know
where they went from here.
Tells us nothing after all.
You're right, Anderson, nothing.
Except his shoe size, his height,
his gait, his walking pace.
Having fun? Starting to.
Maybe don't do the smiling.
Kidnapped children?
How could he get past the CCTV?
If all the doors were locked.
He walked in when they weren't locked.
But a stranger can't just
walk into a school like that.
Anyone can walk in anywhere
if they pick the right moment.
Yesterday, end of term, parents
milling around, chauffeurs, staff.
What's one more stranger among that lot?
He was waiting for them.
All he had to do was find a place to hide.
Molly!
Hello, I'm just going out. No,
you're not. I've got a lunch date.
Cancel it, have lunch with me.
What? I need your help.
One of your old boyfriends,
we're tracking him down.
He's been naughty. Moriarty?
Of course it's Moriarty!
Jim wasn't my boyfriend,
we went out three times. I ended it.
Then he stole the Crown
Jewels, broke into the
Bank of England and
organised a prison break.
For the sake of law and
order, I suggest you avoid
all future attempts at
a relationship, Molly.
Oil, John. The oil
in the kidnapper's footprint.
It'll lead us to Moriarty.
All the chemical traces on his shoe
have been preserved.
The sole of the shoe is like a passport.
If we're lucky, we'll see
everything he's been up to.
I need that analysis.
Alkaline.
Thank you, John. Molly. Yes.
I...O...U.
Glycerol molecule.
What are you?
What did you mean, IOU?
You said IOU.
You were muttering it while you were
working. Nothing, mental note.
You're a bit like my dad. He's dead.
No, sorry.
Molly, please don't feel the need to make
conversation, it's really not your area.
When he was dying, he was
always cheerful, he was lovely,
except when he thought
no-one could see.
I saw him once, he looked sad.
Molly.
You look sad,
when you think he can't see you.
Are you OK? And don't just say you
are, because I know what that means,
looking sad when you think
no-one can see you.
You can see me. I don't count.
What I'm trying to say is,
that if there's anything I can do,
anything you need, anything at all,
you can have me.
No, I just mean, I mean, if there's
anything you need, it's fine.
But what can I need from you?
Nothing. I don't know.
You could probably say thank you, actually.
Thank you?
I'm just going to go and get
some crisps. Do you want anything?
It's OK, I know you don't.
Well, actually, maybe I'll...
I know you don't.
Sherlock? Hmm?
This envelope that was in her trunk,
there's another one. What?
On our doorstep. Found it today.
Yes, and look at that.
Look at that, exactly the same seal.
Breadcrumbs. Uh-huh.
It was there when I got back.
A little trace of breadcrumbs.
Hardback copy of Fairy Tales.
Two children led into the forest by a wicked
father, follow a little
trail of breadcrumbs.
That's Hansel and Gretel.
What sort of kidnapper leaves clues?
The sort that likes to boast,
that thinks it's a game.
He sat in our flat and he said
these exact words to me...
"All fairy tales need
a good old-fashioned villain."
The fifth substance, it's part of
the tale. The witch's house. What?
The glycerol molecule.
PGPR! What's that?
It's used in making chocolate.
This fax arrived an hour ago.
What have you got for us?
We need to find a place in the city where
all five of these things intersect.
Chalk, asphalt, brick dust, vegetation.
What - chocolate?! I think we're
looking for a disused sweet factory.
We need to narrow that down.
A sweet factory with asphalt?
No, too general.
Something more specific.
Chalk, chalky clay. That's a far
thinner band of geology.
Brick dust?
Building site.
Bricks from the 1950s.
There's thousands of building sites
in London.
I've got people out looking.
So have I!
Homeless network, faster than the police,
far more relaxed about taking bribes.
John.
Rhododendron ponticum. Matches.
Addlestone. What?
A mile of disused factories between the
river and the park, matches everything.
Right, come on. Come on!
OK, you look over there.
Look everywhere.
OK, spread out, please, spread out.
Quietly, quietly!
This was alight moments ago.
They're still here! Sweet wrappers?
What's he been feeding you?
Hansel and Gretel.
Ugh!
Mercury. What?
The papers, they're painted
with mercury, lethal.
The more they ate...
It was killing them. But it's not
enough to kill them on its own.
Taken in large enough quantities,
eventually it would kill them.
He didn't need to be there
for the execution.
Murder by remote control,
he could be 1,000 miles away.
The hungrier they got, the more they
ate, the faster they died. Neat.
Sherlock. Over here!
I've got him, don't worry.
Right then, the professionals are finished.
If the amateurs want to go in
and have their turn.
Now remember, she's in shock
and she's just seven years old,
so, anything you can do to...
Not be myself?
Yeah, might be helpful.
Claudette, I...
No, no, I know it's been hard for you.
Claudette, listen to me.
Out. Get out!
Makes no sense.
Kid's traumatised.
Something about Sherlock reminds her
of the kidnapper. What's she said?
Hasn't uttered another syllable.
And the boy? No, he's unconscious.
He's still in intensive care.
Don't let it get to you,
I always feel like screaming
when you walk into a room.
In fact, so do most people.
Come on.
Brilliant work you did finding
those kids from just a footprint,
it's really amazing.
Thank you.
Unbelievable.
Ah.
You OK? Thinking.
This is my cab, you get the next
one. Why? You might talk.
'Is this chocolate?' 'We're looking
for a disused sweet factory.'
'Get out!'
'Aaaargh!'
Problem?
'..this stunning evening wear set
from us at London Taxi Shopping.
Can you turn this off, please? 'The
set comprises of a beautiful...'
Can you turn this off?!
'Accompanied by four
spangly diamond bracelets...'
Hello.
Are you ready for the story?
This is the story
of Sir Boast-a-lot.
A footprint, it's all he had.
A footprint.
Yeah, well, you know what he's like.
CSI Baker Street.
Well, our boys couldn't have done it.
Well, that's why we need him,
he's better. That's one explanation.
And what's the other?
Sir Boast-a-lot was the bravest and
cleverest knight at the round table.
But soon the other knights began
to grow tired of his stories
about how brave he was
and how many dragons he'd slain.
And soon they began to wonder, "Are
Sir Boast-a-lot's stories even true?"
Only he could have found that evidence.
Oh, no.
The girl screams her head off when she sees
him - a man she has never seen before,
unless she had seen him before.
What's your point?
You know what it is, you just
don't want to think about it.
So, all of the knights
went to King Arthur and said,
"I don't believe
Sir Boast-a-lot's stories.
"He's just a big old liar who makes
things up to make himself look good."
You're not seriously suggesting
he's involved, are you?
We have to entertain the possibility.
And then, even the King began to wonder.
But that wasn't the end
of Sir Boast-a-lot's problem.
No.
That wasn't the final problem.
The end.
Stop the cab.
Stop the cab!
What was that?!
What was that?
No charge.
Watch out!
Thank you.
Sherlock!
That is him. It's him.
Sulejmani or something,
Mycroft showed me his file.
He's a big Albanian gangster,
lives two doors down from us.
He died because I shook his hand.
What?
He saved my life,
but he couldn't touch me. Why?
Four assassins
living right on our doorstep.
They haven't come here to kill me.
They have to keep me alive.
I've got something that all of them want.
But if one of them approaches me...
The others kill them
before they can get it.
All of the attention is focused on me.
There's a surveillance web
closing in on us right now.
So what have you got that's so important?
I need to ask about the dusting.
Precise details, in the last week,
what's been cleaned?
Tuesday, I did your lino. No, this
room, this is where we'll find it.
Any break in the dust line.
You can put back anything but dust.
Dust is eloquent.
What's he on about?
Cameras, we're being watched.
What?! Cameras? Here?
I'm in my nightie!
No, Inspector. Why?
The answer's no.
You've not heard the question!
You want to take me to the station.
Saving you the trouble of asking.
Sherlock.
The scream? Yeah.
Who was it? Donovan?
I bet it was Donovan.
"Am I somehow responsible
for the kidnapping?"
Ha ha, Moriarty is smart.
He planted that doubt in her head.
That little nagging sensation.
You're going to have to be strong
to resist.
You can't kill an idea, can you?
Not once it's made a home...there.
Will you come? One photograph,
that's his next move.
Moriarty's game.
First the scream, then a photograph
of me being taken in for questioning.
He wants to destroy me inch by inch.
It is a game, Lestrade,
and not one I'm willing to play.
Give my regards to Sergeant Donovan.
They'll be deciding. Deciding?
Whether to come back with a warrant
and arrest me. You think?
Standard procedure. You should have
gone with him. People'll think...
I don't care what people think.
You'd care if they thought
you were stupid or wrong.
No, that would just make them
stupid or wrong.
Sherlock, I don't want the world
believing you're...
That I am what?
A fraud.
You're worried they're right. What?
That they're right about me.
No. That's why you're upset.
You can't entertain the possibility
they may be right.
You're afraid you've been taken in.
I'm not.
Moriarty is playing with your mind,
too. Can't you SEE what's going on?!
No, I know you for real.
100 percent?
Well, nobody could fake being such
an annoying dick all the time.
Sherlock Holmes? Yes, sir.
That bloke that's been in the press?
Mm-hm.
I thought he was some sort of private eye.
He is. We've been consulting with
him, that's what you're telling me?
Not used him on any proper cases
though, have we?
Well, one or two.
Or 20 or 30.
What?!
I'm not the only senior officer
who did this. Gregson... Shut up!
An amateur detective given access to
all sorts of classified information.
And now he's a suspect in a case.
With all due respect...
You're a bloody idiot, Lestrade!
Now go and fetch him in, right now.
Do it!
Proud of yourselves? Well,
what if it's not just this case?
What if he's done this to us
every single time?
So, still got some friends
on the force. It's Lestrade.
Says they're all coming over here now.
Queuing up to slap on the handcuffs.
Every officer
you've ever made feel like a tit,
which is a lot of people.
Yoo-hoo.
Oh, sorry, am I interrupting?
Some chap delivered a parcel,
I forgot, marked perishable.
I had to sign for it.
Funny name, German, like the fairy tales.
Burnt to a crisp.
What does it mean?
'Police!' I'll go.
'Sherlock.
'Excuse me, Mrs Hudson.
We need to talk to you.
'You can't just barge in like that!'
- 'Have you got a warrant?
- Have you?'
'Leave it, John.
'Eh? Manners!'
Sherlock Holmes, I'm arresting you on
suspicion of abduction and kidnapping.
It's OK, John. He's not resisting.
No, it's not all right, this is ridiculous.
Get him downstairs now.
You don't have to do this.
Don't try to interfere
or I shall arrest you too.
You done?
I said it. Hmm?
First time we met. Don't bother.
Solving crimes won't be enough.
One day he'll cross the line.
Now ask yourself, what sort of man
would kidnap those kids
just so he can impress us all
by finding them?
Donovan? Sir? Got our man?
Er, yes, sir.
Looked a bit of a weirdo, if you ask me.
Often are, these vigilante types.
What are you looking at?
Are you all right, sir?
Joining me? Yeah.
Well, apparently it's against the law
to chin the Chief Superintendent.
Hmm. Bit awkward this.
There's no-one to bail us.
I was thinking more about
our imminent and daring escape.
'All units to 27.' What?
'All units to 2...'
Aah!
Ladies and gentlemen, will you all
please get on your knees?
NOW would be good! Do as he says!
Just so you're aware, the gun
is his idea, I'm just a...you know.
My hostage. Hostage, yes,
that works. That works.
So what now?
Doing what Moriarty wants,
becoming a fugitive. Run!
Get after him, Lestrade!
Take my hand.
Now people will definitely talk.
The gun! Leave it!
Sherlock, wait!
We're going to need to coordinate.
Go to your right. Huh?
Go to your right.
Everybody wants to believe it,
that's what makes it so clever.
A lie that's preferable to the truth.
My deductions were a sham.
No-one feels inadequate,
Sherlock's an ordinary man.
Mycroft, he could help us.
Big family reconciliation,
now's not really the moment.
Sherlock...we're being followed.
I knew we couldn't outrun the police.
That's not the police, it's one of
my new neighbours from Baker Street.
Let's see if he can give us some answers.
Where are we going?
We're going to jump in front of that bus.
Oof!
Oh...
Tell me what you want from me.
Tell me!
He left it at your flat.
Who? Moriarty.
What?
The computer key code. Of course.
He's selling it. The programme
he used to break into the Tower.
He planted it when he came around.
It's a game-changer.
It's a key, it can break into any system
and it's sitting in our flat right now.
That's why he left that message, telling
everyone where to come, "Get Sherlock!"
We need to get back into the flat
and search. CID will be camped out.
Why plant it on you?
It's another subtle way
of smearing my name,
now I'm best pals with all those criminals.
Yeah, well, have you seen this?
A kiss-and-tell.
Some bloke called Rich Brook.
Who is he?
Too late to go on the record?
Congratulations,
"The Truth About Sherlock Holmes."
The scoop that everybody wanted
and you got it. Bravo!
I gave you your opportunity.
I wanted to be on your side, remember?
You turned me down, so...
Then lo and behold,
someone spills all the beans.
How utterly convenient.
Who is Brook?
Oh, come on, Kitty, no-one trusts
the voice at the end of a phone.
All those little meetings in cafes,
those sessions in the hotel room when
he gabbled into your Dictaphone.
How do you know that you can trust him?
A man turns up
with the Holy Grail in his pockets.
What were his credentials?
Darling, they didn't have any
ground coffee, so I just got normal.
You said that they wouldn't find me
here, you said that I'd be safe here.
You are safe.
Richard, I'm a witness, they wouldn't
harm you in front of witnesses.
So that's your source?
Moriarty is Richard Brook?
Of course he's Richard Brook,
there is no Moriarty.
There never has been. What are you
talking about? Look him up.
Rich Brook, an actor Sherlock Holmes
hired to be Moriarty.
Dr Watson, I know you're a good man,
don't, don't, don't hurt me.
No, you are Moriarty!
He's Moriarty!
We've met, remember?
You were going to blow me up!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
He paid me, I needed the work.
I'm an actor, I was out of work.
Sherlock, you'd better explain,
because I am not getting this.
I'll be doing the explaining, in print.
It's all here, conclusive proof.
You invented James Moriarty, your nemesis.
Invented him?! Mm-hm.
He invented all the crimes, actually.
And to cap it all,
he made up a master villain.
Don't be ridiculous! Ask him.
He's right here. Just ask him.
Tell him, Richard. For God's sake,
this man was on trial!
Yes, and you paid him to take the
rap. Promised you'd rig the jury.
Not exactly a West End role,
but I'll bet the money was good.
But not so good he didn't
want to sell his story.
I am sorry. I am. I am sorry.
So this is the story
you're going to publish?
The big conclusion of it all,
Moriarty's an actor? He knows I am.
I have proof. Show them...
Kitty, show them something.
Yeah, show me something.
I'm on TV. I'm on kids' TV.
I'm the story-teller.
I'm the story-teller. It's on DVD.
Just tell him.
It's all coming out. It's all over.
Just tell them. Just tell them.
Tell them! It's all over now!
No! Don't you touch me!
Don't you lay a finger on me!
Stop it now!
Don't hurt me!
Don't let him get away!
Leave him alone!
No, no, no. He'll have back-up.
Do you know what, Sherlock Holmes?
I look at you know and I can
read you...and you repel me.
Can he do that?
Completely change his identity,
make you the criminal?
He's got my whole life story.
That's what you do when you sell a big lie,
you wrap it up in the truth
to make it more palatable.
It'll be your word against his.
He's been sowing doubt into
people's minds for 24 hours.
There's only one thing he needs to
do to complete his game and that...
Sherlock?
There's something I need to do.
What? Can I help? No, on my own.
You're wrong, you know?
You do count.
You've always counted
and I've always trusted you.
But you were right.
I'm not OK.
Tell me what's wrong.
Molly, I think I'm going to die.
What do you need? If I wasn't
everything that you think I am,
everything that I think I am...
..would you still want to help me?
What do you need?
You.
She has really done her homework,
Miss Riley,
and it's things that only someone
close to Sherlock could know.
Ah. Have you seen your brother's
address book lately?
Two names - yours and mine...
and Moriarty didn't get this stuff from me.
John... So how does it work,
your relationship?
Do you go out for a coffee
now and then, you and Jim?
Your own brother
and you blabbed about his entire
life to this maniac.
I never intend...I never dreamt...
This...this is what you were
trying to tell me, isn't it?
"Watch his back
because I've made a mistake."
How did you meet him?
People like him,
we know about them, we watch them.
But James Moriarty...
..the most dangerous criminal mind
the world has ever seen,
and, in his pocket, the ultimate weapon.
The key code.
A few lines of computer code
that can unlock any door.
And you abducted him
to try and find the key code?
Interrogated him for weeks.
And? He wouldn't play along.
He just sat there
staring into the darkness.
The only thing that made him open up...
I could get him to talk, just a little.
But...
In return you had to offer him
Sherlock's life story.
So, one big lie...
..Sherlock's a fraud,
and people will swallow it
because the rest of it's true.
Moriarty wanted Sherlock destroyed, right,
and you have given him
the perfect ammunition.
John.
I'm sorry.
Oh, please!
Tell him, would you?
I got your message.
The computer code is the key to
this. We find it, we can use it.
Use it? He used it to create
a false identity
so we can break into the records
and destroy Richard Brook.
Bring back Jim Moriarty again.
Somewhere in 221b,
somewhere on the day of the verdict
he left it hidden.
Uh-huh.
What did he touch?
An apple, nothing else.
Did he write anything down?
No.
Oh.
Yeah, speaking.
What?
What happened? Is she OK?
Oh, my God! Right, yes, I'm coming.
What is it? Paramedics.
Mrs Hudson's been shot.
How? Probably one of the killers
you managed to attract. Jesus!
She's dying, Sherlock. Let's go.
You go. I'm busy.
Busy?!
Thinking. I need to think.
You need to...?
Doesn't she mean anything to you?
You once half-killed a man
because he laid a finger on her.
She's my landlady.
She's dying...you machine!
Sod this. Sod this! You stay here
if you want, on your own.
Alone is what I have.
Alone protects me.
No, friends protect people.
# I've been kicked around since I was born
# But now it's all right, it's OK
# You can look the other way
# We can try to understand
# The New York Times' effect on man
# Whether you're a brother
or whether you're a mother
# You're stayin' alive... #
Well...here we are at last.
You and me, Sherlock.
And our problem - the final problem.
Staying alive!
It's so boring, isn't it?
It's just staying.
All my life I've been searching
for distractions
and you were the best distraction
and now I don't even have you
because I've beaten you.
And you know what?
In the end, it was easy.
It was easy.
Now I've got to go back to playing
with the ordinary people,
and it turns out you're ordinary,
just like all of them.
Ah, well.
Did you almost start to wonder
if I was real?
Did I nearly get you?
Richard Brook.
Nobody seems to get the joke, but you do.
Of course. Attaboy.
Richard Brook in German is Reichenbach.
The case that made my name.
Just trying to have some fun.
Good. You got that too.
Beats like digits.
Every beat is a one, every rest is a zero.
Binary code.
That's why all those assassins
tried to save my life.
It was hidden on me, hidden inside my head.
A few simple lines of computer code
that can break into any system.
Told all my clients,
last one to Sherlock is a sissy.
But now that it's up here, I can
use it to alter all the records.
I can kill Rich Brook
and bring back Jim Moriarty.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is too easy.
There is no key, doofus!
Those digits are meaningless.
They're utterly meaningless.
You don't really think a couple
of lines of computer code
are going to crash the world
around our ears?
I'm disappointed in you, ordinary Sherlock.
But the rhythm... Partita no 1!
Thank you, Johann Sebastian Bach.
But then how did you...? How did I break
into the bank, to the Tower, to the prison?
Daylight robbery! All it takes
is some willing participants.
I knew you'd fall for it.
That's your weakness.
You always want everything to be clever.
Shall we finish the game?
One final act.
Glad you chose a tall building.
Nice way to do it.
Do it? Do what?
Yes, of course.
My suicide.
Genius detective proved to be a fraud.
I read it in the paper so it must be true.
I love newspapers.
Fairy tales.
And pretty grim ones too.
Oh, God, John, you made me jump.
Is everything OK with the police?
Has Sherlock sorted it all out?
Oh, my God.
Taxi!
No, no, no. Police...sort of!
Thanks, mate. Thanks a lot!
I can prove that you created
an entirely false identity.
Oh, just kill yourself.
It's a lot less effort.
Go on.
For me.
Please!
You're insane.
You're just getting that now?
Wo-wo-wo!
OK.
Let me give you a little extra incentive.
Your friends will die if you don't.
John?
Not just John. Everyone.
Mrs Hudson? Everyone.
Lestrade? Three bullets,
three gunmen, three victims.
There's no stopping them now...
..unless my people see you jump.
You can have me arrested,
you can torture me,
you can do anything you like with me,
but nothing's going to prevent them
from pulling the trigger.
Your only three friends in the world
will die unless...
Unless I kill myself
and complete your story.
You've got to admit, that's sexier.
And I die in disgrace. Of course.
That's the point of this.
Oh. You've got an audience now.
Off you pop.
Go on.
I told you how this ends.
Your death is the only thing that's
going to call off the killers.
I'm certainly not going to do it.
Would you give me one moment, please?
One moment of privacy.
Please.
Of course.
What?!
What is it?
What did I miss?
You're not going to do it.
So the killers can be called off,
then there's a recall code
or a word or a number.
I don't have to die if I've got you.
Oh!
You think you can make me stop the order?
You think you can make me do that?
Yes.
So do you. Sherlock, your big
brother and all the King's horses
couldn't make me do a thing
I didn't want to.
Yes, but I'm not my brother, remember?
I am you.
Prepared to do anything.
Prepared to burn.
Prepared to do what ordinary
people won't do.
You want me to shake hands with you
in hell? I shall not disappoint you.
Nah.
You talk big.
You're ordinary.
You're on the side of the angels.
Oh, I may be on the side of the angels,
but don't think for one second
that I am one of them.
No...
..you're not.
I see.
You're not ordinary.
No.
You're me.
Thank you...
..Sherlock Holmes.
Thank you.
Bless you.
As long as I'm alive, you can save
your friends, you've got a way out.
Well, good luck with that.
No.
Yes, sir. Thank you. Bye.
Hello?
John.
Hey, Sherlock. Are you OK?
Turn around and walk back
the way you came. I'm coming in.
Just do as I ask!
Please.
Where?
Stop there.
Sherlock?
OK, look up. I'm on the rooftop.
Oh, God.
I...I can't come down, so we'll
just have to do it like this.
What's going on?
An apology.
It's all true.
What?
Everything they said about me.
I invented Moriarty.
Why are you saying this?
I'm a fake.
Sherlock...
The newspapers were right all along.
I want you to tell Lestrade,
I want you to tell Mrs Hudson and Molly.
In fact, tell anyone who will
listen to you...
..that I created Moriarty
for my own purposes.
OK, shut up Sherlock. Shut up.
The first time we met...
the first time we met,
you knew all about my sister, right?
Nobody could be that clever.
You could.
I researched you.
Before we met, I discovered
everything that I could
to impress you.
It's a trick. Just a magic trick.
No. All right, stop it now.
No. Stay exactly where you are.
Don't move. All right.
Keep your eyes fixed on me.
Please, will you do this for me?
Do what?
This phone call, it's...
..it's my note.
It's what people do, don't they?
Leave a note?
Leave a note when?
Goodbye, John. No. Don't...
Sherlock!
Sherlock.
Sherlock...Sherlock.
I'm a doctor, let me come through.
Let me come through, please.
He's my friend. He's my friend...
Please.
Please, let me just...
Oh, Jesus!
No.
God, no.
There's stuff that you wanted to say...
..but didn't say it. Yeah.
Say it now.
Sorry, I can't.
There's all the stuff.
All the science equipment.
I left it all in boxes.
I don't know what needs doing.
I thought I'd take it to a school.
Would you...? I can't go back to
the flat again, not at the moment.
I'm angry.
It's OK, John.
There's nothing unusual in that.
That's the way he made everyone feel.
All the marks on my table and the noise,
firing guns at half past one
in the morning... Yeah.
..bloody specimens in my fridge.
Imagine, keeping bodies
where there's food. Yes.
And the fighting! Drove me up
the wall with all his carryings-on.
Listen, I'm not actually that angry, OK?
OK. I'll leave you alone to,
you know...
Erm...
Hmm.
You...you told me once...
..that you weren't a hero.
Erm, there were times I didn't
even think you were human,
but let me tell you this, you were...
the best man...
the most human...human being
that I've ever known
and no-one will ever convince me
that you told me a lie, so...
..there.
I was so alone...
..and I owe you so much.
But, please, there's just one
more thing, one more thing,
one more miracle, Sherlock,
for me, don't be...
..dead.
Would you do that just for me?
Just stop it. Stop this.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd