Previously on Lost.
Son of a bitch.
We're gonna get you to
the hospital. Mr. Locke?
Mr. Locke?
You found what they
were hiding in the submarine.
I most certainly did.
Aah!
- Hello, Hugo.
- We have to talk to you.
"We"?
Okay, guys.
Come on out.
Hello, Jack.
I was hoping you'd come.
I think we have some
catching up to do.
Hurley...
this was your idea.
You all right with me
talking with him alone?
It's all you, dude.
All right, let's catch up.
You look just like him.
Does it bother you?
No, what bothers me
is I don't have any
idea what the hell you are.
Sure you do.
Why John Locke?
Because he was stupid
enough to believe that
he'd been brought
here for a reason.
Because he pursued that belief
until it got him killed...
and because you were
kind enough to bring his
body back here in
a nice wooden box.
He had to be dead before
you could look like him.
That's right.
Who else have you looked like?
Jack, what do you
really want to ask me?
The third day we
were here, I saw...
I chased my father through
the jungle... my...
my dead father.
Was that you?
Yes, that was me.
Why?
You needed to find water.
This may be hard for
you to believe, Jack...
but all I've ever been
interested in is helping you.
To help me?
To do what?
Leave.
But because Jacob chose you...
you were trapped on this island
before you even got here.
But now Jacob's dead,
we don't have to
be trapped anymore.
We can get on an airplane and
fly away anytime we want to.
And if we can just fly
away whenever we want,
why are you still here?
Because it has to be all of us.
What?
John Locke was the
only one of us
that ever believed
in this place.
He did everything
he could to keep us
from leaving this island.
John Locke was not
a believer, Jack.
He was a sucker.
Sinus tach at 130, B.P. Dropping.
Last read was 62 over 30,
- possibly due to internal bleeding.
- Any signs of neurological damage?
No response in lower reflexes.
- That's because he's a paraplegic.
- You know this man?
Yes. He's a substitute teacher
at my school. His name is...
Locke. Mr. Locke.
I don't know his first name...
but he uses a wheelchair.
Where is it?
Smashed to pieces. That thing
probably saved his life.
I saw the man that did this,
the... the hit-and-run driver.
He... he was at our school.
When we get to the hospital,
you can talk to the cops.
But do you know anyone
we can contact for him?
I have no idea. Like I
said, I barely know him.
- Helen.
- What did you say?
Helen Norwood.
I was... gonna marry her.
Well...
you're still gonna marry her
'cause you're gonna
be okay, Mr. Locke.
John...
my name is John.
Blunt force trauma victim,
late 40s male.
- He needs a C.T. scan.
- We got a gunshot wound here. Female.
- Entry wound... upper right quadrant.
- Baby! Baby!
Yes, sir. I understand
she's pregnant.
- We're gonna take good care of her.
- Baby!
- 500 lost cc's. External blood loss.
we're gonna do
everything we can.
What is it?
You can come out.
You following us, Claire?
Yeah.
Why?
'Cause he's my brother.
Looks like you two have a
lot of catching up to do.
I'll leave you to it.
Claire, I'm...
I'm so sorry tha...
Did he tell you?
That he was the one
pretending to be our father?
Yeah.
Yeah, he told me.
You know, I pretty
much gave up hoping
that you'd ever come back.
Now that you're here...
it's... it's good
to see you, Jack.
Yeah, it's good to see you, too.
You know, I... I never really had
much in the way of family,
so it... really means a lot
that you're coming with us.
Actually, I haven't... I haven't
decided if I'm coming with you.
Yeah, you have.
What do you mean?
You decided the moment
you let him talk to you,
just like the rest of us.
So... you know,
whether you like it or not...
you're with him now.
Season 6 Episode 13
"The Last Recruit"
He's got a submarine?
keep your voice down, damn it.
Yeah, Widmore's got a sub.
We're using it to
get off this rock.
Are we gonna tell Sun?
Kate's telling her now.
I thought we might
want to avoid huddles.
What about Sayid?
Sayid ain't invited.
He's gone over to the dark side.
Yeah, but you can always bring
people back from the dark side.
- I mean, Anakin...
- Who the hell's Anakin?
Look, just keep your mouth shut.
Don't say nothin' to no one.
Hey.
Hey, Claire.
Hey, Hurley.
You look great.
It's so nice to have
everyone back together again.
Want an apple?
Hey, Schaub, I'm the
one who brought her in.
Wanna give us a minute?
Katherine Anne Austen.
Wanted for arson, assault
on a federal officer...
murder in the first degree.
Funny. You don't strike
me as the murdering kind.
That's because I'm not.
You be sure and mention that
to the feds when they get here.
Is there something you wanted?
You remember me...
from the airport?
We were on the same
flight from Sydney.
Yeah, I remember.
Well, don't you
think it's weird...
you and me being
on the same flight,
having that little
meet-up in the elevator?
And a week later... boom.
Of all the cars in Los Angeles,
you smash into mine.
Almost like someone's
trying to put us together.
Are you hitting on me?
It'd never work, sweetheart.
- I'm a cop, you're a murderer...
- I already told you. I'm not a murderer.
Yeah, well, I'm still a cop.
So why didn't you arrest me?
- I did arrest you.
- No, in L.A.X... the elevator.
You saw I was wearing handcuffs.
I didn't see any handcuffs.
All I saw was a pretty lady
who needed the door
held open for her.
You know what I think?
I think you let me go because
you went to Australia,
and you didn't want anyone
to know you were there.
Should I tell that to the feds
when they get here?
- Oh, I like you.
- Oh.
Jim. Got a live one, come on.
Sorry...
duty calls.
We caught a multiple
homicide at a restaurant.
Victims were a
lowlife named Keamy
and three goons on his payroll.
Korean female G.S.W. at the scene,
and her boyfriend witnessed it,
but he doesn't speak English.
Any suspects?
Yeah, an A.T.M. surveillance camera
grabbed this jaboney
fleeing the scene.
All righty.
Put a name to that face.
That's our bad guy.
He's different now.
Guess we're all different now.
So what did Locke say to you?
He said that he wants to leave...
and we all have to go together.
- And do you believe him?
- I'm not sure yet.
Hands up.
Stop right there.
Where's the man in charge?
Who's she?
That's Widmore's number two.
What can I do for you?
You took something from
us... and we want it back.
I'm sorry. I don't know
what you're talking about.
It's okay.
- Do you have a fix on my position?
- Roger that.
Show them what we're capable of.
You have until nightfall
to return what you took.
Or next time... we won't miss.
Call me when you're ready
for us to pick him up.
Well...
here we go.
Uh, hi. I have an appointment
with the Western
Pacific adoption agency.
15th floor. And sign in, please.
Sure.
Hey there.
How are you?
Uh, we met at the airport...
the... uh, the baggage claim.
- Oh, yeah. Hi.
- Nice.
Hi. I'm Desmond.
Desmond Hume.
Um, I never got your name. Uh...
"Claire Littleton."
So... so how you doin'?
Um, I'm okay. Better now.
I actually had a bit of a scare,
- ended up in the hospital.
- Oh, no. I'm sorry. Are you...
Oh, no. It's all good now, so...
Oh, by the way... uh,
you were right...
it's a boy.
I have a nose for these things.
Look, um...
excuse me if this sounds
a bit personal... but, um,
I couldn't help noticing
you're going to an
adoption agency... alone.
Uh... yeah. You're right.
It is personal.
No, I just meant you should
have some... some legal representation.
What, are you a lawyer?
No. No.
But, uh, it just so happens
that I'm on my way to see one.
You know, adoption
contracts are complicated.
And you should be careful
because you could find
yourself in a situation
that's irreversible.
Yeah, I-I don't have
money for a lawyer.
What floor?
Um... I'm-
I'm going to 15 as well.
Look... this, um, this attorney
I'm seeing... she's excellent.
Uh, you know... plus,
she owes me a favor.
So...
why don't you just
come and meet her?
You know, I think she
could really help you.
Look, I promise you...
it won't cost you a cent.
Please.
It'd be my absolute pleasure.
Uh, sure.
Great... this way.
Thanks.
Hi. Uh, Desmond Hume to
see Ms. Verdansky, please.
Oh, yes. Mr. Hume.
She's expecting you.
- Have a seat.
- Great.
Hey, um... thank you.
You're very welcome.
- Desmond!
- Ah, Ilana.
Uh, Claire, this is Ilana.
Ilana, I'd like you to
meet a friend of mine...
Claire Littleton. Um...
I was hoping you'd
be able to help her.
I'm sorry.
Claire Littleton from Australia?
Um, do I know you?
No, but this is
quite a coincidence.
We've been looking for you.
Desmond, do you mind if I
speak with Ms. Littleton alone
for a few minutes?
No. Absolutely fine.
Go right ahead.
Listen up, everyone.
Hey.
What's going on?
People are trying
to kill us again.
All this is happening a bit
sooner than I'd expected...
but these people
have forced our hand.
Claiming we stole
something from them...
trying to provoke us
into a confrontation.
Well, if that's what they want,
that's what they'll get.
Gather your things.
We're going to the other island
and we're getting on that plane.
James, I need your
help with something.
There's a boat moored
just a few hours down
the shore from here.
I want you to get it...
and meet the rest of us
on the other side
of these bluffs.
We'll all sail over to the
other island together.
Can you do that, James?
How come we're not all
heading for it together?
The bigger the group,
the slower it moves.
All right. I could use
another pair of hands.
Take whoever you want.
How about it, Freckles...
know anything about sailing?
I know enough.
Good. We'll be waitin' for you.
Sayid, you got a minute?
Can you give me a
hand with somethin'?
Listen up, 'cause I'm
only gonna say this once.
We're not going to that
rendezvous point
to pick up Locke.
I got a deal with Widmore.
What kind of deal?
Just listen.
First chance you get...
you double back,
hoof it to this spot.
There's an old dock.
Grab Hugo, Sun and Lapidus.
Kate and I will meet you there.
What about Sayid and Claire?
Sayid's a zombie
and Claire's nuts.
She gave up her ticket when
she tried to kill Kate...
and I ain't gonna let
that happen again.
That's Hugo, Sun and the pilot.
Only them... understand?
But how am I supposed to get
us away from... from Locke?
You figure it out.
Ready to roll?
- What was that all about?
- Guy talk.
I need you to go out to
where I've got Desmond.
I thought you weren't
going to give him back.
I'm not...
you're gonna kill him.
And that's not gonna be
a problem... is it, Sayid?
You do still want what
you asked me for, right?
Yes, I do.
Then go do what I said.
So what did he offer you?
If you're gonna shoot me
in cold blood, brother...
I think I have a right to know
what you're gettin'
in exchange for it.
He told me I could get
something back I lost.
And what did you lose?
The woman I loved.
And where is she now?
Dead.
And what makes you think
Locke can bring her back?
I died...
and he brought me back.
So what will you tell her?
What do you mean?
This woman...
when she asks you what you
did to be with her again...
what will you tell her?
Sayid.
What's going on?
Everything will be
okay for you now.
I took care of it.
What do you mean?
Where are you going?
I have to leave.
Did you hurt someone?
Nadia... I'm leaving,
and I'm never going to be
able to come back again.
What did you do, Sayid?
Stall them.
Who is it?
L.A.P.D.
May I see some identification?
Can you open the door, please?
Mrs. Jarrah,
I'm Detective Straume.
I need to ask you
some questions.
Do you have a few minutes?
That's good. Stay down.
Sayid Jarrah?
You're under arrest.
There she blows.
You ready to get wet?
Oh.
You sure this is a good idea?
You see a bridge?
- Going back to get Locke.
- Of course not.
It's a terrible idea.
Which is why we ain't doing it.
What?
We're gonna ditch Locke.
You, me, Jack, Hurley, Sun and
that pilot that looks like
he's stepped off the set
of a Burt Reynolds movie.
When were you planning
on telling me this?
Now.
Wait. You didn't say Claire.
'Cause she ain't comin'.
The Claire you came
back for is gone.
I promised I would
bring her back.
That was before she started
drinkin' Locke's kool-aid.
She's dangerous.
You really want her around Aaron?
Let's go. We ain't
got much time.
Hey, Claire.
Jack.
How long have you
been with Locke?
Ever since you left.
So you trust him?
Yeah.
Why?
'Cause he's the only one
that didn't abandon me.
Sun... have you seen Sayid?
He was supposed to catch up with
us about a half a mile back.
Oh, the silent treatment?
I'm sorry, Sun... but I
didn't do anything to you.
James should be
on his way by now.
Just keep everyone
moving to the beach.
- I'll catch up with you there.
- where are you going?
I wanna make sure
nobody got left behind.
- Hurley, wait up.
- Yeah?
Sun.
We have to go now.
- Go where?
- There's no time.
We just gotta go. Follow me.
Um, I think we should
stick to Sawyer's plan,
- or he'll be really pissed.
- This is Sawyer's plan. Let's go.
Sayid?
Where have you been?
Doing what you asked.
Then what took you so long?
I just shot an unarmed man.
I needed a moment.
Did you kill him, Sayid?
Of course I did.
Go and check if you like.
Come on. We have
a boat to catch.
I hope you know
where you're going...
'cause that smoke thing
runs a hell of a lot
faster than we do.
Sawyer said there'd be a
dock around here somewhere.
There they are!
Hey.
All right. Let's go.
Everybody on-board. Let's go!
We sailin' home on this, huh?
Won't work... not without a bearing.
For three years,
the only way Dharma folk
ever got on or off
this island was by sub.
So that's what we're doing.
Nice job, doc.
Uh-oh.
Where you going?
Claire...
It's okay.
Kate.
We're leaving the island.
Then, uh, why aren't
you waiting for John?
Because that's not John.
And whoever he is,
he's not one of us.
Claire...
come with us.
I can get you back to Aaron.
- Wait a damn min...
- Sawyer, shut up. She is coming or I'm not.
Come with us, Claire.
- John promised me...
- No, I'm promising you.
I was there when he was born.
And I never should've
raised him.
It should've been you.
I came back to get you so
you could be with him again.
It's the only reason I came
back to the island, Claire.
So, please, come with us.
Let's go home.
All right. Get on the boat
before Locke gets here.
He finds out we're gone...
he's gonna be mad.
It's your mom.
Hey.
Yeah, we just got here.
Thank you.
Uh... I don't know.
I'll have him home as soon as I can.
Maybe, like, 5:00?
Actually, um, we might grab
a bite to eat afterwards.
So, uh... maybe more like 7:00?
All right.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll drop him off.
Hey.
You know,
hearing your grandfather's
will being read...
I know it's not the
most fun, but...
it'll be over soon, I promise.
And it's... it's okay to be sad.
I'm sad for you, dad.
Let's go.
Mr. Shephard.
Hello.
- And you must be David.
- Hi.
We're set up in the
conference room.
I've got a surprise for you.
Do you believe in fate?
This is Claire Littleton.
Claire, this is Mr. Shephard
and his son David.
Hello.
I'm... I'm Jack Shephard.
Hi, it's, uh, it's
really nice to meet you.
You found her.
Actually, she found us.
Uh...
You were in my father's will.
Do you mind if I ask
you how you knew him?
He was my father, too.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
This is the, uh,
this is the service.
Yeah, this is Dr. Shephard.
No, no, it's not
a very good time.
Yes, they can go
ahead and prep him.
I'm 20 minutes away.
I'm so sorry. There's been
an emergency at the hospital...
and, um...
we're gonna have to reschedule.
I know I'm a little late
to the party, Captain...
but you mind filling us in
on what your game plan is?
My plan, Chesty...
is to land on hydra island,
get ourselves nice and
cuddly with Widmore
until we get a chance
to jump on that sub.
Then I'm gonna put a
gun in someone's face
and make 'em take us home.
I like that idea.
I saw some canned food
down in the galley...
anybody else starvin'?
Freckles... take the wheel a minute?
Sure.
Be nice.
Yeah, yeah.
Didn't think you'd show up, doc.
Sorry?
Taking orders ain't
your strong suit.
Nice to see you
finally came around.
This doesn't feel right.
What doesn't feel right?
Leaving the island.
You wanna tell me why not?
Because I remember how I
felt last time I left...
like a part of me was missing.
They got pills for that, doc.
We were brought here
because we're supposed
to do something, James.
And if Locke... that... that thing...
wants us to leave...
maybe it's afraid of what
happens if we stay.
Get off my damn boat.
What?
You got a decision to
make and you make it now.
Either you're with us...
you keep that damn
crazy talk to yourself,
- or you're going in the water.
- James, this is a mistake.
And I know there's a part
of you that feels that.
The island is not
done with us yet.
Yeah, well, I'm done
with this island.
So if you wanna take a leap
of faith, Jack... then take it.
Get off my damn boat.
I'm sorry that I
got Juliet killed.
Jack?!
- What did you say to him?
- He changed his mind.
What do you mean,
he changed his mind?!
- What did you say to him?
- He ain't comin' with us.
We have to go back and get him.
We're done going back, Kate.
So all these years, you had no
idea your dad
had another kid?
Nope. None.
Wow. I can't believe he
never even mentioned her.
Yeah, well, your grandfather
kept a lot of things to himself.
Is that where you get it from?
Yeah, probably.
All right. Uh...
- you gonna be okay hangin' while I do this?
- Uh, yeah, sure.
Good luck, dad.
Thanks.
Car V. Ped.
How bad?
Bad.
But here's the kicker...
the victim was already
in a wheelchair.
Pre-existing spinal condition.
Dural sac's obliterated.
That's why we called you.
We're in a bit over our heads here.
Yeah.
I got this.
- We ready to cut?
- Say the word.
Scalpel.
What is it?
I think I know this guy.
Nice day for a swim.
Sawyer took my boat, didn't he?
Yeah.
Everybody stay close.
The camp's over here.
We're not gonna have much time
before Locke figure's out
we made off with his ride.
- Hands up!
- Hey! Whoa!
- Whoa! Take it easy!
- Drop your weapons! Drop 'em!
Drop 'em now!
It's all right. I know him.
Who else is with you?
Nobody! If you're
wondering where Locke is...
he's still back on
the main island.
Turn the fences off.
Ford just showed up on a boat
with five of his friends.
Sun?
Jin?
- Jin!
- Sun!
I love you.
I love you, too.
I never stopped looking for you.
Looks like someone
got their voice back.
We'll never be apart again.
I promise you.
Are you sure?
I-I understand, Charles.
That Widmore?
What the hell are you doin'?
What's it look like I'm doin'?
Hands up now.
On your knees, all of you!
Down!
- We had a deal!
- Deal's off.
We got 'em.
If you've got a sight-line on Locke,
fire when ready.
Roger.
Get down!
Jack... you all right?
Don't worry. It's gonna be okay.
You're with me now.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Edited by Scooby