Mr. Hume.
My name is Zoe.
I know you're disoriented.
You've been unconscious for the last three days.
But you're off the I.V. sedation now.
And I've just given you a shot to help you wake up.
Are you a nurse?
You're not in a hospital anymore, Mr. Hume.
We had to move you.
What? Move... move me? Move me where?
Where's my wife?
No. Wait. Mr... you shouldn't... you shouldn't...
I wanna see Penny.
I'm afraid that's not gonna be possible, Desmond.
You.
Mr. Hume...
- Easy. Easy. I'll take it from here.
- You should sit.
Desmond.
What happened to me? Where am I?
You were shot by Benjamin Linus.
Do you remember that?
Yes, I remember.
Yeah, I wanna talk to Penny. Penny!
She's not here. But I assure you,
both she and your son are perfectly safe.
I'm really sorry for taking you away from them,
but I didn't have a chance to explain, and...
if I had, you never would've come with me.
Come with you?
Come with you where?
I brought you back to the island.
I... can't imagine how you must be feeling.
But if you'll give me a chance to explain...
- Damn it! Don't hurt him!  - You take me back!
- You take me back right now, you hear!?
- I can't take you back.
The island isn't done with you yet.
Aah!
What is Desmond doing here?
It will be easier for me
to show you than to tell you, Mr. Kwon.
Take him with you to the generator room.
I'll be along with Hume so we can start the test.
Charles, that... that... that test isn't scheduled till tomorrow.
I know when it's scheduled. Get them ready now.
Come on. No time for sightseeing.
They're bringing Hume down now.
- What?!
- You heard me. We are go right now.
- What's your time Frame?
- We're not even close to being ready.
This generator probably hasn't run in 20 years.
- How am I supposed to...
- Widmore doesn't want to wait.
- What are you doing here?
- Running a little test.
- What kind of test?
- All right, let's see where we are.
- Can we get a functioning M. Field going, people?
- Sure thing.
- Let's try a power test. Generator to full, please.
- Okay.
Okay.
Here we go. On my count...
Three... Two... One.
And power on.
Great.
We probably got a faulty contact somewhere. Find it.
Simmons, go down and check the circuits on the solenoids.
- Yes, sir.
- Try it again.
Guess what, Angstrom?
You're going in there next.
Found it!
It's a bad breaker on the genny.
- Bringing it back online now.
- No!
No!
Turn it off! Turn it off!
Zoe.
- Are we ready?
Stop.
You can take him now. Thank you.
Put him inside.
No! Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
Uhh! Aah!
- I know how this looks, Desmond.
- Aah!
But if everything I've been told about you is true,
you'll be perfectly fine.
You don't have any metal on you, do you? Keys? Change?
Of course he doesn't, you idiot.
I hate to resort to forcing this upon you, Desmond...
But once it's over,
I'm going to ask you to make a sacrifice.
And I hope, for all our sakes, you'll help me.
Sacrifice?
What the bloody hell do you know about sacrifice?
My son died here for the sake of this island.
Your wife...  my own daughter...
hates me.
And I've never even met my grandson.
But if you won't help me, Desmond,
all of it will be for nothing.
Penny, your son and everyone else
will be gone... forever.
Aah!
Uhh!
All right. Turn it on.
No. If you want me to help you with whatever you're doing here,
you need to explain to me...
That man is the only person I'm aware of in the world
who has survived a catastrophic electromagnetic event.
I need to know that he can do it again,
or we all die.
Turn it on.
- Do we have full power?
- Yeah, but...
Let me out!
Let me out of here, you bastards!
Let me out of here!
It's Carousel 4.
Sorry?
You were on the Sydney flight, right?
- Yeah.  - Our bags are on Carousel 4.
I double-checked it with the dude at the counter.
Thank you.
Hang on. I've got it. I got it.
Thank you so much.
Pleasure.
Do you have any more bags?
No. Uh, that's it, thank God.
- Boy or a girl?  - Um...
- Oh, I'm sorry. I... I... I didn't mean to pry.
- Oh, no, no. It's... it's fine.
I just, um... I don't know what it is.
Oh, right.
Well, you're braver than I. I'm not a big fan of surprises.
Oh, excuse me. That's mine.
So... have... have you got someone meeting you?
Uh, yeah. I... I don't know. Maybe they got the...
Flights mixed up or something.
Because I've got a car picking me up.
You know, if you need a ride,
I'd be more than happy to give you a lift.
Oh, no, no, no. That's, um, that's really sweet of you,
- But I'm... I'm good. There's cabs, so...
- Oh. Oh, all right. Yeah.
- Well, it was nice meeting you.
- Yeah, nice to meet you, too.
A boy.
- What?
- I bet it's a boy.
... Lockers located at Baggage Claim Entrance.
Detailed baggage claim information on...
Looks like I'm with you.
Mr. Hume. Hello. Let me grab that for you.
Thank you.
- My name is George.
- Hi, George.
So I will take you back to your hotel?
The office.
Office. Wonderful. Um, this way, please.
So, uh, you... you flew in from Sydney, huh?
Yeah. That's right.
And what... what were you doin', uh....
Down Under?
I was closing a deal for the boss.
Oh. Good for you. Congratulations.
Hey, listen, if you need anything at all
while you're in town, I know everyone.
If you need a reservation, you just pick a restaurant.
Uh, the Room Service at the hotel is excellent.
Thank you.
You, uh,
you looking, uh, for some company?
Well, I noticed that you weren't wearing a wedding band,
and there are a lot of lovely ladies
offering their, uh, "companionship."
I'm not looking for any companionship.
I'm here to work.
Guess that's why you're e boss's right-hand man,
and I am the driver.
Okay. Got it.
- Good morning, Mr. Hume. How was your flight?
- Lovely, thank you.
- He said to send you right in.
- Thank you.
Charles.
Hello, Desmond.
Welcome to Los Angeles, my friend.
Thank you.
I don't give a bloody damn what he did
or how much it's going to cost.
Just get him arraigned and get him out of there.
Sorry, Desmond.
Looks like our celebration of the Australian deal
is gonna have to be cut short.
You are aware that my son is a musician?
Yes. I've heard he's quite talented.
Yeah, he is, quite.
Anyway, my wife is putting together
one of her charity events,
and, uh, the boy had the crazy idea
to combine classical music with modern rock.
Have you heard of a band called Drive Shaft?
No can't say I have.
Their bass guitarist overdosed and, uh, got himself arrested.
And now if I don't get this junkie to my wife's event,
she will, simply put, destroy me.
- So you want me to babysit him.
- I know it's beneath you,
but I need someone I can trust to do the job right.
Say no more, Charles. It's done.
You really do have the life, son.
No family,
no commitments.
Ah, to be free of attachments.
I'm a blessed man, sir.
No, it is I who am blessed
to have you in my employ.
A drink to celebrate your indispensability.
That's your 60-year-old Scotch, Charles.
Nothing's too good for you.
Slaninte.
Mr. Hume?
That's right.
Bail's all been taken care of.
Remember, he's not allowed to leave the state.
Mr. Pace, I'm Desmond Hume.
Charles Widmore sent me...
Hey.
Where you going?
He's all yours.
Hey!
Hey! What's wrong with you?!
Come on.
Yeah, I'll have whatever he's having.
One drink, then we go.
So what's your job then...  to babysit me?
What are you? Mr. Widmore's chief lackey?
Henchman?
No title.
Plenty of perks, though.
Mm. Such as?
I get to meet charming people.
Well... Cheers, then.
Tell me, perky. Are you happy?
Quite.
No, you're not.
Well, I've got a great job, lots of money,
Travel the world. Why wouldn't I be happy?
- Have you ever been in love?
- Dozens of times.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about spectacular, consciousness-altering love.
Do you know what that looks like?
I wasn't aware that love looked like anything.
I've seen it, mate...  on the plane back from Sydney.
Is that so?
Well, we were on the same flight, so...
maybe I saw it, too.
Trust me. You didn't.
No? Enlighten me.
There was this woman
two rows in front of me...  in handcuffs...
sittin' with a cop.
He looked at me,
knew I was holding.
If I didn't take action, I'd be caught.
So I got up, went to the lav...
proceeded to eliminate the evidence
by swallowing my stash.
And at that exact moment,
we hit turbulence.
I choked.
The entire bag of heroin is stuck in my throat.
It's, uh, it's over. Everything starts to go dark.
I'm slippin' into the abyss, and then...
I see... her.
"Her"?
A woman.
Blonde.
Rapturously beautiful.
And I know her.
We're together.
It's like...
You've always been, and...
always will be.
This...
feeling, this...
love.
And just as I'm about to be engulfed by it.
I open my eyes,
and this sodding idiot
is standing there, asking me if I'm okay.
But I saw it.
Just for a moment, I saw what it looked like.
Well, that's just...
poetry, brother.
You know, you should... you should write a song about that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I know what you're saying.
"Poor suicidal rock star."
But I've seen something real. I've seen the truth.
No, that's not the truth.
You wanna know the real truth, Pace?
Right now you have a choice.
You can keep on drinkin', or you can come with me.
Now before you make your choice, realize that if you stay here,
it will very likely result
in the extermination of your musical career.
And if I go with you?
20 minutes,
you'll be luxuriating in a five-star hotel,
right on the harbor front. Charles Widmore,
one of the most powerful men in this town,
will owe you favor.
Doesn't really seem like a choice.
There's always a choice, brother.
# You all, everybody #
- # You all, everybody #  - That's my band.
- # Acting like you're stupid people #  - Drive shaft.
- Our first single.  - # Wearing expensive clothes #
The beginning of everything great.
# You all, everybody #
You like it?
- # You all, everybody #  - Sure. For what it is.
I feel sorry for you, mate.
You think you're happy. You think you got it all.
This... your life.
But you don't.
Hmm. Why, because none of it's real?
# You all... #
All right, Mr. Hume. How about I offer you a choice?
What's that?
I can either show you what I'm talking about,
or you can get out of the car.
Why in god's name would I want to get out of...
Charlie! Charlie!
Come on!
Come on, damn it!
You sustained a pretty bad bump in your accident.
Any nausea?
Nope.
- Double vision?
- No.
Listen, I need to find the man that I was brought in here with.
How about hallucinations?
What do you mean?
Hallucinations. Seeing things that aren't there.
Um...
I'm not sure.
Well, your C.A.T. scan was inconclusive.
I'm gonna send you downstairs for an M.R.I.
No, I don't have time for this.
- I need to find the man I came in here with.
- I'm afraid you're not finding anyone
till we know what's going on inside your brain.
Are you wearing any metal, carrying keys or chains?
Any metal inside your body...  pacemakers, pins, bullets?
- Steel plate inside of your head?
- No, nothing.
I see you didn't list an emergency contact.
No friends or family?
Um...
Just put down my employer...  Charles Widmore.
This machine is super loud.
You're gonna want these.
And you need the button.
- Button?
- Panic button.
You need to stop, press it. But try not to,
'cause we'll have to start all over again from the beginning.
I'll be in that booth over there.
You'll be able to hear me. 30 minutes, okay?
Okay, here we go.
Desmond?
Hey!
Hey, let me out of here!
- What happened, man? Are you all right?
- I need to find the man I came in here with.
I need to find the man I came in here with.
His name is Charlie Pace. He came in an hour ago.
- If you'd just give me his room number...
- If you're not a relative, that's confidential information.
Look, we were in an accident together. I need to see him.
Sorry, sir. There's nothing I can do.
Hey.
E... excuse me.
Um... We were on the same Oceanic flight.
Um, from Sydney.
Yeah, yeah. You were, uh, you were sitting next to me.
- Desmond, right?
- Yeah, that's right.
Listen, I-I wonder if you can help me, brother.
I need to find someone. He was on our plane.
- He's somewhere in the hospital.
- Wait. He was on our plane,
and now he's here in the hospital?
- None of this matters! None of this matters!
- No! Sir, please! Stop!
Take it easy.
- Why you running?
- 'Cause no one here can help me. Now let me go.
- Why'd you try and kill me?
- I didn't try and kill you.
I was trying to show you something.
- You wanna show me something? Show me your hand.
- What?
Your hand. Show me your bloody hands now.
You saw something, didn't you?
In the water.
What was it?
What are you looking for, mate?
Who's Penny?
I don't know.
Ah.
- You felt it, didn't you? I didn't feel anything.
- Then why are you accosting a man in a dressing gown?
- All right, come on. We're leaving.
Whoa! You think I'm gonna go play a rock concert after this?
This doesn't matter.
None of this matters.
All that matters is that we felt it.
You wanna try and stop me? Good luck.
Hey. Where you going?
If I were you, I'd stop worrying about me
and start looking for Penny.
What do you mean he's gone?
He knocked over a doctor with a bloody crash cart
- and then ran out of hospital.
- And you let him go?
He's a junkie who drove my car into the ocean, Charles.
- I'm fine, by the way. Thanks for asking.
- And I'm thrilled you survived, Desmond.
But when I give you a job to do, I expect you to do it.
- With all due respect, sir, it's just a bloody concert.
- I'll tell you what, Desmond.
If you can't deliver Pace,
why don't you tell Mrs. Widmore it's only a bloody concert?
Mr. Hume.
So you've never met the boss's wife, huh?
No.
Good luck.
Please tell me how it is
that someone in your line of work is not aware
that the butter knife is placed handle to the right?
- Blade facing left just so.
- Okay.
For god sake.
Mrs. Widmore?
Yes?
My name is Desmond Hume. I work for your husband.
Oh, of course, Mr. Hume.
Charles has told me so much about you.
It's a travesty we haven't met before.
Well, it's about time.
Well, the feeling is mutual, Mrs. Widmore.
Oh, please. It's Eloise.
Eloise.
So, uh, what crisis forced Charles
to send his best fix-it man
into the bowels of charity balls?
Well, Eloise, um...
I'm deeply sorry,
but it appears as if, uh, Drive Shaft
won't be able to perform alongside your son.
And, um, I take full responsibility...
Don't worry about it.
Excuse me?
Oh, my son will understand.
I suppose if one employs so-called rock stars,
a certain unpredictability comes with the territory.
Yeah. Y... you're not angry?
Oh, not at all, dear.
What happened, happened.
Thank you so much, Mr. Hume,
For coming and telling me in person.
- A pleasure meeting you.
- And you. Thank you.
Uh, center that flower arrangement, please.
Have a good evening.
Thank you.
Leifer, Stephanie... plus two.
Markey, Mary... plus one.
Milton, Penny... solo.
Pepper, Nicholas... plus one.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry. Um...
Did you just say "Penny"?
- And who are you?
- Um, I work for Mr. Widmore. May I see the list?
You absolutely may not.
That list is confidential.
Begging your pardon,
I... I'm entrusted with confidential items every day...
Are you questioning me?
No, I... just want to look at one name on that list.
- And if, for some reason, that's a problem...
- Come with me.
Out, everyone. Now.
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry if I've overstepped my bounds, but I just...
Stop talking, Hume.
I've heard what you've had to say. Now you listen to me.
I want you to stop.
Stop? S... stop what?
Someone has clearly affected the way you see things.
This is a serious problem. It is, in fact, a violation.
So whatever you're doing,
whatever it is you think you're looking for...
you need to stop looking for it.
Do you...
do you know what I'm looking for, Mrs. Widmore?
I don't know why you're looking for anything.
You have the perfect life.
On top of it, you've managed to attain
the thing you wanted more than anything...
My husband's approval.
How do you know what I want?
Because I bloody do.
I need to see that list...
Or you need to tell me why I can't.
You can't because you're not ready yet, Desmond.
Ready?
Ready? R... ready for what?
That bad, huh?
Is there any alcohol in this car?
Oh, yeah.
Whatever you need.
So, uh...
Where to, Mr. Hume?
Just drive, George.
- Mr. Hume.  - Yes?
My name is Daniel. Daniel Widmore.
We need to talk.
Look, uh, Mr. Widmore, um...
Dan. Please, call me Dan.
"Mr. Widmore" is my father.
Dan, um, look, if... if this is about Charlie Pace
not being able to perform with you,
I'm... I'm very sorry.
Do you believe in love at first sight, Mr. Hume?
Excuse me?
The first time I saw her, I was walking through this museum
a few weeks ago.
She... she works here. She was on her lunch break.
She was eating a chocolate bar.
She has these incredible blue, blue eyes, red hair.
And as soon as I saw her,
right... right in that moment, it was like...
it was like I already loved her.
And that's when things got weird.
That same night after I saw that woman...
I woke up and I wrote this.
So what is it?
I'm a musician. I have no idea.
So I took it to a friend of mine at Caltech.
He's a math whiz. He said this is quantum mechanics.
He said these equations are so advanced that
only someone who'd been studying physics their entire life
could've come up with them.
So...
so what do they mean?
Okay, imagine... imagine something terrible is about to happen,
something catastrophic.
And the only way to stop it from happening
was by...
releasing a huge amount of energy.
Like setting off a nuclear bomb.
You wanna set off a nuclear bomb?
Just listen. What if this... all this...
what if this wasn't supposed to be our life?
What if we... we had some other life
and for some reason, we changed things?
I don't want to set off a nuclear bomb, Mr. Hume.
I think I already did.
Listen, mate, um...
I don't know what any of this has to do with me. So...
Why did you ask my mother about a woman named Penny?
It happened to you, too, didn't it?
You felt it.
I don't know...
I don't know what I felt.
Yes, you do.
You felt love.
That's impossible because
I don't know anything about this woman.
I don't know... I don't know where she is.
I don't even know if she exists.
She's...
She's an idea.
No, Mr. Hume.
She's my half-sister.
And I can tell you exactly where and when you can find her.
Excuse me?
Yeah?
Are you Penny?
Uh, yes.
Hello.
I'm Desmond.
Uh, hi.
Checking in now.
He's okay.
Indeed he is.
How are you, Desmond? How are you feeling?
Fine.
H... how long was I unconscious for?
Oh, no more than a few seconds.
Will you help me up, please?
I'm really sorry we had to do this to you, Desmond.
But as I told you, your... talent is vital to our mission.
So if you just let me explain...
It's all right. I understand.
What?
I said I understand.
You told me you brought me here to the island
to do something very important.
Yeah.
When do we start?
What happened to you?
What do you mean?
What I mean is 20 minutes ago,
you were beating the crap out of Widmore with an I.V. Stand,
and... and now you're Mr. Cooperative.
A lot can happen in 20 minutes.
Sure it can.
That thing fried your brain.
Did it?
Whatever. Doesn't change that you're gonna...
Run.
Desmond, I don't have time to explain,
but these people are extremely dangerous.
We need to go now.
Aye, of course.
Lead the way.
Hello? You okay?
What happened?
Well, I shook your hand, and then you fainted.
I must have quite an effect on you.
Aye.
Aye, you must have.
Have we met before?
I... I think we'd remember it if we have
Yeah.
Well, as long as you're sure you're all right...
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hey, listen. Um...
Would you like to go for a coffee?
What, now?
I'm a sweaty mess.
I just fainted in front of you.
I'd say we're even.
There's a coffee shop
on the corner of Sweetzer and Melrose.
I'll meet you there in an hour.
Absolutely.
- Okay.
So... did you find what you were looking for?
Yes, George, I did.
Corner of Melrose and Sweetzer, please.
You got it.
And if there's anything else I can do for you, Mr. Hume,
you just name it.
Actually, there is one thing, George.
Can you get me the manifest from my flight from Sydney?
Oceanic 815.
Just the names of the passengers.
Sure, I can.
Do you mind if I ask you what you need it for?
I just need to show them something.