Previously on Lost.
Anything over $10,000
has to be declared.
You... didn't declare this.
Sir, you're gonna
have to come with me.
- I told you people, I don't know anything!
- Dude, just calm down!
Why did you follow me?!
Your wife sent me!
There's something we have to do.
She said you have to stop
the man in black.
You have to stop him
from leaving the island.
What's on Hydra Island?
A plane. The same plane
that brought your friends back.
So I want you to go over there
and do some recon.
Who are you?
Put your weapon down!
Take me to your leader.
So why don't you tell me what
brought you over to this island?
John Locke sent me.
Well, here's the deal, chief.
I'll go back over there
and tell him the coast is clear,
that I didn't find anybody.
Then I'll bring the old man
right to your doorstep.
And what do you want
in exchange, James?
You give us safe passage
off the island.
Want some cocoa?
Where'd you find cocoa?
I didn't. Pretend.
How's the leg?
Still hurts.
You should leave the bandage off
for a while. The air'll do it some good.
I'll try that.
You mind if I sit down?
I know you and I haven't
had time to talk,
but I was wondering
if James had filled you in
on what I showed him
at the cliffs.
You mean the cave. The one
with the names on the wall.
Most of the names
have been crossed off now.
There are just a few left.
"Kwon" is one of them.
Does that mean me or Sun?
Well, Jin, I'm not sure.
But what it does mean is that
the only way we can leave the island
is if all the names
that haven't been crossed off
go together.
But Sun's not here.
You just take care
of that leg.
I'm workin' on it.
All right, Mr. Kwon,
here's your suitcase
and your watch.
Money?
I'm sorry. Federal law says we have
to confiscate your $25,000.
- C-confiscate?
- It means that if you want it back,
you're gonna have to fill out
the necessary paperwork.
Uh... money.
You can exit
right over there, sir.
May I help you?
Paik.
A reservation for Paik.
Yes.
I've got it right here.
We've got a beautiful ocean view
room for you on the 8th floor.
Two room. Two.
No marry.
Oh.
Kwon. Jin Soo Kwon.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Yes, there is a separate
room reservation for Kwon.
Room 842. Here you go, sir.
Miss. Paik, Mr. Kwon,
welcome to Los Angeles.
I'm leaving for a little while.
I got an errand to run.
When will you be back?
Morning.
Keep an eye on the camp
while I'm gone.
I don't feel anything.
Excuse me?
Anger,
happiness...
pain.
I don't feel it anymore.
Maybe that's best, Sayid.
It'll help you get through
what's comin'.
What are you doin', Hoss?
I'm getting out of here
before that thing comes back.
What thing?
Locke.
And you're just
sitting around here,
- listening to whatever he tells you.
- I ain't listenin' to nobody.
I already told you
I have a deal with Widmore.
So if you just calm...
It doesn't matter who
you have a deal with.
I've waited long enough.
I'm going to find my wife.
- Find her where?
- I'll go back to the temple.
And if she's not there,
I'll try the beach.
But I will find Sun,
so stop trying to...
Go! Uhh!
Aah!
Uhh!
Is this the guy?
Yeah. Let's take him.
Lost Season 6 Episode 10
"The package"
Play your card, Captain.
Now what?
We wait.
Wait... for what?
For Richard to come back.
You'll forgive my scepticism, but
the last thing Richard said before
he went stomping off into the jungle,
was that we were all in hell,
and he had no idea what
we were supposed to do next.
In fact, I would bet money
we never see him again.
Hugo will find him.
He will track him down
and bring him back.
Unless Alpert's covered
in bacon grease,
- I'm not sure Hurley can track anything.
- Hey. Don't talk about bacon.
Jacob has never lied to me before.
If he said Richard knows what to do,
then Richard knows what to do.
He'll come back.
And until then, we wait.
How are the tomatoes?
Dead.
I remember when you
first planted this here.
It feels like a hundred years ago.
You don't believe Alpert's
coming back, do you?
I don't care
if he comes back.
What about us...
being candidates?
What about it?
Hurley took me
to a lighthouse.
To Jacob's lighthouse.
And... there was a mirror,
and all around it, there were...
there were hundreds of
names written down.
I don't care. I don't care about
Alpert or being a candidate.
Sun...
There's a reason why
we were brought...
I don't wanna hear about how
this is our purpose or destiny!
I just want you to go away
and leave me alone.
Sun.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to startle you.
Bad day?
What are you doing here?
I found your husband.
What?
I promised you
I would reunite you two.
Took me a little longer
than I thought it would.
But he's with my people back
at my camp across the island.
I can take you
to him right now.
I don't believe you.
You killed those
people at the temple.
Those people were confused.
They were lied to.
I didn't want to hurt them.
Any one of them could've
chosen to come with me.
And I'm giving you
that choice, Sun, right now.
I would never make you
do anything against your will.
I'm asking you.
Please.
Come with me.
Jin is waiting.
Sun!
Sun, wait!
Miss. Paik.
Hi.
I'm, uh, Martin Keamy.
I'm a friend of your father's.
You mind if I come in?
I believe you've got
something for me. Hmm?
Sun?
Sun, can you hear me?
What happened?
You all right?
I'm sorry, what?
Sun, slow do. Tell me
what happened in English.
Who did this to you?
Locke.
Sayid.
Hey.
What happened?
We were attacked.
By whom?
I don't know.
Where is Jin?
Hey!
Wow, that was weird, huh?
Where am I?
It's called room 23.
The Dharma Initiative
was doing experiments
on subliminal messaging in here.
But you know all about the Dharma
Initiative, don't you Mr. Kwon?
- Why did you bring me here?
- Relax. You're safe.
I'm leaving.
Sorry.
But we went
to a lot of trouble
getting you here
of the other island.
And I can't let you leave.
What do you want from me?
These are grid maps that...
that the Dharma people used
to identify pockets
of electromagnetism.
Whoever signed these
could really help me out.
Uh, I know... I know
the writing's difficult to read,
but... but it sure looks like
it says, "Jin Soo Kwon."
So...
Is it you or isn't it?
You want answers
to your questions?
Then get me your boss.
I want to talk
with Charles Widmore.
Well, then you're in luck...
Mr. Kwon. Because he'd like
to talk to you, too.
You a good swimmer?
- Good enough.
- Wrap this in plastic.
You don't want it to get wet.
We're taking the outrigger.
Something wrong, Claire?
Um...
What... what you said to Jin...
about the names on the wall.
You told him you needed
them all to get off the island.
Yes, I did.
Was, uh... was my name
on the wall?
No.
Well, then it doesn't matter
if I get on that plane, then.
I mean, you don't need me.
No, that's not true
Claire. I need you.
And there's plenty of room
on that plane for all of us.
Well, when we go home,
Aaron's not gonna know me.
Stranger to my own son,
he thinks Kate's his mother.
Is her name on the wall?
No, Claire, it isn't...
not anymore.
But I need Kate.
Why?
Because I'm three people shy
of getting off this island,
and Kate can help me get
these people on that plane.
But once she does...
then whatever happens, happens.
What's up with the guns?
You two going somewhere?
We're taking a boat ride
over to the other island.
What do you need a boat for?
Can't you just turn into smoke
and fly your ass over the water?
Do you think if I could do that,
I would still be on this island?
No, 'cause that'd be
ridiculous.
What the hell you going
over there for, anyway?
I thought you were trying
to avoid Charlie Widmore.
They took one of
our people, James.
So I'm going to get them back.
Oh, this for me?
Uh, this is really nice.
Your bodyguard is supposed
to give me some money.
Where's Mr. Kwon?
No English.
Hmm?
All right. Uh, sit down.
I checked his room.
He's not there.
Check the bathroom.
Come on. Let's go.
Mr. Kwon, why don't you
come and join us?
Look, thank you
for the watch, okay?
But you're also supposed to give me
an envelope with money in it...
$25,000.
Yeah?
Stop that.
I feel like I'm in a
damn "Godzilla" movie.
What's that guy's name? The, um...
The Russian guy... speaks like,
nine different languages.
Uh, uh, Danny's friend.
- Mikhail.
- Mikhail. Can he speak Korean?
- I think so.
- Okay, go get him.
Now put your damn clothes on.
She says the money her father
gave them was taken at customs.
Mm, that's not my problem.
She wants you to let them
please go to the bank.
They will get it for you.
You take her to the bank.
I'll take Casanova here
to the restaurant.
And then we'll meet there.
What's he whining about?
He wants you to promise,
that you won't tell her father
that they are involved.
Oh, hey, don't worry about that.
Okay. Your secret
is safe with me.
Okay? Just bring me the money,
and then we can all live
happily ever after, right?
What?
Oh, for the fourth time,
I was gathering mangoes,
and she was already
unconscious when I found her.
- Why won't you believe me?
- Because you're speaking.
You got a pretty
decent-sized bump.
Might be a slight concussion.
You can understand
what I'm saying,
but you can only speak Korean.
She hits her head
and forgets English?
Are we supposed to buy that?
Asked the man who
communes with the dead.
It might be aphasia.
It's, um, a condition
that's caused by trauma
and affects the language
centre of your brain.
But it's usually temporary.
Sun.
You're gonna be okay.
What are you smiling about?
Pack your bags. We're leaving.
Don't move!
Let me see your hands!
Easy, friend.
I come in peace.
Do you know who I am?
Charles Widmore.
Obviously, you're not John Locke.
Everything else I know
is a combination of myth,
ghost stories and jungle
noises in the night.
I think you know more than that,
judging by these... pylons.
Why did you come here?
You took one of
my people, Jin Kwon.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
A wise man once said that
war was coming to this island.
I think it just got here.
Where exactly are we going, Richard?
- Where's Locke?
- What?
You said he came to recruit you.
Where did he say he'd be?
Hydra Island.
Which is exactly where
you landed the plane
- that you flew back here, right?
- That's right.
This... man wants
to leave the island,
and that plane's the
only way he can do it.
You wanna know where we're
going? We're gonna stop him.
This is your fault, isn't it?
Sort of.
How are you gonna stop him
from getting on that plane?
We have to destroy it.
Why isn't she speaking English?
She was hit on the head when
she was running away from Locke.
He came back here?
What... what did he want?
What did he say to you?
You... you understand me?
I don't think she wants to come.
Miss. Paik would like to know
if there is a problem.
I'm sorry. I'm showing
that your account was closed.
The balance is zero.
If she may ask, who
closed the account, please?
Looks like... her father.
Mr. Woo Jung Paik had access.
The funds were transferred
to one of his other accounts
at our main branch in Seoul.
- Uhh!
- Get in here.
Let's get in.
Come on, get In.
What's going on?
I bumped his head on the door.
Oh, come on Omar. You gotta
be more careful than that.
I got this.
And go get the Arab guy.
Hey. I'm an Arab.
Just go pick him up.
Sorry about that.
Omar's loyal, but he
lacks attention to detail.
You don't really understand a word
I'm saying to you right now, do you?
Nothin'?
All right. Just hold still, okay?
I'm gonna strap you in here.
Just in case you figure out
what's about to happen to you,
I can't have you freaking out.
I don't think you realize...
how unhappy Mr. Paik was
when he found out that
you were doing his little girl.
Well, you know that 25 grand
that you were supposed to deliver?
That was my fee
for popping you.
From what I hear, you know
anyone who works for, Paik
knows the cardinal rule...
hands off the boss' daughter.
But you... you couldn't
resist her, could you?
The heart wants
what the heart wants.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Some people just aren't
meant to be together.
What the hell
were you thinking?
I'm sorry. I know.
I know we panicked.
This was not supposed
to happen for days.
We had a timetable.
See, he was leaving their camp.
Well, you should have let him leave
and taken him in the jungle.
Well, maybe you should put
a mercenary in charge
instead of a geophysicist.
What's done is done.
I need you to get the
package from the submarine
and take it to the infirmary.
Can you do that
for me please, Zoe?
Yeah, sure.
Mr. Kwon.
My deepest apologies for everything
that's been done to you.
- My name is...
- I know who you are.
Why did you bring me here?
We searched the Ajira plane,
discovered your wife's luggage
and found this inside.
I thought you might want
to have it. Go ahead.
Turn it on.
Her name is, Ji Yeon.
Your daughter.
I understand you've never
seen her before.
I have a daughter, too.
I know what it's like
to be kept apart.
I understand the one thing you want
is to be reunited with
your wife and daughter.
But it would be short-lived
if that... thing
masquerading as John Locke
ever got off this island.
Your wife, your
daughter, my daughter...
everyone we know and love...
Would simply cease to be.
I came here to make sure
that doesn't happen.
How?
Come with me.
I think it's time for
you to see the package.
What package?
It's not a "what."
It's a "who."
Who are you?
No English.
I don't know why you're here,
and I don't really care.
No!
Free.
Free!
Good luck.
Martin
Martin?
Who did this to you?
Look behind you, you idiot.
I brought you a couple of things.
I was thinking about a patient
that I had during my residency.
Car crash, banged his head.
When he woke up,
he couldn't talk.
The guy was frustrated. I mean...
who wouldn't be?
And then one of the nurses said,
"just because he can't speak
doesn't mean
that he can't write."
Think you could give it a try?
It'll take a little longer
to get your point across,
but at least you have
your voice back.
I went back out to your garden
to see if he was there.
He wasn't, but...
then I found this.
That's one stubborn tomato.
Guess no one told it
it was supposed to die.
Don't worry about it.
You're not the first person
to tell me to leave them alone.
Locke...
What did he say to you?
Why didn't you go with him?
Do you trust me?
Sun...
come with us, and
I'll help you find Jin.
I'll help you find him, and I'll
get you both on that plane
and as far away from
this island as you can get.
I promise.
Where'd you go?
What?
Looked like your brain
took a little stroll.
Why aren't you worried, James?
I am worried.
Just really good
at pretending I ain't.
But I got a feeling
this is almost over.
'Cause if Locke rode over there
on the boat with Sayid,
then Charlie Widmore blew him
right out of the water.
And what if he didn't?
Well, then we're screwed
six ways from sun...
Oh, hell.
He's alone.
Thought you went
over there to find Jin.
They said they didn't have him.
- And you believed that.
- No.
Where's Sayid, Did
you lose him, too?
When you over there, James,
you mentioned that
Widmore had someone
guarding a room
on his submarine...
guarding something that
he didn't want you to see.
Yeah, so?
I don't like secrets.
Okay, come on. All right.
Hey, be careful with him.
All right.
Okay. The guy can hardly stand.
Well, what do you expect?
Oh!
How much did you give him?
Obviously, I gave him too much.
But, we needed him
knocked out for the trip.
I'm not a nurse.
Come on. Get him up.
Let's go Mr. Hume.
Be careful.
Come on.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Edited by Scooby