Aah! Aah!
That's a lovely name.
Where are the rest
of your people?
There's only me.
How did you get here?
The same way you got here...
by accident.
- How long have you...
- Every question I answer
will simply lead to
another question.
You should rest.
Just be grateful you're alive.
There were other people
on my ship. I need to go...
No.
If there are other people on
the island, I will find them.
The baby?
Oh!
It's coming.
That's it.
Push! Push harder.
I can't!
Yes, you can.
That's good!
One more push.
Oh! Oh!
It's a boy.
His name is Jacob.
Can I...
There's another baby.
Aah!
Push again.
Here it comes.
Now!
It's another boy.
I only picked one name.
Oh. Shh. Shh.
May I see him?
I'm sorry.
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh
Season 6 Episode 15
"Across The Sea"
What is it?
It's a game,
you play it.
How do you know how?
I just know.
Will you show me how to play?
If you promise not
to tell mother.
Why can't we tell her?
Because she'll take it away.
So... do you wanna play
or don't you, Jacob?
Yes. I wanna play.
- Hello, Jacob.
- Hello, mother.
Where's your brother?
He's down at the beach...
Staring out at the ocean.
Can I help you?
If you like, you can sort that.
What were you and your brother
doing down at the beach?
We were just... walking.
Do you love me, Jacob?
Yes.
Then tell me what happened.
May I join you?
Sure.
Jacob told you what I found.
Of course he did.
Jacob doesn't know how to lie.
He's not like you.
Why? What am I like?
You're...
special.
Can I keep the game?
Of course you can.
That's why I left it for you.
It came from you?
Of course it did.
Where else would it come from?
From somewhere else.
Across the sea.
There is nowhere else.
The island is all there is.
Then where did we come from?
You and your
brother came from me -
and I came from my mother.
Where is she?
She's dead.
What's "dead"?
Something you will never
have to worry about.
Hurry up! He's getting away!
Hide!
- Who are they?
- Shh!
Mother!
What's wrong?
We saw people. Men.
- How many were there?
- Three. They killed a boar.
Did they see you?
No.
I don't think so.
Where did they come from?
They looked like us.
They're not like us.
They don't belong here.
We are here for a reason.
What reason?
It's not time yet.
Mother, what reason?
Come with me.
- Did you know about the people?
- Yes.
Why didn't you
tell us about them?
Because they're dangerous, and I
didn't want to frighten you.
What makes them dangerous?
The same thing that
makes all men dangerous.
They come. They fight.
They destroy. They corrupt.
And it always ends the same.
- They "come"? Come from where?
- Another part of the island.
And you're never to go
looking for them.
If they found you,
they would hurt you.
Why would they hurt us?
Because they're people Jacob,
and that's what people do.
But we're people. Does that mean
that we can hurt each other?
I've made it so you can
never hurt each other.
What is this place?
This is the reason we're here.
Don't go in there.
What's down there?
Light.
The warmest,
brightest light
you've ever seen or felt.
And we must make sure
that no one ever finds it.
It's beautiful.
Yes, it is.
And that's why they want it,
because a little bit
of this very same light
is inside of every man.
But they always want more.
Can they take it?
No, but they would try.
And if they tried,
they could put it out.
And if the light
goes out here...
it goes out everywhere.
And so I've protected this place,
but I can't protect it forever.
Then who will?
It will have to be one of you.
- You can't do that, Jacob.
- Why not?
Because it's against the rules.
- You made the rules.
- I found it.
One day, you can make
up your own game,
and everyone else will have
to follow your rules.
It's all right.
Don't be afraid.
What?
What's wrong?
I'm going for a
walk to the beach.
I'll meet you later.
Hello.
Why can't Jacob see you?
Because I'm dead.
Will you come with me?
I'd like to show you something.
Show me what?
Where you came from.
It's across the island,
a place you've never seen.
Who are they?
They came here 13 years ago...
the day before you were born.
Their ship was wrecked
in a storm.
Ship. What's that?
It's a way for people to get
from one place to another.
It's how we came across the sea.
But there's nothing
across the sea.
There are many things
You come from across the sea, too.
No. That's not true.
That's not what
my mother told me.
She's not your mother.
I am.
Jacob.
Jacob, wake up.
Come with me.
Why do you have all your things?
They're our things.
I took them because
we're leaving,
- and we're never coming back.
- What?
Just follow me.
Follow you where?
To the people.
No. We're supposed to
stay away from them.
They're our people, Jacob,
and we're gonna live with them.
No, mother said...
She lied. She lied about
everything... all of it.
I know you don't understand,
but you have to come with me.
- I don't want to go by myself.
- We can't. Mother loves us.
- She doesn't love us.
- stop!
- It was all a lie!
- Stop it!
- She's not even our mother!
- Aah!
No! Jacob!
- What are you doing?
- He's leaving!
He's going to them!
To the other people!
What?
I know now.
There is another place
across the sea.
It's where I'm from,
and I'm gonna go there.
I'm gonna go home.
Who... who told you that?
My mother!
I'm your mother.
You killed my mother.
Jacob...
she was your mother, too.
We don't belong here.
We don't belong with her.
Come with me.
No.
My love, you need to know this.
Whatever you have been told,
you will never be able
to leave this island.
That's not true.
And one day, I can prove it.
- Do you think he'll come back?
- No.
He said you killed our mother.
Is that true?
Yes.
If I had let her live,
she would have taken
you back to her people,
and those people are bad,
Jacob... very bad.
I-I couldn't let you
become one of them.
I needed you to stay good.
Am I good, mother?
Yes. Of course you are.
Then why do you love
him more than me?
I love you in...
in different ways.
Will you stay with me, Jacob?
Please?
Yes.
For a while.
What do you think?
It's very nice, Jacob.
Are you all right?
I'm just tired.
She know you visit me?
She never asks about you.
Then I'm sorry I asked
about her.
Why do you watch us, Jacob?
I watch because I wanna
know if mother's right.
Right about what?
About them.
Oh, you mean my people.
You wanna know if they're bad.
That woman may be insane,
but she's most definitely
right about that.
I don't know.
They don't seem so bad to me.
Well, that's easy
for you to say,
looking down at us
from above. Trust me.
I've lived among
them for 30 years.
They're greedy, manipulative,
untrustworthy...
and selfish.
Then why are you with them?
They're a means to an end.
What end?
I'm leaving, Jacob.
- I found a way off the island.
- No, it's impossible.
There is no way
off the island.
There are very smart
men among us.
Men who are curious
about how things work.
Together, we have discovered
places all over this island
where metal behaves strangely.
When we find one of these sites...
we dig.
And this time we
found something.
Come with me Jacob, please.
What are you gonna
do when she dies?
She's never gonna die.
Jacob, everything dies.
Well, I don't wanna
leave this island.
It's my home.
Well, it's not mine.
Where were you?
You know where I was.
What did he say to you, Jacob?
He said he's finally found
a way to leave the island.
May I join you?
Yes.
How are you?
I'm worried.
Well, mother... you should be.
I've spent 30 years
searching for that place
You brought me as a child.
That... waterfall with
that beautiful light.
I've walked this
island from end to end...
not once coming
close to finding it.
But then I began to think,
What if the light
underneath the island...
what if I could get to
it from someplace else?
Figuring out how to reach
it took a very long time.
The people with you...
they saw this, too?
Yes. They have some
very interesting ideas
about what to do with it.
Do with it? You don't
have any idea wh...
I have no idea because you
wouldn't tell me, mother.
What is that?
It's a wheel.
We're going to
make an opening...
One much bigger than this one.
And then I'm going
to attach that wheel
to a system we're building.
A system that channels
the water and the light.
And then I'm going to turn it.
And when I do...
I'll finally be able
to leave this place.
How do you know all this?
How do you know it will work?
I'm special...
Mother.
Please don't do this.
Don't go.
I have to go.
- Why?
- Because I don't belong here.
Then I suppose this is good-bye.
Good-bye, mother.
I am so sorry.
Aah!
Uhh!
Jacob.
It's time.
Something happened, didn't it?
Yes. I had to say
good-bye to your brother.
You're letting him go?
I don't have a choice.
It's what he wants.
Do you recognize this place?
Yes.
Do you remember what
I showed you here?
The light.
You're going to protect it now.
What's down there?
Life, death...
rebirth.
It's the source,
the heart of the island.
Just promise me...
no matter what you do,
you won't ever go down there.
Would I die?
It'd be worse than dying Jacob.
Much worse.
Here...
drink this.
What happens if I do?
You'll accept the responsibility
that you will protect this
place for as long as you can.
And then you'll have to
find your replacement.
I don't want to
protect this place.
- Someone has to.
- I don't care.
My time is over.
- Why? Why is your time over?
- It has to be you, Jacob.
No, it doesn't.
You wanted it to be him.
But now I'm all you have.
It was always supposed
to be you, Jacob.
I see that now...
and one day you'll see it, too.
But until then...
you don't really have a choice.
Please...
take the cup and drink.
Now you and I...
are the same.
Storm comin'.
Yes, there is.
You should go get some firewood...
before it rains.
Jacob...
be careful.
I'll see you back home.
Why wouldn't you let
me leave, mother?
Because I... I love you.
Thank you.
Jacob.
What'd you do?
Wait. Listen.
- What did you do?
- No.
- What did you do?!
- No. Wait...
Don't. Jacob, don't do this.
She burned them. She was crazy,
she burned them all!
You can't kill me, Jacob.
She made it that way.
You can't!
Don't worry, brother...
I'm not going to kill you.
Uhh!
- She brought you back here?
- Yes.
Why would she?
Because I have to protect it now.
Aah!
You want to find the light?
You want to leave
this place, brother?
Then go.
Uhh!
Who are they?
Where'd they come from?
Didn't you guys shoot a
polar bear last week?
Yeah.
Where'd that come from?
Hello? Anybody there?
Who were these men?
Actually, one of them's female.
Our very own Adam and Eve.
Good-bye, brother.
Good-bye.
Edited by Scooby and addic7ed.com