We gonna sing "kumbaya"
on the way?
It's not a guitar, man.
Then what is it?
You going with them?
No, I'm gonna bury her.
Let me help you.
Help Sayid.
Hey, Miles.
You mind hangin' back?
You got it, boss.
I'll make sure to leave a ail.
I ain't followin' nobody,
kate.
You guys ready?
Whenever you are.
oceanic passenger
Jack shephard.
Jack shephard, please go to
the nearest courtesy desk.
attention
all arriving passengers...
Hi. Uh...
I'm jack shephard.
I was just paged.
Oh, mr. Shephard.
Hello. Yes, that was me.
Uh, sorry, I meant
to meet you at the gate.
Well, um, I'm here now,
so--
Yes. Mr. Shephard,
I am deeply sorry,
But there seems
to have been a mix-up
Involving the, uh... Cargo
you checked in sydney.
Cargo?
Yes,ir. A coffin.
I don't...
I don't understand.
I mean, are--are you saying
that it's not here?
It appears it was never
put on the plane.
The funeral is in two hours.
When is it getting here?
Mr. Shephard, I can't tell you
how deeply sorry we are.
But we don't know
when it will arrive...
Because we're not exactly sure
where it is.
That's a big wall.
How are we gonna get him
over the top?
We're not. We're bringing him
in through here.
Who brings a book into a cave?
And why is his arm missing?
It was ripped off when he was
attacked by the black smoke.
Well... This is gonna
be awesome.
now watch your step.
Yeah.
Okay.
Where's kate?
she's right over there.
Kate?
Kate!
Can you hear me?!
jack!
We can't leave say--
hey! Let--
Hurley! Jin!
Hurley!
You okay?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
Guess we found the temple.
Anything to declare?
Just aderer.
Okay.
I need to go
to the bathroom.
Hold it.
I can't hold it.
Sure you can, kiddo.
I believe in you.
Edward...
Please.
All right. Come on.
Anybody in here?
Is anybody in
the ladies' room?
Don't move.
Okay.
You got two minutes.
Thank you.
Ocks door)
You done?
Not yet.
All right, time's up!
Get out of there.
One minute.
No, open this door right now.
I'm not finished.
Yes, you are. Open it.
austen, I swear to god,
You don't open this door,
I'm coming in there--oh!
Uhh!
Mm.
Although I've seen it before,
it was something... Oh, my god.
I, uh, he--he just
walked in here and attacked me.
I shed h. I-just--
I need to get out of here.
Officer, come quick.
Come quick.
Wait, hold the door!
Welcome aboard.
We were on the same flight.
Sydney.
How about that?
ganson,
calhoun, what's your 20?
Uh, we're on theouth elevator,
headed to ground.
Get your asses
to international baggage claim.
We got a 341.
Yeah. We're on our way.
Sounds serious.
What's a 341?
That's confidential, sir.
Well, if it's confidential,
How the hell am I supposed to
know if I see one?
Uh, sorry.
Excuse me. Ladies first.
Thanks.
Take care.
I think that'll do it,
boss.
Stop calling me "boss."
You ain't my deputy anymore.
You got it.
Are you thirsty? I think I saw
some beers in the van.
Construction guys hid 'em
in the wheel well.
Whathe want to tell me, Miles?
Excuse me?
Juliet.
She said she wanted to tell me
something, and then she died.
What was it, miles?
That's why you asked me
to stay here with you?
You're the only one around
that talks to dead people.
J-jim, that's not
how it works.
What did she wanna
tell me, miles?
It... it doesn't matter.
It does matter.
It's not gonna help.
Just do it. Just ask her...
She's gone, james.
I know she's gone. I know.
Now tell me.
okay.
Okay.
All right.
What?
It worked.
What did she want
to tell me?
That's what she wanted
to tell you.
"it worked."
What worked?
stop right here.
who are you?
I know who they are.
They were on
the first plane...
Eanic 815, along with me.
You sure?
Shoot 'em.
Whoa! No, hey! No! No! No! No!
Jacob sent us! Jacob sent us!
uh, what did--
what did you just say?
I said jacob sent us.
He said you would help
our friend.
He wants you to prove it.
Uh...
no.
He gave me that guitar case!
did you look inside it?
Maybe.
Dude!
what are your names?
Hugo.
Hugo reyes.
Tell him.
Jin-soo kwon.
Kate austen.
Jack shephard.
What about him?
Sayid jarrah.
Pick him up.
Get him to the spring.
Hey! Excuse me.
I carried that case
Across the ocean
and, like, through time,
So I wanna know
what that paper says.
That paper said that if
your friend there dies...
We're all
in a lot of trouble.
And what business
are you in, sir?
No english.
Be prepared to show
your passport to customs...
This letter says
the watch is a business gift.
But can you tell me
what business you're in?
Step back, sir.
What are you doing
with this?
Anything over $10,000
has to be declared.
You... Didn't...
Declare this.
Sir, you're gonna
have to come with me.
Let's go have a talk--
This way.
Anne, taer
to the waiting area.
Ms. Paik?
Do you understand
any english?
Because if you do,
If this is just
a misunderstanding,
You should speak up now.
Do you understand me?
No... English.
The water isn't clear.
What happened?
What is he doing?
I don't know.
Who did this to him?
It's my fault. I-I didn't
shoot him, but it's my fault.
If we do this,
there are risks.
You understand?
Do what you have to do.
Take off the coveralls,
put him in.
What are they doing?
Can unconscious people
hold their breath? - No.
He's awake. Let him up.
What are they waiting for?
That's enough!
I said let him up!
You're not saving him!
You're drowning him!
Your friend is dead.
Jack.
Jack, stop what
you're doing.
Jack, he's dead.
He's not coming back.
Stop it!
passengers arriving
On flight 2230 from Argentina,
Claim your baggage
on carousel 3.
Attention all passengers
Arriving on flight 3226
from Sao Paulo, Brazil,
Please proceed
to baggage claim 5.
announcing the arrival
of flight 150 from quito...
all passengers
wildisembark from door 85.
Welcome to Los Angeles
international airport.
This is a nonsmoking facility.
Thank you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I don't
think so, lady. The line.
There's a line!
Sorry.
where are we
on the outback grosses?
Did laura get a response
on the title registration thing?
Well, it should've cleared.
Outback's just a name.
What are they saying,
they own the entire outback?
That's just stupid.
Have 'em cover it, okay?
She's gonna
be coming out of customs,
So I want you guys
to take the other door.
Oh, I didn't get the, uh,
tustin inventory report yet.
get on it.
Hey!
hey! Watch it!
Go! Go now!
Lady, I already have
a customer.
I said go.
Hey, what are you doing?
Go now!
Hey! Hey! Stop the cab!
Thought you might like a little
something to eat or drink.
Zack, emma, then take the rest
to the people over there.
Thank you.
just drop 'em in here.
Hey. What happened?
(gasps
they jumped us
in the jungle.
He took four of them out
Before one of them hit him
with a damn rock.
You. Come with me.
Come with you where?
He wants to know what
Jacob told you.
He told me to come here,
Said you guys would
save Sayid.
he was beyond saving.
Wait a sec.
You're not translating
anhing I say to him,
Which means you totally
understand me, dude.
I don't like the way
english tastes on my tongue.
When's Jacob getting here?
What do you mean?
Is he coming to the temple?
I really don't think
that's gonna happen, man.
Why not?
You know... 'cause he's dead.
What?
You guys didn't know?
everyone to your posts!
On the walls!
Prepare the ash!
Ten men to the north side!
Send the warning!
Light it!
Guess we're not
getting out of here, huh?
This isn't to keep you in.
It's to keep him out.
"him" who?
What are you?
I'm not a "what," ben.
I'm a "who."
You're the monster.
Let's not resort
to name-calling.
You used me.
You couldn't kill him
yourself,
So you made me do it.
I didn't make you do
anything.
You should know...
He was very confused
when you killed him.
I seriously doubt
that jacob was ever confused.
I'm not talking about jacob.
I'm talking about john locke.
Do you wanna know what
he was thinking while you...
Choked t life out of him,
Benjamin?
What the last thought
that ran through his head was?
"I don't understand."
Isn't that just the saddest
thing you ever heard?
But it's fitting in a way.
Because when john first came
to the island,
He was a very sad man.
A victim
Shouting at the world for being
told what he couldn't do--
Even though they were right.
He was weak
And pathetic
and irreparably broken.
But despite all that,
There was something admirable
about him.
He was the only one of them
who didn't want to leave.
The only one who realized
How pitiful
the life he'd left behind
Actually was.
Hmm.
What do you want?
Well, that's
the great irony here, ben,
Because...
I want the one thing
that John Locke didn't.
I want to go home.
Good-bye, dude.
If you ever wanna talk,
I'm around.
What?
Nothing.
Hey.
Where are we?
We're in a temple.
We got caught
by the others again.
Yeah.
Only this time,
they're protecting us.
I think.
of course they are.
You all right?
I'm so sorry.
You know what you said
back at the hatch?
He's just trying to help us.
I ain't gonna kill Jack.
He deserves
to suffer on this rock
Just like the rest of us.
Yeah.
I know, and--you think
I knew this was gonna happen?
I scheduled it so soon because
want to get it over with.
attention all passengers...
I don't know, mom.
He's not here, so I can't
tell you what to tell them,
Other than we can't
have the service without him.
Yeah.
I will call you
if I hear anything.
What did you lose?
Oh, they lost one of my bags.
What about you?
you wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
try me.
They lost my father.
I'm sorry?
He died in australia
a couple days ago,
And, um, I flew down
to get him.
My condolences.
Yo.
The coffin was supposed
to go on thelane in Sydney,
But it didn't.
Apparently,
he's somewhere in transit,
Which is their way of saying
They have no idea where the hell he is.
Well, how could they know?
Well, they're the ones
that checked him in.
I mean, they've gotta have
some kind of tracking system.
No, I'm not talking about
the coffin.
I mean, how could they know
where he is?
They didn't lose your father.
They just lost his body.
Either way, your story
beats the hell out of mine.
All that was in my suitcase
was a bunch of knives.
Thanks.
You some kind of salesman?
Yeah, somethin' like that.
Well, it's nice talking to you.
I-I hope you find that coffin.
I hope you find your knives.
Yeah, thanks.
Mind if I ask
what happened to you?
I'm sorry. I'mnly asking
because I'm a spinal surgeon.
I-I didn't mean to...
Oh, no, don't worry
about it. Uh...
Uh, surgery isn't gonna
do anythg to help me.
Uh, my conditi
is irreversible.
Nothing's irreversible.
Um...
If you ever want a consult...
Just, uh, give me a call.
It's on the house.
Well, thanks.
Jack shephard.
I'm john. John locke.
It's nice to meet you, john.
Nice to meet you, too.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
what the hell is that?
Don't shoot him!
I'm seein' it,
But I'm still not
believin' it.
Hello, Richard.
It's good to see you
out of those chains.
You?
Me.
I am very disappointed...
In all of you.
You're Shephard?
We need to speak
to you privately.
If you've got something
to say to me, then say it.
Otherwise,
just leave me alone.
I don't think you're
understanding me here.
I'm asking politely.
You either get up
and come with us on your own,
Or I'll have you dragged out.
Because we are going
to have this conversation,
And it's not going
to be here. - Is that right?
Jack!
Oh, my god.
what...
What happened?