Previously on lost
we are now beginning our final descent
into Los Angeles international airport.
Mr.Sherphard, there seems to be
a mix up involving the a... coffin.
They lost my father.
He died in Australia
a couple days ago.
Who are you?
Jacob sent us.
He said you would help our friend.
Get him to the spring.
What happened?
He says you have to give
your friend this pill.
- What is in it?
- Poison.
Why would you people
wanna kill Sayid?
There is a darkness growing in him.
How can you be sure of that?
Because it happened to your sister.
Claire?
Hey, mom.
Have they found him yet?
No, I-I called a couple hours ago,
and they think the coffin
was checked through Berlin.
How do you lose a body?
I don't know, mom,
but there's nothing we can do
- except for wait for more information.
- I don't want to wait, Jack.
How am I supposed to
get anything done?
I can't even find his will,
papers everywhere.
Look, mom, I'll come
over in a couple hours,
and we'll find it
together. Okay?
Okay.
Good. Now, mom, when did I
have my appendix taken out?
You were 7 or 8 maybe.
You collapsed at school.
Your father wanted to do
the procedure himself,
but they wouldn't let him.
You don't remember that?
Yeah, I...
I guess I do.
Oh, damn it. Mom, I gotta go.
Well, don't forget to...
Sorry I'm late.
I thought I had enough time to
go home and change after work.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sorry, David. Okay?
Okay, dad.
I was afraid you'd left.
Is leaving an option?
Everything is an option.
But I would have to stop you.
Well, I appreciate your honesty.
Your friends, Ford and
Austen and Kwon...
they're not coming back, are they?
No, probably not.
I appreciate your honesty.
Tie again, dude.
Shocker. That's it for me.
You hungry?
Are you?
I could eat.
Hey, man.
Do you know if there's like,
a kitchen in this place?
It's all the way down
the hallway, Hugo.
Dude, what are you doing here?
I'm here because I need you.
For what?
You should probably get a pen.
You're gonna have to
write a few things down.
- What kind of things?
- Someone is coming to the island.
I need you to help them find it.
Lost Season 6 Episode 5
"Lighthouse"
Hooked up the cable in here
so you can watch the
Red Sox if you want.
Thanks.
You reading this?
Yeah.
I used to read this to
you when you were little.
You always wanted to hear
about Kitty and Snowdrop.
They were Alice's...
Hey.
David.
What are you listening to?
You haven't heard of them.
I'm just trying to have a
conversation with you, David.
Why?
We see each other like, once
a month, can't we just...
get through it?
Damn it.
Yeah, mom?
Where are you? I thought
you were coming over.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Um, I'm heading out right now.
- I'll be right there.
- Okay.
I have to go over to
your grandmother's house.
- You wanna come?
- No, thanks.
All right, well,
I'll be back in about an hour.
And then we'll eat, okay?
Great.
Jack.
Sayid.
Why are they all staring at me?
Just ignore them.
Look, you told me these people
think I have an infection,
that they wanted to give
me some mysterious pill
that you instructed me not to take.
And then you disappeared.
What are you hiding from me?
The pill was poison.
They wanted me to kill you.
Whatever it is they
think happened to you,
Sayid...
They say it happened
to someone else, too.
Who?
Claire!
I'm gonna get you out of there.
How long have you been out here?
Since you all left.
How long ago was that?
Three years.
I gotta get you somewhere safe.
Come on. You think you can walk?
I don't know.
Aah! Okay. Okay. Okay.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm just... you know, looking...
cause I'm a big fan of temples
and like, history...
and Indiana Jones' stuff.
You shouldn't be here.
Go back to the courtyard.
Tell him you can do what you want.
Tell him you're a candidate.
I'm a candidate,
and I can do what I want.
Who told you that?
Doesn't matter.
Why don't you go back
to the courtyard?
- What'd he say?
- You don't want to know.
What are you doing here, Hugo?
Going through the secret
passageway like you told me.
I told you to bring Jack with you.
You ever tried to get
Jack to do something?
it's, like impossible.
I can just go myself.
You have to bring
him with you, Hugo.
Okay, it's bad enough you already
made me write down way too much stuff,
and I just lied to a Samurai.
Look, if you have any
idea on how to get Jack
to go on your little adventure,
I'm listening, Dude.
Be cool, man,
act natural.
What?
Dude, keep your voice down.
I'm gonna get up and go.
Wait ten seconds
and then follow me.
Follow you where?
I found a secret tunnel that
leads out to the jungle.
You found a secret tunnel.
Well... Jacob told me about it.
He said you and me have to go.
I'm not going anywhere, Hurley.
I told him you'd say that,
so he told me to tell you...
you have what it takes.
What did you just say?
I said, "You have what it takes,"
he said you'd know
what that meant.
- Where is he?
- What?
Jacob. Where is he?
He's kind of dead.
He turns up whenever he wants,
like Obi-wan Kenobi.
But if you wanna talk to him,
he's where we're going, Dude.
Well, then let's go see Jacob.
Claire?
Come on. Get in there!
So, look what I found, one of
the men who tried to kill you.
He was just pretending to
be dead, but he wasn't.
Now we get to talk to him.
You wanna talk to me about what?
About where you're hiding my son.
Gotta get that cleaned up.
If there's one thing that'll
kill you around here,
it's infection.
I'll be right back.
Don't move, okay?
Claire?
Have you been out here all
this time... by yourself?
Oh, no, I'm not by myself.
Look, we've gotta
get out of here now.
It's okay. I know her.
No, I know her.
You have any idea what
she's gonna do to us?
If we don't get out of here now,
she's gonna kill us both.
Which way?
It's this way.
Whoa. Hey.
It's me.
Jack!
I almost shot you.
I noticed. What are
you doing out here?
Where's, uh,
where's Jin and Sawyer?
Jin went back to the
temple, and, um...
Sawyer's on his own.
Hey, Kate, there's a secret
door to get back in the temple,
on the north wall
behind the big tree.
Yeah, I'm not going
back to the temple.
I'm going to find Claire.
- Kate...
- I'm going back to the beach camp,
- she might still be there, Jack.
- Kate, she's not up at the beach.
The people at the temple
said that something...
something happened to her.
Do they know where she is?
I don't know, they didn't say.
I-I have to find her.
Kate, wait, wait.
Come with us, and then we'll all
go back to the temple together.
Dude, Jacob said just you and me,
she's kind of not invited.
I'm inviting her.
Jack, it's okay. Just go.
It's all right.
I hope you find what
you're looking for.
We're never going to find it.
Take it easy, Mom.
It's somewhere in here,
and we'll find it.
It's like a needle
in a damned haystack.
Why your father wouldn't just
give his will to his lawyer
is beyond me.
Well... why would he
make it easier on us now?
You want a drink?
Uh, no. No, no thanks.
Good for you.
How's David holding up?
What?
He was really upset at the funeral.
He was?
He didn't tell you?
No. No, he didn't.
Communication is not one
of his strong suits.
Well, it runs in the family.
When you were David's age,
your father was lucky
if he could get more than one
word out of you at a time.
That's because I was
terrified of him, mom.
How do you know, David
isn't terrified of you?
Why would he be?
I don't know, Jack.
Maybe you should ask him.
Found it.
"Last will and testament."
Jack?
Yeah?
Did you father
ever mention a...
Claire Littleton?
Psst. Hey.
Untie me before she comes back in.
Why would I do that?
Are you not listening to me?
She's gonna kill us both.
Loosen my ropes,
and when she comes back in,
I'll snap her neck.
So...
I'm, uh, really sorry you
got stuck in my trap.
Gonna get you all
cleaned up now, okay?
It's all right. You're doing good.
Well, at least you don't
have to stitch yourself up.
I had to do that once.
They shot me right here.
You've been living
here since we left?
Not always here.
I, um, had to move around
quite a lot to hide from them.
Lucky I'm still alive.
What are you gonna do with him?
He's gonna tell me where
they've got my baby...
- Where... where they've got Aaron.
- We don't have your kid.
You're lying, okay?
I know you have him.
You're crazy. We never took your...
- Shut up.
- Claire, how do you know they took him?
- How can you be so sure?
- How can I be so sure?
Okay, well, first
my father told me,
and then my friend told me,
so I'm pretty damn sure.
Your friend? Who is your friend?
My friend.
You're still my friend,
aren't you, Jin?
Yes.
Yes, of course.
Good.
I'm glad.
All done. Good as new.
Okay.
So...
Now it's your turn.
Sorry, dude.
For what?
You know, what happened back there,
wrecking your game with Kate.
Don't worry about it.
There's nothing left to wreck.
Yeah? Whatever
happened to you guys?
I thought you guys
were gonna get married
- and have, like, a dozen kids.
- Guess I wasn't cut out for it.
Really? I think you'd
make a great dad.
I'd make a terrible dad.
What is that?
Asthma inhaler.
Dude, it's Shannon's.
We're at the caves.
The caves we used to live in?
I totally forgot these
were in here, man.
Wait a sec.
What if we time travelled again
to like dinosaur times,
and then we died and
then we got buried here?
What if these skeletons are us?
What's that?
I ever tell you how
I found this place?
You were looking for water, right?
No.
I was chasing the ghost
of my dead father.
He led me here.
That was his coffin...
before I smashed it to pieces.
Why'd you do that?
Because he wasn't in it.
David?
I got us a pizza.
Hey, dinner's...
This is David. Leave a message.
David, it... it's me again.
Listen, uh...
If I did something to upset you,
I am really, really sorry.
Uh, I'm gonna drive over
to your mother's house.
I know that she's out of
town, so if you are there,
just... just don't
go anywhere, okay?
Whatever I did, I'm... I'm sorry.
David?
Uh, yes, this message
is for David Shephard.
Hi, David.
This is Dr. Summerland from
the Williams Conservatory.
Just calling to confirm your slot,
next Friday the 24th at 7:00 P.M.
We look forward to seeing you,
and good luck.
Hey, David. It's dad.
I'm, uh...
I'm in Sydney, Australia.
Something...
something happened, and I...
I just needed to hear your voice.
Um, I guess I'll try again later.
I love you.
This is cool, dude.
Very old school.
What?
You know, you and me...
trekking through the jungle...
on our way to do something
that we don't quite understand.
Good times.
You mind if I ask you somethin'?
Sure.
Why'd you come back?
You know... to the island.
Back in L.A...
Jacob hopped into
the back of my cab
and told me I was
supposed to, so I came.
What?
If you have a better
reason for coming back,
let's hear it, man.
I came back here
because I was broken,
and I was stupid enough to
think this place could fix me.
Dude, I'm sorry.
How much further we got, Hurley?
It's not far. It's not far at all.
It's right there.
It's a lighthouse.
I don't understand.
How is it that we've
never seen it before?
I guess we weren't looking for it.
So tell me where my son is.
I don't know where your son is.
Stop covering for them,
they're not gonna
help you anymore.
All you've gotta do is
just tell me the truth.
I am telling you the truth,
we don't have your kid.
We never had your kid!
Stop lying to me!
Your people took me to the
temple and tortured me.
No, we captured you because you
were out here in the jungle
picking our people off.
Claire, wait!
Hold on.
"Hold on"?
Jin, they stuck me with needles!
They branded me.
And if I hadn't been able
to escape from the temple,
they would've killed me.
No, you're not
remembering things right.
Oh, shut up, okay?!
You've got one more chance.
One more chance.
Just tell me where my son is.
I don't know where
your damn kid is!
Kate, Kate took him!
Kate took Aaron.
She took him with her
when she left the island.
What do you mean she took him?
He's been with her, with Kate...
for the past three years.
Aaron is 3.
He's telling you the truth.
We had nothing to do with this.
So if you just untie me,
I'll leave,
and I promise I will never tell
anyone I ever even saw you.
Just untie me.
Pretty cool, huh?
Jacob's in here?
I guess so.
But first we gotta go upstairs
and turn this thing on.
It doesn't say anything on your
arm about the door being jammed?
No.
After you.
Thank you.
Is that your son?
Yes.
He's really good.
They are too young to have
this kind of pressure,
aren't they?
Yes. Yes, they are.
It's hard to watch and
be unable to help.
Your son has a gift.
How long has he been playing?
I...
I don't know.
Whoa.
Dude, this is cool.
Must've built this to help
ships get here and stuff.
I guess they used
a mirror 'cause...
electricity hadn't
been invented yet.
- Where's Jacob?
- Uh, he's not here yet.
Let's get started.
Tell me when it
gets to 108 degrees.
Stop.
Did you see that?
Did I see what?
The mirror. I saw
something in the mirror.
It's just ocean, dude.
These are our names.
Turn it to 23 degrees.
Oh, I-I don't think Jacob wants...
What? What is that?
It's my house.
- It's the house I grew up in.
- Huh...
That's weird.
I haven't lived in that
house since I was a kid.
He's been watching us.
The whole time, all of us.
Hurley.
Where's Jacob?
I don't know.
You said that he would be here.
Well, I was just...
kind of assuming.
Hurley...
I wanna know why
he was watching me,
I wanna know, so you're
gonna ask him right now.
It doesn't work like
that, I told you.
He just kinda shows up
whenever he feels like it.
What are you doing?
- Why was he watching me?
- I don't know.
- Why is my name written down on this thing?
- He didn't tell me.
- What does he want from me?
- I was supposed to do...
What does he want from me?
What does he want from me?!
I don't know, Jack!
Don't!
You were great in there.
You saw me?
I missed a couple of notes.
It sounded perfect from
where I was standing.
David, you scared
the hell out of me.
You were at grandma's.
I thought I could get back to
your place before you got home.
I didn't even know you
were still playing.
I made mom promise
not to tell you.
Why?
It was always such
a big deal to you.
You used to sit and
watch me practice.
You were so... into it.
I didn't tell you I was
coming here because...
I didn't want you to see me fail.
You know, when I was your age,
My father didn't want
to see me fail either.
He used to say to me that...
He said that I didn't
have what it takes.
I spent my whole life
carrying that around with me.
And I don't ever want
you to feel that way.
I will always love you,
no matter what you do.
In... in my eyes,
you can never fail.
I just wanna be a
part of your life.
Okay.
I've got some pizza back
at the house. You hungry?
Sure.
Good.
Let's go home.
How'd it go?
Where were you, man?
Doesn't matter. He wouldn't
have been able to see me anyway.
Yeah, well, I'd you
had told me that
and had, like,
explained everything, then
maybe Jack wouldn't
have freaked out
and smashed your mirror
into a billion pieces.
Thanks for the seven years
of bad luck, by the way.
You got ink on your forehead.
I have ink on my forehead,
that's all you have to say?!
Jack, broke your lighthouse, dude!
Mission unaccomplished.
Whoever you said we needed
to help get to the island
- is totally screwed.
- Oh, I'm sure they'll find some other way.
So...
everything you wanted me
to do, didn't get done,
and... you don't even care?
Wait a minute.
Did you want Jack to see
what was in that mirror?
Why?
It was the only way for him to
understand how important he is.
Well, if that was your plan,
I think it backfired, man.
Jack is here because
he has to do something.
He can't be told what that is,
he's gotta find it himself.
Sometimes you can just hop
in the back of someone's cab
and tell 'em what
they're supposed to do.
Other times,
you have to let him look out
at the ocean for a while.
Well, next time, how about you
tell me everything up front?
I'm not big on secret plans, okay?
I couldn't risk you
not coming, Hugo.
I had to get you and jack
- As far away from that temple as I possibly could.
- What? Why?
'Cause someone's coming there.
Someone bad.
Dude, we gotta warn them.
You can't warn them, Hugo.
I'm sorry. It's too late.
Look, if I didn't kill him,
he would've killed me.
I'm glad you didn't untie him.
Claire, please,
whatever you're thinking...
Why'd you say that
Kate was raising Aaron?
I was lying.
Why?
Because I wanted to save his life.
But you were right,
the others have your baby.
Aaron is at the temple.
I know because I saw him there.
But, you'll need me to get to him.
How do we get in?
There's a secret way.
No one will see us.
Thank you, Jin. Thank you.
And I'm so glad to
know you were lying
because, if what you
said was the truth,
if Kate was raising Aaron?
I'd kill her.
Am I interrupting?
John?
That's not John. This is my friend.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Minor edits by Scooby