Previously on "Lost"...
Juliet.
You did this.
Kate? Hurley!
Pick him up. Get him to the spring.
- The water isn't clear.
- What happened?
You're not saving him!
You're drowning him!
- Your friend is dead.
- Jack!
What happened?
He's alive.
It worked?
Dude, you're okay!
Hurley, let him breathe.
Miles, can you go get some water?
Yeah, on it.
Sayid. Hey.
How are you feeling?
A little light-headed.
Jack...
What happened to me?
You died.
How is that even possible?
I mean...
One minute he's gone, and now he's fine?
Of course he's fine.
What does that mean?
He's an Iraqi torturer
who shoots kids
he definitely deserves
another go-around.
What are you looking at?
How many guys with guns you
think are outside this place?
- What?
- I was out cold when they brought me in here.
How many guards did you
see? Five? Ten? A hundred?
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking about running, Kate.
She's got hands in handcuffs,
but she's probably
got 'em covered, okay?
Hey!
Hey, watch it.
Go!
Go now! Lady, I already have a customer.
- Damn it, I said go!
- Okay.
Ooh! Easy, easy. Slow down.
- Hey, just slow down. Slow down!
- Okay! Okay! You said go!
Just get us out of here.
Hey! Hey! Stop the cab!
Please, please just let
me out of the car...
Be quiet!
What are you doing? Move!
There's a guy. I'm not
gonna run him over.
Hey. I'm walkin' here! I'm walkin' here!
Do not get out of this car.
Just go.
- Go now! I don't care about the guy! Go!
- Okay.
Hey! Hey! What the hell?!
Hey, I got your license plate!
At the light, take a left.
Can you... can you please,
please just let me go?
I promise I won't say
anything to anyone.
Hey! Hey!
Damn it!
Please. Please.
Give me your purse.
- What?
- I said, give me your purse!
Now get out of the car.
Can I please just...
just get my suitcase?
No, you can't! Get out of the car!
Easy.
Right over there.
All right.
Who are these people?
What do they want?
It's the others, dude.
They caught us...
Again.
I don't know. I think
they're trying to protect us.
Yeah, and as... as you can see, uh,
Hugo here has assumed
the leadership position,
so... that's pretty great.
What?
The wound.
It's almost completely closed.
Thank you, Jack.
- For what?
- Saving my life.
Mr. Jarrah, will you
come with us, please?
-  Come with you where?
- Inside. Nothing to worry about. We...
I'm coming with him.
Oh, I'm sorry. We need
to talk to him alone.
- Just a few questions.
- You have a few questions? Well, so do we.
I mean, let's start with, who are you?
Why are you holding us here?
You...
Once we've spoken to
Mr. Jarrah, we'll be more than happy
to tell you everything
you want to know.
Something tells me,
that you're not going to
be happy to tell us anything.
Don't shoot! Lower your weapons!
Please, you don't have to do this.
- We won't hurt your friend.
- He ain't my friend.
You do what you want
with him and anybody else.
But me? I'm walking outta here.
James?
I'm gone. You understand?
Please.
You have to stay.
No, I don't.
Don't come after me.
Where are they taking Sayid?
Hey, calm down!
Everybody calm down!
- Where'd Ford go?
- What?
Ford. Your friend who just
- ran out of here... where did he go?
- I don't know.
You really expect me to believe that?
He told me he wanted
to kill me. You believe that?
- I can bring him back.
- You know where he went?
No, but I can track him.
Let me go.
I will bring him back,
and I can make him stay.
Kate...
You sure you wanna go out
there alone with these people?
I'll go with her.
It's very important that
he gets back here safely.
What makes you think
he's gonna listen to you?
I can be very convincing
when I wanna be.
Where's your tire hammer?
You got a problem.
So do you. Where's your tire hammer?
Tire hammer'll just
cut off your wrists.
Your problem is you
need a punch press,
and you're not gonna be able
to use one of those and
keep that gun pointed at me.
- You volunteering?
- I got steady hands,
but I kinda feel like we
got off on the wrong foot.
I'll give you $200.
Now hold still.
Thanks.
So why the bracelets?
I'm wanted for murder.
Murder?
You don't happen to have
somewhere I could change, do you?
Bathroom's over there.
Make it quick.
Thank you.
You better not slow us down.
You better not slow me down.
I'd go with you, but...
But... Sawyer would kill you?
I'll take care of James.
You take care of Sayid.
Deal.
Good-bye.
Be careful.
What is it you want?
Please, whatever you're thinking of doing...
What is that?
Just tell me what you want.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
I don't have any secrets.
Ask...
I'm sorry we had to
put you through that.
- It was a test. We had to be sure.
- Test to be sure of what?
Don't worry.
You passed.
I just lied to him, didn't I?
Yes.
Where were you going?
What?
Before I got in the cab,
where were you going?
Why, so you can hijack them, too?
I was waiting for a bus.
I came to bring you your stuff.
Relax. I didn't take your money.
Well, uh, gee, thanks.
- So where were you goin'?
- Don't worry about it.
Fine.
Langdon street.
Brentwood.
You got family there?
Uh, no.
It's the... couple who's
adopting my baby.
They were, um, they were
meant to meet me at the airport,
but I guess they got their
days mixed up or somethin'.
- It's not like they abandoned me.
- Brentwood's not far. Get in.
Seriously?
Do you want a ride or not?
So why do you people want
us to stay at the temple?
We're protecting you.
- From what?
- You've been on this island for a while, right?
Ever see a big pillar of black smoke...
- makes a "ticka ticka" Sound, looks pissed off?
- Yes.
From that.
Do you know anything about
another plane coming in?
- An Ajira flight.
- I'm sorry. Is this a press conference?
I think he means the one that landed...
Justin. Shut up.
No, no, no, that's a decoy trail.
He went this way.
- And you're basing this on what?
- Experience.
Aldo.
What?
I think she's right.
Of course she is.
After you, princess.
So what's your strategy for
bringing your boyfriend back?
I hope you got one, because
he shot a guy on his way out.
If he tries that on me,
- I'm gonna blow his head off.
- Whoa. Watch it.
Thank you.
Looks like one of Rousseau's traps.
- The Frenchwoman?
- No, she's been dead for years.
- This... this couldn't be one of her...
- Justin!
Shut up.
What was he gonna say?
You don't even remember me, do you?
You don't recognize me?
Well, maybe this will jog your memory.
Three years ago,
You staged yourself a little
prison break, and you did it
by knocking the guard out
with the butt of you rifle.
That would be me.
Aah!
What are you doing?
Escaping.
Sayid!
You okay, man?
Jack! He's back!
Sayid, what happened?
- They tortured me.
- Why?
Don't know. They
didn't ask me any questions.
Step aside.
Hey, Shephard.
We were hoping you'd
come on your own.
What the hell did you do to Sayid?
We... we didn't do anything
to him. Y-your friend is sick.
Sick with what?
He's...
Yeah, I... not really...
There's not really a literal translation,
the closest thing would be...
- Infected.
- Infected?
He's not even running a fever.
What...
Did I say something funny?
I doubt it. He doesn't
really have a sense of humor.
He says you have to
give your friend this pill.
Are you serious?
Why don't you give it to him?
Because it won't work
unless he takes it willingly,
and he won't take
it willingly from us.
Well, then maybe you
should've asked him to take it
- before you tortured him.
- We didn't torture him.
- We were diagnosing him.
- To see if he was infected.
Yes.
I'm not gonna give anything to Sayid
unless I know what's in it.
Tell me, Shephard...
your friend...
how did he get shot?
He was, um...
he was helping me.
So it was your fault?
Yes.
And there have been others
who were hurt or died...
helping you?
Yes.
Well...
Then this is your chance
to redeem yourself.
It's medicine,
and your friend needs it.
What happens if I don't give it to him?
The infection will spread.
So... nothing? There wasn't anything?
No white light? Angels singing?
No dead relatives?
I remember being shot.
You're not a zombie, right?
No. I am not a zombie.
Hey.
You mind giving me
and Sayid a minute?
Yeah, see, private talks
kinda freak me out
'cause they usually lead
to me having to do something
I don't quite understand.
I'm right there with you.
It's fine. We'll be in the
food court if you need us.
So did they tell you why they
burnt me with a hot poker?
They said they were
trying to diagnose you.
Right.
They told me it was some sort of test,
which they said I passed.
Clearly, I didn't.
What's that?
They want you to take it.
It's medicine, according to them.
What about according to you?
I don't know.
And you know, before when you...
when you thanked me
for saving your life, I...
I didn't have anything
to do with it, Sayid.
I didn't fix you, they did.
I don't care who fixed me.
I only care about who I trust,
so if you want me
to take that pill, Jack,
I'll do it.
Wait. Where are you going?
Catching up with Sawyer.
So you never planned to
bring him back to the temple.
No. I'm not interested in
being a prisoner. Are you?
- Where did your plane land, Kate?
- What?
The Ajira plane that you, Jack
and Hurley came in on...
- Where did it land?
- I don't know.
Sun was on that plane, too,
and I have to find her.
You think they're gonna tell you?
You think they care about you
or about Sun or about any of us?
Who do you care about, Kate?
Good luck, Jin.
Once you catch up with
Sawyer, then what?
I guess we'll figure that out together.
So, uh...
What happened to your handcuffs?
I cut them off.
It's a beautiful neighborhood.
I bet they're a really nice couple.
What?
I didn't say anything.
What, you... you think they didn't
come to the airport on purpose?
Why would I think that?
Good, 'cause they didn't.
This is it.
Um...
Will you come in with me?
Are you kidding me?
Please, I-I just...
I really don't want to go
up there on my own.
Uh, hi. Uh, Mrs. Baskum?
I-I'm... I'm Claire Littleton.
Oh, my god.
I'm so sorry.
Um...
My husband...
He left me,
and... believe me,
I wanted the baby so much,
but...
I can't do it alone.
I'm sorry.
Look, I know I should've called you...
So, uh, wh...
Y-y-you just changed your mind?
Look, my... my life is just...
a little bit complicated right now.
She came all the way from
Australia, and you don't call?
Oh, my god.
Are you okay?
Aah! It's coming!
Who's there?
Better come out now
or so help me, I'm
just gonna start shootin'.
What the hell are you doin' here?
I was worried about you.
What's happening?
- I-I think I'm having contractions.
- When did they start?
- Um, about 20 minutes ago.
- Try to relax.
We're gonna take you to
the M.F.C.U. To get you looked at.
Are you with her?
- Yeah.
- Okay, follow me.
What are you doing?
What... what's going on?
Hold on. The doctor will
be with you in just a moment.
What... what's going on?
Is something wrong?
Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
- Are you a doctor?
- Yes. I'm Dr. Goodspeed.
Can I please get your help in here?
Ms. Littleton?
Claire, how are you feeling?
Uncomfortable, what...
w-what's happening?
What's happening...
Is that mother nature's gotten
a little ahead of herself.
Are you ready to have your baby?
- I-I'm sorry. What?!
- You're at 36 weeks.
3 centimetres dilated
and about 80% effaced.
Which means, if you want,
you can have your baby tonight.
If I want? So what, you mean...
you mean you can stop it then?
Maybe. However, to do that
would require a number of drugs.
Drugs? I mean, w-will
that hurt the baby?
No, they're perfectly safe.
I just don't want to have to
stick you with needles
if I don't have to.
So it's up to you.
- I'm... I'm not ready.
- Okay.
Let's get her started
on the nifedipine drip.
Wh... what... what is it?
Margaret, let's do an ultrasound.
I wanna get a picture of
what's going on in there.
Ah, it... it could just mean
the baby's out of position.
W-w-what are you...
what are you saying?!
W-what... what's
happening to my baby?!
Is my baby okay?
Is Aaron okay?
See?
There he is. Everything is just fine.
Your boy just likes to move around.
140 B.P.M.
Perfectly normal.
I have a feeling
That Aaron is gonna be a handful.
Now let's see if we can slow this down.
You did great, mommy.
Thanks.
A couple of days ago,
you asked me why I
came back to the island.
I need to find Claire.
I thought...
maybe if I could catch up
to you, you could help me,
and then...
Maybe if we could find her
and bring her back to Aaron,
then maybe all of this
wouldn't have been for nothing.
I'm sorry.
I never should've followed you.
Which time?
That was your house, right? With Juliet.
Yep.
I'm sorry.
You already said that.
No...
for Juliet.
If I hadn't come after you on the sub,
then you two would've left,
and she would've never died.
It's not your fault she's dead.
It's mine.
She was sittin' right there,
right where you are now,
tryin' to leave this place.
And I convinced her to stay.
I made her stay on this island
'cause I didn't want to be alone.
You understand that, right?
But, uh...
but I think some of us
are meant to be alone.
I was gonna ask her to marry me.
Ahh.
You can probably make it back
to the temple by nightfall.
What's that?
It's a baseball.
You speak pretty good English
for someone that
needs a translator.
We both know that I
don't need a translator.
Then why do you have one?
Because I have to remain separate
from the people I'm in charge of.
It makes it easier,
when they don't like the
decisions I make for them.
Who are you?
My name is Dogen.
Are you from here... the island?
I was brought here like everyone else.
What do you mean, "brought here"?
You know exactly what I mean.
You didn't give your
friend the pill, did you?
No.
Why not?
Because I don't know what's in it.
- It will eliminate...
- The infection, yeah.
I got that.
- But what's in it?
- I cannot explain.
- Try.
- There isn't any time.
- He'll die if you don't...
- He already died.
What is in it?
You just have to trust me.
I don't trust myself.
How am I supposed to trust you?
Let's see where trust gets us.
Now... are you gonna tell me
What's in it?
Poison.
Come in.
Excuse me. Ms. Littleton?
Um, yeah?
I'm detective Rasmussen.
- Is Ms. Hart here?
- Uh, I'm sorry. Who?
Joan Hart. She signed in with you.
Oh. She was just the,
um, the cab driver.
I needed help, and she
brought me up here.
She left after they
treated me, though.
Did she, uh,
give you any indication
where she was headed?
Why? Is something wrong?
No. It's nothing for you to
worry about. Come on. Let's go.
E.K.G. Tech to 3-1-5. E.K.G. Tech to 3-1-5.
Thanks.
Sure.
Thank you.
Why... why are they after you?
What... what did you do?
Would you believe me
if I said I was innocent?
Yeah. Yeah, I would.
Well, I should go.
Oh, wait. Um...
Here. Take my credit card.
No.
There's not much of a
limit on it, but it's something.
You don't have to do this.
You didn't have to
do what you did either.
Aaron's a great name.
I don't know why
I said it. It's like...
I don't know. I
knew it or something.
I think you should keep him.
Well, um, good luck.
Yeah.
You, too.
Thanks.
He swallowed it?
Yes.
What's this?
Tea.
Why would you people
want to kill Sayid?
We believe he has been...
Closest translation is "claimed."
Claimed.
By what?
There is a darkness growing in him
and once it reaches his heart,
everything your friend once was...
will be gone.
No, I...
how can you be sure of that?
Because it happened to your sister.
Get up!
That's for my head.
Uhh!
Now...
- Where's that bitch?
- I don't know.
You don't understand.
I'm going back to the temple!
Yeah, right.
It looks like he's alone. Maybe
we should take him back.
Or maybe we didn't find him alive.
Aldo, no. We can't. He's one of them.
He may be one of them.
Hey! Hey!
Aah! Uhh!
Where you goin'?
Uhh!
Claire?