This island's goin' down!
Linus, come in!
Come in!
Miles, is that you?
Yeah. What--what the hell
is happening?
Are you with Claire?
She's here, but
she doesn't want to come with us.
Come with you where?
Lapidus is working on the plane
right now.
Then we're taking off.
Hey, how much longer till
we get this thing in the air?
I still have to check the electrical
and the hydraulics!
- Five hours, maybe six.
- You've got maybe one!
Get your asses over here!
We're leaving in an hour!
Son of a bitch!
How the hell are we supposed
to get over there?!
I know how we can get there!
Locke has a boat!
Locke!
I want you to know, Jack...
You died for nothing.
Aah! Uhh!
I saved you a bullet!
You're too late.
Nice work, Dr. Shephard.
What happened to your neck?
Damn it.
Okay, he's stable.
I'm gonna hop in the shower
And see if I can catch up with
David before the concert's over.
So just give me a call
if you need me.
Dr. Shephard?
He's waking up.
I watched the anesthesiologist.
He got the full dosage.
Okay.
I'll take it from here.
Mr. Locke?
Can you hear me?
John, are you awake?
You just had major surgery,
So I need you
to try not to move
And just relax, okay?
It worked.
Well, it went well.
But we won't know how well you
responded to the surgery for--
No, Dr. Shephard. It worked.
I can feel my legs.
John, it's highly unlikely
That you would regain sensation
that quickly.
So let's just take it s--
Ooh.
Oh!
?
Ohh.
- Did you see that?
- See what?
You don't remember?
Um...
Mr. Locke,
Please, just, uh, just relax.
What we need to do--
what we need to do is go.
No, no, no. Hey, John.
- Will you come with me?
- We're not going anywhere.
You just had extensive
spinal surgery...
and I-I need
to go see my son.
You don't have a son.
What?
You don't have a son, Jack.
Doctor?
Jane, um...
Would you give Mr. Locke
something to help him rest?
I need to go.
Jack.
I hope that somebody does
for you
What you just did for me.
Oh. Oh, my God.
Oh!
- Ohh. Jack.
- I'll be fine.
Just find me some thread,
and I can count to five.
Hey!
Oh, my God!
What the hell happened?
Locke's dead.
It's over.
It sure don't feel like it's over.
Excuse me. Ms. Paik?
Yes?
Hi.
I'm Detective Ford. L.A.P.D.
I'm sorry.
I heard you were shot,
But I didn't expect you
to be checking out so soon.
Hey.
Hello... Detective.
Well, I came by to check
if you've seen this man.
He escaped custody, and we're
worried he might come after you.
I'm gonna assign a uniform
to keep an eye on you
- Until we can ap--
- You don't have to do that.
All due respect, I have a job
to do here, ma'am.
- I need to keep you safe.
- It's okay. I am safe.
We'll see you there.
See me where?
Alright.
It ain't pretty, but it's gonna work.
I've gotta reset
the electronics.
Something's wrong with the hydraulics
down in the nose wheel.
Is either one of you guys
mechanical?
Yeah?
I-I worked for a-a contractor
renovating apartments
- For a couple summers.
- Here, take that...
And this... And this.
Go down there, make sure
everything's hooked up right.
Go!
- Lapidus?
- Yeah?
Frank, how's it going over
there? What's your timetable?
Don't bother me!
Sounds like
they're making progress.
- We gotta go now.
- I don't understand.
Locke's dead.
Why is this still happening?
Because whatever Desmond
turned off,
I need to
turn it back on again.
But if it doesn't work--
if I don't get it done--
You all need to leave now.
You need to be on that plane.
You can come with us, too, Jack.
You don't have to do this.
No, I do have to do it.
No, you don't.
Let this island sink, Jack.
Kate, I can't.
You think you can get that boat across
the channel in time?
Yeah, I can manage.
Good luck to you, James.
Thanks, doc, for everything.
James!
If the island's going down,
I'm going down with it.
Hugo. You better get going.
Unh-unh. No way.
You think I'm going down that?
I'm with you, dude.
Okay.
Kate...
You gotta go.
Get Claire on that plane.
Tell me
I'm gonna see you again.
I love you.
Can you fix it?
I don't believe
in a lot of things,
But I do believe in duct tape.
Yeah, I think we're good.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Yo, chesty.
It's Sawyer and Kate.
Yeah?
We're on our way
down to the sailboat,
Then we're heading to you.
Don't leave without us!
We're gettin' off the ground
While there's still ground
to get off.
So if you wanna go, you better
get your asses in gear.
Lapidus! Lapidus!
- Son of a bitch!
- What now?
We jump.
- I'll see you at the boat.
- Kate!
Hey, you know where I can get
some grub around here?
Uh, the cafeteria's closed,
But there's a vending machine
down the hallway.
Thanks, doc.
Yeah, no problem.
Oh, come on.
Unbelievable.
Can I help you?
It's okay. I'm a...
I'm a cop.
Mm. Maybe you should
read the machine its rights.
- That's funny.
- Mm.
- Can I tell you a secret?
- Please.
If you unplug it, and then
you plug it back in again,
The candy
just drops right down.
Is that right?
Yes,
and it's technically legal.
Oh.
I'll give that a shot.
Oops.
It worked.
Oh.
Whoa.
Did you feel that?
- We should get coffee sometime.
- I'd love to,
But that machine ate my dollar.
I only got one left.
We could go dutch.
?
Juliet.
Juliet, it's--it's me.
Julie.
It's me, baby.
I got you.
I got you, baby.
Yeah.
Kiss me, James.
You got it, Blondie.
It's over.
Excuse me?
The concert.
It's over.
You looking for someone?
Yeah. My son.
I was supposed to bring him here
tonight and then...
I couldn't come, and...
I'm sorry.
Where do I remember you from?
I stole your pen.
What?
Um...
Oceanic 815.
From Sydney.
I bumped into you
coming out of the bathroom,
And... I stole your pen.
And that's how I know you?
No.
That's not how you know me.
I missed you so much.
Are you okay?
What is happening to me?
Who...
Who are you? I don't...
I know you don't understand,
Jack.
But if you come with me,
You will.
It's over there.
How we gettin' down there?
We're not. I'm going alone.
Dude, you can't go down there alone.
Desmond didn't make it.
How the hell are you gonna survive?
No.
No way.
I'm not gonna let you die.
Hurley, I'm already dead.
- You said you'd protect the island!
- And that's what I'm doing.
- You're committing suicide!
- I'm not. This is the way it has to happen.
This is what
I'm supposed to do.
You're not supposed to die!
The island needs you!
Hurley...
It needs you.
What?
It needs to be you, Hugo.
I can't.
It's supposed to be you.
It was only supposed to be me
so I could do this.
But if someone has to
take care of the island,
If someone has to protect it,
then... Then it should be you.
Hurley...
I believe in you.
Alright, I'll take it.
But it's only temporary.
As soon as you get that light
back on, I'm pulling you up,
And I'm giving it right
back to you. Deal?
Deal.
Do you have anything to drink?
Anything to drink out of?
- A-a cup. A canteen.
- I do.
Is that okay?
Perfect.
Drink this.
Is that it?
Now you're like me.
Second time's a charm.
It better be, 'cause we sure as hell don't
have the battery power for a third time.
Is that good?
That, my friends,
is pure music.
Easy.
Easy. Easy.
Dude!
Desmond!
Can you hear me?
Aah! Ah!
The light...
I put it out.
It didn't work.
I thought I'd leave this place.
I got you. Come on.
Come on.
Ah!
I'm still here.
You were right, Jack.
Yeah, well, there's a first time
for everything.
Aah!
Uhh! I have to put it back.
- It was like a drain.
- That's what you did?
You took that stone out of that hole
over there?
Jack, you can't. Listen.
Even if you turn it back on,
it'll kill ya. It has to be me.
Desmond, you've done enough.
You wanna do something? Go home
and be with your wife and son.
How about you, Jack?
I'll see you in another life,
brother.
Claire?
Oh, that ain't good.
Miles, go look out the door! You're gonna
be my eyes while I back this out of here.
Richard, go tell me what he says.
Claire!
Are you okay?
Come on! We gotta go!
Come on!
- Claire, come on, please.
- I can't!
- Why?!
- Look at me!
This island's made me crazy.
I-I don't want Aaron
to see me like this.
I don't--I don't even know
how to be a mother anymore.
Listen to me.
None of us do.
Not at first.
But you're not alone.
Let me help you.
Now come on.
Let's go.
- Are we clear?!
- Miles, are we clear?
- Yeah, it looks like it to me!
- He says we're good.
You better pray we are, Ricky boy,
'cause I'm gonna spin her around.
Hold on!
Sawyer! Tell him to stop!
Tell him we're coming!
Lapidus! Lapidus!
Lapidus, hold on!
All right, we're good to go!
Let's go!
What the hell?
Boys, we got some late arrivals.
Open the door.
Come on!
We're running out of time!
- Way to wait till the last second, Jim.
- Good to see you, too, Enos.
We got 'em!
Everybody, buckle up tight!
Hold on!
Here we go, Frank.
Come on.
Amen.
He did it.
The light's back on.
Dude, pull.
Hang on, Jack!
Got him!
Desmond?
No.
Jack!
Thank you.
Hello, Benjamin.
Hello, John.
Is everyone already inside?
I believe
most of them are, yes.
Mm.
I'm very sorry
for what I did to you, John.
I was selfish
And jealous.
I wanted everything you had.
What did I have?
You were special, John.
And I wasn't.
Well, if it helps, Ben,
I forgive you.
Thank you, John.
That does help.
It matters more than I can say.
What are you gonna do now?
I have some things
that I still need to work out.
I think I'll stay here a while.
You know, I don't think you need
to be in that chair anymore.
Mm.
Good-bye, Ben.
I think Desmond's
gonna be okay.
Jack's... Gone.
Isn't he?
He did his job, Hugo.
It's my job now.
What the hell
am I supposed to to do?
I think you do
what you do best.
Take care of people.
You can start
by helping Desmond get home.
But how?
People can't leave the island.
That's how Jacob ran things.
Maybe there's another way.
A better way.
Will you help me?
I'm sorry?
I could really use someone
with, like... Experience
For a little while.
Will you help me, Ben?
I'd be honored.
Cool.
Oh! Hey, dude.
Hello, Hugo.
We're all inside.
I don't think I'm coming in.
You know...
You were
a real good number two.
And you were
a great number one, Hugo.
Thanks, dude.
I'll see you.
Do you know where we are?
This is where I was gonna
have my father's funeral.
He died in Australia.
I'm sorry.
Why did you bring me here?
Because this is where you were gonna have
your father's funeral.
You can go in around back.
Wait. W-where are you going?
Inside.
I'll be waiting for you
there...
Once you're ready.
Ready for what?
To leave.
?
Hey, kiddo.
Dad?
Hello, Jack.
I don't understand.
You died.
Yeah.
Yes, I did.
Then how are you here
right now?
How are you here?
I died, too.
It's okay.
It's okay, son.
- I love you, dad.
- I love you, too, son.
Are you...
Are you real?
I sure hope so.
Yeah, I'm real.
You're real.
Everything that's ever happened
to you is real.
All those
people in the church--
They're all real, too.
They're all...
They're all dead?
Everyone dies sometime, kiddo.
Some of them before you,
some...
Long after you.
But why are they all here now?
Well, there is no "now" here.
Where are we, dad?
This is a place that you--
that you all made together
So that you could find
one another.
The most important part
of your life
Was the time that you spent
with these people.
That's why all of you are here.
Nobody does it alone, Jack.
You needed all of them,
And they needed you.
For what?
To remember.
And to... Let go.
Kate--
She said we were leaving.
Not leave. No.
Moving on.
Where are we going?
Let's go find out.
?
We've been waitin' for ya.
Syncing CD1 by n17t01
Syncing CD2 by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com