Previously on Lost.
When you were over there
James, you mentioned that
you mentioned that Widmore had someone
guarding a room on his submarine...
guarding something that
he didn't want you to see.
Yeah, so?
I don't like secrets.
You told me you brought
me here to the island
to do something very important.
When do we start?
Run.
These people are
extremely dangerous.
We need to go now.
- Lead the way.
- This man wants to leave the island,
and that plane's the
only way he can do it.
Do you wanna know where we're going?
We're gonna stop him.
How are you gonna stop him from getting
on that plane?
We have to destroy it.
In a world of conflict
and strife,
there is but one fact we
all can agree upon...
everybody loves Hugo.
Born to humble surroundings,
Hugo reyes has always been
a beacon of light
for all who crossed his path.
Hugo's lifelong love
affair with chicken
led him to acquire and then expand the
Mr. Cluck's chain
into a worldwide phenomenon.
The exponential growth
of Hugo's success
was startling.
But financial success
wasn't the end,
it was the beginning.
Hugo and giving
became synonymous...
Parks...
Playgrounds...
Hospitals...
The Mr. Cluck's house
for children.
The philanthropy was
unparalleled...
Which brings us to this evening
and the opening of the Hugo
Reyes paleontology wing
at the Golden State
Natural History Museum...
a lasting beacon of culture
that bears the name
of one of our city's
greatest benefactors.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our man of the year...
Hugo Reyes!
Whoo!
It's a pretty cool trophy, huh?
Mm-hmm, Hugo. Oh,
you know we got the human fund
- next Saturday night. Can you make it?
- Another trophy.
Everybody loves Hugo.
You know who doesn't?
Women.
Ma!
You need a woman in your life,
especially one who
has not nursed you.
That's disgusting.
And I'm too busy to meet someone.
You're not too busy.
You're too scared.
I'm not scared.
- Good, because you have a date tomorrow.
- I do?
Grandpa Tito's neighbor's
daughter, Rosalita.
She agreed to lunch with you.
What's she like?
- Willing to meet you.
- Ma.
You're going!
She's gonna love you.
And if she doesn't,
we will find someone who does.
A lot of crazy stuff's
been happening.
I kinda wish I could talk
to you about it in person.
A lot of people have come to
talk to me after they've...
You know, gone.
It would be nice
if you could, too.
Hugo?
You ready to go?
Once I'm back, we're leaving.
- Where you going?
- "The black rock."
If we're gonna destroy that plane,
we'll need dynamite.
You sure that's the right move?
No. But it's the
only move we have.
Well, you're the expert.
Whose grave is this?
Her name was Libby.
She was in the tail
section of the plane.
We were gonna have our first date.
It was gonna be, like, a picnic.
But...
Then she was murdered.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me, too.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to stop you from
getting everyone killed.
Sync by kuniva // Edit by Don4EveR
(Addic7ed / subscene.com)
You gonna say something?
Why should I trust you?
You murdered Libby and Ana Lucia.
That doesn't matter right now.
What matters is you
going across the island
to blow up that plane?
People are gonna die...
a lot of people,
and it's gonna be your fault.
What?
Because people are listening
to you now, Hurley.
Hurley.
Who are you talking to?
Um...
No one.
Come on.
We're leaving.
Can I get you some more
homemade tortilla chips?
Sure. Whatever.
Uh, can you leave those?
I'm meeting someone.
She's running late.
Right. Chips are on the way.
Hugo?
Uh, hi.
Nice to meet you.
Wow.
Uh, I wasn't expecting
someone like you.
Uh, I'm sorry?
You know, someone who's so...
pretty.
Please. H-have a seat.
You don't look like a Rosalita.
Oh. Um, my name isn't Rosalita.
I-it's Libby.
So... you're not my blind date?
No, I-I just saw you
from across the room.
Well, how'd you know my name?
Well, if I tell you,
you're gonna think I'm crazy.
No, I won't.
Hugo,
do you believe that two
people can be connected,
like soul mates?
I guess.
You don't remember me, do you?
Should I?
What are you doing, Elizabeth?
Are you bothering this man?
No. No, he... he's an old friend.
Actually, we just... wait.
What's... what's going on?
- I apologize for the intrusion. Come on.
- No, Dr. Brooks, if I could just...
- Doctor?
- I'm sorry. She just wandered off.
Wandered off from where?
Everything that I said, Hugo,
I meant it.
Forgive us.
Yeah, just four of us.
All right, let's go.
We have to make it
to the outriggers
and across the channel to Hydra Island
before nightfall.
- You have the dynamite?
- Four sticks...
enough to destroy the cockpit
and all the instruments.
That plane'll never fly.
Um, I don't know if
that's a good idea.
I mean, for one thing,
that stuff's really unstable.
You have to trust me. I've been
training my whole life for this.
- To blow stuff up?
- To protect you.
Yeah, but how is blowing
up the plane protecting us?
With that plane gone,
- that thing won't be able to leave the island.
- Yeah, well, neither will we,
and then we'll be
stuck here with it,
- and it'll be ary at us.
- Jacob said Richard would know what to do.
- And Richard said to blow up the plane. Correct?
- Yes.
Well, Jacob never said
anything about it to me.
I mean, what if Richard's wrong?
Hugo, I'm looking out for your
best interests, all of you.
Nothing is more
important than this.
That thing is evil,
and God help us if it ever
leaves this island, bec...
That gonna be a spear?
I'm not sure what it's
gonna be yet, James.
When the time is right,
it'll tell me.
- You talk to wood now?
- Sawyer.
What?
Something I can do for you two?
Is there something you can do?
How about anything?
Those bastards on the
other island grabbed Jin.
We're just sitting around
twiddlin' our damn thumbs,
doin' nothin' about it.
There's a difference between
doing nothing and waiting.
So what are we waiting for?
You were only able to
come back to this island
because you all did it together.
If we're gonna get on
that plane and leave,
it has to happen the same way.
We're waing for your
friends to get here, Kate...
Hugo, Sun, Jack...
that's the only way
we're ever getting off
this godforsaken rock.
- Well, I don't see that happening.
- Well, let's just hope you're wrong.
Where you been?
Can I speak to you in private?
Absolutely.
Everything go all right?
Yes.
Did Widmore see you?
- No, but his people did.
- And you let them live?
I didn't see the
point of killing them
- when I had what I came for.
- So you found what they were hiding
- in the submarine?
- I most certainly did.
Now what?
We get me dynamite or
else she died for nothing.
Maybe she died to show us
- to stay the hell away from dynamite.
- Well, Jack, that's a risk I'm willing to take.
Richard, I promised Sun that
I'd get her off this island.
Well, Jack, I-I wish
you hadn't done that.
If it makes you feel any better, you can
blame it on me.
I think Richard's right.
It's the only choice we've got.
Trust me, Jack.
Okay.
- Good.
- Let's get moving.
38? Number 38?
Mr. Reyes!
What an honor.
Give me a bucket, family size.
Of course. Right away, sir.
41?
Number 41?
What?
I'm sorry.
Have I seen you before?
I own the place.
Maybe you saw my commercial.
You want a clucketeer keychain?
N-no. It's not that.
Were you on Oceanic Flight 815?
- About a week ago, from Sydney?
- Uh, yeah.
- So was I.
- Wow. What a coincidence.
Yeah. Listen, you mind if I join
you while I wait for my order?
Be my guest.
Ooh. That is a lot of chicken.
- I eat when I'm depressed.
- Ah. So what's her name?
I met a girl on a blind
date the other night.
And you didn't-
it didn't go how you'd hoped?
Mm. She was totally awesome,
expect for one thing- she's crazy.
Well, all women are a
little bit crazy, brother.
No. This one actually
lives in the looney bin.
I mean, I saw the van.
She's full-on nuts.
I mean, she started sane,
but then she told me that
we already knew each other...
and that? I'd remember.
Tell me something...
did you believe her when
she said she knew you?
Yeah.
Kinda.
You know, I say go with your gut.
You know, maybe you should...
You should try to find out where
she thinks she knew you from
before you give up on her.
42? Order 42?
Ah, that's me, brother.
Well...
Uh...
It was nice bumping into you.
Hello.
I'm sorry Sayid tied you up,
but he was afraid you'd run before we
had a chance to talk.
I don't blame him. Although as I explained
to him before he left,
I have nowhere to run to,
brother.
Well, if that's not the best
argument against captivity
that I've ever heard,
I don't know what is.
You mind if I ask you a
couple questions, Desmond?
Not at all.
Why did Charles Widmore bring
you back to the island?
Considering I was kidnapped,
you'd have to ask him.
They had him under armed guard.
He threw me into a wood shack
and blasted me with a massive
amount of electromagnetism.
If you don't mind my asking,
Desmond,
how can you be sure what it
was that he blasted you with?
Experience.
Do you know who I am?
Of course.
You're John Locke.
Head back to camp.
I'll be back soon.
Where are you going?
Desmond and I need to take a walk.
Something I'd like to show you.
Kinda makes you think, doesn't it?
What's that?
Ilana.
There she was,
handpicked by Jacob,
trained to come and
protect you candidates.
No sooner does she
tell you who you are,
then she blows up.
The island was done with her.
Makes me wonder what's gonna
happen when it's done with us.
All right, everyone.
This might take a few minutes.
I don't want anyone but
me handling that dynamite,
so I'm gonna go in alone.
Where's Hugo?
- I thought he was up front with you.
- Run!
Run!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Why the hell did you do that?!
I'm protecting us.
- What the hell were you thinking?!
- Calm down.
- Now what... what are we supposed to do now?
- That's it. That's enough.
We're dead. We're all dead.
A warning might have
been nice there, Hugo.
I did say "run."
Why'd you do that?
Michael told me to.
Who?
Michael.
He's one of the
people who come back
and yell at me after they die.
He told me I had to stop everyone
from blowing up the plane.
So... no dynamite,
no more blowing up.
That happen a lot,
dead people yelling at you?
It happens enough.
And you just listen
to whatever they say?
Dead people are more
reliable than alive people.
How can I help you, Mr. Reyes?
I wanted to ask you about
that girl the other day.
Libby?
I was wondering if
maybe I could see her.
Well, I don't think
that's a good idea.
She's not well.
Clearly, she's well enough
for, like, a... fajita field trip.
Well, that's my mistake.
I misjudged her condition.
Her condition?
She has issues with reality.
What do you mean?
I just think it probably
wouldn't be a good idea
for you to see her right now.
It'll only confuse her.
You said "probably,"
which means you might
make an exception.
Well, perhaps for family.
Or a generous donor?
I'm sorry?
The rec room looked pretty
gnarly on my way in.
What do you think 100k might buy?
You remembered?
No.
I'm sorry.
Then why are you here?
Where is it you think
you know me from?
Um, I'm not sure.
I...
I know it won't make sense.
Try me.
A few days ago, I was watching TV,
and one of your
commercials came on.
And the moment that I saw you,
it was like I was
hit over the head.
All these memories
came washing back... of my life,
only... it was...
Another life.
What kind of memories?
There was a plane crash.
And...
I was on an island.
And I was there?
I think so. We... knew each other.
We...
liked each other.
And then when I got here,
it was almost like
I'd been here before.
And for some reason, Hugo,
I have a memory of
you being here, too.
Um...
This is the first time I've
ever been in a mental hospital.
Yeah, I know. But I can't
get you out of my brain.
That's why the other night when I saw you,
I had to talk to you,
because if you remembered me...
I wish I could, Libby, but...
I can't.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm crazy.
Yeah, probably,
but... we all got
something, right?
I mean, it takes a lot of guts
to go up to a total stranger
and tell them you know them
from some bizarro
alternate universe.
I'm scared just
saying "hi" to a girl.
You're doing fine.
Hey, can you ever, like...
get outta here?
On a day pass or...
Yeah. I'm here voluntarily.
Well...
Would you like to...
do something?
You mean...
A date?
Uh...
Yeah.
I'd love that.
Remind me, Desmond...
How long were you down in that hatch,
pushing that button?
Three years.
And here you are, back for more.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say this island has it in for you.
Do you know better?
Excuse me?
Well, there's nothing
special about me, brother.
This island has it
in for all of us.
Yes, it does.
What?
Who's that?
Just ignore him.
- Do you know that boy?
- I said ignore him.
Where you going?
Ben, back at the Dharma barracks...
There's still grenades there?
Explosives?
- Yes, I think so.
- Then that's where we're going.
- Maybe we should talk about this a minute.
- Talk? There's no time to talk, but if you know
what we need to do,
if you know how we stop that thing
from leaving the island
without blowing that plane up,
- then let's hear it. Let's all hear it.
- I know what we need to do.
Really? What's that?
We have to go talk to Locke.
Are you trying to get us killed?
It's not my idea. It's his.
Jacob says we have
to talk to Locke.
Jacob's here right now?
Yeah.
Ask him what the island is.
What?
A while back, Jacob told
me what the island was,
and if he's really standing
here right next to me,
then just ask him.
I don't have to prove
anything to you, Richard.
You either come with me
or you can keep trying
to blow stuff up.
Your call, dude.
He's lying.
Jacob isn't telling us what to do
because Jacob never tells
us what to do.
I'm gonna make this simple...
If that thing leaves the island, that's it.
I-it's over.
- What's over?
- Everything. I'm destroying that plane,
and I can use all
the help I can get.
Who's coming with me?
I am.
I saw that thing in action, man.
It doesn't want to talk.
Sorry.
Anyone else?
Sorry, Richard.
If Jacob says we go talk to Locke,
we go talk to Locke.
- I'm going with Hugo.
- Really?
Don't get in our way.
All right, Hurley.
Let's go talk to Locke.
Probably.
So what do you think we should...
say to Locke when we get there?
I mean...
How do you break the ice
with the smoke monster?
Don't worry about it.
Something tells me he's gonna
do most of the talking.
Or he could just kill us all.
Yeah, he could.
I didn't see Jacob back there.
Uh, I just said it 'cause I
wanted everyone to listen to me.
I know.
Then why'd you come with me?
Ever since Juliet died,
ever since I got her killed,
all I've wanted was to fix it.
But I can't.
I can't ever fix it.
You have no idea how hard
it is for me to sit back
and listen to other people
tell me what I should do.
But I think maybe
that's the point.
Maybe...
Maybe I'm supposed to let go.
Unless you letting
go gets us killed.
Going to see Locke was my idea,
not Jacob's.
Hurley, you asked me to trust you.
This is me trusting you.
Well, it's a good
thing you do, dude,
'cause I have no
idea where I'm going.
Wait. It's cool. I think I
know what these things are.
Oh, yeah? What the hell are they?
Wait here.
Hey. You around?
Michael?
You're stuck on the island,
aren't you?
Because of what I did.
And...
There are others out here...
Like you, aren't there?
That's what the whispers are?
Yeah.
We're the ones who can't move on.
Do you know where Locke is?
There.
Thanks.
Is...
Is there anything I
can do to help you?
Don't get yourself killed.
Okay.
Mm.
And, Hurley?
If you ever do see Libby again...
Tell her I'm very sorry.
I'll be sure and do that, dude.
I got, like, six different
kinds of cheeses.
I don't even know what they are,
but the lady at the store
said they were good, so...
I figured you'd like cheese
because everybody likes cheese.
Is something wrong?
No, not wrong, just...
Off.
Have you been here before?
No.
It's just... being here with
you feels so familiar.
It's like a date we never had.
Wow. I sound completely
insane, don't I?
No.
Not completely.
Why do you even wanna be with me?
Why you wanna be with me?
What?
Come on.
Look at me.
I want to be with you...
Because I like you.
Yeah, but...
You like me because...
Well, you're... delusional.
What? What's wrong?
Whoa.
- Dude.
- What?
I...
I think I'm remembering stuff.
You are?
You mean I'm not crazy?
No, I don't think you are.
We're here.
What is it?
It's a well.
Let me guess...
You're wondering how deep it is.
You read my mind.
You have any idea how old
this well is, Desmond?
Very old?
That's exactly right. Very old.
So old, in fact,
that the people who dug this well
did it completely by hand.
God knows how long it took 'em.
Well, it seems like a lot of
work just to get some water.
Oh, they weren't
looking for water.
They were looking for answers.
A long time ago,
places like the one we're
standing at right now
made compass needles spin.
And the people
holding the compasses
needed to know why,
so they dug.
Did they find what
they were looking for?
No, they didn't.
The reason I wanted you
to see this, Desmond,
is because Charles Widmore
is not interested in answers.
He's only interested in power.
And he brought you
back to this island
so that you could help him
find what he's looking for.
After all,
this isn't the only well.
And that's the reason
you wanted me to see this?
Why aren't you afraid?
Excuse me?
You're out here,
middle of the jungle,
with me.
Not a person on earth
even knows you're here.
Why aren't you afraid?
What is the point in being afraid?
Aah!
How is our friend?
We don't have to worry
about him anymore.
Where you been?
I went for a walk, James.
Well, now that you've stretched
your legs, maybe you can...
Son of a bitch.
Um... hey.
Hello, Hugo.
I don't know who you are, dude,
or what you want,
but we have to talk to you.
"We"?
There are other people with me.
But the thing is,
you got weapons,
and we got weapons,
and I don't want
anyone to get hurt...
Or killed.
So we're not gonna do anything,
and I want your word that you're
not gonna do anything either.
You have my word.
Okay, guys.
Come on out.
Hello, Jack.
Hello there.
Are you waiting for
someone in particular?
Excuse me?
Well, I noticed you've
been parked here a while,
watching the kids, and,
well, it is a school.
Do you have a child who goes here?
No. No. I was, um,
uh, I just moved to
the neighborhood,
and, um, and, uh, I'm looking
for a school for my son.
- What's your son's name?
- Charlie.
Well, as a teacher here,
I can vouch for it completely.
It's a wonderful school.
That's great to hear. Thanks.
Well, it was nice talking to you.
Have a good day.
Mm-hmm.
Oh!
Call 9-1-1! Do it now!
Mr. Locke?
Oh, my God.
Don't... don't move. We're gonna
get you to the hospital.
Mr. Locke?
Mr. Locke, can you hear me?
Sync by kuniva // Edit by Don4EveR
(Addic7ed / subscene.com)