Mr. Locke.
- Hmm.
- Mr. Locke.
Mr. Locke,
can you hear me?
Welcome back.
I know you.
We were on the same
flight back from Sydney.
I met you in the
baggage claim office.
You had lost your knives.
I'm Jack Shephard.
What happened?
You were run down by a car.
You just came out of surgery.
Am I...
Am I all right?
Your dural sac ruptured.
But I think I got everything
back were it belongs.
Mr. Locke, while I was
operating, I got a look
At the initial injury to your spine...
the one that put you in the wheelchair.
And I was hoping you could
tell me how that happened.
Why?
Because I think
you're a candidate.
A candidate for what?
A new procedure.
A surgery we're
developing, and...
if it works, it could restore
feelings to your legs.
In fact, you may
even walk again.
If you'll give me
a shot, Mr. Locke,
I think that...
that I could fix you.
No, thank you.
Well, now there's minimal risk,
and... and the benefit could...
I said no, doctor.
John?
- Oh.
- Oh, John.
It's the first time they let
me see you.
Oh!
- Are... are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Are you his doctor?
- Yes, I am. Dr. Shephard.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving him.
Welcome to Hydra Island.
At least you didn't
have to paddle.
Get in.
Uh-uh.
Ain't no way I'm gettin'
back in those cages.
- Well, I've got the gun, so you...
- Not anymore, Dough-boy.
Drop the gun!
Put the gun down
or I'll kill her!
You ain't gonna kill anybody.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
be throwing us in a cage.
I have a list of names.
Ford, you're on it,
as are Reyes and the Kwons.
Kate Austen? She's not.
It doesn't matter to me
whether she lives or dies.
Don't listen to him.
You may not believe it,
but I'm doing this
for your own good.
You're right...
I don't believe it.
- Is the fence live yet?
- They're saying about an hour.
We haven't got an hour.
Tell them to work faster.
He's coming.
Season 6 Episode 14
"The Candidate"
Hello?
Excuse me?
- Hello?
- Hmm?
Oh!
I'm sorry. There was
no one out front...
and I heard the drill.
Do you know where
I can find Dr. Nadler?
Well, you can
find him right here.
And if you're not a patient,
you can call me Bernard.
Hi.
Jack Shephard.
Um, I'm a surgeon
over at St. Sebastian,
and I was hoping to get a look
at one of your patient files.
And which patient would that be?
His name's John Locke,
and our records said
that you had done some emergency oral
surgery on him about three years back.
- And what are you looking for, exactly?
- I wanna know how he was hurt.
Do you mind if I ask you why you're
so interested in Mr. Locke, Jack?
Um...
He and I met about a week ago.
We were on the same flight back
from Australia.
Oceanic 815.
I sat across the aisle from you.
If memory serves,
you were flirting with my wife Rose
when I was in the bathroom.
It's pretty weird, huh?
Yeah.
Well, then... maybe you're on
to something here, hmm?
Now I can't break
patient confidentiality
and tell you something
I shouldn't,
but I can tell you that when
I treated Mr. Locke...
there was another man in
the same accident with him.
Wait, that was... three years ago.
You just...
remember that?
Of course I do, Jack.
Anthony Cooper.
Good luck, doc.
I hope you find what
you're looking for.
What happened?
There was a mortar attack.
Widmore's people fired on us.
Locke saved you.
What about the rest of your group...
what happened to them?
The ones who weren't killed,
scattered into the jungle.
It's just the three of us now.
Why did he bring me here?
Because your friends got
themselves captured.
And now...
we're gonna have to rescue them.
Rescue them from what?
Widmore has them in a cage
about a half a mile inland.
- Why would he...
- You know, I would ask him,
except I don't think he's gonna
give me a straight answer.
But I can't imagine that
his intentions are good.
If we move right now...
we can break your people out,
run for the plane -
and be off this island before
Widmore knows what hit him.
They're not my people...
and I'm not leaving the island.
Well, Jack, I'm hoping you'll still
change your mind about that.
But your friends do
want to leave...
and since they just ran
away from me on my own boat,
I'm gonna need your help convincing
them that they can trust me.
Why should I trust you?
Because I could kill you,
Jack... right here, right now.
And I could kill every
single one of your friends...
and there's not a thing that
you could do to stop me.
But instead of killing you...
I saved your life and
now, I wanna save them, too.
So will you help me?
You feel like we're
runnin' in circles?
Back in these cages...
except last time,
the gun was to my head.
He wouldn't have
killed me, James.
That cave I told you about,
where all the names are written?
Your name was there, too.
But it was crossed out.
He doesn't need you, Kate.
So she's with your mother?
Yes. You saw her pictures... how?
Widmore's people found
your camera on the plane.
He showed me the pictures.
Our daughter...
she's so beautiful.
I have your ring.
Uh-oh.
What happened?
Somebody shut us down?
What's going on?
Somebody killed the power.
Get a team to that generator now!
And we're dead.
Go! Go! Go!
Aah!
Hey.
I think I can reach the keys.
Hurry. When that thing's done
with them, he's coming for us.
Well, I ain't waitin'.
Uhh! Damn it!
What are you doing here?
I'm with him. Come on.
How much further to the plane?
I'd say about a quarter-mile,
just over that ridge.
So you're coming with us now?
I'm gonna take you to the plane,
but I'm not getting on it.
I'm sorry, Kate. I'm...
I'm not meant to go.
Thanks for coming back for us, doc.
Appreciate it.
No, it's okay.
Sayid's with us. He was the one
who turned off the generators.
Great. The more the merrier.
We need to go. Locke's waiting.
Are you a relative
of Mr. Cooper's?
Uh, no. No, I'm not, but...
M-may I ask the
nature of the visit?
Um... Dr. Shephard?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Um, I'm here to see
Anthony Cooper.
Do you know him?
Is that why you're here, too?
What do you want with Anthony?
I wanna talk to him about the
accident that he
was in with Mr. Locke.
Um, Dr. Shephard...
just go.
Look, all I wanna
do is help him.
I know. John told me
about the operation.
He doesn't want it.
Why doesn't he want it?
Please, Dr. Shephard,
just leave this alone.
You saved John's life.
Why can't that be enough?
Because it's not.
Housekeeping, dial 23.
Housekeeping, extension 23.
Hi.
This is Anthony Cooper.
He's John's father.
Hey! Stop!
Stop right there!
Well, all righty.
Let's see what it'll take
to get this baby to fly.
Son of a bitch.
His neck's been broken.
That's because I broke it.
If it's any consolation...
Widmore knew that I
would kill these men.
What are you talking about?
They were only guarding
the plane for show.
If Charles had really wanted to
keep me from actually getting on-board,
he wouldn't have... moved
his little fences.
Well, wait. Now he wants us
to leave the island?
No, Hugo. He wants to get us all
in the same place at the same time...
A nice, confined space we have
no hope of getting out of.
And then he wants to kill us.
- Kill us with what?
- With this...
four bricks of C4.
I found 'em in one of the
overhead compartments,
wired to the electrical
system of the plane.
If we would've turned it on...
boom.
So what now?
We can't be sure he didn't put more
explosives on the plane. It's not safe.
If we're gonna leave the island,
I think we have to
take the submarine.
Well, that's what I've been
sayin' all along.
Dude, wait.
He's not supposed
to leave the island.
- I mean, Alpert said...
- Screw Alpert. He ain't here.
That's twice you've
saved our asses.
Guess I was wrong about you.
Thank you, James.
That submarine is
gonna be heavily defended.
We're gonna need everyone.
I'll help you, but like I said...
I'm not going with you.
Fair enough.
Let's go.
Hey.
- I-I'm sorry that I...
- That's all right, Claire.
I understand why
you went with them.
Hey, doc... listen up.
You don't wanna leave this island,
that's your own damn business.
But I'm gonna ask you
for one last favor.
I don't trust that
thing one bit.
So here's what I need you to do.
Once we get to the dock...
you make sure it
doesn't get on the sub.
How am I supposed to do that?
You saw what it did back there.
Just get it in the water...
I'll take care of the rest.
Mm.
C.T. test to trauma 3.
Mr. Locke, are you awake?
Push the button.
Mr. Locke... can you hear me?
I wish you had believed me.
Excuse me?
Ms. Littleton?
Dr. Shephard. I-I was
just looking for you.
The, um, the lawyer
told me you work here.
Um, c-can we talk?
Yes. Yes.
Oh. No. I'm okay.
Sorry I had to run out
Of the--the will
reading the other day,
- but I did have an emergency and...
- Oh. N-no worries.
Um, I know this is as awkward for
you as it is for me.
I never even met this man.
Anyway, the, uh...
the lawyer gave me this.
She said, uh... there'd
be more stuff to come,
but that my father especially
wanted me to have this.
You know why or what
it's supposed to mean?
I have no idea.
But then...
I-I didn't know about you, either.
Our father, uh...
you mind... you mind
if I ask how he died?
He was found in an alley
outside a bar in Sydney.
He drank himself to death.
I flew down to bring
his body back,
but then, uh...
the airline lost it.
I just flew in from
Sydney a few days ago.
When?
Uh, last Wednesday.
Oceanic flight 815?
Uh... yeah.
Do you mind if I
have a look at that?
Um, sure. Go ahead.
I'm sorry. I-I wish I knew why
he wanted you to have this.
Yeah. Me, too.
Well, um, it was nice
seeing you again.
Thanks for trying to help.
Where are you staying?
Uh, just down
the road... a motel.
Why don't you come stay with me?
Stay with you?
I mean, we're...
we're strangers.
No, we're not
strangers. We're...
we're family.
Just 'cause there ain't
any goons on the dock,
doesn't mean they
ain't on the sub.
We're going in hard. Got it?
Lapidus, Hugo, Jin,
Sun... you're with me.
The rest of you wait 30 seconds,
head down the dock behind us.
You think you two
can get our backs?
Absolutely.
All right.
Let's go home.
After engine room,
power the bilges.
power the bilges, please.
Where's the damn Captain?
Put your damn hands up.
Nothin' personal.
Okay, Hoss. How about you get
ready to fire this thing up?
I got it.
Let's go.
You sure you won't
reconsider, Jack?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Whoever told you
you needed to stay,
had no idea what they
were talking about.
John Locke told me
I needed to stay.
What happened?
Kate?!
Aah!
Claire! Let's go now!
What's going on up there?
What happened?
Widmore's people shot her.
Hurley, I need a first aid kit.
- Who else is up there?
- Claire.
Claire!
James!
Lapidus... if you can hear me,
- dive, dive!
- Let's go!
- Hey! Wait, wait!
- Claire, wait!
- Wait!
- Claire!
What the hell are you doing?
What we came
here to do... leaving.
- It's all right. It's all right.
- No!
They're leaving us!
No, trust me. You don't
want to be on that sub.
- Claire?
- Kate.
- Claire? Where's Claire?
- She's still up there.
No, we can't leave
without her. We can't...
Kate. Kate.
Is she gonna be okay?
Jack, I can't find
the first aid kit, dude.
Jin... my pack.
There might be a shirt in
there I can use for pressure.
It's okay. Just relax.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Here. Can you help her?
I think the bullet went
straight through...
What?
Dude, where'd that come from?
Locke.
We did exactly what he wanted.
- We have to get to the surface.
- What the hell?
We have to get
to the surface now!
Lapidus, take us up.
- We're divin'!
- Just do it!
You heard him. Up!
- Dude, how'd that get on the sub?
- Locke put it in my pack.
Why would he do that?
He wanted to come with us.
You're damn right he did.
That's why I shut his ass out.
He wanted you to shut him out.
Any idea how that thing works?
- Can we turn it off?
- This watch is jury-rigged to the battery.
- The battery detonates the explosives.
- How much time till we're up, Frank?
At least five minutes.
We ain't got five minutes.
What's it gonna be, Sayid?
These wires... they're
leads from the watch.
If we disconnect them
from the battery,
technically speaking,
the bomb should be inert.
"Technically"?
Yes, but you need to pull
them out simultaneously,
- and I'm not sure...
- Step aside.
- No, wait. Wait.
- What the hell are you doing, doc?
Nothing's gonna happen.
- What?
- Don't pull those wires out...
we're okay.
Nothing's gonna happen.
If I don't pull these wires,
Locke's gonna blow us
- to kingdom come.
- No, he's not!
Locke can't kill us.
Uh... what?
This is what he wanted.
This is what he's been waiting for.
Everything that he has done
has been to get us here.
He wanted to get us
all in the same place
at the same time...
a nice enclosed space
- where we had no hopes of getting out of.
- I don't understand.
Locke said that he can't
leave the island without us.
I think that he can't leave the island
unless we're all dead.
He told me that he could
kill any one of us
whenever he wanted. So what
if he hasn't because he's...
he's not allowed to?
What if he's trying to get
us to kill each other?
Stay out of my way, doc.
Now if he wanted that
thing to blow up...
why would he put a timer in it? Why not
just throw it inside?
- I don't care.
- Nothing is gonna happen.
It's not your decision to make.
- He can't kill us!
- I'm not gonna stand here and do nothing!
James...
we are going to be okay.
You just have to trust me.
Sorry, doc... I don't.
Listen carefully.
There's a well on the main island
A half mile South from
the camp we just left.
Desmond's inside it.
Locke wants him dead,
which means you're going to need him.
Do you understand me?
Why are you telling me this?
Because it's going
to be you, Jack.
Sayid!
Oh, hell.
Uhh!
- Are you okay?
- What happened? Did Sayid just...
Help!
- Sun!
- Help!
Wait!
- Hold on. I'll get you out.
- Jin!
No!
- Sawyer! I need help!
- Jin!
Hurley!
You gotta take Kate outta here.
- What about everybody else?
- I'll take care of them!
I have to go after Sayid!
There is no Sayid!
Listen to me. Take this tank
And buddy-breathe and swim out
where the blast hole is, okay?
Hurley, you can
do this... okay?
Okay.
Go.
Doc!
Push. On three.
One... two... three.
Sawyer!
Jack!
Sawyer.
Jin...
go.
- No.
- Save yourself.
I'm going to get
you out of here.
Go. Go. I'll get her free.
No. We can do this!
Just go!
Save Sawyer.
Jin!
Take this. I can get
him out without it.
No. You can't, Jack.
Just go.
Go.
Jin.
You have to go.
No, I can do this.
No. No, you can't.
Please go.
I won't leave you.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Go.
Go. Please.
Go!
I love you, Sun.
I love you.
Is somebody meeting
you, Mr. Locke?
Yes. My fianc?e, Helen.
She's, uh...
Probably stuck in traffic.
Hey, I'll take it from here.
You know,
I'm pretty good at this.
- Well, best of luck to you, sir.
- Thank you. See ya.
Mr. Locke.
I'm glad I caught ya.
I hadn't had a chance
to say good-bye yet.
Well, good-bye.
And thanks again, Dr. Shephard.
I went to see your father.
W-what?
When you didn't
want the surgery,
I felt like I had to understand why.
And, uh... you know,
I thought that if I could find
out why you're in this chair...
- that maybe...
- I was in a plane crash.
I had, had my... my private
pilot's license for a week,
and, uh, I begged my father to
be my first official passenger.
He was terrified of flying.
But I looked him right in
the eye and I told him he could
trust me.
And we barely got
off the ground.
I-I still don't re...
I don't remember
what I did wrong.
But it was my fault.
It was my fault
That this man who I
loved more than anything
will never walk or... talk or...
you know, the first
time you and I met... um,
back at the... at the airport.
You told me that
my father was gone...
and, uh...
It hurt to hear that,
but I knew you were right.
Your father's gone
too, Mr. Locke.
- Uh, no, no, he's not.
- Yes, he... he is,
and you can punish yourself
as much as you want
and that's never
gonna bring him back.
What happened, happened...
and...
you can let it go.
What makes you think
letting go is so easy?
It's not.
In fact, I don't really
know how to do it myself.
And that's why I
was hoping that...
maybe you could go first.
Good-bye, Dr. Shephard.
I can help you, John.
I wish you believed me.
Jack.
I couldn't find you.
- Is he okay?
- He got hit in the head pretty hard,
But he's breathing.
What about Jin and Sun?
It sunk.
What, t-the submarine?
But... they...
they were all on it.
Everyone.
- What they're... they're all dead?
- Not all of them.
Wait. W-where you going?
To finish what I started.
Sync by n17t01
Re-sync by honeybunny
www.addicted.com
Edited by Scooby