Previously on Lost.
- Who is he?
- His name is Richard Alpert.
He's a kind of... advisor.
And he has had that job
for a very, very long time.
Why do you want to die?
I devoted my life...
longer than you
can possibly imagine
in service of a man,
who told me that everything
was happening for a reason.
That he had a plan a
plan that I was a part of...
and now that man's gone.
So why do I want to die?
Because I just found out my
entire life had no purpose.
I'm here because I need your help.
Will you help me, Ilana?
Yes.
There's six people I
need you to protect.
I'm gonna give you
a list of their names.
This is what you've
been preparing for.
These people... who are they?
They're the remaining candidates.
Candidates?
Candidates for what?
To replace Jacob.
She said I was one of them
and so are you,
and so is Hurley.
Well, that's great. So
what do we do now?
I don't know.
Then who does?
After I've brought
them to the temple...
what do I do?
Ask Ricardus.
He'll know what to do next.
Who's Ricardus?
He is.
So, Richard...
What do we do next?
I have no idea what "we" do next.
You didn't tell your friends that
I was trying to kill
myself when you found me?
Does that sound like
someone who has a plan?
Why would Jacob say you
knew what to do if...
Because everything
he ever said is a lie.
What are you talking about?
You wanna know a secret, Jack?
Something I've known
a long, long time?
You're dead.
- You mean that figuratively, right?
- No. I mean, literally.
We're all dead... every
single one of us.
And this... this... all this?
It's not what you think it is.
We're not on an
island. We never were.
We're in hell.
So I'm not interested
in what Jacob said.
In fact, maybe it's time
we stopped listening to him
and we started listening
to someone else.
And that's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
Season 6 Episode 9
"Ab Aeterno"
What are you doing?
- I'm going after Richard.
- Why? You heard him.
He doesn't... he doesn't
know what we need to do next.
He knows. Jacob
told me. He has to know.
Alpert has lost his mind.
He thinks that
we're... we're in hell.
And if he cared
about what Jacob said...
he wouldn't be talking about...
about listening to someone else.
Wait.
You know who he meant?
Oh, this should be interesting.
What?
He meant Locke.
Locke is dead.
If it's any consolation,
it's not exactly Locke.
Hurley.
What's he sayin'?
Uh, wh... what's who saying?
- Jacob. I saw you talking to him.
- I'm not talking to Jacob.
Don't lie to me. Please,
if you something...
- anything that can help us figure out...
- It's not Jacob, man.
Then who is it?
Sorry, Jack, but this has
nothing to do with you.
- Shephard is right, you know.
- Right about what?
Richard.
Going after him is a waste of
time. He doesn't know anything.
- What makes you so sure?
- I've known him since I was 12 years old.
That should count for something.
So you guys met when
you were kids, huh?
No, Frank, I was a kid.
Richard looked just
like he does today.
You're saying this guy doesn't age?
That's exactly what I'm saying.
And how the hell do
you think that happened?
In nomine patris et
filii et spiritus sancti.
Amen.
No.
- Is this him?
- Yes.
Calm down!
You say he speaks English.
Yes, Mr. Whitfield.
Do you speak English?
I asked, do you speak English?
Take him away and bring me another.
- Hang him.
- Yes, I speak it! Yes, I speak it!
Wait.
You have strong hands. What
sort of work did you do?
I... I work... I work...
i... in the fields.
I understand you're interested
in going to the new world.
- Yes.
- Well, then...
- This is your lucky day.
- Thank you, father.
This man is now the property
of Captain Magnus Hanso.
I hope you don't get seasick.
Do you see anything?!
- Bring me the Captain.
- Sir, Captain Hanso's dead.
Good God, we're in the
middle of a bloody jungle!
Thank God. Thanks.
Thank you very much.
No! Stop! No!
No! Stop!
No, No No!
No! Stop! Stop!
What are you doing?
Aah!
I'm begging you.
Don't do it.
Don't do it, please.
We are shipwrecked in
the middle of the jungle.
We have no fresh water
and limited supplies,
and there are only five officers left.
No! No! No!
Why... why are you doing this?
Because if I freed you,
it would only be a matter of time
before you tried to kill me.
No!
Shoot it! Shoot!
Aah!
What happened up there?
I said report!
Isabella!
Shh. Here.
Water.
Who...
Who... who are you?
A friend.
I am...
In hell?
Yes, I'm afraid you are.
You...
you were not on this ship.
I was here...
long before your ship.
Did you see my... my wife?
- I'm sorry?
- Isabella. My wife.
She was here. She was...
but... then the black smoke came,
and she ran.
And she hasn't come back?
That probably means he has her.
Who?
I think you know who.
If she's a... alive, I must save her.
Please. Please, help me.
Of course. Of... of course I'll help.
I want to be free, too.
As luck would have it...
I found these on one
of the officers outside.
I think they'll work.
But before I try, I need to
know that you will help me.
Yes. Yes. Of... of course.
You'll do anything I ask?
Yes. Yes, anything. Yes, I promise.
Then we're agreed.
Thank you.
Of course, my friend.
It's good to see you
out of those chains.
Thank you.
We're gonna have to
get you on your feet.
You're gonna need your strength
if we're going to escape.
Escape?
That's right.
I'm afraid there's only
one way to escape from hell.
You're going to
have to kill the devil.
When you're finished eating,
you'll walk due west.
Once you get to the ocean,
you'll be able to see the statue.
The statue?
Your ship smashed through
it on its way inland.
Broke it into pieces.
That's where you'll find the devil.
You only have one chance.
Put this through his chest.
Do not hesitate, do
not let him say a word.
If he speaks, it will
already be too late.
He can be very persuasive.
How... how can I
kill him with this?
He... he's... black smoke.
No.
I am.
My wife Isabella...
She was running from you?
She was running from him.
I'm sorry. I saw him take her,
but I couldn't do
anything to stop him.
But... but if you are
the black smoke, you...
You aren't the only one who's
lost something, my friend.
The devil betrayed me.
He took my body,
my humanity.
You... you killed the
officers on the ship.
I'm not the one you
need to worry about.
The devil has your wife,
and you are going
to have to kill him
if you ever want to get her back.
Murder is wrong. That
is what brought me here.
My friend...
You and I can talk all day long
about what's right or wrong.
But the question before
you remains the same.
Do you ever want to
see your wife again?
Yes, I do.
What are you doing
here? Who gave you this?!
Where is my wife?
What?
I... I don't know your wife.
- Did she come here on the ship?
- No. She's dead.
Then why are you
asking me where she is?
Did you meet a man in the
jungle dressed in black?
Yes.
What did he tell you?
He said you are the devil.
And?
He said the only way I
would see my wife again
is if I kill you.
I... I saw her here...
in this place. Where is she?!
- That wasn't your wife.
- Yes, it was!
- She is dead, just like me.
- You're not dead.
I... I am in hell. I
know that I am in hell!
- You really think you're dead?
- Where else would I be?
All right then.
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no!
- Still think you're dead?!
- Aah!
Aah!
- Still think you're dead?
- Stop!
Why should I stop?!
Because I want to live!
That's the first sensible
thing you've said.
What's your name?
Ricardo.
Get up. We need to talk.
What is inside?
No one comes in
unless I invite them in.
Are you the devil?
No.
Then who are you?
My name is Jacob.
I'm the one who brought
your ship to this island.
You brought it here?
Why?
Think of this wine as what
you keep calling "hell."
There's many other
names for it, too.
"Malevolence."
"Evil."
"Darkness."
And here it is, swirling
around in the bottle,
unable to get out,
because if it did,
it would spread.
The cork...
is this island.
And it's the only thing
keeping the darkness...
where it belongs.
That man who sent you to kill me
believes that everyone is corruptible
because it's in their
very nature to sin.
I bring people here
to prove him wrong.
And when they get here,
their past doesn't matter.
Before you brought my
ship, there were others?
Yes. Many.
- What happened to them?
- They're all dead.
But if you brought them here,
why didn't you help them?
Because I wanted them
to help themselves...
To know the difference
between right and wrong
without me having to tell them.
It's all meaningless if I have
to force them to do anything.
Why should I have to step in?
If you don't, he will.
Do you want a job?
What, a job?
Doing what?
Well...
if I don't want to step in,
maybe you can do it for me.
You can be my...
my representative...
an intermediary between
me and the people
- I bring to the island.
- Well, what will I get in return?
- You tell me.
- I want my wife back.
Can't do that.
Can you absolve me of my
sins so I don't go to hell?
I can't do that either.
Then I never want to die.
I... I want to live forever.
Now that...
I can do.
You let him talk to you, didn't you?
He told me to give you this.
I'm sure you realize
that if you go with him,
you'll never be with
your wife again.
I understand.
He can be very...
convincing.
But I want you to know if
you ever change your mind...
and I mean ever,
my offer still stands.
I have something for you.
You must have dropped it.
I found it on the ship.
I've changed my mind.
Are you listening to me?
I was wrong!
You said I could
change my mind.
You said the offer would stand!
Does the offer still stand?
What offer, dude?
What the hell are you doing
out here? Did you follow me?
- Well, kinda.
- Get... get out! Get out!
Hey!
- Did... didn't you hear what I said?
- I was just...
I told you people, I
don't know anything!
Dude, just calm down!
- Why did you follow me?
- Your wife sent me!
What did you say?
I said your wife sent me.
Isabella.
She wants to know why
you buried her cross.
H-how do you know about that?
- Because she just told me.
- What do you mean, "just told you"?
Isabella saw you dig it up, man.
She's standing right next to you.
I... I... I don't see her.
She's right there.
She says your English is awesome.
Close your eyes.
She wants you to close your eyes.
It's okay. I'll tell
you what she says.
It was not your fault
that I died, Ricardo.
Is she gone?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah, you got it.
Something wrong?
Well, she kinda said
one more thing.
Something you have to do.
What?
She said you have to
stop the man in black.
You have to stop him
from leaving the island.
'Cause if you don't...
- Good morning.
- Morning
I see you got my present.
Don't gloat, Jacob.
It doesn't become you.
So you try to kill me?
You expect an apology?
No.
I guess I'm just wondering
why you did it.
Because I wanna leave.
Just let me leave, Jacob.
As long as I'm alive,
you're not going anywhere.
Well, then, now you know
why I wanna kill you.
And I will kill you, Jacob.
Even if you do, somebody
else will take my place.
Well, then I'll kill them too.
Here,
something for you
to pass the time.
I'll see you around.
Sooner than you think.
Re-sync and corrections by honeybunny
& chamallow35 www.Addic7ed.Com
Re-edits by Scooby