Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
I was offered a summer research
fellowship at Princeton.
A fine institution.
The place where
Albert Einstein taught,
and where Leonard got his PhD,
so it may have gone downhill.
Gentlemen, you may
remember Dr. Nowitzki.
She's back at Caltech
for her postdoc.
- Hello.
- Hi.
are you seeking a romantic
relationship with me?
What if I were?
Well, that would raise
a number of problems.
We're colleagues, I'm
currently in a relation...
Amy? Amy.
Amy?
Will you marry me?
One moment, please.
Really, you're going to
answer that right now?
It's Leonard.
I don't want to be rude.
Hello?
Oh, hey, where you been?
We've been calling you
for hours.
Oh, I'm sorry, my phone was
on "airplane" mode.
Why?
Because I was on an airplane.
Hey, put him on speaker.
- Yeah.
- Hey, where are you?
I came to Princeton
to see Amy.
It's a funny
story, actually.
I was having lunch
with Dr. Nowitzki,
and she kissed me.
- Excuse me?
- What?
I'm sorry?
And in that moment,
I realized
that Amy was the only woman
I ever wanted to kiss
for the rest of my life.
So I came to New Jersey
to ask her to marry me.
Oh, that's so sweet.
- Sheldon...
- Yeah, although
there was one man
whose blessing I needed first.
I've thought about it,
and I really want to spend
the rest of my life with Amy.
Do I have your blessing?
Well, Sheldon...
...I think you should make
her finger like Saturn
and put a ring on it.
You asked Stephen Hawking
and not her father?
Stephen Hawking's a genius.
If he said no, I wasn't gonna
waste my time on her father.
But you did ask my father?
I did. He said yes.
Although, not in a robot voice,
so it wasn't nearly as cool.
Okay. Oh, my God, I can't
believe you guys are engaged.
We're not engaged, yet.
She's taking forever to answer.
Because you're on the phone!
We'll call you back.
She said yes.
Yay!
Congratulations!
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 11x01 ?
The Proposal Proposal
Original Air Date o
@elder_man
Mother, I have
some good news to share.
We're engaged.
I am so happy for you two,
but I'm not surprised.
I've been praying for this.
Well, God had nothing
to do with it.
It happened because I was
kissing another woman,
and it made me realize
I wanted to be with Amy.
More than one woman
was interested in you?
I might have prayed
a little too hard.
Wait, oh, and I just...
I want to let you know
right now
that we are not
getting married in a church.
That's all right, Sheldon.
Anywhere Jesus is
is a church.
Well, he won't be
at our wedding.
He's in my heart,
so if I'm there,
he'll be there.
Okay, well, then,
he's your plus-one.
You don't get to bring
anyone else.
That's fine.
Love you.
Love you, too.
Bye.
Lord, thank you.
Even though you can do anything,
that was mighty
impressive.
We're engaged.
Oh, my God, that's amazing!
Wait, uh, tell me everything.
Well, Dr. Nowitzki was
kissing me...
Okay, you can stop leading
with that part of the story.
Well, congratulations.
I'm so happy
for you two.
Hold on, I have to
tell Bernadette.
Hey, Bernie, guess what?
Sheldon and Amy got engaged.
Can you believe it?
Oh, my God.
I cannot believe it.
She's so happy...
I think she's crying.
Do you think
Sheldon's gonna want
some weird
Star Trek wedding?
I don't know.
Well, Leonard could barely
finish the words
"Doctor Who wedding cake"
before I shut that down hard.
Mm-hmm.
Are you listening to me?
Yeah, you're mean
to Leonard. I heard you.
Is everything okay?
Look, I'm gonna
tell you something,
but you can't freak out,
because I'm already
freaking out.
Oh, my God,
what is it?
I'm pregnant again.
Wha...
Interesting.
Howard's gonna lose his mind.
Wait, you haven't
told him yet?
No.
You told me first?
Oh, Bernie!
This wasn't supposed
to happen-- we were careful.
Yeah, I didn't even think
you could get pregnant
while you were
breastfeeding.
Well, guess what?
You can.
Okay, look, look,
this is a good thing.
Halley's gonna have
a little brother
or sister to play with.
I guess that would be
pretty cute.
And, you, know, I was
a surprise to my parents,
and my dad said
it was the best thing
that ever happened to them.
Okay. Maybe this baby
actually is a blessing.
Oh, my God, honey,
of course it is.
How am I pregnant again?
Yeah, what were you thinking?
All right, I'm all
checked in to my flight.
Well, I'm sad
you're leaving.
Why'd you only book
a flight for one day?
I came here to propose.
If you'd said no,
I wouldn't want to stick around
looking at your stupid face.
Now, mind you,
your face is only stupid
in the "no" version
of the story.
But I said yes, so I get
a lifetime of this.
Yes, you do, smart face.
Why don't you stay
a few extra days?
Well, I don't have
any other clothes.
We'll get you some.
Oh, I don't know,
I'm pretty particular.
Well, there's a comic book store
less than a mile from here.
Perfect, let's go shopping.
Oh, um, and I'm having dinner
with some colleagues tonight.
I'm sure they'd
love to meet you.
Come on, what do you say?
Aw, you're nagging me.
It's like
we're already married.
Is that a yes or a no?
Geez, save some
for the honeymoon.
Look at Nowitzki
over there.
I can't believe
she tried to steal
Sheldon from Amy.
You know what?
I'm gonna go there and tell her
that they're engaged now
and that her little plan
didn't work.
Because you're sticking up
for Sheldon,
or because you're still mad
she rejected you?
Too far away, can't hear you.
Hello, Ramona.
Mm. Hello.
Why are you
sitting by yourself?
Oh, that's right,
Sheldon's in New Jersey
being engaged to Amy.
I heard.
Now that Sheldon's
out of the picture,
I could give you one more chance
to go out with me.
Nope, I'm good.
You sure?
I will not ask again.
I sincerely hope not.
Very well.
I'm going to leave
before this gets awkward.
Hey.
Want me to make dinner?
Uh, sure, but first,
why don't you have a seat?
There's something
I need to show you.
Ooh, if it's how to make
dinner, that'd be great.
Is this a... pregnancy test?
Yes.
That means... positive?
No.
Yes.
N-- No.
No!
How could this even happen?
Uh, w--
we were careful.
- Well, it did.
- No!
- Yes! Yes!
- No! No!
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
Well, w-what are we gonna do?
What do you mean
what are we gonna do?
We're gonna have another baby.
- No! No!
- Stop that!
- Yes!
- I'm trying!
Look, I know
it's scary, but...
we're both responsible adults,
we can do this.
You really think so?
No!
Hey, Stuart.
Oh, hey, Raj.
What can I help you with?
I need to buy
an engagement gift.
Well, you came
to the wrong place.
It's for Sheldon and Amy.
No way! They're engaged?
Yeah.
Well, that's exciting news.
Who would've thought Sheldon
and Amy would be the next two
to tie the knot?
Tell me about it. I'm the one
who caught the bouquet at
Leonard and Penny's wedding.
Okay.
Uh... you know,
they might like this.
Superman and Wonder Woman,
it's kind of romantic.
Hmm.
You know what?
Why am I buying them a gift?
They have love.
Screw them and
their happiness.
What do you have for someone
who's bitter and alone?
Literally everything.
Sheldon, these are the heads
of my research team.
Oh, hello.
Dr. Zane, Dr. Harris,
this is my fianc?,
Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
That's the first time
I've said that
and it kind of gave me
the goose bumps.
Dr. Cooper,
- we are so excited to meet you.
- Oh.
Well, that's very kind of you.
If you'd like, I could autograph
your menus after dinner, yeah?
But I better not see those
on eBay.
No, no, no, we're just
excited to meet the man
who landed
this brilliant woman here.
Oh!
That wasn't hard,
she threw herself at me.
Now, getting the universe
to show me its naughty bits,
that-that took some doing.
Sheldon's a physicist.
Oh.
Oh, that's nice.
Amy, I recently read
your paper on lesions
in the olfactory receptors
in the brain.
It was inspired.
Oh, well,
I guess it didn't stink.
But if it did,
that rat wouldn't have known it.
I'm sorry,
I'm sure you don't
want to sit here
and listen to
a bunch of work talk.
Oh, no, I love it.
No, but let's talk about work.
Amy's work, my work.
Yeah, why don't
we start with my work?
Actually, I do have
a question for Dr. Cooper.
When Amy first
told you about
her approach to
synaptic tracing,
did you think it was gonna
revolutionize the field?
Really?
That's your question?
What are you,
Entertainment Tonight?
You know what?
Let me give you a
better question. Here,
um, "Dr. Cooper,
"I heard you were working on
a top-secret project
"for the U.S. military.
Why don't you tell us
about that?"
See, that's a great question.
Okay, what was that like?
Oh, I can't tell you that,
it's top-secret.
Boy, that was exhausting.
You know, no offense, but your
colleagues were pretty rude.
Really, they were rude?
Yes.
They just kept talking about you
and how great you are,
no matter how many times
I brought me up.
You know,
these are my colleagues
and they want to talk
about my work.
Why does that bother you
so much?
Because I was there.
It's like having
Optimus Prime over to dinner
and not asking him
to turn into a truck.
You know what, Sheldon?
You're not always the smartest
person in every room.
You may not even be the smartest
person in this room.
Oh, I am sorry.
What, is Neil deGrasse Tyson
hiding behind the couch?
'Cause if he is,
he's not that smart,
it's pretty dusty back there.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm storming off to my room.
Well, then where am I
supposed to storm off to?
Well, you're so smart,
why don't you figure it out?
Is there another bedroom?
Perhaps a-a den?
So, how are you guys
doing with all the new
events in your womb?
Good, you know?
Obviously,
it was a surprise.
There was some crying
and some yelling.
Some suggestion
of make-up sex
that did not go over well,
even though it's not like
we can get more pregnant.
But then we realized that
it's a gift, in the sense
that we didn't
ask for it,
and we may not
have chosen it...
And we already have one.
You know, whenever
I find a top I like,
I always go back and get a
second one in a different color.
Which I hope is not the case
with your baby.
I know you guys are freaked out,
but you're great parents,
and if you ever need help,
we are here for you.
Yeah, anything at all, just ask.
Ooh, you know what you could do?
You could have a baby, too.
I'm sorry, what?
No, that's a great idea,
we could go through it together.
Wouldn't that be fun?
You guys were just saying
how freaked out
and miserable you are.
I say lots of crazy things.
I'm pregnant and hormonal.
Do it! Have a baby, do it!
Come on, it'd be so cute,
our kids playing together?
What do you say, why don't
you two hit the old mattress
and whip up a family?
Okay, we're not
gonna have a baby
just to make you
guys feel better.
Yeah, if we're gonna have a baby
it's gonna be when we are ready,
or when I'm certain
Penny is gonna leave me.
Exactly.
They're my friends,
and I should be happy for them.
A-And I'm trying,
but all I feel is this gnawing,
empty sensation in my gut.
I had that once.
Turned out it was a tapeworm.
Cool. Uh...
It's just...
it's hard talking
to my other friends about this,
but I knew you would understand.
Why is that?
Because you and I
are both alone,
which is actually
kind of comforting,
because at least
we can be alone together.
Mm. This is-this is awkward.
I, um, I was actually gonna
close up a little early tonight
'cause I have a date.
Really?
Yeah.
Forgive me if I'm having trouble
being happy for you.
Don't be silly,
I'm loving your pain.
Is this how our marriage
is going to be?
Sometimes people
will be more interested
in talking to her than to me?
Are you sitting in a bathroom?
Yes.
I needed a place to storm off to
and it was all
that was available.
Fine.
But if I hear a flush,
this conversation is over.
Those people were in the
presence of a world-class mind,
and all they wanted to talk
about was their own nonsense.
Can you see the irony
in that statement?
How about now?
I'll wait.
Uh...
Surprise.
Oh, crap, is it our anniversary?
No.
Wait.
All right, so what
are we celebrating?
Well, you know, Bernadette
and Howard are pregnant again,
and Amy and Sheldon
are getting married.
I didn't want you
to feel left out.
Ah. Left out?
Well, Bernadette has to grow
a baby inside of her,
and Amy has to marry one.
My life is great.
So do you not want the cake?
Try and take it away,
see what happens.
Oh, crap,
it is our anniversary.
Happy anniversary!
Amy.
There's something
I need to say to you.
I'm listening.
I've been thinking
about the Avengers.
I believe that.
But I don't think
that's something
you needed to say to me.
I realized
that Iron Man is great.
And also,
that Captain America is great.
And sometimes, Iron Man
is in a Captain America movie,
and he's not mad
it's not an Iron Man movie.
You know, he can fly in,
give the audience a thrill,
and then fly away.
And that should've
been me tonight.
I should've been the delightful
cameo in your movie.
Thank you, Sheldon.
Instead, I was like
the Hulk, and I...
Okay, please stop talking
about the Avengers.
Anyway.
I'm proud of you.
And I'm going to try
to do a better job
of sharing the spotlight
because we're a team.
You know?
Much like t-the Dodgers.
If they had superpowers,
and fought crime.
And Thor was in them.
Sheldon, I know this isn't easy,
but you'll have
a whole lifetime to practice.
I-It could take that long,
I'm really bad at it.
You know, maybe, um,
I should start right now,
and go back to Pasadena
and let you have
this experience to yourself.
You just want to go back
'cause that's where everybody
makes a fuss over you.
You know, your colleagues
are right, you are brilliant.
Hello.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Amy, welcome back.
Oh, l-let me see the ring.
Ooh, nice.
H-Hey, her eyes are up there.
I-Is that the woman
who kissed Sheldon?
Uh... Could be.
Hard to say.
Tell us about Princeton.
Excuse me for a minute.
Not-- well, we'll
catch up later.
This is going to be
the biggest smackdown
since my Aunt Noopur showed up
at the family reunion
wearing the same sari
as my cousin Sruti.
Dr. Nowitzki?
Oh.
Dr. Fowler. Um, hello.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man