All right, Saturday
is the big day.
A lot of people thought
this would never come.
I may have been
one of those people.
Wait, wait, are we talking
about the wedding?
Yes.
Oh, yeah, I was definitely
one of those people.
And yet, here we are.
Now, we got a lot of family
coming in tomorrow.
I'm gonna need everyone's help.
Think of this as one of
your comic book movies.
There's a bunch of superheroes,
each with a different task.
Oh, like
the new Avengers.
Which one was that?
The one you slept through
last weekend.
Oh, that was
a good nap.
I-I think it's more like, uh,
like Lord of the Rings,
and you're the Fellowship.
Uh, someone's
got to go to Gondor,
someone's got to go to Mordor,
someone's got to hold off
the demon of shadow and flame.
You mean the Balrog?
I mean my mother.
That is a perfect
metaphor, Amy.
Thank you.
Because it also involves a ring
that binds me
in servitude forever.
Aw, he said forever.
? The Big Bang Theory 11x24 ?
The Bow Tie Asymmetry
Original Air Date o
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
That was Wil Wheaton.
He's really excited
about tomorrow.
As am I.
If you'd have told me as a child
that an actor from Star Trek
would be officiating my wedding,
I would've said,
"Ooh, William Shatner?"
And if you'd have said,
"No, Wil Wheaton,"
I'd have said, "Well, did you
even try William Shatner?"
And if you'd have said,
"Yes, but he costs too much
money," I'd have said,
"Ah, well,
Wil Wheaton's good, too."
Why do you keep tying
and untying that bow tie?
I can't seem to get it even.
Well, I don't think
it's supposed to be even.
Sometimes a little asymmetry
looks good.
In the Renaissance,
they called it "sprezzatura."
The Renaissance?
Amy, you know I'm more
of an Enlightenment person.
At some point, we have to decide
how we want to raise
the children.
So are you feeling okay?
No wedding jitters?
No.
There is nothing
in the world
that would stop me from
marrying you tomorrow,
even me from the future coming
back to prevent the wedding
and the subsequent birth of a
child who will destroy humanity.
Because if you came
from the future,
that would mean you already
went through with the wedding
because you believe that
time travel is on a closed loop.
I love you
so damn much.
Uh, Mr. Fowler,
are you okay back there?
Do you need more air?
He's fine.
I'm surprised
Amy didn't pick us up.
Oh, well, you know,
she's pretty busy the
day before her wedding.
Too busy for her mother?
She used to be
such a devoted daughter.
Now she's just waiting for me
to die so she can get my china.
Thank you again
for picking us up.
My pleasure, Mrs. Cooper.
You know,
our driver to the airport
was also a Indian fella.
Mom...
Oh, so now it's racist to notice
when somebody's Indian.
I don't think it's racist.
I noticed you were both white.
See? You'll have
to excuse her.
She's just pregnant
and hormonal.
Oh, yeah, congratulations
on baby number two.
Yeah. Whoopie.
Her husband would be here,
but he stayed home
to watch their older son,
so e-everything's fine!
Stop it.
We're separated.
You don't say.
So, you're Sheldon's
big brother.
Uh, yeah.
He got the brains.
I got the bod.
And the face and the hair.
I like your accent.
Sheldon, did you
used to sound like that?
Can you still?
I can. I will not.
Amy, you said something
about my bow tie
that I can't stop
thinking about.
Don't you mean...
"Y'all said
something 'bout my bow tie"?
Go on, say it.
Say it.
Hey, guys, look who I have.
- Oh.
- Hey.
Hey, Shelly.
I'm so glad you made it, Missy.
This is my fianc?e, Amy.
Amy, this is my sister.
If I ever need a kidney,
this is where you get it.
- It's so nice to meet you.
- ?Aw.
I've always wanted a sister.
Really? Why?
I love you, too, Sheldon.
Where's Mom?
Uh, she wanted to stop by
the hotel and freshen up,
and then call her pastor
to pray for Missy's soul.
Oh, my God.
There's mama's girl.
- Hi, Mom.
- ?Oh!
Oh, Larry, look at her!
Can you believe our little lamb
is finally getting married?
He can't believe it.
And neither can I.
Hi, Dad. How you doing?
What the hell is that?
Come on, you know this one.
It's a... dog.
I found him in the backyard.
And don't worry,
I already called the owner.
Good, 'cause
we don't need a dog.
We already have two babies,
you and Stuart.
That's probably him.
Hi.
I'm gonna need a minute.
That's Mark Hamill!
Hello.
Thank you so much
for finding this guy.
Oh, my goodness.
Hey, Bark. How are you, buddy?
Y-Your dog's name is Bark?
Yeah.
Bark Hamill?
Yeah. Well, I let the fans
name him online.
I got lucky, though.
He was almost
Honey Baked Hamill.
Anyway, thanks so much.
I-I want to give you a reward
for finding him.
Oh, no, I
couldn't take your money.
It's just an honor
to meet you.
No. No, please. You don't know
what this dog means to me,
and I thought
he was gone for good.
Please? There must be
something I can do for you.
Anything.
Oh, you're gonna regret
that.
Hey, dude.
Dude?
Yeah, you know,
just want you to know
that I don't think
of you as a woman.
Oh, perfect. I don't
think of you as a man.
Great.
So, as two genderless blobs
of human flesh,
how would you like to go
to Sheldon and Amy's wedding
with me?
Oh, Stuart.
Look, I appreciate that,
but it just might be
a little weird,
considering you're my boss.
Guess who's gonna officiate
Sheldon and Amy's wedding!
Mark Hamill!
Luke Skywalker
is gonna be at the wedding!
You'll need to
buy me a dress.
And did you know
that my Amy
played Amelia Earhart
in the eighth grade?
Amy, you never said you
were in a school play.
Oh, no, no, at home.
I'd never let her
do a school play.
Those kids just take drugs
and have intercourse.
You know, Amy still
does some performing.
She and Sheldon do an
Internet show about flags.
Amy?
V-Videos on the Internet?
You know what men
use those for.
If you're talking about
Fun with Flags,
I use it to go to sleep.
Sheldon,
you're awfully quiet.
Are you okay?
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry.
I was thinking about
string theory.
But catch me up.
What'd I miss?
Are you seeing
this, Larry?
These are the people I'm
gonna have to live with
after you're dead.
Welcome, Bert.
Don't you look nice.
Yeah. Like a geode,
I clean up good.
Don't you crack a geode open?
It's not a perfect metaphor.
Oh, my God.
- Is that Mark Hamill?
- ?Yeah.
Oh, my God.
- Is that...
- Bert, go find your seat!
W-What is he doing here?
I found his dog
and guilted him into
officiating the wedding.
Don't tell Sheldon.
It's a surprise.
Wait, I-I thought
Wil was officiating the wedding.
Yeah, so did he.
How did he take the news?
I'll let you know.
Hey, Wil!
Are you having an allergic
reaction to my boutonniere?
No. I'm just so
happy for you.
And for me.
After today, you
are officially--
and, more important,
legally-- Amy's problem.
Don't be silly, Leonard.
I will always be your problem.
Hey, baby.
Hello, Mother.
Leonard, could you
give us a moment?
Oh, of course.
Oh, Shelly.
I wish your dad
could see you now.
Me, too. I miss him.
He would be so
proud of you.
I know that I am.
Thank you.
I mean, for everything.
My whole life.
Oh.
Let me
straighten your tie.
No, no, no, it's all right.
It's supposed to be
a little asymmetrical.
Apparently, a small flaw
somehow improves it.
I can see that.
Sometimes it's the...
imperfect stuff that
makes things perfect.
Excuse me.
Case in point.
So, we finally meet.
I'm sorry, who are you?
I'm Wil Wheaton.
I was supposed
to officiate this wedding.
I was up all night
preparing these notes.
Well, thanks so much.
It's gonna be a great help.
Amy.
Come in.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Wow, you look amazing!
That's not what I need
to tell you.
But you do!
What's wrong?
Something incredible
just happened.
Remember when you were
telling me about my bow tie
and how a little asymmetry
is good?
- Yeah?
- My equations have been trying
to describe an imperfect world,
and the only way to do that
is to introduce imperfection
into the underlying theory.
So, instead of supersymmetry,
it would be super asymmetry?
Super asymmetry.
That's it!
- Give me your lipstick.
- What?
Just give it to me,
you beautiful thing!
We have work to do!
Hey, uh, the
bride and groom
seem to be running
a little behind.
Do you think
you could stall?
Stall? How?
Hey, everybody!
Uh, it's gonna be a few
more minutes, but while we wait,
does anyone have any
questions about Star Wars?
You got this.
So if I make
slightly asymmetric knots
with sheets in four dimensions,
I can bootstrap
the whole idea
to a large asymmetry
in 11 dimensions.
Maybe even at
the initial moment of creation,
the fundamental forces
lacked symmetry.
Everyone's waiting.
What are you guys doing?
Super asymmetry.
Super asymmetry?
Is that a thing?
We're inventing
it right now.
Don't you think
this can wait until...
Hold on.
This is interesting.
So, yeah, Mr. Mark?
When you were on the,
uh, Wookiee home planet,
how did you even understand
what they were saying?
I don't remember ever being
on a Wookiee home planet.
Uh, actually, Luke was
on the Wookiee home planet,
Kashyyyk, in the
Holiday Special
when he helped Chewie
get home to his wife.
Chewie had a wife?
Her name's Malla.
Wow, that's impressive.
Yeah.
Hey, uh, I got a question.
Why aren't there tires on
any of those Star Wars vehicles?
I'm sure some of them had tires.
Actually, they don't.
I mean, the HAVw A5 turbo tank
has metal gripping wheels,
but I wouldn't call them tires.
You are so hot.
This is taking too long.
I bet that Sheldon
stood my baby up.
Uh, excuse me.
Where-where are you going?
This whole thing
was a big mistake.
I'm gonna find Amy
and get her out of here.
- ?Sit down!
Excuse me?
Sheldon loves Amy,
and he would never hurt her
on her wedding day
or any other day, so park it.
Oh, you sit down, too.
Are you gonna let her
talk to me like that?
Say something.
Thank you.
Uh, according
to Google, there are
zero papers
that mention super asymmetry.
This is brand-new.
No one's thought of it.
What are you lunatics doing?!
Sheldon had a breakthrough.
Actually, Amy and I
had a breakthrough.
Oh, science? Shocking!
You don't understand.
This could be really big.
No, Penny's right.
We have our whole lives
to do science together.
Let's get married.
All right.
It's go time!
I am pumped!
Okay, everyone. Here we go.
Leonard.
That's Mark Ha-Ha-Ha...
It's-it's Mark Hami-Ha-Ha...
Yep. Thank Wolowitz.
He set it up.
Thank you.
Congratulations
on your wedding.
Thank you.
When this is over, I have
4,000 things for you to sign.
Thank you, Daddy.
I-I thought Wil was marrying us.
Wolowitz got us an upgrade.
Another sci-fi
guy with a beard.
Seems lateral, but okay.
Welcome.
We are gathered here today
in the sight of family,
friends and Almighty God.
That's too religious.
That lady over there
made me say it.
He heard you,
and he can't un-hear you.
We're here
to celebrate the marriage
of Sheldon Lee Cooper...
...and Amy Farrah Fowler.
I had more prepared,
but I'm just gonna skip
to the rings and vows,
since I've been answering
your questions for 45 minutes.
Yeah, he answered 'em.
Amy, you're up.
Sheldon, when I
was a little girl,
I used to dream
about my wedding.
But, eventually,
I stopped,
because I thought that
day would never come.
And then I met you.
From the first moment
in that coffee shop,
I knew that there was
something special between us,
even though I did
work on a study
that disproved love
at first sight.
I loved that study
the moment I read it.
Ironic, huh?
Clearly, it was wrong.
Because I felt
something that day,
and those feelings have only
gotten stronger with time.
I can't imagine loving you
more than I do right now.
But I felt that way yesterday
and the day before yesterday
and the day before that.
Is that growth linear
or accelerating?
Accelerating.
Oh, maybe we could
graph it out.
Save something
for the honeymoon.
Smart.
Sheldon,
I don't know
what the future holds,
but I know that I've never
been happier than I am
in this moment marrying you.
Well, that was
unexpectedly beautiful.
I might need a minute.
Amy...
...I usually know
exactly what to say.
But in this moment...
I have no words.
I guess...
I'm overwhelmed by you.
In a good way.
Not in the elevator
in the Haunted Mansion way.
Even if I can't
tell you now how I feel,
I will spend my life showing you
how much I love you.
Do you...
Hey, I'm just saying, I'm here
if you need me to step in.
No, no, no.
I got this.
Amy, do you take Sheldon
for your lawful wedded husband?
I do.
And, Sheldon, same thing.
Then by the power vested in me
by
EvenYouCanPerformWeddings.com...
...I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
? At wast... ?
? My wove has come awong ?
? My wonewy days are over ?
? And wife is wike a song ?
? Oh, yeah. ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man