I thought angels were
supposed to be guardians --
fluffy wings, halos.
You know, not dicks.
Read the Bible.
Angels are warriors of God.
[ Screaming ]
I'm a soldier.
Crowley: I think I know
the identity
of Lucifer's newest vessel.
I give you one Jefferson Rooney,
President
of these United States.
I just know you'd make
an amazing father.
A Nephilim is come into being,
the offspring
of an angel and a human.
Lucifer.
I can't have this baby.
[ Grunts, gasps ]
I'm afraid I'll have to insist.
[ Gasping ]
Princeps Inferni!
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Groans ]
[ Grunts, groans ]
What about the girl?
Sanchez: Kelly Kline.
She's a presidential aide.
We don't know where she went
or if she's still alive.
Mary: What's happening?
[ Engine sputters ]
Yeah, Dean. 'Sup?
Billie?
The reaper?
Sam: We made a deal.
Come midnight,
a Winchester goes bye-bye.
We made a pact,
bound in blood.
You break that,
there's consequences
on a cosmic scale.
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Thud ]
Cass, what have you done?
What had to be done.
Yeah, you made a deal.
You made a stupid deal,
and I broke it.
You're welcome.
[ Gunfire ]
[ Buttons clicking ]
?
Unplugging things now.
Hint, hint.
Yes, I'm almost finished.
[ Gunfire continues ]
[ Glass bottles clink ]
You don't have to beat
that game every night.
I disagree.
Fine.
I'm gonna take this out.
Time I get back,
we are closed.
You leave. End of story.
[ Bottles clink ]
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
You're too old
for video games.
Oh.
Were you waitin' to play?
Everyone deserves a turn.
[ Scoffs ]
I'm sorry. Have we met?
Have we?
[ Building crumbles,
chirp, beep ]
Move out of my way.
Or?
Or I will move you.
Really? Go ahead. Try.
[ Sighs ]
Suit yourself.
Oh, Benjamin.
Your little angel tricks
won't work on me.
Who are you?
[ Blades clank ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Blade clatters ]
?
Aah!
[ Blade clatters ]
[ Panting ]
Don't. Please.
[ Laughs ]
Oh-law zeer ah tee-loh-kah.
Oh-law zeer
ah tee-loh-kah.
Yar-ree fee-fee-suh, pie neez.
[ Electricity crackling ]
That's right.
Call your friends.
Nuh-nah-ee-luh zee-rum
ah-duh-fantuh.
Oh-law zeer ah tee-loh-kah.
Yar-ree fee-fee-suh,
pie neez.
Nuh-nah-ee-luh zee-rum
ah-duh-fantuh.
Oh-law zeer ah tee-loh-kah.
Yar-ree fee-fee-suh,
pie neez.
Nuh-nah-ee-luh zee-rum
ah-duh-fantuh.
Nuh-nah-ee-luh zee-rum ah-duh-fantuh.
I've waited so long.
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Thud ]
[ Exhales ]
?
[ Door opens, closes ]
? Supernatural 12x10 ?
Lily Sunder Has Some Regrets
Original Air Date o
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Yeah, I was looking
at that earlier.
[ Sighs ]
Cass has been busy, huh?
Yeah, busy not finding
Kelly Kline
or her Rosemary's baby.
[ Chair slides ]
I mean, how's a chick like this
just drop off the map?
Well, I think that's what
he's trying to figure out.
Hey, you, uh,
you hear from Mom yet?
Yeah, she called last night,
said she's got a line
on a shapeshifter in Atlanta.
I said we could come help,
and she said, “Don't bother”"
Apparently, she's “got it”"
[ Chuckles ]
Then she's probably got it.
Yeah.
Mom's good.
I just think
she jumped back into this
a little quick, don't you?
I don't think we have
the kind of mom
who's gonna stay home
and make us chicken soup
for dinner, you know?
You talk to Cass yet?
No.
[ Scoffs ] So, what,
you're just gonna
keep walking past each other in
the kitchen, not saying a word?
Maybe.
Look, yes, Cass killed Billie,
but he saved us.
He saved Mom. How long are you
gonna stay pissed?
I'm not pissed that
he cares about us, you know.
I'm -- I'm grateful.
But Billie said there would
be “cosmic consequences”
if that deal got broken.
You have any idea what
that means?
No.
Neither do I,
but I'm pretty sure it ain't
jellybeans and g-strings.
My point is, Cass thought
he was doing the right thing.
I was doing the right thing.
[ Footsteps approach ]
You sure about that?
Yes.
Yeah? Well, I'm not so sure.
And when the other shoe drops --
I'll deal with it.
[ Scoffs ]
I have to go.
Got a lead on Kelly?
No. This is personal.
Meaning what?
Another angel. An old friend.
He called out for help.
Oh. Good old reliable
angel radio.
He was begging for help
and then he just stopped.
I need to know
if he's still alive.
Yeah, all right. Well...
we'll come with you.
Both of you?
Sure. Yeah, we could help.
Gotta make sure you don't do
anything else stupid.
[ Engine purring ]
All right, who wants music?
I'm good.
You?
[ Castiel groans ]
Okay.
Cass,
is there anything specific
we should know
about your friend?
All right.
Guys, you know what?
This -- this silent treatment
thing, it's silly.
It's not gonna work.
Whatever we're walking into,
we should, you know,
probably have an actual plan.
[ Sighs ]
What do you wanna know?
Oh, he speaks.
Enough.
Cass, you said
when you heard Benjamin,
he -- he was screaming.
It was, um...
Look, Benjamin wouldn't
call for help lightly.
And he wouldn't put himself in
harm's way if he could help it.
Wow, this Benjamin seems like
he's pretty cool, you know.
Like he wouldn't make any
half-cocked, knee-jerk choices.
Yeah, you know what I like
about him?
Is that he's sarcastic,
but he's thoughtful
and appreciative, too.
Now what is that supposed to mean?
Okay, okay, the road, road.
[ Horn blares ]
Dude, watch the road.
I got it.
Anything else, Cass?
[ Sighs ] Benjamin is always
very careful.
Long ago, he found a powerfully
devout vessel in Madrid,
and her faith, it...
she gave him everything --
her trust and her body.
Wait. So Benjamin's a woman.
Benjamin is an angel.
His vessel is a woman.
But it -- it's --
it's more than that.
She's not just his vessel.
She's...
She's his friend.
Yeah.
Benjamin would never put her
in unnecessary danger.
Okay, well, if this Benjamin
is so careful,
then what happened?
I don't know.
That's what I need to find out.
?
[ Indistinct whispering ]
[ Whispering indistinctly ]
The police report is
calling it a stabbing.
Man: Sure, yeah.
That's the official story.
I mean, I was outside,
and...
Dead woman? No blood?
Come on.
And these crazy burn marks?
[ Helicopter hovering ]
It's a cult thing, right?
That's why the FBI's --
Get out.
-What?
-Get out.
He means we can take it
from here. Thanks.
Yeah.
We'll call you when we're done.
Dude. You all right?
No.
No, Benjamin and I,
we fought together.
He was...
he was a gifted soldier.
I don't know how this
could've happened.
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
Got something.
Looks like we had a little
angel-on-angel action.
This isn't Benjamin's blade.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
What?
[ Whispering indistinctly ]
Castiel.
We have to go. Now.
[ Kisses ]
All right, who we meetin'?
His name is Ishim.
Before I, uh, commanded
my own flight of angels,
my own battalion, I served
under him with Benjamin.
And you think he knows
what's going on?
We'll find out.
You wait here.
Whoa, wait. Excuse me?
Ishim said to come alone.
He doesn't like humans.
If I plan to do anything else
stupid, I'll let you know.
[ Door bell jingles ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Mirabel. Ishim.
Kept your vessels all this time.
I'm impressed.
We are not careless.
But you, Castiel...
I liked the old you better.
We've been waiting.
I suppose it does take longer
to get places now
without our wings.
You had a hand in that, correct?
Now, Mirabel,
some angels think of Castiel
as a hero.
[ Cash register bell dings ]
After he left us, he had
his own flight to command.
Balthazar, Uriel.
Great soldiers.
Both dead now, of course.
You had a hand in that, too.
So is he a hero?
Is he a spanner in the works?
I don't know.
I'm not a hero,
but sometimes doing the right
thing requires sacrifices.
True,
but it just always seems
that it's other angels
sacrificing for your good deeds.
Their wings, their lives.
Are you here to insult me
or talk about Benjamin?
Can't we do both?
In the years since we lost
our wings,
two others from our flight have
been murdered, like Benjamin.
We're all that's left.
Why didn't I know
about this?
We didn't think you'd care.
And you're gonna storm in
right...
now.
[ Door bell jingles ]
Hey.
Dean.
[ Door closes ]
Feel a little left out
over there.
Scoot over.
I said to come alone.
These are my friends --
my friends who don't listen
very well.
How you doing? I'm --
We know who you are.
Check outside to see
if there are others.
[ Spoon clinking ]
I only brought
Sam and Dean.
As far as you know.
[ Crash in distance ]
?
Mirabel, right?
[ Screaming ]
[ Exhales ]
Well, who wants some pie?
You know, when I knew Castiel,
he was a soldier.
[ Packet crumpling ]
He was a warrior.
He was an angel's angel.
[ Smacks packet ]
Now look how far
he's fallen.
Dean: How about a little coffee
with that sugar?
No wings, no home.
Just a ratty old coat and a pair
of poorly trained monkeys.
Oh. Well, you can go to Hell.
Dean, it's fine.
No. No, it's not.
Sam, this isn't about me.
It's about Benjamin.
Now that
is refreshingly accurate.
But since you brought
a couple of extra “people”
to our little chitchat,
we should go somewhere
more private.
I have a safe house nearby.
I'll go get Mirabel.
[ Bills rustling ]
So nice to see you, old friend.
Have some pie.
[ Door bell jingles ]
Wow.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Door closes ]
Hell of a friend, Cass.
Why do you let him
talk to you like that?
If Ishim can help me find
whoever killed Benjamin,
then I have to.
Okay, yeah, look,
I-I get that we need
super dick there,
but, I mean, come on.
The angels that I served with
are being killed.
So I will put up with Ishim,
I will put up
with everything else,
and so will you. I have to go.
[ Door bell jingles ]
?
Mirabel.
You! [ Grunts ]
[ Laughs ]
You can't smite me, Ishim.
I'm not powerless anymore.
But how --
No!
Castiel. Kill her! [ Grunts ]
Ah! Aah! Oh!
[ Blade slices ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Blade clatters ]
?
I know you.
Sam: Hey!
[ Grunts ]
[ Cocks gun ] I don't wanna hurt you.
I don't want to hurt any human.
Just let me finish
what I started.
Yeah, not gonna happen, Patches.
[ Grunts ]
[ Whoosh ]
Can't see.
Sam? Hey.
[ Engine starts ]
[ Engine revs ]
I can't see. Did you get a plate?
Yeah, I got it.
Who the hell was that?!
[ Crows cawing ]
Castiel: Ishim, let me tend
to your wound.
I'm fine.
[ Sighs deeply ]
Ishim, how is she still alive?
Wait a second. You know her?
Yes.
You don't owe them
an explanation.
Okay, hang on now.
Uh, One-Eyed Willy back there
wasn't trying to kill us.
She was after you.
So talk before she kicks in
the damn door.
Before the Apocalypse,
angels, um...
well, we rarely came
to Earth.
Yeah, uh,
basically never, right?
Right,
except this once.
Many years ago,
there was an anomaly.
An anomaly?
They won't understand.
Cass, what's going on?
?
[ Bird chirping ]
Castiel, are we all here?
Yes.
Why are we even on Earth?
It's so wet.
Stop complaining.
We're here because one of
our fellow angels
has taken a human wife.
They also have a small daughter.
A Nephilim? You're sure?
Father has wings.
Mother's a primate.
And this child
has a human soul
mixed with angelic grace.
Now that's --
Dangerous.
Nephilim are forbidden
by the oldest laws in heaven.
We jumped down here for a kid?
Castiel: Nephilim grow up.
They grow into their power
and then --
Entire worlds die.
So we've come
to set things right.
?
[ Door thuds ]
[ Whispers ] Akobel, please.
Go back inside.
Just...
[ Whispers indistinctly ]
[ Crows cawing ]
You have no business here.
Me?
You were sent here to observe
humanity, to watch and to learn.
But instead, taking up
with a filthy animal.
Have you no shame?
Who are you to lecture me
about shame?
Humans aren't animals.
Most of them are good
and true and...
[ Horse whinnies in distance ]
How could anyone know them
and not love them?
Touching, but we're not --
I know why you're here.
[ Blades clank ]
[ Groans ]
Castiel.
Akobel, Seraphim of
the Sixth Choir,
you have lain with a human
and you fathered a Nephilim.
What?
Continue.
You have broken
our most sacred oath,
and the penalty is...
death.
[ Gasps ]
[ Thud ]
Dispose of his vessel.
This next part,
I'll do alone.
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
No! No!
Stay away from
my daughter!
[ Girl screaming ]
Cass, you, um...
We completed a mission.
Some mission.
It was horrific, but it was
necessary. It was right.
Well, you say so.
And the woman?
Ishim: Lily Sunder.
She was a professor
of Apocalyptic Literature.
Studied angels,
speaks fluent Enochian.
I took mercy on her
by letting her live.
And now she wants revenge.
Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, she's gotta be what,
100 years old?
Castiel: No. More.
Yeah, but somehow,
she's still kicking ass?
No. Not somehow.
I know what she's up to.
She made some kind
of demonic pact.
Keeps her young,
keeps her strong.
Keeps her immune from
our powers.
All right, but we'll find her,
me and Sam.
No, Dean.
Cass, she doesn't care
about us, okay?
She's gunning for you guys.
Yeah, maybe we can
reason with her.
Uh, four dead angels indicate
that perhaps she is not
reasonable.
If she has this dark power,
it will take all of us
to fight her.
And I need to heal your wound.
Wait -- wait a second,
Cass.
Her family was murdered.
I mean, I-I know you were just
doing a job, but --
Are you saying that those angels
deserved to die?
What?
You think I deserve to die?
No, no.
That's not what he's saying.
What is he saying?
I'm saying maybe if
we find her,
we can explain to her that
you're different now, you know?
Sam, that won't work.
She won't quit.
Think about it. Would you?
Castiel's right. It won't work.
We have to try.
He's right,
and we're not askin'.
?
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Inhales deeply,
exhales slowly ]
[ Exhales slowly ]
[ Whooshing ]
?
The way you let
those simians talk to you...
Castiel, when did you get
so gooey?
[ Grunts ] You know why
we're meant to stay away
from them humans?
Hmm?
It's not because we're
a danger to them. [ Groans ]
They're a danger to us.
Case in point.
Well, my friendship with Sam
and Dean has made me stronger.
You can't really believe that.
Your wound is deep.
This'll be painful.
[ Stomps foot ]
Ohh.
[ Whooshing ]
Ah. [ Exhales slowly ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Inhales deeply, grunts ]
[ Grunts, exhales sharply ]
[ Elevator bell dings ]
You sure about this address?
Well, Lily's car was a rental,
so I called the company.
I told them she was wanted
for questioning by the FBI.
They pinged the LoJack --
Okay, you could've
just said yes.
Yes.
So what's the plan?
Well, we knock on her door
and ask her nicely
not to kill anymore angels.
And if she says no?
Then we burn that bridge
when we come to it.
[ Gasps ]
Whoa! Whoa!
Give us a second.
How did you find me?
We're here to talk, that's it.
We come in peace.
Just hear us out.
We heard what happened
to your family.
My family?
See, Cass is our family,
so we can't let you hurt him.
Let me?
We don't wanna kill you.
I don't wanna kill you.
Okay, good. Look, there we go.
Agreed.
Listen, it's not Cass' fault
that Heaven has
these crazy rules
about Nephilim.
Your daughter.
You think...
[ Exhales ]
?
[ Voice breaks ]
Her name was May,
and she was beautiful.
[ May humming ]
[ Whispers ] I find
that doll disturbing.
Her father gave it to her.
She loves it. Let her be.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
I had a life,
a wonderful life,
until...
They took everything from me.
Akobel, please.
Go back inside.
Take May. Run.
?
You have no business here.
Mommy?
It's fine, sweetheart.
Everything is going to be fine,
I promise.
[ Akobel gasps ]
[ Gasps ] Come on. Come on.
[ Whimpers ]
All my life,
I dreamed about angels.
I studied them.
I made them my life's work,
until finally I learned
the spell to summon one --
Ishim.
[ Gasps ] When I first saw him,
it was like
looking into the face
of the Divine.
I thought he was perfect.
But he is a monster.
[ Voice breaks ]
Ishim, what have you done?
Oh. [ Sighs ]
What have you done?
I shared all of our secrets
with you,
taught you all of our ways
for your precious studies.
[ Sighs ]
I...
I loved you.
You didn't love me.
You were obsessed with me.
That isn't love.
[ Sighs ] I loved you.
You threw me away for him.
No. I never should've let you
into my life.
I needed Akobel
to protect me from you.
Well, that didn't work,
did it?
You killed him?
Obviously.
[ Voice breaks ] And now
you're gonna kill me?
No.
[ Inhales sharply ]
You broke my heart, Lily.
[ Sniffles ]
Now I'm gonna break yours.
?
[ Screaming ]
Mommy!
[ Screams ]
You are powerless
to do anything.
No.
You...are...powerless.
No. No! [ Crying ]
Stay away from my daughter!
[ May screams ]
No!
[ Sobbing ]
I had my daughter
long before I ever laid eyes
on an angel.
Wait, so...
My daughter was human.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Just... [ Clears throat ]
Um...
[ Lowered voice ]
Are you buying any of this?
[ Whispers ] Yeah, kinda.
All right, well,
we gotta make sure, you know.
I mean, Ishim's a tool, but --
You know what?
I'm gonna call Cass.
[ Cellphone beeps,
line rings ]
[ Ring ]
[ Whispers ] Come on, come on, come on.
Yeah, he's not answering.
[ Disconnects call ]
Okay.
Just go. I'll stay here.
What?
And leave you here with her?
You kidding me? She --
She is no threat whatsoever
to humans.
And she can hear you.
[ Exhales ]
Okay.
?
[ Inhales deeply ] Mm.
I haven't felt this good
in a millennia. Mm!
Oh, goody.
Ah, quit your whinin'.
You'll regain your strength
soon enough.
[ Sighs ] Where's my phone?
You'll have to keep better track
of your things, Castiel.
[ Exhales slowly ]
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
I-I get wanting revenge.
I-I really do.
But...why wait so long?
I had no choice.
Before the angels fell,
before they lost their wings,
there would've been no way
to hunt them down.
But now...
Patience is a talent.
You'd be amazed
what a person can do
with a little bit of purpose
and an abundance of time.
Hmm.
Ishim said you made
some kind of pact,
um...
that you're using
dark magic.
Did he?
I've studied angels
all my...
very long life.
I use their magic to fight,
to hear them,
to stay alive.
Enochian magic.
That's...possible?
It is if you're willing
to pay the price of admission.
Every time I use
one of their spells,
a piece of my soul burns away.
And once it's gone...
You won't feel anything
anymore.
You won't, uh, care about
anything anymore.
You won't be human anymore.
I used to dream about
my daughter every night.
Do you know what
I dream about now?
Nothing.
You don't trust me.
I understand.
But when your brother
confronts Ishim,
the angel will kill him.
Ishim's a big man in heaven.
He's got too much to lose
if the truth comes out.
And when your brother's dead,
you won't stand
in my way anymore.
You'll help me.
And for that, I can wait.
?
Cass?
[ Groans ]
Hey. You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
And Ishim
is fully recovered.
Yeah. Okay.
Uh, maybe wish you hadn't
had done that just yet.
Wait, why?
This Lily chick?
Says that her daughter
was human.
I think Ishim...
I think he's playing you.
You're back.
So what's new?
?
Is it...
is it true, Ishim?
Is what true?
Lily Sunder's daughter,
was she human?
Who told you that?
She did.
Said you were pretty obsessed.
Well, she's a liar.
Why would she lie?
She's human.
It's kinda what they do.
Well, if she's a liar,
she's pretty good at it.
You, on the other hand,
kind of suck.
Who are you gonna believe?
Your brother,
or some filthy ape
who's always talking down
to you, always mocking you.
You know, Cass and I might not
agree all the time,
but at least he knows
who his real friends are.
Why do his words bother you
so much, Ishim?
Who is he to question
my choices?
Who is he to question yours?
Well, it seems that some
of my choices
may need to be questioned.
Now tell me. The girl --
was she human?
Oh, you're not gonna like
the answer.
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunts, groans ]
I used to envy you, Castiel.
You believe that?
[ Grunts, growls ]
You survived Hell.
[ Blade clatters ]
You were chosen by God.
But now look at you.
You're just sad
and pathetically weak.
?
So now... [ Panting ]
I'm gonna help you. [ Sniffs ]
I'm gonna cure you
of your human weakness
same way I cured my own --
by cutting it out.
[ Panting ]
Don't move.
Do it.
You blast me away,
you'll blast away every angel
in the room.
I'll survive.
Castiel, on the other hand,
he's hurt.
He might live
or he might just end up
a bloody smear on the wall.
Roll the dice.
?
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
Ishim! No.
Hello, my love.
Hey. Hey.
I thought you were supposed
to keep her out of this.
Yeah, I changed my mind.
[ Groans ]
Good call.
[ Grunting ]
All right, Plan B. Come on.
Aah! [ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Panting ] It's over.
No.
I will never
be powerless again.
?
You can't hold me here
forever.
[ Exhales ]
?
Aah!
[ Groans ]
[ Roars ]
[ Thud ]
[ Exhales ]
You held him
for long enough.
?
Sam: All right, so, uh...
[ Sniffs ]
What now?
Dean: He's dead.
Are you done?
?
Revenge is all I've had
for over a hundred years.
It's what I am.
Wrong answer. You're done.
Dean. [ Sighs ]
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
And...while it's true
that I didn't know
we were killing an innocent,
ignorance is no excuse.
I truly can't imagine
the depths of your loss.
This was your child.
I can't imagine the pain.
So if you leave here
and you find that
you can't forgive me...
I'll be waiting.
Thank you.
?
[ Owl hooting ]
You earned it.
Well, this will do very little
for me,
but I-I appreciate the gesture.
What Ishim said...
You're not weak, Cass.
You know that, right?
I mean, obviously,
you've changed,
but it's all been
for the better, man.
And you have been with us
every step
of this long,
crazy thrill ride.
And no matter how crazy it got,
you never backed down.
And that takes real strength.
Thank you.
Cass, I don't like how the whole
Billie thing went down. Okay?
I know you think you were
doing the right thing.
And I'm not mad. I'm worried.
Because things like
“cosmic consequences”
have a habit
of biting us in the ass.
I know they do.
But I don't regret what I did,
even if it costs me my life.
Don't say that, man.
So what are you gonna do
if you find Kelly
and, uh, Lucifer Junior?
It is a Nephilim, right?
Oh, no. It's more than that.
An ordinary Nephilim is one of
the most dangerous beings
in all of creation.
But one that's fathered by
an archangel, the Devil himself?
I...I can't imagine the power.
But, Cass, at the end of
the day, it's a mom and her kid.
I mean, do you -- do you think
you'll be able to...
There was a time
when I wouldn't have hesitated.
But now, I don't know.
What are we gonna do?
Let's drink,
and hope we can find
a better way.
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man