- Hello, brother.
- Kelvin.
- Oh, you remember?
- What are you doing here?
Same reason as you.
So what do you say
we help each other out?
You help us track down
Kelly Kline,
and you'll be welcomed back
into the fold.
And you have the power
to do that?
Oh, no. I can't.
I'm just the messenger.
But Joshua can.
All we ask
is that you hear us.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Come on, Cass.
I've called you three times now.
[ Grunts ]
And you said
you were a demon.
I'm a demon. You're Rosemary,
complete with baby.
Kelly, the angels?
The Winchesters?
The good guys?
They want you dead.
But I can protect you.
I can protect your son.
Cass, it's me.
I've been trying to get ahold
of you for days.
[ Gasps ]
Stay cool. Walk with me.
We wanna help.
You call this helping?
She's here.
[ Wind gusting ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gunshots ]
You hear anything from Cass yet?
No. Still MIA.
You think he's all right?
I don't know.
Apparently, Mick let
Sam and Dean get their hands
on the bloody Colt.
[ Cocks gun ]
Welcome back, sweetheart.
Hey.
Vitamin time.
Don't.
[ Muffled voice ] No.
[ Whimpering ]
[ Singsongy ]
Be a good girl.
[ Muffled shouting, grunting ]
[ Chain rattling ]
There.
[ Scoffs ] Really, Kel?
[ Swallows, coughs ]
Not taking your pills,
picking at your food...
refusing to bathe?
[ Coughs ]
[ Sighs heavily ]
Stop disrespecting [ Breathing heavily ]
the God inside of you.
[ Whispers ]
He's gonna kill me.
Yeah.
And he's not gonna
stop there.
Every sad, weak human,
every tight-ass angel,
every sniveling demon...
they'll all be consumed.
So go ahead.
Play your games.
But whether you're healthy
or sick, filthy or clean,
He will be born.
[ Sighs ]
Good times.
But until then...
[ Unlocks cuff ]
Do us both a favor?
Take a bath.
[ Ascending footsteps ]
[ Sniffling ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Chains rattle, door closes ]
[ Groans ]
[ Sniffles, sighs ]
Oh.
?
Kelly: I love you.
[ Water running ]
But we won't ever be together.
There is no happy ending
for either of us.
And if what she said is true...
if this is
what you really are...
[ Voice breaking ]
what you'll do to the world,
all that pain,
all that death,
I can't let that happen.
?
[ Crying ] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[ Slices ]
[ Grunts, gasps ]
Oh.
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Shard clatters ]
?
? Supernatural 12x19 ?
The Future
Original Air Date on April 27, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
?
Whoa.
What's up, Beautiful Mind?
Guess I just figured
we can't exactly track Dagon,
so I've been reading up
on nephilim,
trying to figure out how much
time we have before --
'Lil Lucifer pops?
Yeah.
Okay, so we know
Kelly got pregnant
sometime in early December.
According to the lore,
nephilim don't need 9 months
to get to full term,
so I think she will
be giving birth
around May 18th.
Which means...
We have less than a month
to find her.
Yeah, and exactly no idea
where to start.
Okay, but even if we do
find her, what then?
I don't know.
I mean, I-I...
[ Door opens ]
Cass.
Hello.
Hey.
You're all right. Um...
Where have you been?
Let me rephrase that for Sam.
Where the hell have you been?
And why have you ignored
our phone calls?
Where I was, the --
the reception
was, uh...poor.
No bars?
No bars. That's his excuse.
Wow.
I was in Heaven.
I was working with the angels.
When I saw Dagon had
captured Kelly,
I-I thought they could help.
And?
Nothing.
Well, at least you're back.
We're glad you're back.
Really?
No, I'm sorry.
Okay, 'cause while you were
striking out in Heaven,
we had a shot at Dagon,
and we lost.
I know.
I...received your messages.
Oh, you did -- you did
receive the messages?
Okay, that's good.
Dean.
So not only
were you ditching us,
but you were also ignoring us?
That's great.
'Cause we really could've
used the backup.
But, uh, you were too busy
with, um...
[ Clicks tongue ]
What was it?
Nothing?
Dean, I --
What the hell is wrong
with you, man?
You know, whatever. That's...
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah. Welcome back.
Dean, y--
?
[ Knock on door ]
[ Door opens ]
Sorry, Dean.
Um...
I just wanted to return this.
It's a gift.
You keep those.
Oh.
Cass, you can't...
With everything
that's going on,
you can't just go dark
like that.
We didn't know
what happened to you.
We were worried.
That's not okay.
Well, I didn't mean to add
to your distress.
I...
Dean, I just keep failing.
Again and again.
When you were taken,
I searched for months
and I couldn't find you.
And then Kelly escaped on my
watch, and I couldn't find her.
And I just wanted...
I needed to come back here
with a win for you.
For myself.
You think you're the only one
rolling snake eyes here?
Me and Sam, we had her.
We had Kelly
and we lost her.
And if you find her again?
Sam's working on it.
Of course, he's hell-bent
on finding something
that doesn't mean killing her
or her kid.
Right. And if he doesn't
find something?
If you run out of time,
could either of you
kill an innocent?
We will find a better way.
You mean, we?
Yes, dumbass. We.
You, me, and Sam,
we're just better together.
So now that you're back,
let's go, Team Free Will.
Let's get it done.
I'd like that.
Great.
And I'd like a beer.
[ Door opens ]
?
What did you do?
He wouldn't let me die.
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Sighs ] Hey, come on, man.
Get some sleep, all right?
You're not gonna find
Dagon tonight.
Dean, what if we've been
going about this whole thing
the wrong way, you know?
I-I mean, we -- we can't
track Dagon, right?
We know that. We've tried.
But -- but what if we can
track the nephilim?
[ Clears throat ]
How?
Well...
Okay, the baby's half-angel,
right?
So remember Gadreel?
The psycho angel who took
your body for a test drive?
Yeah, what about him?
All right, well...
there was this, uh,
there was this spell --
Cass and I were working on it --
to -- to find him.
Yeah, but it didn't work.
Yeah.
You needed Gadreel's grace,
and he couldn't yank enough
out of you.
[ Chuckles ] Of course.
Of course what?
Of course I am an idiot.
Well, there's no argument there.
No, stop. Dean...
The grace extraction.
The tracking spell was
a bust, right?
But -- but the extraction ritual
worked.
So?
So what if Cass used it
on Kelly's kid?
I mean, a-a nephilim's just
a human soul
with angelic grace, right?
So you remove the grace --
Kid's just a kid.
That way, Kelly wouldn't
have to die,
and -- and neither would
her baby.
Hot damn.
I mean, we still obviously
have to find Kelly in the first place.
I mean,
it's just a theory, but --
No, no, no. No, no.
That's...
This is it.
This is it, Sam.
[ Chuckles ]
I'll get Cass.
[ Knock on door ]
Cass?
Yo, Cass?
[ Switch clicks, door thuds ]
?
You really thought
that was gonna work?
You get the chance to be
Mary of Nazareth, Part 2,
Evil Jesus Edition.
He's not.
Excuse me?
He's not. My baby's not evil.
He saved me.
That's what
you think happened?
[ Laughs ]
Uh, he saved himself.
He doesn't care about you.
Nothing's changed.
He's born, you die.
But don't worry.
I'll be there,
right by his side,
to nurture him, love him,
to help him to...
kill everything.
You know,
like a mother should.
?
[ Sighs ]
Hello, brother. Is it done?
Yes.
Bullets?
There were only two
in the chamber,
and I couldn't exactly
ask for more.
It's enough.
One for Dagon...
Yeah.
One for Kelly.
They're close.
The celestial pulse we felt,
Joshua tracked it
to a house nearby.
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Ring ]
[ Touchscreen clicks ]
You're doing the right thing,
you know.
Committing to Joshua's plan,
putting angelkind
above the Winchesters.
I mean, your reputation
in Heaven is --
This has nothing to do
with my reputation.
I am doing this
for the Winchesters.
I-I stole the Colt
to keep them out
of this mission
and to keep them safe
from Dagon,
and I...
I will kill this girl
so that Sam and Dean
don't have to.
Hozai.
Castiel.
Dagon, the girl,
they're in the house.
Showtime.
?
Man: And now we've got
5 seconds to see more
of the Super Catch Phrase
and win the bank.
Here we go.
?
[ Bell dings ] Cindy, for $350,
tell us what it is.
Cindy: Pumping iron?
Not right.
[ Audience groans ]
[ Laughs ]
Chip and Cindy --
Got a lot of people in the audience
who think they know,
but we have
a Toss Up Catch Phrase for you.
?
[ Bell dings ] Now your opponent knows,
but she can't guess.
Only you are entitled.
There's $400 in the bank.
Chip, what is it?
Chip: The Iron Curtain!
No!
[ Laughs ]
Yes!
[ Laughs ] Whoo!
[ Cheers and applause ]
I got so excited there myself...
[ Cocks gun ]
that I went to
the opposite thing.
Well, whatcha know?
[ Gunshot ]
?
[ Grunts ]
[ Blade clatters ]
[ Cocks gun ]
Hey, find the girl.
Ah!
[ Groans ]
Aah!
[ Loud clattering,
punches landing ]
[ Cocks gun ]
Castiel?
?
[ Chains rattle ]
[ Sighs deeply ]
Castiel: This is my voicemail.
Make your voice...a mail.
[ Beep ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Let me guess -- no answer.
I mean, how did Cass even get
the Colt out of the safe
in the first place?
Dean, you -- you put the Colt
back in the safe, right?
Dean?
It was under my pillow.
It...
I like to keep it close.
[ Sighs ]
He came into my room
and he played me.
Yeah, he played us both.
Well, I say we find him
and we kick his feathered ass.
Dean, Cass wouldn't have
taken the Colt
if he wasn't going up against
something big.
Okay, I say we find him,
figure out what's going on,
and then we kick
his feathered ass.
[ Faint beeping ]
Guess you finally caught me.
Back there in the basement...
you came to kill me.
[ Faint beeping ]
[ Voice breaks ]
But you didn't.
Thank you.
Please don't thank me.
[ Faint beeping ]
I had a mission
and I failed.
And now?
Now, I don't know.
I'm just trying to put as much
distance between you and Dagon
as I can.
Everything's fine.
Just put the container down
for a nap.
Did you?
Dagon...
[ Singsongy ]
I know you're lying to me.
What happened?
My Lord, I...
Tell me.
[ Whoosh ]
[ Groans ]
Look, I...
[ Sighs ]
The angels, they found us.
One of them took her.
Which one?
[ Sighs heavily ]
Castiel.
[ Laughing ]
Okay, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
So you let
the Winchesters' purse dog
take my son?
[ Screams ]
[ Exhaling sharply ]
I didn't...Mm.
I will find them.
Yes, you will, or that
little fantasy of yours,
ruling Heaven and Earth,
you, me,
baby makes three...
It's not a fantasy.
That was your promise to me.
Here's another promise
for you --
find my boy,
or the torments
I will visit upon you
will be infinite.
Promise.
You make this right, Dagon.
Make it right.
I will.
?
What's going on?
I was communicating
with Joshua.
He's an angel. I, um...
I was getting my orders.
I couldn't kill you
back there.
But now,
I will take you to Heaven.
Your life will end,
and your baby's, too.
It'll be swift and painless.
No.
[ Sighs ]
No, you don't know...
What if it doesn't work?
No human form can step through
that gate and survive.
Your souls will ascend
to Heaven,
and every cell of your beings
will return to the universe.
I am sorry, Kelly.
The son of Lucifer...
this is a human/archangel
hybrid.
That power...
it's beyond comprehension.
Your child could bring
the universe to its knees.
Or lift it to its feet.
This baby,
nothing is born evil.
I can't take that chance.
None of us can.
[ Engine stalling ]
Aah! Aah!
[ High-pitched ringing ]
I don't know.
Right.
Suicide mission,
no contingencies,
blah, blah, blah.
I believe you.
You don't know
where Castiel is.
But he's an angel,
you're an angel.
Got a feeling,
ya dig deep enough,
you can make
an excellent guess.
Why would I tell you?
You're just Lucifer's desperate,
clingy side piece.
[ Laughs ]
'Cause being
Lucifer's side piece
has its perks.
[ Groaning, gasping ]
Now think.
Where's he going?
WWCD.
What would Castiel do?
You need to keep
out of sight
until I can get us
back on the road.
[ Sighs ]
I'm thirsty. I just want...
Just...sit.
[ Faucet turns on, off ]
Something happened to me,
Castiel.
I lost hope. I tried to...
I killed myself.
I slit my wrists.
I died.
And then...
[ Sighs ]
He saved me.
He brought me back to life.
Well, that was the pulse.
We felt that in Heaven.
His power...
his soul surged through me,
and it was good.
Pure. I feel...
I know he is good.
Kelly...
what your child did, that's
a testament to his power,
but it's not proof
of some goodness.
He needs you alive.
Maybe.
Or maybe it was a miracle.
Maybe...maybe everything that
I've been through,
everything that I still
have to go through,
is happening for a reason.
Maybe it's part
of some plan.
No, it isn't.
I used to believe
in a plan.
I used to believe that I had
some mission.
But I have been through
enough now to know
that everyone
is just winging it.
Some of us quite badly.
Lucifer...
he's just breaking toys.
He's sowing destruction
and chaos,
and there is no grand purpose
at work.
And there's no special role
for you.
When Lucifer took over
Rooney's body...
I'm sorry.
You were just there.
[ Sighs deeply ]
I know my baby can be good
for this world.
Kelly, if he's born...
that is not something
you can survive.
So even if you are right,
and even if the worst
isn't inevitable,
then who will care for him
when you're gone?
[ Sighs ]
Who?
Who is strong enough
to protect him
and to keep him from
evil influences
and to keep him
on the righteous path?
?
[ Grunts ]
What?
He just -- he just kicked.
Do you want to...
Oh. No.
It's not a big deal,
Castiel.
He does it, like,
20 times a day.
?
You stay away from her.
[ Gasps ]
Kelly?
[ Knock on door ]
Yeah, that's mine.
What the hell are you
thinking, huh?
- Dean?
- What?!
Dean!
?
Kelly?
- Hey.
How did you find us?
Well, while you were
scamming me for the Colt,
Sam put a tracking app
on your phone.
Cass, when you came back, you
didn't even look us in the eye.
You wanna explain
what's going on here?
Yeah. I found Dagon.
And?
Did you kill her?
No.
But...
She's difficult to kill, okay?
Yeah.
You think?
All right, so what are you
doing here, then?
I... [ Sighs ]
My truck broke down.
Then...
Then why didn't you call us?
Cass, we could've helped you.
I know. I wanted to keep you
out of this.
I-I was trying
to keep you safe.
You're not our babysitter, Cass,
okay? That is not your job.
And when in our whole lives
have we ever been safe?
This is my responsibility
because it is my plan.
Your plan?
He's taking me to Heaven.
You...
You're taking her
to the sandbox?
Yes. I'm ending this,
once and for all.
Kelly and her baby
have to die.
No, they don't.
Listen, we found another way.
And you would know that
if you would answer your phone.
Wait, what are you
talking about?
What you did with me, with --
with Gadreel, remember?
The -- the grace extraction.
We take the grace from
the baby, from the nephilim,
and then the baby
just becomes --
Human.
Wait a minute. That extraction,
it nearly killed you.
Yeah, but it didn't.
Because we didn't finish it.
We don't even know if
this would work.
There are kinks, yes,
but it's a plan.
And it beats the hell
out of certain death.
Am I right?
No.
Hey, Kelly. Kelly. Hey, wait,
wait. Wait a second, look.
We -- we can't imagine what
you've been through, okay?
But we promised we'd find
another way, and we did.
We found a better way.
This can work.
I'm going with Castiel.
No, Kelly, if you go with Cass,
you die. Your baby dies.
I go with you, you take away the thing
that makes him special.
How does that matter
if you're both dead?
That's the only thing
that matters.
Okay, this girl has lost her mind.
Hey, Dean.
Meanwhile, can we take this
conversation elsewhere, guys?
We're kind of sitting ducks
out here.
Sam's right. Dagon is after Kelly.
Your truck is broke down.
Why don't we get in the Impala,
we'll head back to the bunker,
and we'll talk?
We'll figure it out. Right.
Okay, we'll talk.
Great.
It's like herding cats.
Yeah.
Okay, so what?
We -- we go back to the bunker
and we just try to convince them
to stay there forever?
Dean. Locked.
[ Door creaks ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Keys thud ]
It's not supposed to happen
this way.
[ Sighs ]
[ Sam speaking indistinctly ]
Kelly.
[ Engine starts ]
What are you doing?
[ Tires peal ]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Whoa!
[ Tires squeal ]
[ Thunderclap ] Turn around.
Where are you going?
To Heaven.
The...sandbox,
if you tell me how to get there.
Kelly, I can make you
stop this car.
Why haven't you?
Okay,
why are you doing this?
Because he chose you, Castiel.
When you put your hand
on my stomach, I heard him.
He spoke to me.
He told me that even if
it seems scary,
if I just went to the gate,
if I just followed your plan,
that you would make sure
he was born.
Sam and Dean, they want to
take away his powers
because they're scared.
[ Sighs ] But I'm not.
Kelly, you --
You asked me
who would protect him,
guide him when I'm gone.
I know now.
It's you.
Me? That's...
I...
I am not someone
that you should put
your faith in, Kelly.
I couldn't kill Dagon
back there.
I lost two of my men.
I betrayed my friends,
my family.
Before all this happened,
I was
a cut-rate political flack
in an embarrassingly
unprofessional relationship
with my boss.
I don't know why it's me.
And I don't know why
it's you.
But I know that we are destined
for something here.
Something great.
Well, I wish I had
your faith.
You will.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
Sam: How did this happen?
[ Scoffs ] What?
The lying? The Heaven plan?
Or the fact that I'm working on
this stupid truck?
No, I mean,
what's wrong with Cass?
Well, he hasn't exactly had
a banner year.
I mean, think about it.
Between Lucifer...
[ Blows air ]
killing Billie, Ramiel,
everything's been
blowing up in his face.
And he's so desperate
for a win right now,
he can't even see straight.
Go ahead and give it a try.
[ Engine starts, squeals ]
?
This is it?
This is it.
Kelly, are you sure?
As long as you're here,
I know it's gonna be okay.
[ Sniffles ]
[ High-pitched ringing ]
Castiel.
Kelly.
It's good to see you.
Hello, Joshua.
I know you must be scared.
But don't be.
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
Ugh.
Hey, girl.
Wow! You two got so close!
If I hadn't made it here at
the last possible second, uh...
J.K.
Flipped your pal Kelvin
ages ago,
then smoked him.
I've been here for hours.
You stay away from her.
What, no Colt?
Wait.
You don't even have it
anymore?
Hilarious.
[ Grunting ]
Look at him,
your angelic defender.
You really thought
he was gonna save you?
This sad, fluttering,
aimless little moth?
[ Grunts ]
[ Whispers ] No.
[ Choking ]
[ Continues choking ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Hammer clicks ]
[ Groans ]
[ Clips click ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Cocks gun ]
[ Bone snaps ]
[ Grunts ]
Yeah.
Time to take this
off the board. [ Grunts ]
[ Sizzling ]
No!
[ Barrel thuds ]
Okay. Who wants ice cream?
?
[ Scoffs ] Kid, come on.
It's just getting sad.
[ Labored breathing ]
Run.
Aw! Adorbs!
[ Whoosh ]
[ Crackling ]
-Cass!
-No!
How...
Call it a miracle.
[ Sizzles ]
[ Groans ]
[ Screaming ]
?
Cass?
What was that?
It was, um...
It was me.
But it was also...
You're hurt.
[ High-pitched ringing ]
Thank you for coming
to fight for us.
Are you okay?
I am.
I've been so lost.
I'm not lost anymore.
And I know now that
this child must be born
with all of his power.
You can't actually mean that.
Yes. I do. I have faith.
?
We have to go.
Hey, Cass, wait a second.
Wait, hold on. Just...
You have to just trust me.
No, no, no, wait. Okay,
whatever that thing did to you,
we're not just gonna let you
walk away.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
Yes, it is.
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Thud ]
Don't. [ Inhales sharply ]
I'm sorry.
?
[ Exhales sharply ]
What did he tell you?
He didn't tell me.
He showed me.
The future.
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man