Did you know people tell
stories about us?
Yeah. Apparently,
we're a little bit legendary.
? Carry on, my wayward son ?
? There'll be peace when
you are done ?
Pew.
? Lay your weary head to rest ?
? Don't you cry no more ?
?
- Let's begin.
- Mom?
I have
sort of been working
with the British Men of Letters.
I know how much
you hate them.
No, we hate them.
Us. Together.
Lucifer is back.
? Once I rose above
the noise and confusion ?
? Just to get a glimpse beyond
this illusion ?
Crowley's dead,
and the Devil
is out looking for his son.
A nephilim is come into being.
I can feel it. I'm its mother.
? Though my eyes could see ?
My baby's not evil.
? Though my mind could think ?
He showed me the future.
How?
I have faith...
Don't.
...in this child.
? I can hear them say ?
? Carry on, my wayward son ?
She will shoot you.
? There'll be peace when
you are done ?
? Lay your weary head to rest ?
Mary.
? Don't you cry no more ?
?
God, please.
I need help.
I'm trying to help you, ma'am.
Are you, Sven?
Because if you ask me if I have
the quarter-inch Allen wrench
one -- one more time,
I am going to come down there
and burn your giant
Viking junkyard of a store
to the ground!
Do you understand?!
Are you sure it wasn't
in the box?
God!
Kelly.
I told you
I'd put this together.
I'm very good
at following instructions.
And you need to rest.
No, I don't.
Kelly --
No, Cass, I don't.
I can't.
I don't know how long until...
I don't know how long
I have left.
And I...I'm never gonna be able
to teach him how to ride a bike
or watch him get married
or even
look him in the eyes.
But I can
build him a stupid Swedish crib!
I can do that.
Kelly, I know
how hard this is.
That's a lie.
I have no idea how hard
this is for you.
But I promise you...
I will do everything.
I will give my life
for your son.
And I will raise him.
And I will make him
someone you will be proud of.
I know.
Okay, let me just
get this straight.
So...
we beat the Brits,
we kicked their psycho,
tea-swilling asses,
and instead of popping champagne
and headin' to Vegas,
we get Lucifer.
And you're sure it's him?
Yeah.
That's his old vessel, too.
How is that possible?
Crowley, I guess.
And now he's dead.
Well, that's what Hess said.
But Crowley's
a freakin' cockroach.
I'll believe he's gone
when I see the body and burn it.
This is gonna hurt.
?
We don't need Crowley.
We need Rowena.
I mean, she's the one who can
slam Lucifer back into the Cage.
Great. So where is she?
Oh, hey, Sammy.
? Supernatural 12x23 ?
All Along the Watchtower
Original Air Date on May 18, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
What?
Oh, if you're
looking for Rowena,
she is presently indisposed.
Which is a delicate way
of saying,
I stomped on her face
till the white meat showed,
and then set her on fire,
just in case.
Ah. Gingers.
It was messy and...
screamy,
but it had to be done, Sam.
I'm about to be a dad.
Can't raise the little nipper
from a jail cell now, can I?
Speaking of...
you know where
your little pal Castiel is?
Go to hell.
Ooh! Good one. Witty.
I'll use that in the future.
All right, well,
I'd love to chat with ya,
but, uh,
why waste my time, right?
It's not like you matter.
I don't need to put on
the old Sam suit anymore, do I?
You know, if you think we're
just gonna let you walk --
Oh, hey, Dean!
Y--
I know you fellas are gonna try,
you know, whatever.
Whatever you're gonna try.
But you can't kill me.
You've never been able
to kill me.
And with, uh, witch bitch gone,
you can't put me
back in the Cage,
so like I said...
you don't matter.
Okay?
Buh-bye. Buh-bye.
Bye, dear.
I'm just saying,
the checkout guy looked at us
like we were super weird.
Ah, you'll get used to it.
Okay, but...Cass, I mean,
you went a little overboard.
I disagree.
I have read 74 books
on child rearing,
and there is one thing that
they all agree on --
everybody poops.
Well, you're not wrong.
I'm fine. I'm...
I'm fine.
You know, Lucifer's right.
We can't kill him and we can't
slam his ass back in the Cage.
Yeah. Okay. So maybe
we play for time.
Find Cass and Kelly,
keep 'em moving.
If Lucifer can't find them,
he can't hurt them.
You think Castiel is
gonna go along with that?
You think we'll give him
a choice?
?
And the baby?
Hopefully, we can still
siphon off its grace.
If not, uh...
we'll figure something else out.
Yeah, we better.
All right, then.
Kind of always wanted
to punch the Devil in the face.
So how do we find them?
All right, look, we know Kelly's
gonna have that kid soon.
Like, really soon.
And according to the lore,
whenever a nephilim is born,
there are signs.
Uh, storms,
outbreaks of disease,
uh, plague of locusts.
Things get Biblical.
Exactly. That much power
into the world,
whenever and wherever
it happens,
things get weird.
So we're looking
for something...weird.
?
Yeah. Story of our lives.
Where...
How...
You?
Hi, Jack. It's, uh...
I'm your mom.
I know you're gonna be okay.
You are gonna be...
amazing.
You have an angel
watching over you.
God, I love you, Jack.
I love you so much.
Sorry.
I love you.
?
Oh.
Hey, listen to this --
two-headed calf was born
in Lava Hot Springs, Idaho.
That's weird.
That is weird.
Yeah, but not our kind of weird.
Look, whatever this thing
is gonna be,
it -- it's gonna be big
and bad --
You rang?
Hello, boys.
Did you do it?
Did you let Lucifer out?!
I didn't “let” --
Don't!
Moose,
a little help here!
Dean, wait.
Seriously?
Look, just don't kill him.
He worked the Cage spell with
Rowena. Maybe he can help us.
And what if he can't?
Well, then we kill him.
Cage spell?
Thought you had mother for that.
Rowena's dead.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Lucifer.
Funny.
I always thought
I'd be the one to kill her.
Crowley...why did you do it?
Save Lucifer --
What did you want?
I wanted to win.
I perverted mother's spell,
put Lucifer in a vessel
of my own making
because I wanted to win.
You have any idea
how many people
have made a play for my throne
over the years?
Lucifer, Abaddon,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Too damn many.
I thought if I could put
the Devil on a leash...
my own personal nuke,
no one would ever dare
challenge me again.
Yeah.
That worked out great.
All ended with
me narrowly escaping death
by hiding in a rat.
Wait.
In an...actual rat?
Wasn't too bad, really.
Gave me time to think.
You know, I've been focused
for so long on keeping my job.
Never realized I hate it.
All those whining demons,
the endless moan
of damned souls,
the paperwork!
I mean, who wants that?
You.
Unh-unh. Once, maybe.
So why are you here?
Well, whenever there's
a world-ending crisis at hand,
I know where to place my bets.
It's on you,
you big, beautiful,
lumbering piles of flannel.
So if you'll forgive
my transgression,
I'll make it worth your while.
Which means?
After we put Lucifer
back in his cage --
together --
I'll seal the gates of Hell.
You'll never see
another demon again,
apart from, of course,
yours truly.
You would do that?
Why not?
They stab me in the back,
I'll happily stab them
in the front, the sides,
and right up their little
black-eyed asses.
So...
we have a deal?
?
Cass?
Castiel?
Kelly.
Where were you?
I, um...
uh, nowhere.
Um, is everything okay?
No.
The baby, it's...
I think it's time.
Oh, my God.
Look at me.
Oh, God.
- Everything's gonna be fine.
- Ooh.
This is what you do when
I'm not here?
Type?
Yep.
Wait a second. I got something.
Okay, two hours ago, there was
a massive power outage
in the Pacific Northwest.
Sounds like
the right kind of weird.
Oh, yeah. Wait.
They tracked the outage
to an address
in North Cove, Washington,
to a house
currently being rented
by one James Novak.
That's Cass. Let's roll.
It's about time.
Aah!
Think we're gonna trust you
out there after what you pulled?
Hmm?
No. You stay here,
you sit down, and you shut up.
?
You're all right.
The pressure waves are still
very far apart.
“Pressure waves”?
It's what they --
it's what they called
contractions in my doula class.
I-I took it online.
First-time mothers,
labor can be 12 to 18 hours,
sometimes longer.
It...
Although, given this is
the child of Lucifer
and a quasi-celestial being...
They didn't cover that
online?
They did not.
?
Cass?
Thank you.
For everything.
Of course.
?
Kelly.
Tell me again.
Tell me again what you saw.
Right, I saw -- I saw...
I saw the future.
?
I saw a world without pain
or hunger or want.
I saw the world
that this child...
that your child...
Mm.
...will create.
And it is a world
without fear
and without suffering
and without hate.
Mm.
I saw paradise.
?
Dean?
Cass,
is this place warded?
Yes, heavily.
Heavy enough to stop Lucifer?
Lucifer?
He could be right behind us.
I don't...
What are you doing here?
Saving your ass.
Look, you and Kelly just
taking off was a stupid move.
But there's no way we're letting
Lucifer get his hands on that kid.
It ain't happening.
Look, Sam's right, okay?
We'll work through our crap.
We always do.
But right now, we are here
to get you, get Kelly, and get gone.
She can't be moved.
She's having a --
I'll check on her.
How much time do we have?
We don't know.
Hey, if he shows,
can you flame on again?
Can you torch Lucifer
like you did Dagon?
I don't know. No, that
wasn't me. That was the child.
And in case you haven't noticed,
he's a little busy.
Son of a bitch.
Here, Dean.
Mm.
Let me.
Thanks.
All right, we should
double-check the warding.
Wait.
Right. So listen, if we, uh...
Cass? What is that?
It's a tear
in space and time.
Uh, and that means?
It's a doorway to another world.
Anoth-- What, like Narnia?
No. No, through there
it's Earth,
but...but different.
It's a --
it's an alternate reality.
So it's a Bizarro world?
Or -- or like the place we got
zapped to where we were, uh,
uh, actors on a TV show.
Oh, yeah.
The supernatural wasn't real.
Yeah.
And you were Polish.
R-right.
Wait, Cass,
how did this get here?
Well, the child being born,
his power,
it seems to be puncturing
the fabric of our universe.
Awesome.
Yeah.
And what exactly is on
the other side?
You don't wanna know.
Probably.
But we need to.
?
Whoa.
Cass, what is this?
As I said, it's -- it's Earth.
But this Earth is
locked in eternal war
between Heaven and Hell.
There are armies of angels
fighting hoards of demons,
and the few humans that remain
are caught in between.
How do you know that?
A friend told me.
Oh, good. Now you're makin'
friends? That's...
All right, on a scale
of 1 to 10, how bad is this?
I don't know.
I gotta say, a, uh,
hole in reality
to a bombed out
Apocalypse world?
I'm gonna go with 11.
Sounds right.
You don't have to worry.
The child, he opened this door.
He'll close it.
You sure about that?
I have faith.
Really?
In your unborn baby-God?
Yes.
Well, then, you're a dumbass.
?
Guys. Guys!
Hey! Hands in the air!
No. Don't.
Bobby?
?
Do I know you?
Bobby...
Sam. Dean. Cass.
Uh-huh.
You say that like
it's supposed to mean something
to me, but...naw.
Sam, this is Bobby,
but it's your B--
Bobby, it's us.
Sam and Dean Winchester.
The only Winchester
I ever heard of was John.
Yeah.
John Winchester, our father.
Doubt it. He's dead.
Been dead over 40 years now.
Only reason I know about him
is this Hunter I ran with,
Mary Campbell.
You get a few pints of shine
into her,
and she always told
the same story
about the man she loved --
John Winchester.
Azazel killed her
about 10 years ago.
Cass, what the hell is this?
This is a world
where you were never born.
It's a world you never saved.
Aah!
Okay.
I think they're less than
five minutes apart now.
It's almost time.
How you doin'?
I'm dying.
I know.
?
But that's okay.
'Cause wouldn't you die
for your sons?
Yeah.
When this...
whatever opened up,
all sorts'a alarms went off
back at my place.
I got here just in time
to see your boy get ambushed
by a tempter demon.
A what?
It's, um...
black eyes, pointed teeth,
horns.
Wait a second.
Demons have horns now?
Whole new world, Sam.
Usually I gun down flyboys
on sight.
But, uh, he looked...
different.
Wasn't wearing a necklace made
out of baby ears, for one thing.
We got to talking about
where I came from
and our two worlds.
From what he says,
pretty much peaches and cream
on your side.
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
It's better than this.
Well, I don't know.
Ain't so bad here,
if you like killing angels.
And you do?
It's my hobby
and my passion.
So...I figured,
it's only a matter of time
before the dicks upstairs
get wind'a this.
And when they show...
me and Rufus go to work.
He's loaded
with a hundred rounds,
cast from old angel blades.
Wait, angel-killing bullets?
Awesome.
Okay. Okay.
You're okay.
Are you all right?
No, Cass.
Pretty far from all right.
I mean, we've got Lucifer
on this side,
we've got Mad Max World
on that side.
I mean, yeah, we've been
down before, but this?
I-I mean, I don't even know
where to start.
Oh, come on!
Hello, boys. Again.
Wait a second,
how the hell did you --
I improvised.
Lucky I did.
Turns out I'm the answer
to all your problems.
?
May I speak with her?
Sure.
Mary.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Cass...
what's wrong?
?
You ready?
Nope.
When has that ever stopped us?
Yeah.
You know, Cass has faith in this kid.
Mm.
I hope he's right.
But me?
I have faith in us.
You, me, Mom, Cass.
And Crowley. Sometimes.
Mm.
This is gonna work.
It has to.
Don't worry.
It will be fine.
Remember -- paradise,.
Well...
this is a fun surprise.
?
I gotta hand it to you guys.
You never give up,
even when you should.
Even when it would be
so stupid not to.
Look, whatever you're
planning on doing,
Chuck...God will stop you,
just like he did last time.
You're right.
What should I do?
Oh, God!
Don't strike me dead!
Come on, Sam.
You sound like a virgin
in Jesus camp.
“We can't. God is watching.”
No. Chuck “walked.”
He's gone.
So you're just gonna
smash his toys?
Exactly.
'Cause every time I look at this
sad trash fire of a world,
you know what
I keep thinking?
I could do so much better.
So Apocalypse, take two.
That's your plan?
When in doubt,
go with the classics.
That's what I always say.
Well, boys,
enough with the foreplay.
Let's do this.
See you on
the other side, boys.
Aah!
Well, that worked.
Mature.
Real mature!
You guys?
I really want to enjoy this.
Really wanna savor
just ripping you apart,
gettin' all up in there,
and gettin' all gooey.
But, you know,
little slugger's almost here
and, uh...
Well, I'm on the clock.
?
Interesting.
Mm.
Nice.
You wanted the Apocalypse?
You got it.
Sammy.
Hey.
Where's your big bro?
Right here.
Ooh. Sweet toy.
Yeah, I got it off an old --
new pal of mine.
See, we have this bet,
see if it works against
an archangel.
So...
say hello
to my little friend.
Took you long enough.
Not now, Crowley. Come on.
Yeah, baby!
Come on!
Uhh!
?
We do this ritual,
we seal that rift,
and we lock the Devil
in this godforsaken place.
That's the plan, remember?
Two birds, one spell.
Right, right. Just hurry.
You lose.
Uh, Dead Sea brine,
uh, mercury,
lambs blood, holy oil.
Here we go.
That's the last of it.
That's everything.
No, it's not.
What?
If we wanna seal that rip,
we need one more
minor ingredient.
-What?
- A life.
Ah, I could do this all day.
You make such funny noises.
Surprise.
Crowley!
You sneaky little...
So I guess I get to kill you
twice, huh, Crowley?
I doubt it.
Oh, no, no.
You had your chance.
You could've put me
back in the Cage, but...
you had to make it personal,
didn't you?
You're right.
It is personal.
You humiliated me.
I...
I hate you. Deeply.
Truly.
I'm gonna enjoy wiping
that smug, self-satisfied look
off your face.
Personally.
You mean...this one?
Come on, Crowley.
You know whatever you try,
you're gonna lose.
You're right.
Bye, boys.
Cass?
No, come on. Come on!
Cass!
Cass! Cass!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
We gotta go! We gotta go!
I love you.
?
Cass.
No!
That was fun.
Seriously, guys,
points for trying.
Super impressed, but, uh...
playtime's over.
?
Get away from them.
Mary, right?
Yeah, I've heard about you.
You, uh, are certainly
living up to the hype.
Look, seriously, I just wanted
to say thank you for everything.
I owe ya, kid.
Mom, Mom, Mom.
I love you.
?
Cute.
Is that all you got, mama?
Mom!
Aah!
- Mom, Mom! No!
- No! No!
No, no! No!
No!
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man