They're dead.
[ Growls ]
They're all dead.
Mary: I'm not trying
to recruit you,
but you need to know,
things are changing.
You're just in time
for the briefing.
I mean, that is
if you wanna hear
how we're gonna exterminate
every last vampire in America.
You're always playing
the middle.
For once, why don't you pick
a side?
[ Snarling ]
The hellhounds.
See, when you sell your soul
to a demon,
they're the one that
come and rip it out of you.
Crowley: Stay!
You can control them?!
Getting you here...
[ Groans ]
...I managed to pervert
that spell
so your essence
wasn't sent back to the Cage.
How do you think
this is going to end?
You're not even gonna see it
comin' when you get taken down.
By you?
And my flesh and blood.
You remember Kelly Kline?
Castiel: This is not a baby.
This is the spawn of Lucifer.
Kelly, the angels? They want
you dead. But I can protect you.
I don't even know your name.
Dagon.
Sam: The Alpha Vampire is dead.
You're changing the world,
and I wanna be a part of it.
I'm in.
Mick: And your brother?
Give me some time.
[ Scoffs ]
Man: Oh, my God.
Babe, we're gonna need
more wood.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay, but first,
check out this video.
This bear goes crazy
on these guys, and he j--
Um, no. That's not why
we come out here.
We come out here
to commune with nature,
not watch people get eaten
by it.
Okay, first of all...
[ Sighs ]
...he -- he doesn't eat them.
He chases them up a tree,
and they cry.
[ Man sobbing ]
A lot.
What do they want?!
[ Laughing ]
It's hilarious.
Oh, my God. Please --
And second of all,
“commune with nature”?
I thought you brought me
out here
to get naked
and do weird stuff.
Yeah, it's not gonna get
that weird.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs contentedly ]
?
I'll miss this.
I'll miss you.
And I get it.
I mean, Washington has
the best veterinary program
in the country.
You got in.
I mean, you have to go.
But people make
this long distance thing
work all the time, right?
Right. Sure.
I'm gonna get more firewood.
Okay.
?
Will you marry me?
Just man up. She'll say yes.
[ Sighs ]
[ Branch snaps ]
?
[ Growling ]
[ Growling continues ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Snarls, barks ]
Aah!
Gwen! Run!
Marcus?
[ Barks ]
Aah! [ Grunts ]
[ Screaming ]
Oh, my God!
[ Gasps ]
Aah!
[ Barks ]
[ Growling ]
[ Heavy steps ]
[ Barking ]
[ Screams ]
[ Slices ]
[ Yelps ]
[ Panting ]
[ Whimpering ]
? Supernatural 12x15 ?
Somewhere Between Heaven and Hell
Original Air Date on March 9, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ Groans ] Hoo-hoo!
Back to back to back.
That was one for the books.
Yeah.
Man!
Dad loved this thing.
[ Bat thuds ]
Dude, on the -- on the --
[ Sighs heavily ]
No, don't, don't, don't, don't!
Don't s--
What?
Dean, you're covered in ghoul,
man, and -- and -- and wraith.
You...
you have a piece of siren
in your hair.
Ugh.
[ Squish ]
[ Laughs ]
Gross.
Yeah.
Dude, why don't you
take a shower
and change your clothes?
You've been wearing the same
pair of boxers for four days.
Okay, one,
weird that you know
how much underwear I packed.
That's what's weird about this?
And B, it's two and two.
Doesn't count if you flip 'em
inside out. [ Clicks tongue ]
[ Cellphone alert chimes ]
[ Groans ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Got another case.
Really? Already?
How'd you do that?
Same as the others.
I-I made a computer algorithm
that scrapes data
from police scanners,
emergency calls,
uh, local news sites,
and then it puts everything
through a h--
The computer told me.
[ Clears throat ]
Computers. [ Chuckles ]
Monsters, porn.
Is there anything they can't do?
All right.
[ Hits tabletop ]
Well, let's get to it, then.
Yeah, that's fine.
And, dude, um...
after you get cleaned up.
I got baby wipes in the car.
Dude. Dean, I'm serious, man.
You smell like roadkill.
That's 'cause I do
all the heavy lifting.
You --
All right. [ Sighs ]
I'm using that fancy shampoo
you keep hidden from me.
[ Sighs ]
?
[ Police radio chatter ]
Oh, really?
Oh, that's great, Mom. Oh.
- No, we're -- we're fine. We, uh...
- It sounds like somethin'.
Yeah. Love you, too.
All right, Cass. Let us know.
All right, bye.
You first.
Mom just finished working
a haunting in Akron.
The Brits?
Yeah.
Great. Who you gonna call?
Douchebusters.
What about you?
[ Sighs ] That was Cass.
He's in Coeur d'Alene, Idaho.
Someone's killing angels. Again.
[ Radio chatter continues ]
[ Lorene Mercer's “Ballad
of a Truck Driver's Wife” ]
Woman: All right, sounds good.
I'll get your waters right away.
?
Hello. I'd like to speak
to your manager, if I could.
Hiya! [ Chuckles ] Hey!
I'm, uh, Herb Nelson.
I run this joint.
Pleasure to meet you,
Agent...Solange.
[ Sighs ]
I'm, uh, I'm here about...
Oh, I-I-I know why
you're here.
Uh...follow me.
Quietly.
? When you had to go ?
?
[ Herb groans ]
[ Metal door creaking ]
What is this?
Well...
[ Door clanks ]
You know... [ Groans ]
[ Locks clank ]
Can't be too careful.
They're always watching,
listening.
They are?
Oh, yeah.
But we're safe in here.
[ Loud thuds ]
Ow. [ Chuckles ]
Reinforced steel.
Nothing's gettin' through
this sucker.
Mm. Yeah.
Ahh.
So, uh,
you're here about Sara.
Yes, your waitress.
In this article,
you said, uh,
you said that she was killed
by an alien.
Well, not just aliens.
Reptilians.
You know...
like the Queen of England.
Right.
Okay, well, that's by helpful.
Thank you so much for your time.
And I-I got proof.
Um...
[ Opens drawer ]
[ Objects clattering ]
You know...
Ah. See?
[ Closes drawer ]
Most sheeple can't handle
the truth.
But not me. I'm woke.
It's, uh...
[ Plastic case clatters ]
...why I don't use, uh,
new tech.
Anything past '96, it's a trap.
You know...Palm Pilot.
It's more like Tracking Device.
Am I right?
[ Static hissing ]
Right.
Exactly.
[ Pushes button ]
Now watch this. [ Sniffs ]
[ Thud ]
Now, here we go.
Okay, now I-I don't know
who she is.
Probably another alien.
She's preggers, so my money's
on brood queen.
Now, I don't know who
he is either.
There! That's Sara.
Look, look, look.
See? Silver knives.
That's, uh, star metal.
[ Static hissing ] Yeah, the -- the camera
got fried.
But you...
you saw it, yeah?
R-right...
[ Pushes button ]
...there.
She has...
Yellow eyes.
[ Speaks inaudibly ]
[ Sighs ]
Like I said -- reptilian.
Now the local cops, they...
they think there's something --
you know, they don't believe me.
They think there's something
weird with the camera.
But, I mean,
that's why you're here.
The -- the FBI Man in Black.
[ Locks clank ]
Well, you know, beige.
You ask me, a bear got him.
[ Sighs ]
Maybe a cougar.
Found a fair amount of blood
over here and some there,
but no body.
Figure whatever did this
dragged him off.
So unless you guys
are lookin'
to make a Federal case
on some critters...
Sir, you said
there was a survivor.
Yeah. Gwen Hernandez.
Uh, but she's pretty shaken up,
saying all sorts
of strange things.
Like what?
Like that they were attacked
by a wolf --
an invisible wolf.
[ Chuckles ] Girl says that,
you know, it came outta nowhere
and that it's coming
after her next.
Right.
[ Laughs ]
Sheriff, thank you.
?
Invisible dog, huh?
Sounds like a hellhound to me.
Yeah.
Gwen! Run!
Marcus?
[ Growls ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Screams ]
Oh, my God!
Aah!
?
[ Growling ]
[ Engine turns off ]
[ Sighs ] This is dumb.
It's a dumb idea.
Listen, Gwen saw something
kill her boyfriend
and she thinks
it's coming for her next.
We just gotta tell her --
Tell her what?
[ Sighs ] No, seriously, Sam,
what are you gonna say?
“Hi, my name
is Sam Winchester.
“This is my much handsomer
brother Dean. We hunt monsters.
“Oh, and that guy
you were banging?
We're pretty sure he made
a deal with a demon,
“so a hellhound came
and dragged his soul to Hell.
“But you? You're cool.
And since there's nothing around
for us to kill, peace out.”
You done?
Yeah,
we don't say that, Dean.
We say something
that'll give her peace.
- You know, help her sleep at night.
- Oh, so we lie?
[ Sighs ] Yeah, a lot.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Doorbell rings ]
[ Growls ]
[ Lock clicks ]
Gwen Hernandez?
Uh, Agents Baker and Clapton.
FBI. May we come in?
I...I don't want any...
We just wanna talk.
That's all. About Marcus.
[ Bolt slides ]
Thanks.
?
[ Front door closes ]
Uh...
You can have a seat.
Right.
Gwen, uh, we're here today
because we, uh,
we know what you told
the police,
that you feel like
something...
supernatural is after you.
But we've concluded
our investigation,
and the thing that killed
your boyfriend --
Was a bear.
Now we found it
and put it down.
So you're no longer
in any kind of danger, okay?
I don't...
I-I know what I saw.
Gwen, when you go through
a traumatic experience,
sometimes your mind can
make things up.
Get out.
Sorry?
Get out of my house.
Okay, calm down.
We're just trying to help.
I don't need your help.
I know what I saw.
Gwen...
Get out!
[ Sighs ]
Okay.
?
Oh, yeah. She's gonna sleep
like a baby.
[ Low growling ]
[ Car door opens ]
?
[ Growling ]
[ Claws scraping ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Barking ]
[ Panting ]
[ Snarling, barking ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Barking, growling ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Yelps ]
[ Yelps, growls ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Whimpers ]
Hey. Hey.
It's okay. You're gonna be okay.
All right?
?
It must really burn you,
knowing I'm the one
who put you in this prison.
Me.
I own you,
and I have big plans for us.
[ Inhales deeply ] Ooh.
I'm flattered.
All this hard work,
all that...grr!
You get 'em, slugger!
I'm still gonna peel off
your skin and eat your soul.
Is that so?
Yeah.
I mean, it will be...
little bit messy,
Hmm.
But...
You know, gotta protect the rep.
You understand.
I do. But you, in --
in those chains?
I mean, forgive me if I'm not
quaking in my Testonis.
Oh, I think both you and I
understand that this?
[ Chains rattle ]
It's just
a temporary situation.
Oh, do we?
See, I understand
that whatever sad little scheme
that you're brewing up,
I'm already 10 steps ahead.
And I thought pride was
my sin.
[ Scoffs ] It's not pride.
It's fact.
You cross me, I crush you.
You hit me, I hit you back
twice as hard.
You make me your dog,
I make you my slave.
?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Pounding on door ]
Hello?
Crowley. My lord.
[ Imitates British accent ]
My lord.
[ Normal voice ]
Duty calls.
[ Growls ]
Don't worry about me.
I'll just sit right here.
[ Metal jangles ]
[ Jangles ]
Yes, you will.
Hmm. Kinky.
[ Door creaks ]
[ Lock clanks ]
What?
Apologies, Your Excellence.
It's just, um...
You're already an hour late
for the weekly meeting.
And we had to push last week,
so...
You have
410 crossroad deals
that need
senior management approval,
on top of
the 638 other matters
that require
your immediate response.
Fine.
Gwen, that, um,
that thing was a hellhound.
A...what?
Hellhound.
Kind of hard to explain.
Uh, basically,
giant, invisible hounds
from Hell.
Huh. Wasn't hard at all.
[ Chuckles ]
So you guys are not cops,
are you?
No. Not exactly.
Um...My name is Sam.
That's my brother Dean.
And we hunt monsters.
And we've tangled
with hellhounds in the past.
Goofer dust'll keep 'em out.
A demon knife or an angel blade,
that'll kill 'em.
Mm.
Uh...wait.
So why did you tell me that
Marcus got killed by a bear?
Make you feel better.
It was his idea.
[ Sighs ]
[ Sighs ] Listen, I know
this sounds insane --
It does.
But...like I said,
I know what I saw.
And what I saw was insane.
Right.
Now this is awkward,
but, um...
hellhounds only come after
people who sold their souls...
to a demon.
So about 10 years ago,
did you really want something?
Like...I don't know,
a Hello Kitty backpack
or the death of an enemy?
No.
What about Marcus? Did he...
Would he --
No.
?
Hmm.
Great. So what the hell?
I don't know.
But I do know who we can ask.
And moving on to, um, case 41,
Awar, a Rank Three demon,
claims to have had
six babies.
But then Morax,
a Rank Two demon,
took two of his babies,
which would leave Awar with...
yes, um, four babies.
Which I think we can all agree,
isn't enough babies...
[ Laughs ] for a decent meal.
No, not at all. Um, Awar is
looking for compensation
in the form of --
I don't care.
Moving on.
Oh. [ Clears throat ]
Me either.
Uh, moving on to case 42.
This is a good one.
It's on tort reform.
Yeah. [ Clears throat ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Ring ]
[ Beep ]
What the hell do you want?
All right, Peaches, I get that
you're still upset about
the whole, uh...
Upset?
No, I'm totally over how you
and your little band of misfits
sent my son back in time...
to die!
Okay, look, that was totally
Gavin's call.
All right? You know what?
We have a situation here.
Oh, well, in that case...Bye.
Hellhounds, Crowley.
One of your mutts
is going after folks
who didn't sell their souls.
Not possible.
You sure about that?
My hounds...
You have anything to tell me?
Well...
We, uh...
didn't wanna bother you.
It was Ramsey.
She got out, my lord.
Have the kennel guards killed.
Painfully.
[ Sighs ]
I'll be right
here.
Mm.
You miss me?
Nice day out.
Hello, brother.
Kelvin.
Oh, you remember?
We only met the once, so...
What are you doing here?
Same reason as you.
Track down Kelly Kline
and that unholy bun
she's got in her oven.
So what do you say
we help each other out?
You have to understand,
this isn't just a hellhound.
This is the hellhound.
That means what?
Right after God said,
“Let there be light,”
he -- he made
a whole bunch of things --
posies, koalas, hellhounds.
He wanted
The Creator's best friend,
but the hounds were too vicious.
So he planned on having them
all put down,
until along came
our favorite fallen angel.
He rescued one of the hounds --
a pregnant bitch named Ramsey.
Why don't you just tell her
to heel?
I can't control her. No one can.
She's loyal only to Lucifer.
Wait, like the Devil?
Yeah, but he's locked in a cage.
Oh. Good.
Yeah. All right,
so where is Fido now?
Well, if I had to hazard
a guess, I would say
huddled up
in some nice, warm den.
Well, why is she after Gwen?
Ask her.
I...
I don't...um...
When it attacked us,
I did hit it.
With an ax.
Well, there you go. The bitch
does tend to hold a grudge.
So we either kill Ramsey,
or the hound eats her.
[ Claps hands ]
Fun.
Wait a second. “We”?
Pup like that out and about
is not good for business.
Makes it look like I'm not
in control.
But that mutt's head
mounted on my wall?
Good for the brand.
So yes, Moose, for now, “we.”
Great. So we have a hellhound
who's gunning for revenge,
and it's personal.
Ah. Just when I thought this gig
couldn't get any weirder...
[ Chuckles ] Oh.
It can always get weirder.
?
[ Metal scrapes ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Door rattles ]
[ Metal jangles ]
[ Doorknob rattles ]
[ Lock clanks ]
[ Door creaks ]
[ Laughs ]
I knew it.
[ Chains rattle ]
[ Muffled voice ]
Hi, guys.
?
My lord...
[ Thud ]
I'm not worthy!
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
[ Chuckles ]
We knew Crowley was up
to something.
Mm-hmm-hmm.
The way he's been acting?
And how he snuffed out everyone
who was part
of the Cage project?
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
And a lot of us
really don't like Crowley.
He's very prancy.
Mm-hmm.
So we released your hound
to create a distraction,
to see what he was hiding.
Uh-huh.
We --
We hoped --
We knew it could only be you.
Mm-hmm. [ Chuckles ]
[ Chuckles ]
And we brought this.
[ Door and lock clank ]
?
Ah!
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
But -- but...
[ Growls ]
Before we, uh, let you out,
we have a few...
well, I wouldn't call them
demands, exactly.
But...
Hmm?
[ Sighs ]
So hellhounds are invisible
to humans...
unless you sold your soul,
and they're after you.
Or, uh, you're wearing
a pair of these.
They're glasses
treated with holy fire.
All right, Crowley and I are
gonna hit the woods,
see if we can't track down Cujo.
You stick with Sam.
He'll keep you safe.
Okay.
[ Car door opens ]
Take care of her.
[ Car door closes ]
Of course.
Dean, look, even if Ramsey
circles back,
as long as we keep moving,
Gwen's gonna be just...
[ Inhales sharply,
chuckles ]
You're talking about the car.
You tend to ride the brakes.
Dean, I know how to drive.
I'm just saying.
Okay, just imagine she's a...
a beautiful woman.
Oh, come on. Get out of here.
A beautiful, beautiful woman.
I'm done.
Sam...
Ew.
[ Engine starts ]
Come on.
[ Engine revs ]
[ Engine purring ]
So how are things in Heaven?
Functional.
You know, there's
the usual infighting, but...
let's just say Lucifer having
a baby on board has
brought us all together.
You know, this is an all hands
on deck situation, Castiel.
Including yours.
Okay, so you're here
for my hands?
We want you.
Look, you got
more field experience
than the next thousand angels
combined.
I think you overestimate me.
I don't.
Look, I know you're working
with the Winchesters.
Sam and Dean -- their hearts
are in the right place,
but wouldn't it be better
to have us waiting
in the proverbial wings?
All the power of Heaven
behind you?
[ Indistinct conversations ]
You ever miss it? Upstairs?
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I love Earth. It's quirky.
It smells like hay.
But it's not home, is it?
I don't believe I'm welcome
in Heaven.
No, you're not.
They still hold
a lot of grudges up there.
But what if I told you,
you could come back?
That all your sins could
be forgotten?
Forgiven?
I would say that you're lying.
Oh, but I'm not.
You help us track down
Kelly Kline,
and you will be welcomed back
into the fold.
Right.
And you have the power
to do that.
Oh, no, I can't.
I'm just the messenger.
But Joshua can.
?
Joshua.
I thought he stepped aside.
He did.
But like I said,
all hands on deck situation.
Imagine it, Castiel --
free to come and go
as you please,
part of your family,
your true family, again.
Look...
the Gardener's got a plan.
All we ask
is that you hear us,
hear him out.
?
For the greater good.
All right.
[ Grunts ]
Oh, and lastly...
[ Groans ]
You will grant me
a thousand souls per year,
and you will anoint me...
[ Chuckles ]
the new
King of the Crossroads.
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
Great.
Uh-huh.
Hey, Tommy,
you want anything, man?
The only thing I care about is
making Hell great again.
[ Chains rattle ]
See? [ Speaks indistinctly ]
What? Mm-hmm.
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
[ Chuckles ]
All right. Let's do this.
[ Grunts ]
[ Chains rattle, cuffs unlock ]
There we go, my lord.
[ Cuffs and chains clank ]
Mm.
[ Bit unlocks ]
Oh!
[ Chains clatter ]
Ohh!
[ Groans ] Yeah!
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
[ High-pitched yawn ]
I feel so good.
[ Laughs ]
[ Choking ]
We had a deal!
Did we?
[ Snaps fingers ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Chuckles ]
Sorry, kid.
You understand, right?
No -- no witnesses
or anything, yeah?
Yes. Take me, oh, Fallen One!
My life is yours to devour.
See, now you just
made it weird.
[ Snaps fingers ]
Hmm.
Fancy.
Really bring out
your eyes.
Shut up.
I mean it, Crowley.
Go to Hell.
Really, Dean, all these years,
you're so predictable.
Yeah, well,
I guess we've all changed.
I got predictable.
You got soft.
I mean, a few years ago,
who'd have thought
you'd be helping us save
the girl of the week?
I don't care about her.
Yeah, well, maybe
we rubbed off on you.
Don't flatter yourself.
You save Cass.
Just to spare myself
the Winchester Man Pain --
you lot moping about
like a bunch of schoolgirls.
Well, I just wanna say
thank you.
Or...a few years ago,
who would've thought you'd be
working with the King of Hell?
Maybe you've
rubbed off on me.
Maybe I've rubbed off
all over you.
[ Chuckles ]
Ugh.
I'm sorry.
For what?
This.
It's all my fault.
Gwen, this is not your fault.
Yes, it is.
What happened to Marcus...
Gwen! Run!
[ Growls ]
[ Grunts, screams ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Pull over. Please.
Okay.
? A hunting we will go ?
Crowley, shut up.
? Heigh -- ?
Seriously.
[ Click ]
?
Ramsey dragged him back...
to her den.
Well, it's empty.
So where is she now?
[ Crying softly ]
[ Sniffles ]
You okay?
I... [ Sighs ]
I don't think I even know
what “okay” means anymore.
Marcus...
going camping was my idea.
I took him out there
even though I knew.
I knew it was over.
[ Sniffles ]
I liked Marcus.
He was sweet and kind.
And he loved me.
[ Inhales deeply ]
More than I ever loved him.
More than...
[ Exhales shakily ]
If I'd just told him...
If I...
Why couldn't I just tell him
the truth?
?
Gwen...
Yeah, but I didn't.
[ Voice breaking ]
I lied.
I lied to make things easier.
I...
[ Breathes shakily ]
I'm sorry. I...
Mm.
We should go.
[ Sighs ]
[ Sighs ] Right.
[ Growls, barks ]
What?
She's here.
[ Growling ]
[ Loud thud ]
[ Crying ]
[ Glass cracks ]
[ Gasps ]
It's okay. It's okay.
Stay calm.
[ Barking, snarling ]
[ Cries ] Oh, my God.
All right.
[ Growling ]
[ Heavy steps overhead ]
[ Snorts ]
[ Loud thuds ]
We should leave.
It's the only way she'll stop.
[ Thudding continue ]
[ Glass shatters ]
[ Barking ]
Stay in the car.
Stay in the car!
Okay.
?
[ Panting ]
[ Growling ]
[ Barks ]
[ Glasses thud ]
[ Growling ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Smack ]
[ Yelps ]
?
[ Snorting, snarling ]
[ Squish ]
[ Yelping ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Thud ]
[ Panting ]
?
[ Horn blaring in distance ]
This is why
you don't drive.
[ Grunts ]
So...it's over?
It's over.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Ah, dog dead. Must be going.
Hey, Crowley, wait a second.
Um...
Thank you.
[ Horn blaring in distance ]
[ Scoffs ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
He seems nice.
Yeah.
[ Clears throat ]
?
Let's get in.
Hopefully, it still runs.
?
[ Door clanks, creaks ]
Now what was that
you were saying
about always being
two steps ahead?
?
[ Grunts ]
Buh-bye, Crowley.
That's not what I said.
[ Snaps fingers ]
[ Groans ]
Huh? What the...
[ Sighs deeply ]
I'm glad you had
a little taste of freedom.
What I said was,
I'm always 10 steps ahead.
I said you cross me,
I crush you.
You hit me...
[ Crunch ]
Aah! Aah!
...I hit you back
twice as hard.
[ Snaps fingers ]
[ Crunch ]
Uhh! Oh!
You make me your dog,
I'll make you my slave.
[ Crunch ]
[ Groans ]
[ Wincing ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Groans ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
Gah! [ Panting ]
That chain around your neck?
Was nothing.
A stylish accessory.
This vessel...
[ Breathing shallowly ]
That's your true prison.
It's been warded with runes
and spellwork from the Cage,
carved into every molecule.
[ Inhales sharply ]
In there?
I own you.
[ Groans ]
[ Sighs ] I'm just getting
started. So...
I'm gonna put you back
in your hole,
and then I'm gonna go find
your spawn,
and I'm gonna rip him apart
while you watch.
And then?
[ Groaning ]
?
I'm still
just getting started.
[ Thud ]
Cass, what's up?
Hey, I think I have a lead
on Kelly Kline.
Yeah?
She's with Dagon,
Prince of Hell.
All right, what do we know
about him?
Actually, it's a her.
And not much.
It's just rumors and stories.
Dagon is mostly known
for her psychotic savagery.
Great. So where's Kelly?
[ Bag thuds ]
Well, she was
in Coeur d'Alene, Idaho.
Now? I'm not sure.
All right, well,
we'll spread the word.
Let us know
if you find anything.
Of course.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
You ready, brother?
?
He sound weird to you?
[ Cellphone vibrating ]
Mm, is that your computer
talking to you again?
[ Beep ]
Uh...
No. Um...
It's, uh...
Mick Davies.
- What?
- Dean...
I don't have a computer program
feeding me cases.
I-I, uh...
Gwen? Every job we've worked
in the last two weeks?
[ Inhales deeply ]
They've come from
the British Men of Letters.
Really?
Yeah.
I didn't tell you 'cause I know
how much you hate them.
No, we hate them.
Us. Together.
I-I get that. Yeah, I do.
But -- but... [ Sighs ]
Dean, because of Mick
and his guys,
the Alpha Vampire is dead.
They get results.
I don't like them either, but --
but if -- if we can save people,
then it...
[ Sighs ]
?
Either way, I-I shouldn't have
lied to you. And...
I'm sorry, man. I-I...
?
Well, okay.
Okay?
[ Sighs ]
What do you want me to say?
Do I like it? No.
Do I trust them? Hell, no.
But you're right.
We work with people
we don't trust all the time.
I mean, hell, I just
Liam Neeson'd it up with Crowley.
So if you wanna give this
a shot, then...
[ Scoffs ] Fine.
But the minute --
and I mean the second --
something feels off,
we bail.
Yeah. Of course. Deal.
[ Cellphone vibrating ]
It's Mick.
[ Vibrating continues ]
Pick it up.
[ Beep ]
This is Sam.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man