Lucifer is gone.
- To where?
- I don't know.
Lucifer's running
because he's weak.
Hell will never
follow you.
You gave me
what I needed most.
I want to do
the same for you.
Mom?
Toni Bevell. Men of Letters,
London Chapterhouse.
Where's Dean?
Dead.
Put the gun down.
I need you to give me
names and locations
and everything else.
Screw you.
Are you really
gonna make me do this?
You know what they say.
Good things come
to those --
Thanks, Mom.
We stop trying to break his
body. We break his mind.
Maybe you're not as good
at your job as you think.
No!
Wow.
Isn't this
much more pleasant, Sam?
I got to say,
I did not see that happening.
Well, you know
what they say.
Opposites attract.
Oh, we'll get there, Sam.
Just another
couple of questions.
Hmm.
? Supernatural 12x02 ?
Mamma Mia
Original Air Date on October 20, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Fascinating.
But surely you exaggerate.
American Hunters
can't be as bad as you say.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah, they can.
What, they're not
in the U.K.?
No.
No, they work for us.
Tools.
They kill. They don't think.
Huh.
Who recruited you
and your brother?
To whom do you report?
We, uh...
We're not just gonna
talk all night, right?
I haven't found anything on
these surveillance cameras.
I mean, it's like
they just disappeared.
How about you?
Any of the local beat cops
see anybody
that shouldn't be there?
It's pretty rural.
Not a lot of beat cops.
I've checked all the motels,
abandoned buildings.
No sign of Sam.
All right.
I don't know.
You know, check...
real-estate offices.
See if anybody bought
a place or rented a place.
I mean, these people
had a freakin' plane.
Maybe they do things legit.
Okay, I understand.
I'll call you
in the morning.
Cass, hey.
So, here's the thing.
It's been kind of weird here
with, you know, Mom being back.
It's like we don't know how
to act around each other,
so we just kind of make
this small talk and act normal,
but it's --
it's so not normal.
Um, I'm -- I'm not sure.
What -- what has
she said to you?
Well, nothing.
That -- that -- that's
the whole point.
Okay, what have you
said to her?
Well, nothing. I'm --
I don't know what
to say to her, you know?
It -- it's -- it's like
it's all just too much,
and...I don't want
to overwhelm her.
Don't make things
needlessly complicated,
as you humans tend to do.
I'll call you.
Yeah. Great.
That's helpful.
Thanks.
Any news on Sam?
Um, so somewhere
outsi-- here.
Somewhere outside
of Aldrich, Missouri.
Cass is going through it
with a fine-toothed comb,
and I've cracked
every database I could.
Every what?
Right.
No Internet
your first time around.
Our house didn't have
an electric typewriter.
So...are you really afraid
of overwhelming me?
Mom, look, I am...
thrilled that you're back.
I mean, I'm so damn happy,
I-I-I can't even stand it.
I just...
it's just gonna take me a second
to catch up, you know?
Yeah, no, no.
Look, take -- take
all the time you need,
all right?
It's -- it is what it is.
And when we do find Sam...
how am I gonna face him?
What do you mean?
That yellow-eyed thing
would never have come for him
that night if I...
I started all of this.
It's just surprising that
for all your efforts,
yours and all the Hunters,
monsters remain rampant
in this country.
Yeah, we just, uh --
just keep plugging away,
I guess.
Do you ever think -- and don't
take this the wrong way --
that some of your soldiers
may have been compromised?
Or bought.
I mean...
No, I-I don't, um...
Is everything all right?
No!
I shouldn't -- I shouldn't
be talking to you.
You'll have to admit,
it was fun while it lasted.
What did you do to me?
An hallucination created by
potion and powerful spell work.
So...was it good
for you?
Hm.
Sadly, I can't do
the spell again.
Your brain would liquify,
which we don't want.
Yet.
So...
I'll have to resort
to less...
pleasant methods.
Enhanced interrogation was never
part of my job description.
But as it turns out...
...I'm a quick study.
Hey, how'd you sleep?
I had dreams all night.
Good dreams?
Stuff I'd forgotten about.
Funny stuff your dad did.
He was a great father.
Hey, Cass,
what do you got?
I think I may have found
Sam's location.
It's a farm.
It appears empty,
but it was rented two weeks ago
to a woman with
an English accent.
Did you have
a look inside?
No.
No, it's --
it's powerfully warded.
Powerfully warded?
Okay, see, buddy, that --
that was your headline
right there.
Are we still discussing
the same thing?
Where are you?
I'll text you the address.
Okay, got it.
I'm on my way.
I'll get my coat.
Wait.
Uh
Okay.
Why don't I take
this one solo, okay?
We just -- we don't know
what we're walking into here.
We never know.
We're Hunters.
Right. Um...
Okay, I-I can't do my job
if I'm worried about you.
Dean.
You won't have to be.
I can handle myself.
Okay?
All right, good talk.
Oh, boy.
Good morning, Sam.
Let's start again, shall we?
Take our time.
I've cleared my calendar.
I would like names
and locations of every Hunter...
the passcodes to each and every
Men of Letters database
held in the bunker,
and then -- oh, yes --
let's do discuss
your relationship
with the demon Ruby.
Mick.
You've been a bad girl, Toni.
And I've come to fetch you.
I have Sam Winchester.
He's close to breaking.
Just leave me be.
No can do.
You disobeyed orders.
Oh, and you should know,
your Ms. Watt -- quite dead.
Courtesy of Dean Winchester
and friends.
Sent me to
the grandest boarding schools,
but I was a wee imp and ran away
for a life in the arts.
Mother didn't speak to me
until I became a star.
A star?
Of?
Uh, do you follow
the Royal Ballet?
Not a bit.
The Royal Ballet.
You know, it reminds me
a lot of my story.
I left school to work
in a steel mill.
I rose up through the ranks,
and now I own half a dozen.
You're not serious?
More wine, madam?
You're like a boil
that keeps coming back
no matter how many times
I have it lanced.
Let me guess.
Your dinner date
is loaded, single,
and possibly
in delicate health.
What of it?
Well, just a stab,
but you probably don't want me
to reveal that his snookums
is 300 years old
and a witch.
Fergus, the man treats me
like a queen.
It's my chance
to leave behind
monsters and demons
and moldy hideouts.
So help me,
if you muck this up.
Oh, I wouldn't
dream of it, Mummy...
if you do me
one tiny favor.
Help me with Lucifer.
Lucifer?
I have
a score to settle.
Let's hear it
for Vince Vincente
and the rest of the band!
See you the next time around.
Good night, Cleveland!
- Whoo!
- I love you guys!
Good night, Cleveland!
We love you!
Hey, Vinny, we're hitting
the town tonight. Come with us.
Check out the wonders
of Cleveland.
Yeah, um...
I'm good, thanks.
- Tommy, Tommy, come on!
- Yeah.
Hey, I'll catch up
with you guys later.
Dude, you --
You got to start
living your life, man.
You perform, you drink,
you sleep, perform, drink.
I-I get it.
I get it.
Look.
Vince, it's been years
since Jen died.
All I mean, brother,
is, don't you think
she'd want more
for you than just --
Get out of here, Tommy.
Go see Cleveland.
I can't believe I let you
talk me into this.
I'm your mother.
You have to do what I say.
Look.
They targeted the bunker.
They obviously know
a lot about you and Sam.
They'll be expecting you.
I'm the last person
they'd expect.
You were good at this,
weren't you?
Very.
The thing is, Hunters...
no matter how good they are,
they all end up the same way.
You know when you died,
it changed Dad.
I mean, he was Hell-bent
on finding out what happened.
The Hunter life,
it just took him over.
I guess I was the same.
But Sammy -- Sammy,
he was different.
He wanted out.
He went to school.
He went to Stanford.
Sam had a chance
to get out?
And he came back?
When Dad disappeared,
Sam and I looked around,
and something
became very clear.
That the only thing
we had in this world --
the only thing, aside from
this car -- was each other.
Vince.
Hello, front desk?
Hello?
Vince.
No.
Jen.
Yes, Vince.
How?
Why?
I needed
to say I'm sorry.
Swallowing those pills
was selfish.
I've had to live all these years
knowing how I treated you.
At the time,
leaving you seemed fair
since you left me
so many times.
All I want is you.
That can happen, Vince.
What can happen?
You and me together.
Are you a ghost?
No.
I'm an angel.
Those are real?
Real and very powerful,
Vince.
I can take away your pain.
Bring you peace.
You only have to do
one easy thing.
What?
Will you invite me in?
Yes.
Ostende illum mihi quen quaero.
What's the bloody
hold-up?
He's the one and only Satan
in the phonebook.
It's witchcraft,
not Google Maps.
And normally I'd have
a piece of hair
or a belonging
to lock on to.
You don't even know
what he looks like!
He has an aura.
Supreme evil.
Lock on to that.
Do I have
to do everything?
I can't believe
I'm once again
down some dank hole
seeking the devil!
When does it end?
It's exactly why I'm
retiring to Boca Raton.
With Ben.
Ben?
Who makes oatmeal
look fascinating.
He's successful, stable,
and I'll outlive him.
Lucifer?
I think so.
Yes. I'll give you
the location.
No, no, no.
Not now.
I just want to know
who we're dealing with
before we attack.
By "we," I presume you mean
the Winchesters
and their pet angel?
I don't need them.
Just you.
Look, it's obvious.
We got to put Lucifer
back in the cage.
You're the only one
that can do it.
Should've known.
No, Fergus!
I'll not be involved
in that nonsense again!
Maybe I should
tell Ben about you.
Maybe just kill him.
Either way,
it's bye-bye, Boca.
You are a hateful snake.
In any case, Lucifer can't be
sent back to the cage
while he's in a vessel.
He won't be.
Not by the time
we're ready.
Where's all this warding
you mentioned?
It's cloaked.
It's very powerful.
You brought your mother?
Hello, Castiel.
Yes, he did.
You sure
there's anyone inside?
No.
The agent said the lease
was handled long distance,
but someone
warded the house.
I'm gonna go
have a closer look.
Mom, I got this.
You can keep me from driving, Dean.
Not from hunting.
I'm locked out
by the warding.
I could use the company.
Thanks.
Dude, it's noon.
Let me in.
Whoa.
Look at you.
Pretty dressed up
for rehearsal, don't you think?
Rehearsal.
Brother, are you okay?
Yeah, I just can't
make it to rehearsal.
Yeah, you got better plans?
I do.
Vince, I'm serious.
So am I.
All right.
Look, stop screwing around.
I said I had plans.
Son of a bitch.
Screw yourself.
Dean.
I'm as happy
to see him as you are,
'cause while you may
be able to withstand
my snapping apart
your body joint by joint,
can you watch it
happen to Dean?
They told me you'd be here.
Really?
Get off my furniture,
squatter.
Lucifer.
Wearing Vince Vincente,
second-tier star.
I would've thought Bieber
was more your style.
You're either mad or dim.
I have a proposal.
I mean, why in Hell would
you want to rule over a motley,
witless crew of demons?
God's on sabbatical again.
You could reclaim Heaven.
Now, that's real estate
that's worth ruling.
I can handle
the branch office.
Hmm.
Or...I could raise my hand,
smite you into oblivion.
Manete. Manete. Manete.
Manete.
Problem?
Manete. Manete.
Mummy's little
paralyzing spell.
Trust me, it works.
Trust me.
Not for long.
Oh...
Holy water?
Yeah?
Ooh, ouch.
Don't bore me.
Well, actually,
it's top-shelf sulfuric acid.
Harmless to you, I know,
but to your vessel, not so much.
Passcodes, Sam.
Not yet?
Anything to add?
No. No, I just came by
for some tea and a beating.
Really?
See, I thought you might
be on for a little chat
about your mate,
Benjamin Lafitte.
I'm sorry.
You called him Benny.
You know, the vampire
whom you released from Purgatory
and befriended.
I see.
Well...
the English are nothing
if not patient.
Now.
His essence,
send it back to the cage.
Wah tay, fay roh lah!
Mother!
Manete!
It's not working.
Manete! Manete!
Bad, bad Crowley.
Seriously?
You spoil that boy.
Dean.
Hey.
I thought you were dead.
I'm not sure that I'm not.
So?
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you
everything, okay?
First off,
who's Angry Spice?
She, uh -- she's --
she's Men of Letters.
Uh, British Men of Letters.
Is that a thing?
What the hell?
Aren't we supposed
to be on the same team?
Oh, God.
Gentlemen.
So, to recap --
you live in
the Men of Letters bunker,
awash in the world's
greatest collection
of occult knowledge,
and yet you know "nothing."
Right.
What a waste.
It seems you apes have never
read a single book.
The Men of Letters
has a long tradition
of intellectual excellence.
In London, we've undertaken
exhaustive studies
of even the most arcane topics.
For example, parts of the body
most sensitive to intense pain.
The ear drum.
Decaying tooth.
Below the belt, of course.
And my favorite --
under the eyelid.
Did you know it's possible
to die from pain?
Get away from my boys.
Mom?
Yeah.
Drop it.
Ground.
That's the ground.
Holy crap.
Xi.
Kill the spell now.
I'm not kidding.
Shoot me, and your mother
has no chance.
The gun.
Dean!
It's okay.
She was using a Chinese
mind-control technique.
Hard to do when
you're unconscious.
Turns out this ape
did read a book or two.
Well played.
What you were told
is basically true.
We were keen on knowing
about the two of you,
seeing as you seem to be
partially carrying on
the Men of Letters' work here
now that the American chapter
is defunct.
So you sic your attack dog
on us to what, say hi?
Well, part of our group
suspect some kind of malfeasance
amongst
you American Hunters.
No argument --
Lady Bevell went too far.
I deeply apologize.
Mm.
She'll face consequences
in London.
I'll tell you what,
why don't you take a walk,
and she can face those
consequences right here and now?
She's ours.
We'll take care of her.
Now, I'm here to
extend an olive branch.
We want to work with you.
Let me ask you a question,
uh, Mick is it?
Why would we believe
any of this?
Lads...if I wasn't sincere,
if I meant you harm,
there's a dozen ways
I could've come in here
and taken you all prisoner
instead of being unarmed.
Not to mention I powered down
all the wardings in this shack
so your attack dog
could come in.
I reckon you could finish me off
without breaking a sweat.
Am I right?
I don't sweat
under any circumstances.
My number.
Take your time, cool down,
and just think it over.
And what have you got to lose,
except your worst nightmares?
Oh, that was fantastic.
Thank you, Mom.
All I did was point
at some stuff
on a take-out menu.
I would've cooked,
but I, uh...don't.
Well, now, wait.
Your meat loaf was amazing.
Came from
the Piggly Wiggly.
Sorry to
burst your bubble.
But do you still
like pie?
I mean...
Sam.
You keep looking at me like
I'm going to explode.
I'm sorry.
Oh!
But what do we think?
Are we buying that Brit's whole
"Let's be friends" routine?
- No. No way.
- No.
Mmm.
Could you eat that
any faster?
No.
No, I cannot.
Well, we should
call the Internet
and find out as much
as we can about these people.
Did I say that right?
So close.
Yeah, it was close.
You want any?
No. Uh, not now.
You know, I got to say,
Rowena,
I took one look at you,
and all I wanted
was to snap
your miserable neck again.
And keep it snapped
this time.
But I think
I've decided against it.
You won't regret it, sir.
I'm done with all this.
I'll stay far, far away,
sipping martinis with
republicans at my tennis club.
You're missing my point.
A witch
as gifted as yourself,
with access to the Book
of the Damned to boot,
would be much more valuable
as a prisoner.
What?
How's that saying go?
Mm, friends close...
...enemies closer.
No.
No!
Yes?
Hey.
Hi.
Sorry. I hope
I didn't wake you up.
I-I, uh...wanted
to bring you this.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I don't know if
you drink tea, but...
- I do.
- Good.
Uh, and I wanted to say...
if you ever want to talk,
I know what it's like
to come back
and not feel like
you really fit.
I just have so much about
you boys to catch up on.
Mother stuff.
You know, first tooth,
first crush.
Yeah.
I just have a lot
of blanks to fill in.
Right, uh...
Dad's journal.
His writing, his words.
Helped me
fill in some blanks,
answer some questions
I didn't know I had.
And, you know, it -- it --
it keeps him with us, sort of.
Thank you.
Good night.
Dean said you got out
of hunting.
Yeah.
And yet here you are.
Well, this is my family.
My family hunts, you know?
It's what we do.
Mom.
For me...
just, um...
having you here...
fills in
the biggest blank.
[ Heart's "Lost Angel" plays ]
? As it was before ?
? Shall it ever, ever be ?
? Hear it on the crying wind ?
? Hear it weeping on the sea ?
? Lost angel, find us now ?
? From the clouds above ?
? Right down to the ground ?
? Lost angel ?
I will not
get on that plane.
Yes, you will.
Your mission was
to identify American Hunters
and gain their trust.
That's what
the home office wants.
Honey, not vinegar.
I have a dossier,
and I am just getting started.
They've also had
their fair share of successes.
If our goal is to end
the supernatural threat here,
we need to destroy
every obstacle.
The Winchesters,
these American Hunters,
they're no better
than the monsters
they fail to control.
They need
to be eliminated.
Mick.
If push comes to shove,
your ladyship,
I'm prepared for that.
You'll get
your hands dirty?
Well, we have
Mr. Ketch for that.
You'll send for him?
I already have.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man