Hands were I can see 'em.
Is that you, Roy?
Which makes you Walt.
Jody Mills is good people,
and she'll give you
a place to crash
until you get back on your feet.
If only you'd been
as ruthless as I hoped.
- Now what?
- Let's begin.
I do have to hand it
to Lady Bevell.
Your treatment's been
most successful.
Stay where you are.
Hey!
I was talking to you.
Mom?
I really wouldn't move.
She will shoot you.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Ketch.
Your bunker is
an excellent fortress.
An even better tomb.
We've rejiggered the locks,
we've shut off the water,
and once we leave,
the pumps that bring in the air
shall reverse.
Your oxygen
should be gone in...
two days, maybe three.
Come along, Mary.
No!
?
? Supernatural 12x22 ?
Who We Are
Original Air Date on May 18, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
All right. The garage?
Doors are warded and the walls
are reinforced steel.
Okay. Um, you know, maybe we could
get out through the air vents.
You wouldn't get far.
There are choke points
in the duct system
not even I could
squeeze through.
I say we kill her.
I mean, you heard Ketch.
Said we had about
three days of air left.
So if we ice her, maybe that
buys us an extra day.
I assure you, Dean,
I'm an extraordinarily
shallow breather.
Hmm. All right.
If we ever get out of here,
I am the one who programmed
your mother,
which means that I am
the only one who can undo it.
And since I assume
you want Mummy back,
you need me.
You believe her?
I don't know.
Look, if she's lying,
sure, we take her out.
But Mom is still out there,
brainwashed.
If she's telling the truth,
then we do need her.
All right, you're so smart,
how do we get out of here?
The only way out is to pull
the manual override.
Is that a thing?
Oh, it is.
But it's outside the bunker,
where we can't reach it.
Awesome.
Wait a second, guys.
We're in a giant vault
loaded down with --
with occult books and lore.
There's gotta be something
somewhere in here --
an item or a spell --
some hoodoo that can reverse
the lockdown.
I think I got something.
“When the Romani people were
forced to assimilate in Europe,
“the, uh, the Roma used a spell,
“the Abrogation ritual,
as an act of rebellion
“against their persecutors.
“The Devla turns back
complex mechanical processes,
resets equipment, machinery.”
What's it take?
Seems like pretty basic ingredients.
Nothing we don't already have.
Oh.
What?
The mechanisms “must be anointed
with the blood of virgins.”
Not even close.
All right, well, then,
I guess we keep lookin'.
Or we fake it.
Excuse me?
We fake it.
I mean, I've read half a dozen
purification rituals
in the last hour.
If we used one of those on --
on our blood...
Then what? Revirginize it?
Maybe.
So we purify the blood,
then do the spell.
Two-step, hybrid magic.
All right, that's step one.
Step two, you're up.
F?rmichi, f?rmichi,
mashuna parra, mashuna parra.
It's working.
It's working!
No.
What happened?
Ketch! He knew we'd...
He must've put some kind
of mystical dampener
on the bunker's lockdown.
Magic won't work.
Okay, we have...
exhausted brains,
so I saw we try brawn.
How?
Walls.
Now the garage,
the Crow's Nest,
these are all
reinforced steel walls, right?
But right here,
that's nothing but concrete.
And right there,
that's an old sewer pipe,
goes straight up to
the surface...to the override.
So wait a second.
We're just gonna...
Straight Shawshank
this bitch.
?
Goggles?
Goggles.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
We earned a break.
Yeah.
We'll get there.
No.
No, we won't.
We're not gonna hit dirt
for three days.
Two if we're lucky.
I know you feel it --
the air, it's thin.
And it's getting thinner.
How did this happen?
What part?
All of it.
Yeah.
You know, it wasn't long ago,
I thought we had it made.
We saved the world.
We got Cass back.
We had Mom back.
I mean, it wasn't perfect,
but still, we had 'em.
And now...
Now they're all gone.
And Mom,
what they did to her...
I just fell
for their company line.
Man, I...
I saw what they were doing,
and I -- and I thought,
Hunters on that scale,
working together...
how much good we can do.
And once I was in, I...
I just followed.
'Cause it was easy.
Easier.
Easier than what?
Easier than leading.
Is this how you pictured it?
The end?
Oh, you know it's not.
I always thought
we'd go out like...
Butch and Sundance style.
Yeah.
Blaze of glory.
?
Son of a bitch.
Hmm.
You're lunatics.
This is
a colossally stupid idea.
Yep.
Big, beautiful,
and dumb.
I've had this thing
for so long.
Been waiting for
the perfect moment to use it.
The explosion could kill us all.
You could bring the whole bloody
place crashing down.
Yeah.
You're lunatics.
Action movie-loving,
cheeseburger-eating,
moronic American lunatics.
Okay, beautiful.
Yippee ki-yay, mother --
Dean?
Dean!
?
Dean?
Hey, lunatic.
?
Mary?
Hey, Jody.
Uh...
You got a sec?
Yeah.
Dead.
Uh, dead.
Wait, I got one.
Garth? Hey.
Oh, man. It's good
to hear your voice.
Listen, uh, those Brits
I told you about,
they've got a hit out
on American Hunters.
I'm guessing that goes double
for werewolf hunters, so...
No, I don't have time
to explain.
You and Bess need to get
someplace safe.
Okay? All right.
Hey.
Jody.
?
Jody?
Jody. Alex.
Hey.
Hey. Where is she?
Hello, boys.
When she clocked me out of the
blue, I thought she was a demon.
I had no idea that brainwashing
could be so thorough.
Jody, she...
I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault.
Fortunately, Alex came home.
All I did was buy you time.
You knocked her out.
I'll get you something
for the pain.
Make it a double.
Aw.
You wanna play mother
to my son?
He's all yours.
Dean...
that's not your mom.
What's the matter, Dean?
Am I too different from
the Mary you know?
Or too much the same?
Here she is.
Do your thing.
All right, you said you could
fix her, so fix her.
I, um...
Well, I --
She lied.
What?
Mary's programming...
It's permanent.
But you said...
You were going to kill me.
The Mary that you know,
the good Mary,
she's hiding behind
impenetrable psychic walls.
And I'm afraid these walls...
Well, they can't be torn down
with grenades.
Your mother can't be saved.
?
All right, “Lady,” time's up.
We only kept you alive
for one reason.
Hey, guys.
Listen, uh, Ketch keeps callin'
Mom's phone.
I'll get it.
Let it go to voicemail.
Let's take a nice little
short walk to the backyard.
This is not going to stop.
Soon enough, they'll find out
you're alive, and then...
Well, if you want
my advice -- run.
We're not running.
Well, then, you die.
Or...
Or what?
Or we fight.
Feet off the table, Jerry.
Thanks.
That should be the last one.
Walt. Roy.
Well, damn.
We haven't
seen you guys since --
Since you killed us.
No hard feelings.
Uh, uh, please,
get comfortable.
Sure about this?
You gonna tell us what
we're doing here or what?
Ah.
Of course. Yeah.
Um, so my -- my brother and I,
we -- we, um...
No, you know what?
I called you here
because people...
um, our people,
are being slaughtered.
And we're next.
The British Men of Letters,
they came here because they
thought they could do our job
better than we could.
And they hooked us with their
flashy gear and their tech.
Most of you had the good sense
to turn 'em down.
I didn't.
They said they wanted the same
thing we wanted, you know?
A world free of monsters.
That's not what
they really wanted.
They want control.
They want to live in a world
where they can sit
in some office
and decide who gets to live
and who gets to die.
And they've killed people.
They've killed innocent people
just because they got
in the way.
They think the ends justify
the means.
But we know better.
We know hunting isn't just
about killing.
It's about doing what's right,
even when it's hard.
So we go by our gut, right?
We play by our own rules,
and that scares them.
That's why they want us dead,
'cause we're the one thing
they can't control.
So what do you want
from us?
I want you to follow me.
Take the fight to them.
To hit them before they hit us.
We go in fast and hard
and we fight
and we beat them down
until they give up
or until they're dead.
?
Look, they're well-trained
and well-armed.
Some of us might not
make it back.
But we will win.
We will take down the bad guys
because that's what we do.
They're scared of us.
Yeah. Good.
They should be.
?
You know where
we're goin'?
- Yep.
-Gear up. We roll out in 10.
You ready?
Ooh.
Oh, no. I'm not goin'.
What?
No, my leg busted up the way
it is, I'm no good in a fight.
I-I'll take
a jacked up Dean Winchester
over any 10 other Hunters
any day.
Yeah.
I saw you.
You're ready for this.
You show those sons of bitches
who's boss.
What about you?
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna save Mom.
Look, if she's in there,
if our real Mom
is in there somewhere,
then I'm gonna try and find her,
bring her back.
Okay, Donna's --
Waiting for me at a safe house.
I should drive straight there,
no stops.
And you'll call me
when this is all over.
I got it.
And, Jody --
I'll be careful. I promise.
Not what I was gonna ask.
Kick it in the ass.
You got this.
Come here.
You come back.
Promise.
Bitch.
Jerk.
Yeah.
?
Okay, you got inside
my Mom's head once before.
What about me? You get me in?
You? I...
Perhaps.
But I need my rig.
Where is it?
At the base.
But I suppose with
the right materials,
I could cobble something
together.
Target lists will be
distributed shortly.
In Phase Two,
there are no restrictions.
Family members, bystanders.
Don't...leave...witnesses.
That will be all.
?
Paige, I need you
to pull up
the location
of one of our assets,
and I need you to keep it
between us.
Who?
Mary Winchester.
She's in...
Lebanon, Kansas.
?
All right,
where's the stuff you need?
Should be in storage,
next to the dungeon.
Ah.
Think I'm lettin' you
out of my sight?
Need I remind you that
my organization left me to die?
At this point, I'm not
on anyone's side but my own.
So I help you try to save
your mother,
and when the dust clears...
What? I let you go?
I'd like
to see my son again.
I'm not asking for a pass.
I'm asking for a head start.
?
These electrodes sync
your Delta waves with Mary's
forming a psychic link.
But to enter her psyche
will take a certain measure
of concentration and skill.
And as there's no time
to teach you how to reach
the necessary
therapeutic dreamstate,
I'm banking on this.
Hypnotic agents laced with
a potent sedative.
Ah.
It's enough to knock an elephant
on its trunk.
Really?
Little insurance.
You understand.
This will hurt.
?
Sam.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
?
Dean, lunch is ready.
Mom.
We gotta get out of here, okay?
You need to come with me.
Mom?
Mom.
?
Uhh!
What is happening
out there?
Perimeter's breached.
Hunters.
Gentlemen, ladies,
you know what to do.
Get down!
Look, I know that they
messed with your head, okay?
I know it feels better in here.
It feels safer.
But I-I need you
to hear me.
I was thinking maybe we should
take Sammy to the park later,
before Daddy gets home.
Sound good?
Mom, look at me.
You're choosing this.
Your favorite.
Yes!
After you eat.
?
I only want good things
for you, Dean.
I'll never let anything bad
happen to you.
I hate you.
?
Go, go, go, go, go.
Go! Hurry! Hurry!
?
Uhh!
You lied to me.
I was a kid.
You promised
you'd keep me safe.
And then you make a deal
with Azazel.
Yeah, it saved Dad's life,
but I'll tell you
something else that happened.
Because on November 2, 1983,
old Yellow Eyes came
waltzing in to Sammy's room
because of your deal.
You left us.
Alone.
'Cause Dad was just a shell.
His perfect wife? Gone.
Our perfect Mom,
the perfect family...
was gone.
And I...
I had to be...
more than just a brother.
I had to be a father
and I had to be a mother,
to keep him safe.
And that wasn't fair.
And I couldn't do it.
And you wanna know what
that was like?
They killed the girl
that he loved.
He got possessed
by Lucifer.
They tortured him in Hell.
And he lost his soul.
His soul.
All because of you.
?
All of it
was because of you.
I hate you.
And I love you.
'Cause I can't --
I can't help it.
You're my Mom.
And I understand...
...'cause I have made deals
to save the ones I love
more than once.
I forgive you.
For all of it.
Everything.
On the other side of this,
we can start over, okay?
You, me, Sam.
We can get it right this time.
But I need you to fight.
Right now,
I need you to fight.
I need you -- I need you
to look at me, Mom.
I need you to really look
at me and see me.
Mom, I need you to see me.
Please.
?
Dean?
Mom.
No.
Oh, yes.
?
Aah!
Oh, what? Thought you'd get
your Mum back?
Sorry, Dean.
Not how this ends.
This ends with me ending you.
I'm gonna kill you.
You won't,
but I'd very much enjoy it
if you tried.
?
You want to know what your
mother said about you, Dean?
All those long days
and even longer nights
out on the road, hunting?
Hmm?
Absolutely nothing.
Ah. This is fun.
?
Hey!
I got this.
Yeah.
Ah!
When you left us alone
in the bunker,
man, I knew
you were psycho,
but I didn't think
you were stupid.
I may be many things...
...but I'm not stupid.
?
Mom?
Mary.
Ah.
I...
I knew you were a killer.
You both are.
You're right.
Whatever it takes --
open a portal.
Just get me the hell
out of here.
I'm afraid we don't have
the resources
for an extraction
at this moment.
Don't! Don't.
?
Listen, Dean --
It's Sam.
And you must be Hess,
I trust.
You're in charge
of this whole operation?
Or, uh,
what's left of it?
Sam, you might think it in
your best interest to kill me,
to end all of this here.
Mm.
But shooting me now,
severing all ties with
the British Men of Letters,
at this particular moment,
that would be
a grievous mistake.
I doubt it.
There are reasons
to reconsider.
Things that you don't know.
What are these?
Lucifer is back.
Yes, Sam. All thanks
to your good friend Crowley.
Not that it did him
much good.
Crowley's dead.
And the Devil
is out looking for his son,
following in
its mother's footsteps,
tracking her
and your friend the angel.
If Lucifer gets his hands
on that child,
they'll be unstoppable.
You can't face that alone.
You need us.
Listen to her, boy.
?
Pass.
You bastard.
?
Found some expired
prescription painkillers,
so...
lucky me.
Mom, you don't have to do that.
It's not your job.
This...
All of this
is because of me.
It'll be okay.
It's not okay.
Since I've been back,
I know...
I've been distant.
Cold, even.
Leaving you,
working with them...
I was trying
to make things right.
Just from a distance,
because...
being here with you
was too hard.
Seeing what I'd done
to you and to Sam, I...
Mom, what you did,
the deal...
...everything
that's happened since
has made us who we are.
And who we are?
We kick ass.
We save the world.
And Sam?
I'm scared. What...
What if he can't
forgive me?
Mom.
You don't have to be scared
of me.
?
Glad you're back, man.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man