Mrs. Winchester,
I believe you're drawn
to danger.
Drink? Have you
talked to mom lately?
Oh, shouldn't worry about
your mum.
Her and ketch make quite a team.
Would you want your mom
working with him?
Well, that was unexpected.
Dr. Hess. I didn't think
you left London.
I have been tasked
by the other elders
to fix this rapidly
deteriorating situation.
Dr. Hess...
These hunters are out
of control. Exterminate them.
The brothers Winchester,
in particular.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna go.
What?
I got work tomorrow, so...
Naw, dude. Stick around.
Have another beer.
Enjoy the show.
You know you're a freak, right?
Oh, yeah.
Cheers, bud.
Hey.
Ohh, man. Dude.
Daryn! What is this, man?
Hey, real funny, Daryn!
Ha ha!
Hey! Daryn?
No. No.
No, no, no!
This is my voicemail.
Make your voice a mail.
Come on.
Cass, it's me.
I've been trying to get ahold
of you for days.
I don't know what's going on,
but we got a line on Dagon...
And we got
our asses handed to us,
even with the Colt.
So... Could really use
the backup.
Call me back.
So no luck with Cass, huh?
Yeah, still awol.
All right, so let's find him.
I've been trying, Sam.
The GPS on his phone
is turned off,
and there's nothing in
the system about some weird guy
in a trench coat getting
arrested or turning up dead.
Right.
Dean, it's Cass.
I mean, this isn't
the first time
he's dropped off the map,
you know?
And whatever's happening,
he'll be fine.
He always is.
Yeah.
What 'bout you?
You got anything there,
reading rainbow?
I stayed up all night,
going through every book
we have on demons,
and it turns out we have
a lot of books on demons.
Anything on Dagon?
Mentions here and there,
but nothing we can use.
I guess the, uh, princes of hell
are pretty good
at staying off the radar.
Well, yeah, isn't that
kind of their thing?
Hmm.
Just got an e-mail from Mick.
It's a case.
Good.
Looks like a guy named
Jarrod Hayes
disappeared in
tomahawk, Wisconsin, a week ago.
No witnesses. No body.
But Mick says this place has a history.
Meaning?
Well, it means a lot of people
go missing in tomahawk,
one a year, every year,
from 1898 to 1997,
and then nothing until now.
So 20 years?
Yeah. So maybe they're
starting up again?
Maybe it's a cycle of some sort?
Well...
One way to find out.
Pew.
It's time.
I'm sorry, but why the feds
interested in Jarrod Hayes?
Just followin' orders.
Yeah, um...
So what can you tell us
about the case?
Well... Nothing much to tell.
Jarrod and his friends were
hanging out at weather top.
This make-out spot the kids use
out at the woods.
And then he ditched his pals
to hoof it home.
Never made it.
So somebody snagged him?
Mm.
- Maybe.
- Maybe?
Look, maybe Jarrod did get got.
We're working every lead.
But you ask me, he just bailed.
And why would he do that?
Jarrod's had it rough.
Mom left years ago.
And his dad...
Well, let's just say Jarrod
"fell down the stairs a lot,"
you know what I mean.
Wait a second.
Mm. If you knew he was being
abused, why didn't you...
We tried. Trying to take a child
from his parents,
even if they're the worst people
in the world, not easy.
Did you talk to his old man?
Can't. Not really.
Guy stroked out
a couple years ago.
Breathes through a tube.
Guess who gets
to take care of him?
Can you imagine having
to spoon-feed
the guy that wailed on you
for all those years?
Everybody's got
a breaking point.
If Jarrod did blow town,
I wouldn't blame him.
You said that
he was with friends
the night Jarrod went missing.
Yeah, did any of them
say anything?
Nothing worth repeatin'.
Ain't he precious?
Uh-huh. Any idea where
we can find these friends?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Daryn Boston?
Agents Stark and Martell, FBI.
Hell.
Yeah, no, it's cool.
Medicinal purposes, right?
Uh... Yes?
Yeah.
We just, uh, wanted to talk
about the night
Jarrod Hayes went missing.
What about it?
Well, the sheriff says
you were with him.
Yeah, well, the sheriff
is a jackass, all right?
Look, he thinks Jarrod
just skipped town.
You don't?
I know he didn't.
Did you tell that to the cops?
Man, sheriff bishop's
not gonna believe me.
We got... History.
History?
Any time something happens
in this town,
he brings me in for questioning.
Why is that?
Why do you think?
Right.
Well, look, if you won't
tell the sheriff what you saw,
how 'bout you tell us?
Hey! Daryn!
Look,
I ran to save Jarrod, okay?
But...
No, no, no!
The monster, it got him.
Monster?
Black bill.
Hi! "Black bill" is a
local urban legend,
dates back more than a hundred years.
Warm it up?
Thank you.
A folklore story from 1907
that... that mentions
that...
Uh, back then, he was called
"black William."
So it looks like some time
between then and...
Dude, focus.
I am focused. Yeah, black bill.
What do you got?
All right, well,
he lives in the woods,
so he's like
a local Jersey devil.
And apparently, he has
the head of a goat.
A goat?
Like... Goat?
Yeah, a goat.
Well, maybe that's
what Daryn saw.
Unless you think he was lying.
Yeah. Be right back.
Mm, nah, I think he's a little
too freaked out to be lying.
So we got a, uh, goat dude with
a name like a pirate,
which is a little insane,
even for us.
And that bar is...
Super high.
So if it is real, what the hell is it?
I'm not sure.
I mean, there's tons
of human-animal hybrid lore
dating back all the way
to ancient Egypt.
Right, well, why don't you
figure out what the hell it is,
and I'll figure out a way
to kill it. Okay?
All right.
Right. Don't wait up.
What? I already figured
out a way to kill it.
How did you... you don't
even know what it is.
The Colt. Dusts anything.
Work smarter, Sammy, not harder.
Oh, don't do
the hot coffee thing.
Boy, this coffee is hot.
Kind of like...
Hi.
What's your name?
Carmen.
Sorry.
Damn it, Pete!
Daryn...
I don't wanna be
the bad guy here, but...
You clocked in late.
Again.
Yeah, and?
And you're really painting me
in a corner here, pal.
Look, I know... I know that you
and Jarrod, you were close.
And I liked him, too.
He was a-a valued employee
and he was a friend.
Really?
Yeah.
'Cause after you put him
on part-time,
he pretty much hated you.
Well, I would say that
that was his prerogative.
But you can't keep using him
as an excuse to blow off work.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
Daryn, Daryn.
One more thing.
You gotta lay off the reefer.
All right?
At least for tomorrow.
It's a big day.
Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Yeah. No, no, no.
I understand.
Yeah. Well...
Yeah, gotta go.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
- Mm.
- Order up.
Ahh.
Good night?
Awesome.
It was an awesome night.
So awesome.
Ah.
You gonna eat that?
Uh...
Guess not. Be my guest.
I mean, would it kill you
to order pancakes? Once?
Okay, fine. You...
No, no. No.
I'll deal.
How was your night?
Busy. A different kind
of a busy, but good.
Right. Books.
Anything on goat dude?
Yeah, little bit.
I have some idea
what we're dealing with.
Look at this.
It's a satyr...
Half man, half goat
from Greek mythology.
Oh, come on.
This guy's adorable.
He plays a freakin' flute.
Yeah, Dean. That's...
That's pan. It's his flute.
Mm.
So listen, satyrs are creatures
of uncontrollable lust.
They would lead people to
the woods for massive orgies.
Nice.
And when the fun was over,
the satyr would,
"feast upon the flesh of
his victims until his belly
was full to bursting with
their moist, slippery meat."
That's descriptive. Uh...
All right, what do we do?
Well, I was thinking that maybe
we could go talk to Daryn,
see if this is, indeed,
what he saw.
But?
But his mom told me
Daryn never made it home
from work last night.
No screwups, right?
Excuse me, sir.
Hi. Agents Stark and Martell,
FBI.
Uh, we're looking for
Daryn Boston.
Uh, Daryn?
Is he in trouble?
No, no, no, not at all. We...
We spoke with him yesterday.
Just wanna ask
a few follow-up questions.
I don't suppose he's around.
No, Daryn... Daryn didn't
show up for work today.
So when was the last time
you saw him?
Oh, last night.
Closed up.
Talked about our big day today.
What big day?
You see that walking clipboard
over there?
Yeah.
That's a health inspector.
He's trying to shut us down.
How come?
This place is spotless.
It cleans up pretty nice,
but our equipment,
it's a little out of date.
Can't you upgrade?
We would if we could.
Business isn't exactly booming.
We had to shut down half
the plant three months back.
Meanwhile, our owner would
rather play sheriff
than actually take care of business.
Wait a second.
You're telling me that
sheriff bishop owns this place?
Yeah. Barrett bishop, Jr.
Heir to the bishop meat empire.
His family, they've owned
this plant for... Forever.
Barry's inside. He's hopin'
to sweet talk the inspector.
You ask me, it's too little,
way too late.
Mr. Garfinkle.
Excuse me.
Sure.
So we roll into town,
look into a case,
talk to the local badge...
And then our one witness
goes missing.
Last place he was seen
owned by the sheriff.
Sound like a coincidence?
Oh.
You hungry? I'm hungry.
Excuse me, sheriff.
Agents.
What are you guys doin' here?
Well, we could ask you
the same thing,
except... Oh, right.
You run the joint.
Well,
my name's on the paperwork.
Pete handles the day to day.
Are you still trying
to chase down Jarrod Hayes?
Yeah, and, uh, now Daryn Boston.
Yeah. Seems to have
gone missing, too.
Jeez. First I've heard of it.
Yeah.
So tell us, what have you heard
about black bill?
I'm sorry.
Black bill.
Daryn told us he saw
black bill attack Jarrod Hayes.
He didn't wanna tell ya 'cause he
didn't think you'd believe him.
Well... well...
Yeah. He's right.
Look, 'round here,
parents tell their kids
not to go into the woods
or black bill will get 'em.
He's the bogeyman.
Everyone knows that
the bogeyman ain't real.
Sure about that? Seems like a lot
of people go missing in this town.
Yeah, one a year every year
up until '97.
Yeah. Okay.
I mean, people come to town,
they work in the plant
for a while,
then they get bored
and restless,
and they, you know, move on.
And Daryn?
You know, maybe Daryn thinks
he say black bill,
but let's be honest.
Kid was drunk, high, or both.
And I'll bet you
dollars to doughnuts,
Daryn's just holed up,
sleeping one off.
Hell, he's probably waking up
right now, safe and sound.
Hey!
Help, please!
Help!
Help me!
Well, sheriff's not acting
suspicious at all.
Right. Yeah, but how is he
connected to goat dude?
Now that's a good question.
Help!
Help! Help! Please!
Help me! Help! Help! Help!
Help! Aah!
Seriously? Dean?
After what we just saw,
how... how can you eat?
Grow up, Sam, okay?
Burger's beef, bacon's pig,
soylent green's people.
But this... this...
This is heaven.
Wow.
Right. Um, so, uh,
what's the word?
You find anything?
Mm.
Yeah, kind of.
So I cross-checked all the names
of the people who went missing
with the employee roster
at billhook meats.
And? Any more of the vics
work at the plant?
Try all of 'em.
All of 'em? Seriously?
So I guess that means,
safe to say that, uh,
black bill is definitely
connected to the plant?
Yeah.
Or the family that runs it.
Or both.
Well, maybe they just run
an evil petting zoo on the side.
So I, uh, spent some time
at the hall of records.
The bishops founded tomahawk.
Everything.
This is a company town.
If you lived here,
you worked at the plant.
The bishops owned all
the houses, all the businesses.
Or they did
until a few years ago.
Looks like the sheriff
has been selling off
all of their family property.
Uh, everything, really...
Hmm.
For the plant
and the family estate.
Wow. So who lives
at the Addams family house?
It's Mick.
Okay.
Tell him we're cool.
So creepy house?
Creepy house.
It's clear. Onward.
Now remember your orders.
By the time we leave,
Dr. Hess wants to know
everything
about our "friends"
the Winchesters...
Their allies, their habits.
How does Sam get his hair
so shiny?
How many ratty flannels
does Dean own?
So work quick, work quiet,
and leave no trace.
Oh, and apparently, Mick let
Sam and Dean get their hands
on the bloody Colt.
Find it, huh?
Looks empty.
Well, why don't we check
inside? Maybe we'll get lucky.
Dean.
I'd say we just got lucky.
Wow.
Hello?
Goat dude?
Why is it always the rich ones?
I mean, what, are they, like,
"croquet's all right."
But you know what'd be great?
"Murder."
Hiya, sheriff.
Talk.
This is not what it looks like.
Really?
'Cause it looks like
a straight up murder room to me.
Sheriff, what's goin' on?
Oh, you...
You won't believe me.
Try us.
We're pretty open mind.
My family, we...
Got a secret.
All the best ones do.
Is this about black bill?
No. I mean, yeah,
but... He's not real.
Black bill, he's... Us.
Come again?
Uh...
Growing up, my father'd tell me
stories about a monster.
Lived under our house
and made our family rich.
All we had to do was...
Was feed it.
Feed it what?
Blood.
Human blood.
My dad, his dad,
and all the way back,
they'd go out and grab
some poor son of a bitch,
bring 'em here and...
when they did it
they wore a mask.
Black bill...
We made him up.
So goat dude is just a dude?
Then who's the monster?
Moloch.
God of sacrifice.
What, I'm sorry. You... you have
a god living in your basement?
Yeah, one of my people way back,
they bound Moloch,
locked him away...
Starved him.
My family, that's what we did.
We let the god get
so hungry that
he'd do anything for blood.
Aah!
Moloch used his power
to make us rich.
After my father died in '97,
I put a stop to all of that.
Look, I couldn't...
I never killed anybody.
I just wanted to help people
to make up for all the bad
we've done.
I wanted...
To leave a legacy.
Well, aren't you just a peach?
So what happened to Moloch?
I kept him locked up.
Hoped he'd starve to death.
Locked up where?
It's empty.
What?
No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
Stay here. Keep an eye on him.
What? Dean, there could be
a god up there.
I'm cool.
Aah!
Dean?
Hey!
Hey! Open up!
Here. Here.
What are you doing? I'm trying
to track Dean's cellphone.
All right, got it. Let's go.
Just as I thought.
Can't see a damn thing.
Mm.
Hiya, Pete. Nice digs.
I didn't expect to see you
again, agent.
I went to the house
looking for my brother.
Brother?
Barry.
Different moms, same daddy.
Old man bishop, he, uh,
he had an eye for the ladies.
Everyone in town knew about it,
but didn't make a difference.
Barry grew up in the big house.
I grew up in a double wide.
Does that sound fair to you?
Honestly? Sounds like
a bad episode of "dynasty."
You got a lot of jokes.
Yeah, right now,
that's about all I got.
Right.
You know what I got?
A god.
Moloch.
Bingo!
With Barry giving away
the family fortune like that,
I had to get creative.
I went to the old house,
trying to get my hands on
anything I could sell.
But I found somethin' else.
Moloch.
He told me he'd make me rich.
He told me he'd solve
all my problems.
All I had to do was feed him.
And hell, I'm a bishop.
That's what we do, right?
Hunting people. Killing them.
The family business.
Moloch's been starved
for 20 years.
It's gonna take a few meals
for him to get his mojo goin',
but then...
Oh, we are back, baby.
Yeah. I'm savin' this town.
Well, I'll tell that
to Jarrod and Daryn.
Jarrod was a screwup.
He got what he deserved.
And Daryn? Well, sorry, bud,
but once he talked,
he had to go.
Loose ends, you know?
Loose ends. Come on!
Mm.
My jackass half-brother was
supposed to be the next meal,
but you'll do.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.
W... Pete, let's just
talk about this.
Listen...
Let's...
It'll be over soon.
Thanks for helpin' out!
What...
The sweep's complete, sir.
We've photographed
and catalogued every inch.
And the Colt?
I'm afraid not.
The Winchesters must have it.
Bugger.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Just one last thing.
Now then, I could use a pint.
Pete! Pete!
Dean?
Come on, you son of a bitch.
Huh.
Pete!
You have to stop.
Don't act like you care.
I gave you the plant.
Aw, because you knew it was
failing. What a bunch of crap.
That's what I get. I get that
my whole life! The crap!
Ah!
Not anymore.
I'm saving this town.
I'm the hero.
And you're dead.
Mm.
Colt.
Dusts anything.
Hey.
How you feelin'?
Like I just went 12 rounds
with a god.
So, you know... Normal.
Yeah.
You should go.
No, sheriff, uh,
we can help clean up.
No.
This... I'll take care of it.
It's on me.
This?
This is my legacy.
Hey.
Yep.
Next time you hear me say that
our family is messed up,
remind me that we could be
psycho goat people.
Yeah, that's true enough.
You know, I was...
Thinking about what bishop said.
About...
What do you think
our legacy's gonna be?
When we're gone, I mean,
after all the stuff we've done,
you think folks will
remember us?
You know, like,
a hundred years from now?
No.
Oh, that's nice.
Well, I mean...
Guys like us, we're not exactly
the type of people
they write about
in history books, you know?
Mm.
But the people we saved,
they're our legacy.
And they'll remember us
and then I guess...
We'll eventually fade away, too.
That's fine,
because we left the world better
than we found it, you know.
I wonder what's gonna happen
to this place.
After we're gone, you think
some hunter'll move in,
keep fightin' the fight?
Yeah, I hope so.
Yeah. Me, too.
What are you doin'?
Leaving our mark.
Here.
Hmm.
Guess we gotta call Mick,
debrief or whatever.
Right.
Hello, Winchester.
Ketch?
Where's Mick?
Oh, he didn't tell you?
He flew back to London
last night.
After all the...
Oh, unpleasantness
with Dagon and Renny, well...
Mick has a lot to answer for.
So for the time being,
you'll report to me.
Seriously?
I don't like it
any more than you do.
I'd much rather be
with your mother.
Hunting.
For... Chupacabra in Texas.
But for now,
I'm what you've got.
So... Wisconsin?
We fought a god and won.
Well done.
We'll be in touch.
So now we're reporting
to low rent Christian bale?
Seriously?
I don't like that guy.
He creeps me out.
Yeah.
And he rides the oldest, worst,
most unreliable bike.