Cass is chumming it up
with Crowley.
They're hunting Lucifer
together.
That's right...
One's an angel, one's a demon,
and apparently,
they solve crimes.
So Lucifer is now
the Master of Butt Rock.
He jumped into Vince Vincente.
The rock star? The douchebag.
Guy used to roll with
purple hair down to his butt
and a spiked codpiece.
- It was the '80s.
- What, are you defending him?
No. I mean, his third album
was kind of...
not horrible.
I hate you so much right now.
I've seen around all stripes
of Vince, all right?
Drunk Vince, depressed Vince,
megalomaniacal
"I'm a Golden God" Vince.
The Vince who threw me
through that door...
that wasn't him.
If you hear from him,
don't hesitate to call.
Okay, Agent... Beyonce©.
This vessel hopping's
getting old.
Just as I get used to
the limitations of one meatsack,
I gotta cut bait and jump
to the next flawed lump.
Then you want me to make
this vessel permanent?
Strong enough to hold you?
Does look good on me.
Festina!
Red, what did you do?
Sped up the decaying process,
my Lord.
Ginger bitch!
You can't destroy me!
Not yet, but I can send you
far, far away.
Try finding a new vessel at
the bottom of the bloody ocean.
Abi! Aah!
- Dark Lord.
- Apollyon.
Beelzebub.
As your humble servants,
we beseech thee.
We say your names as summonings.
Show thyself!
Serpent. Devil.
Lucifer! Show thyself!
Rain your splendor upon me.
Let me bathe
in your unholy wrath.
Drench me, Lucifer.
Cut it out, Gordy.
Dude, it's not funny.
Dude, you asked Lucifer
to drench you.
I didn't write it, okay?
It's a Satanist Society
of America-approved summoning.
I found it online.
Yeah, like you found
that "artifact."
Face it, Adam,
your "Satan feather,"
is faker than my stepmom's
Chinatown Fendi.
It's real. It's a rock.
Well, it's fossilized.
A feather from Lucifer's wing.
The seller excavated it
from one of his crypts.
Lucifer has "crypts."
Lucifer has "wings."
You're so frickin' dumb.
Actually...
I've been looking for that.
No way! No freakin'...
Aah!
Hiya.
You're...
I-it worked!
My summoning actually...
The only thing that
"summoned" me was this.
This vessel was already
wearing out,
and my trip under the sea
did not help.
With a little power up...
Hey.
Won't last long, but it'll do.
So, you and your... pal,
are you typical of my following
on Earth these days?
'Cause... oof.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't be Lucifer.
You're Vince Vincente.
My mom loves you.
You're... kinda famous.
Kinda famous.
"Twerking." Booyah.
Seriously?
What?
So I've been trying to dig up info
on the British Men of Letters,
keeping an eye out for cases,
and you've been goofing off
with a game
that went out of style
five years ago?
I don't think Mom's quite ready
for Snapchat.
You're playing against Mom?
Yeah.
The same Mom that didn't know
what a cellphone was
a month ago?
Yeah.
Doesn't exactly seem like
a fair fight.
You were saying?
So how she been lately?
She's good. You know,
she... she's dealing.
Hey, Cass.
Hello, Dean.
You still living out
an '80s buddy comedy
with Crowley?
Unfortunately.
Any news on Lucifer?
Actually, yes. Look at the news.
One sec.
No way.
So this is from today.
We're here in front
of DeathSiren Records...
No friggin' way.
With Vince Vincente.
Yes, it's, it's great
having the band
back together again.
In the studio, feeling pumped.
Haven't felt this fired up
in ages.
A lot of people saying
that your style of rock
could never make a comeback
in today's landscape.
What do you say to them?
Go to hell.
- Tell me that's not Lucifer.
- We don't know.
Cass, I-I thought you said
Rowena got some licks in.
Shouldn't he have burned through
his vessel by now?
Yeah, but we don't know.
We don't...
Hello, boys. Long time.
We team up to save the world,
and then bupkis.
You don't call, you don't write.
Yeah, we don't care.
Crowley... Lucifer.
Lucifer. Think about it.
Of all the extinct rock acts,
Ladyheart are
the most Paleolithic.
A major label sponsored
comeback in 2016
for those dinosaurs?
It doesn't feel like
a wholly natural
turn of events, does it?
Maybe Lucifer found a way
to heal his vessel.
Yeah, but still...
I mean, what the hell?
He's in L.A. I'll see you there.
Yeah.
Where are you going?
I know a guy.
Hello, Russell.
Brother Crowley.
One moment. Just let me
tie this off real quick.
All right!
So... what brings you to
the City of... Angels?
You know this is my city.
Ha!
What's with all this
Maharishi crap?
I moved to the Westside
last year.
Started daily meditation,
yoga, green juice.
Helps to keep the ego
and the anger in check.
But enough about me.
How you been?
Health? Family?
Hell?
Doesn't matter, don't care,
and been better.
Well, good news. Good news.
I got a couple of quality
up-and-comers for you.
Thirsty young talent.
Souls ripe for the taking.
You have been pleased with
our... arrangement so far?
As punch.
A soul's a soul.
But there is a certain prestige
to owning a Swift or a Drake.
You like that?
It's a gift from Dre.
This whole Vince Vincente
comeback thing...
It's a joke, right? No.
Deadly serious, my friend.
We've raided, repackaged,
and resold
everything else from our past.
Why not give hair metal
another shot?
Yeah, okay. I doubted it, too,
but Vince came to me
with a killer pitch.
The original Ladyheart lineup
reunited.
Back in the day, those cats
sold, like, 10 mil.
So did Hootie & the Blowfish.
And I'll bring them back, too.
I know Ladyheart might be
a punch line,
but the band's got
off-the-chart name recognition.
And just talking to Vince,
he seemed different, you know?
Energized. Reborn.
Lit.
Like a whole new man.
Exactly.
All right. 450 miles to L.A.
Land of gridlock, Botox,
overtaxing, underachieving,
smell of sweaty desperation.
I mean, you can't breathe.
The beaches are toxic.
You got dudes in skinny jeans
wearing sunglasses inside.
Image-obsessed narcissists.
I do like the yoga pants,
though.
When was the last time
we were in L.A.?
About 10 years ago,
doing a vengeful spirit?
Man, that seems like
forever ago. Doesn't it?
Hey.
Tryin' to talk to you here.
What? You...
What are you listenin' to?
Podcast. Why?
All right, well...
I need something to
keep me awake, so crank it up.
I mean, it's a history podcast.
Well, I like history, you know?
Gladiators and outlaws, pirates.
Hell, we're driving
a piece of history right here.
N-not that kind of history.
This is a...
it's a podcast on the history
of the Protestant Reformation.
A multipart exploration
of each of Martin Luther's
95 theses.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Sam. Dude.
Hair rock? Really?
It's not hair... Come on.
It's not hair rock, Dean.
It's hard rock.
It's legitimate hard rock.
Wow.
Don't judge book by its cover.
Yeah, or a dude by his,
rainbow wig and leopard prints.
Rainbow wig? What?
You know what?
I'm done apologizing.
Lucifer possessed
Vince Vincente.
This is Vince Vincente's music,
so listening to it is research.
No. No. As a matter of fact...
Study up, Dean.
I don't wanna listen to it.
You like it. No. No. No, no. No.
It'll grow on ya.
Your tweet about
Ladyheart's reunion
already has
over a million engagements.
When you were solo, you were
lucky to have 300 "likes."
The band's teaser track
on SoundCloud?
500K streams in 4 hours.
Buzzfeed just posted
a listicle...
"10 Things You Need to Know
About Ladyheart."
This is good, Vince.
This is really good.
Great. It's happening, Vince.
I mean, we are gonna
be famous again.
Vince.
So, we actually gonna
record or what?
Not really feelin' it.
Come on, man.
The band's back together.
We've got an actual
recording budget.
Dude... let's make some music.
Music.
What are the fans saying
about me right now?
They're tweeting about your drinks with
Pam Anderson last night,
speculating if you two
are rekindling.
And they're debating whether
Vince Vincente
is bae, nay, or daddy.
What the hell does that
even mean?
It means it's not about
the music.
It never really was.
You know, rock's not the reason.
It's just an excuse...
to worship, to adore.
See, humans have always
been desperate
to put someone
or something above them.
And let's face it,
God ain't cuttin' it these days.
It takes a Kim Kardashian,
a whatever Justin Bieber is.
A me.
They're enjoying the ride.
So should you.
What?
It's good.
It's vegetable water.
Sam, Dean.
Hey.
You consider switching up
your duds there?
Bit stiff for this town.
He could be an agent
or something.
Yeah, maybe a third-tier agent.
At least I don't look like
a lumberjack.
Okay, enough.
Guys, where's Crowley?
He said he'd meet us here.
Frankly, I appreciate the break.
It's been weeks,
and he's been right there,
just talking and talking
and talking.
It's relentless.
Don't listen to him.
Feathers and I are
all but inseparable now.
You find anything? Yes.
Vince Vincente
is riding with the Devil.
Okay, so what now?
I suggest we go
check out his room.
Vince is scheduled to be
in the studio all day,
so we're covered.
How'd you get the card?
This is L.A.
I know a lot of people.
Well, looks like there
was some kind of a fight.
Yeah. Some kind.
Look at this.
Rock star biographies.
Like, all of them,
from Aerosmith to ZZ Top.
It's like he's studying
how to become famous.
Well, so what, Lucifer's a dork?
That's good to know.
Look at this... "The seeds
of a ripe dragon fruit"
"drizzled with exactly
1 ounce of Acacia honey,
prepared in a ceramic bowl...
No plastic."
What is this spell?
It's breakfast.
It's Vince's rider.
I've seen worse. I don't get it.
Lucifer could be taking over
Heaven and Hell right now,
and instead, he's trying to
act out some rock god fantasy?
Yeah. Who wouldn't?
I found something.
What is that?
It appears to be a human tooth
pulled out by the root.
Can I ask you something?
Why are you spending time
with me?
You ignored me for years,
not that I blamed you.
I was a fool
not to recognize
such sweet devotion.
Talk to me, Roseleen.
Tell me about...
me.
You're Vince.
Vince Vincente.
And I knew I was in love with
you the moment I saw you.
I was 16, just a normal kid
growing up in Arcadia.
Arcadia. Sounds beautiful.
I was watching
"Headbanger's Ball"
and the "Bloody Messiah"
video came on.
And I...
It was your voice.
And your hair. And your eyes.
It was everything.
You were everything.
And even when people
made fun of me...
Younger girls at work,
shredding on
my Ladyheart tattoos
and saying you're a joke...
I never stopped loving you.
And I never will.
How much do you love me?
What would you do to show me?
Anything.
Anything?
Would you bleed?
Then bleed.
Mrs. Greenfield has lost
a lot of blood
and there'll be no fixing
those scars, but she's stable.
And she cut herself?
She carved his name
into her chest.
"Vince Vincente."
Didn't skip a letter.
And she cut deep.
Thanks, Doctor.
Well, again, what the hell?
I'll go talk to her.
No. No, no, no, you won't.
Cass, stay here.
Keep an eye on him.
Well...
together again.
Yay.
We wanna understand
what happened,
but in order for us to do that,
we need you to talk.
Roseleen, did Vince force you
to do this?
No.
Vince didn't.
He wouldn't have to.
I wanted to,
to show him, to make him happy.
You ever stop and wonder
what kind of sicko gets happy
off of watching somebody
melonball their own flesh?
Don't talk about Vince
like that.
He had a reason, a good reason.
He must have.
I'm sure he can explain
everything.
If I could just see him...
I need to get to the show.
Please!
Okay, we're building an aura
of mystery and exclusivity
with tonight's show...
Undisclosed location,
small, select audience.
It's as much about who doesn't
get a ticket as who does.
This could push
your social media profile
to Kimye levels.
Who gets the tickets?
It's an online lottery
of local fans,
but it'll tend towards
the Ladyheart diehards.
They'll be more engaged...
I've had my fill of
the diehards.
They already love me.
Religion, celebrity, Twitter...
It's all the same rules.
If you're not gaining followers,
you're losing followers.
I want a different crowd
tonight. New fans.
Look, getting a new audience
is great
for social media visibility,
which is great for overall buzz,
but they're fickle.
They don't spend any money
on music. They have no loyalty.
Good luck translating their attention
to album or ticket sales.
I don't care.
I want fresh blood.
Got it.
So the show is tonight?
That's what she said.
Can Lucifer even sing
or play an instrument?
I doubt they offer
Intro to Guitar in the cage.
Like it matters.
What Lucifer made that woman do
has got nothing to do
with music.
It's about devotion. Come again?
You little people
wouldn't understand,
but I've been a king.
Having people look at you
like you're everything,
knowing that once they buy in,
you can make them do anything,
it's intoxicating.
Well, that's super creepy.
Okay, so this concert,
all these people, what is...
What is Lucifer planning to do?
Nothing good.
Is Rowena... Dear Mother says
that once we catch Lucifer,
she'll show, no sooner.
Well, without Rowena,
we're outgunned.
With her, we're outgunned.
It doesn't matter, guys.
This is our shot.
We just gotta find out
where he's playing tonight.
All right, let's get to work.
A mystery to even me.
Though, even if I did know,
I probably wouldn't tell you.
You'd threaten
our very lucrative partnership
for one over-the-hill,
bad dye job rock dinosaur?
I'm smelling money with Vince,
bruh.
This is business, Crowley.
It's nothing personal.
No, believe me,
it's personal.
Tommy.
Guys, I'll meet you inside.
Agent. What are you
doing here, man?
Investigating Vince,
same as before.
You hear what happened
to Roseleen?
Yeah, that was, it was awful.
But, I mean, come on, man,
she cut herself, right?
It wasn't like...
You know that's not
the whole truth.
You know Vince isn't Vince.
We're the brothers
that rock together.
We're kind of like
the American Oasis.
Ew. But with synths.
Yeah, right, so, you know,
we're... we're hip.
Exactly.
Who plays what? I'm on keys.
He's on the drums. Guitar.
Drums and guitar.
I pretty much do it all.
We saw online that you represent
Vince Vincente.
We were kind of hoping you could do
for us what you've done for him.
Sorry.
I took this meeting 'cause you
looked hot in your pics,
but I am not feeling this.
Okay, you know what? We're not
actually here for a meeting.
Vince's show tonight...
Where is it?
Who are you guys?
Look, you must've noticed,
Vince is different.
I... don't know!
You're messing with hellfire,
Russell.
You will find out
where that show is.
You will tell me
or I will end you.
Brigitta, get me another
green juice in here.
Namaste.
Where's the show, Tommy?
Man, I don't know what the hell's
going on with Vince, all right?
All the royalties on our hits
dried up years ago.
I got two daughters in college.
I know what I told you
and I know what I saw, but...
And you don't care
who pays the price?
Sorry.
Vince gives me the skeeves,
but he's a playing client.
No, he's the Devil.
Yeah, like, literally.
I'm in P.R.
I've worked for sexists,
racists, even politicians.
My job is making saints
out of devils.
No way I'm threatening
my reputation
by working against
his interests.
So you need to take a step back
or I start screaming.
And in a crowded place
like this?
Girl like me,
two guys like you...
Guess what happens next?
Buh-bye.
And you said you put the fear
in Russell.
I thought I had.
These yoga types.
Just when you think
you've harshed their mellow...
Yeah, well, I've been looking
everywhere online,
and...
no one's linked the venue yet.
Seriously? What?
Dude. Shut up.
Cass.
Anything?
No.
So we couldn't flip
a single member of Vince's team.
Even with the threat
of mass murder,
these SoCal douchebags
won't do the right thing.
Welcome to Los Angeles.
So what happens now?
I've never seen so many
crying emojis in my life.
The people who didn't get in,
they're rending garments
all over Twitter.
Gossip blogs, social media,
they're on fire speculating
about the secret reunion show.
And the winners? Thrilled.
Be more thrilled if we had
new music to sell.
What?
Well, Vince was a no-show
at the studio.
Again.
The muse...
Guess she took a powder.
Relax, Russell.
Tonight's show?
It's gonna kill.
I took a chance on you, Vince.
An aging, well-past-his-prime
buttrocker.
You will get in line.
Or?
Or I take it all back.
Whoa.
Check your contract for it.
You don't do what I say,
I can bury Ladyheart.
I own you.
Do you?
Yeah.
What's happening here?
Hey, man.
Vince, what are you doing?
Hey! Vince, stop!
Hey! Vince!
Hey.
Well...
See you all inside.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
Vince!
Who's ready to have fun?
Vince, I love you!
Hey! Vince!
Thank you!
I love you, Vince! I quit.
Guys.
Tommy's still not answering.
Well, he got us here.
That's what matters.
Enochian handcuffs.
That's your move?
They held me. You're not him.
We have no sure bets here, okay?
Anything that we use is gonna
be like popping BBs.
Great pep talk. Go, team.
Guys, we're here to do more than
just take a shot at Lucifer.
We are?
Yes, we need to save
the people inside, too.
I'll take Lucifer.
He's my responsibility.
No, he's not.
He's all of our responsibility.
Well, the only way you'll clear
that crowd without drawing fire
is if he's otherwise engaged.
Engaged in what, Cass?
Killing you?
Cass, you'll last...
three minutes tops.
Then I'll buy you three minutes.
Make it four.
What? I help.
Have you seen that crowd?
Man, I have not seen
an audience this hyped
since we headlined
Monsters of Rock in '91, man.
No.
And the girls?
Perfect age. Ooh.
Tommy?
You okay?
Our fearless leader.
How you feelin'
about the show, Tommy?
Yeah. Me, too.
The nerves.
Whoops!
Guess I should've practiced
before tonight.
Or, you know, ever.
Who are you?
Who I was...
well, that doesn't matter.
Who I am?
Well, I'm Vince Vincente,
rock god.
And after careful deliberation,
I've decided to cut
the dead weight.
I'm going solo.
Castiel.
Aah!
Took you long enough.
Did you bring the rest
of the Little Rascals?
Just me.
Spanky.
Sorry.
Hey, you guys...
You guys smell smoke?
One, two, three! Vince! Vince!
Did not take you
for the martyr type, Crowley.
I'm really not.
I just hate you that much.
What are you doing, Lucifer?
You mean nothing
to those kids out there.
You think they'd draw blood
for you?
By choice?
Well...
I thought I'd at least ask.
And if they won't give it up
by choice,
maybe I'll just take it. Why?
Because it's fun.
Because I can.
And because being Lucifer?
So much Judeo-Christian baggage.
But Vince? He's famous.
Everybody loves him.
And I need love.
I had a really jacked childhood.
Hey, Tommy.
You think this is fun?
I wouldn't expect you
to understand.
I was inside you.
I know what a weak, duty-bound...
pleasureless dullard you are.
Aah!
And you.
Bad doggy. Sit!
No, seriously, I-I-I think
I smell smoke, everyone.
Sure you're not having a stroke?
Hey, I'm serious.
We need to get out of here.
- Step off, dad.
- Hey, listen to me. We've got to go, okay?
What's your
problem, man? Get off me!
We gotta... All right, yeah.
Get this guy off me!
No, listen to me, okay? Listen,
we gotta get out of here.
What's your problem, old man?
Okay. All right, yeah.
Okay. Look, we gotta get
everybody out of here.
Fire!
Clever girls.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Stick around
for the after-party.
What a crowd!
I love you, Vince!
Look at all those fresh,
new faces.
Everyone excited?
Yeah, you should be!
Tonight's not gonna be
a typical show.
Tonight, you're gonna see
and feel things
you never saw or felt before.
Yeah!
Things might get
a little bit messy.
Screw it.
He's got a gun!
We gotta go! We gotta go!
Go, go! Come on, guys!
No, no. No, no, no.
Go!
Go.
Nuh.
Hey, assbutt.
Hi, Dean.
Sam.
Enjoy the show?
Guys, you know I could
end you all
with a snap of my finger?
Why would I do that
when you can't
do anything...
to me?
Why are you doing this?
Why?
You and God made up.
You forgave him.
What would he think?
I'm not especially interested
in his opinion.
Dear old dad, he finally
apologized for abandoning me.
And what's the very next thing
he does?
He ditches me.
And you, too, by the way.
And rides off into the sunset
with Auntie Amara.
He needed my help,
and he'd say anything to get it.
His words, your words,
they mean nothing.
Don't you get it?
This is all meaningless.
Heaven, Hell,
this world.
If it ever meant anything,
that moment is past.
Nothing down here but a bunch
of hopeless distraction addicts,
so filled with emptiness,
so desperate
to fill up the void...
they don't mind being served
another stale rerun
of a rerun of a rerun.
You know what my plan is?
I don't have one.
I'm just gonna keep on smashing
Daddy's already broken toys
and make you watch.
Yeah?
'Cause it kinda looks like
you're falling apart.
Yeah, you got a little
something, right there.
I mean, face it, rock is dead.
What can I say?
Kicking your ass
took a lot out of me.
But don't worry.
Onward and upward.
How you feelin'?
I'm not dead.
Well, I gotta hand it to you.
You said you were gonna draw
Lucifer's fire
and you drew some serious fire.
It was a grand success.
Well, we didn't catch Lucifer,
but we did save the crowd,
so I'm gonna call that a win.
I wouldn't.
Vince Vincente is dead.
We never even hoped to save him.
And, yes, I know,
the third album...
No, he was still a person,
and he meant something
to a lot of people.
And Lucifer just took all that
and just twisted all that up
and snuffed it out.
Lucifer was bad enough
when he had a plan, a motive.
Now he's just having fun.
I mean, how many people
died tonight?
Them, this, it's all on us.
We let him out.
We're not winning.
We're just losing slow.
And you heard what he said.
Onwards and upwards.
He's gone big.
And he'll go bigger.
And we will stop him.
We will.
It's what we do, man.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man