I've been tortured
by the Devil himself.
What can you do to me?
[ Screams ]
She's British.
Men of letters.
Aren't we supposed to be
on the same team?
Did you know it's possible
to die from pain?
[ Gun cocks ]
Get away from my boys.
- Mom?
- Yeah.
[ Grunting ]
Mom? A hunter?
Dean: You were good at this,
weren't you?
Mary: Very.
Hunters...
no matter how good they are,
they all end up the same way.
I never wanted this
for you and Sam.
So the kid had ectoplasm
leaking out his ear?
It's gotta be
ghost possession.
[ Grunts ]
Uhh!
They get angry enough,
they can take control
of a person's body.
Vince, together, we can heal
your sister Wendy.
We gotta put Lucifer
back in the cage.
You're the only one
that can do it.
[ Groans ]
Seriously?
I've heard of people coming back
from the dead before.
But to actually do it,
after 30 years? [ Beep ]
I just have a lot of blanks
to fill in.
For me, having you here
fills in the biggest blank.
?
[ Indistinct conversations ]
“Played out.” You're kidding.
That place was great.
Another avocado toast?
Please.
Yeah, but avocado toast
with quail egg? Genius.
[ Chuckles ]
How many stars you
giving 'em?
- Two.
- Four.
You realize our ratings are just
gonna cancel each other out.
[ Scoffs ]
Should've bought here
when we had the chance.
I mean, new restos,
new stores --
New prices.
Neighborhood's been picked clean
by flippers - [ Chuckles ]
and condo developers.
[ Baby cries ]
Did you hear that?
Yeah, it came from
that house over there.
[ Baby crying ]
Yeah, but who'd want
to live in there?
- Squatters or crackheads?
- With a baby?
[ Baby wailing ]
Call 9-1-1.
What?
Do it!
Okay, okay.
[ Wailing continues ]
Female dispatcher:
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
Hi, there's a baby in distress
in an abandoned house at...
[ Mouths words ] Nat!
[ Door creaking ]
[ Crying stops ]
Hello?
[ Door closes ]
[ Baby cries ]
[ Crying resumes ]
[ Floorboard creaks ]
?
[ Crying continues ]
[ Gasps ]
What?
[ Electricity crackles ]
Something touched my arm.
I mean, it's something --
- We have to get out of here now.
- Okay.
[ Door slams ]
[ Crying resumes ]
[ Screams ]
? Supernatural 12x03 ?
The Foundry
Original Air Date on October 27, 201
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ Sighs heavily ]
[ Chuckles ]
Castiel.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm always up.
Angels don't need sleep.
Wish I had that problem.
[ Sighs ] Anyway...
I think I'll go try again.
Wish me luck.
Luck.
Castiel?
After you left heaven,
when did it
start to feel like...
like you fit, like you...
belonged here?
Well, I'm still not sure
I do.
[ Whispers ] Yeah.
Mary...
You do belong here.
Goodnight, Castiel.
[ Retreating footsteps ]
?
All right,
so what have you found on
Her Majesty's Secret Suckbags?
[ Sighs ]
Well, I may have turned
the bunker upside down
looking for any reference
whatsoever
to the British Men of Letters,
and all I found
was this letter
tucked into an old ledger,
uh, from
the “London Chapterhouse.”
Okay, well,
that's something.
Yeah, uh...
not so much.
[ Scoffs ]
Awesome.
Morning, sunshine.
Some coffee?
No, thank you. I have to go.
Cass?
Cass, wait up.
Hey.
Wait a second.
Where you off to?
Cleveland, Ohio.
For what?
I think I may have a lead
on Lucifer.
I found a police report
in Cleveland
about a man whose eyes flared
a glowing red.
It could be Lucifer
in a new body.
All right. Yeah,
that sounds like something.
We should check it out.
No.
The Devil is free
because of me.
Finding him
is my responsibility.
Cass, you're gonna want
some backup on this.
If it is him,
I will call you.
In the meantime,
I think you're needed here.
The hell was that about?
[ Clicks tongue ] Mom.
What are you talking about?
Mom's fine.
Sure. I heard her walking around
all night last night.
I mean, don't we think she seems
a bit...withdrawn?
You know, shaky?
Of course she's shaky.
She hasn't been on
this planet
since Jane Fonda was wearing
leg warmers.
Look, all she needs is
a little R&R.
You know,
some good family time...
[ Clicks tongue ]
she'll be aces.
Yeah.
Hey.
Hey. Hi.
Hey. Morning.
Ooh.
Oh, we can fry some more.
That's -- that's probably cold
by now, Mom.
It's bacon.
Wow. We are so related.
[ Chuckling ]
Did you cut your hair?
I'm gonna keep it short
if I'm gonna go out on a hunt,
you know?
Why give the bad guys
the advantage
of long, pullable hair, right?
[ Laughs ] Wow.
I've been trying to tell Sam
that for years.
[ Sighs ]
Did you say, uh,
“going out on a hunt”?
I found a case.
I thought you were
still struggling
with even the idea
of the Internet?
[ Chuckles ] I had Dean pick up
some newspapers
when he went into town.
Whoa, whoa. I...
You didn't tell me
you were looking for a case.
[ Mouth full ] I wasn't.
I just...found one.
Minnesota.
Two dead, locked room.
Victims had put in a call
about a crying baby.
But the place was empty.
The only thing at the scene
was their bodies.
Been five days,
and the coroner still hasn't
put out a cause of death.
Seemed fishy.
It's probably nothing.
I just thought I might...
get out there,
stretch my legs.
I-I thought you weren't
down to hunt in the first place.
Well, things change, right?
Family hunting trip.
Sure.
All right.
Meet at the car in 10.
[ Sighs ]
[ Clears throat ]
What about the R&R?
W--
Look, man, Cass healed
your s'mores foot, all right?
I got Baby back to mint.
We're road ready.
And if Mom wants to hunt,
I say we hunt.
You're gonna...
[ Sighs deeply ]
Nice bike.
[ Bell dings ]
[ Car door opens, closes ]
There's a lot of things that
have gone to seed
since you were here,
but the variety
in snack food flavors
is not one of them.
We got your teriyaki jerky,
we got your sriracha,
and we got your chili lime,
which...
is my personal favorite.
Let's give chili lime
a whirl.
Eh?
It's...good.
Artificial,
kinda tingly.
That's how you know
it's working.
[ Engine starts ]
Steppenwolf:
? I never want to die ?
Hey.
? Born to be wild ?
[ Turns up volume ]
?
? Born to be wild ?
[ Tires squeal ]
[ Sighs ] Look...
I been around all stripes
of Vince, all right?
Drunk Vince,
depressed Vince,
megalomaniacal
“I'm a Golden God” Vince.
The Vince who threw me
through that door...
that wasn't him.
?
And it wasn't just his eyes,
man.
I-I mean, the strength.
He was like --
He was like
an MMA fighter.
Hell, he was like 20.
If you hear from him,
don't hesitate to call.
Okay, Agent...Beyonc??
?
[ Indistinct conversations ]
I guess that makes me
Agent Jay Z.
Agent Shirley Partridge, out of
the Minneapolis field office.
These are my partners,
Agent Cassidy and Agent Bonaduce.
This is a local case.
Why would the FBI be interest--
They're new.
Wanted their first case
to have training wheels.
Mm.
We wanted to have a look
at the bodies.
Now, you haven't filed
a report.
Has there been any problem
determining the cause of death?
Problem? No. No, no, no.
I figured out the cause.
Just doesn't make
any damn sense.
Is this a burn?
Frostbite. Yeah.
Both victims died
of acute hypothermia...
in a 65-degree room.
When I opened them up,
their hearts were literally --
and I mean literally --
frozen.
Wanna tell me how to present
that to the public?
Or to their families?
So much for training wheels,
huh?
Bumping into each other,
working the same leads.
What are the odds, Cassie?
Fate brought us together.
I'm not interested.
Why not?
We made a somewhat effective
team against Amara.
It's been months,
I mean months,
since we last tried
to kill each other.
We both got
very, very good reasons
to want Lucifer dead.
Besides...
...while you were gabbing
with Vince's second fiddle,
I was ransacking his room.
Found these.
Postcards from
his beloved sister Wendy.
Oh, lookie here.
An address and everything.
Worth a look.
[ Door creaking ]
[ EMF meters warbling ]
Dean: You sure you got
the swing of that thing?
For the third time, yes.
Dean, it's analog.
I'm good.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Right.
[ Warbling continues ]
[ Warbles loudly ]
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Warbling continues ]
[ Switch clicks,
warbling stops ]
Dean: Mom, we got something
over here.
[ Door slams ]
Mary: Sam?
Mom?
Dean?
[ Pounds on door ]
[ Door rattles ]
Mom?
[ Pounding on door ]
Mom.
Sam! Dean!
[ Grunting ]
Mom!
Hold on, Mom!
We're coming!
Mom, get away from the door.
Ah!
Mom.
Ah.
Mom, you're hurt.
Let's go. Come on. Come on.
[ Crying ]
?
[ Door opens ]
Okay.
Ready to head out?
Go knock on some doors?
Doors?
Yeah.
Talk to the neighbors,
hit up the Hall of Records,
work the...case?
We still do that, right?
Sometimes.
But the, uh, the Internet has
made a lot of that legwork...
Obsolete.
I mean, I'm already in
the St. Paul Police Department
database.
Anything?
Yeah, a lot.
I got police reports filed
from 2004...
[ Tapping key ]
uh, '91, '89, '85, '78.
All deaths. All kids.
Looks like it started
with this girl here.
Elizabeth Moriarty.
You got all of that from that.
Yeah.
Mom...
Don't worry about it.
We'll teach you how
to do this.
[ Truck door closes ]
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Clears throat ]
?
[ Sighs heavily ]
Hello.
I'm Agent Beyonc?,
and this is my, um...
my partner, Agent Zee.
Um, we wanted to ask you
a few questions
about your bro...
[ Door slams ]
...ther.
Do you think that happens
to Sam and Dean?
Oh, all the time.
Vinny, please call me.
I got two federal agents
asking for you.
Don't know what was with you
yesterday,
but you're in trouble.
How right you are, Wendy.
[ Telephone beeps ]
Ah.
So...
Vince was here.
[ Door closes ]
Yesterday.
Odd.
She's been recently healed.
Is that so?
Let me guess -- your brother
got you up and walking again.
And how are you enjoying
the use of those legs?
You know, the gift he gave you,
I can take away like --
The thing that healed you,
that wasn't your brother.
Something...something else,
something old and evil.
I...I think a part of you
knows that.
We don't want to hurt Vince.
We wanna help him.
He showed up
out of the blue
and he fixed me like
a miracle.
But he did it cold, like...
it was nothing to him.
Like he was running an errand.
Barely said a word.
And then he just took off
with his groupie friend.
His groupie friend?
Red-headed broad.
Didn't say much.
So Vince's cabin
in Sagamore Hills...
Apparently, all of his greatest
records were written there --
“Serpentine,”
“Theater of Mercy”...
I should've known there was something
you weren't telling me.
Rowena?
So mother and I had
an unfortunate,
if not rather embarrassing,
run-in with Lucifer.
You're just mad because
you're only my second choice
for a Lucifer-hunt team-up.
No, actually,
I think it's sweet.
I thought your motivation was
ambition and revenge,
but now I know you just wanna
save your mother.
It's not about saving her.
Lucifer has made off
with a colossally powerful witch
who, by the way,
is the only person alive
who can slam him back
in the cage.
He will either kill her,
control her,
or she will offer her services
to the biggest bad in the town
in order to save her neck,
like she always does.
Do any of those sound
like particularly good
outcomes to you?
You got any beauty spells
locked up
in that witchy brain
of yours?
Huh?
Thought this one would last
a bit longer
before going
all Keith Richards on me.
[ Sighs ]
This vessel hopping's
getting old.
Just as I get used to
the limitations of one meatsack,
I gotta cut bait and jump
to the next flawed lump.
Then you want me to make
this vessel permanent?
Strong enough to hold you?
Does look good on me.
[ Chuckles nervously ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Grunts ]
Show me what you got, Red. Huh?
I-I-I'd help, I would,
but I don't have
the Book of the Damned.
I lost it.
You know damned well
where you put it.
Did you see what I did there?
[ Gasps ]
“Damned.”
Besides, you don't need
the book.
Clever girl like you
must have it all up here
by now.
And if I refuse?
I snap your neck again.
Only this time,
I'll rip your head
clean off afterwards.
Hmm?
?
Mylings?
Yeah, from Scandinavian lore.
Uh, children's spirits,
vengeful ones.
“Their cries to help
lure adults to their death.”
Anything about frozen hearts?
Uh, no, not yet,
but this is just from
old, incomplete folk accounts.
We all know the lore
isn't always 100%.
Hmm.
Mm, maybe, but...
All I know is, that little boy
who grabbed me,
I... [ Sighs ]
He didn't wanna hurt me.
He was scared.
Yeah, um...
it must've felt that way,
but, Mom,
the victims were all lured
to their death by a baby's cry.
Uh, the spirit marked Natalia
right before she was killed,
the same way the spirit
marked you.
I mean, if we hadn't
gotten there in time...
Well, look, we know
all the kids' names, right?
We know that they're all
buried locally,
so I say
we salt and burn 'em.
That's the safe bet.
Agreed.
All right.
Well, let's do that.
[ Distorted voice ] Sammy!
[ Sam crying ]
Help me.
Mom?
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, fine.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
May-- maybe, uh,
you should stay here.
Here.
Call if you need us.
Okay.
All right?
Back soon.
[ Sighs ]
[ Dialing ]
Man: Ramsey County
Register of Deeds.
Hello, I'm looking for
contact information
for the last owner of
1781 Chamberlin Street, please.
Uh...Okay, can't you just use
the website like everyone else?
I'm not everyone else.
Please?
And...thank you.
Woman: Lucas...
[ Inhales deeply ]
was so cold.
I still don't understand
what happened.
I checked on him just a minute
before I found him.
How'd he get so cold
so fast?
Gosh, sorry for going on
like this.
Mary: Oh, don't apologize.
What did Lucas look like?
Well, he was so handsome.
Blond hair
and these crystal blue eyes.
Anything else?
He had a scar on his cheek.
From the neighbors' dog.
Thank you, Cheryl.
I'm sorry for dredging
all this up again.
Oh, it's okay.
Actually, it's kinda nice.
No one talks on the phone
anymore, you know?
I've noticed.
Thank you again.
[ Beep ]
?
[ Match strikes ]
[ Flames whoosh ]
Grim work.
Yeah.
You know,
I'm worried about Mom.
Why?
You're not?
She's back.
I mean, yeah, she's still
working out the kinks.
We're all still working out
the kinks.
But, I mean,
can't we, for once,
just not turn everything
into a problem?
You know, can we, for once,
just have one good thing?
Mom's not a thing.
Okay.
Look, I'm happy, too, Dean.
I am. I'm overjoyed.
But...there's something
about her.
I mean, something's going on
with her.
Yeah, she's adjusting.
No, she's struggling.
I mean, she's trying
to bury herself in hunting
to avoid dealing.
And how do you know that?
Years of personal experience.
I don't know, man. Uh...
Like mother, like sons.
?
[ Sighs ]
Mom?
Weapons bag is missing.
?
[ Door creaks ]
[ Whoosh ]
Lucas.
That's your name, isn't it?
[ Loud thud ]
I talked to your mommy.
She misses you so much.
?
[ Door rattles ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Wood cracks, thuds ]
[ Iron bar thuds ]
Lucas, why did you
bring me here?
Help...us.
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Ring ]
Hello?
Mom, where are you?
I'm at the Chamberlin house,
on a hunch.
Yeah, we salted and burned
all the remains.
Yeah. Didn't work.
[ Static crackling ] Okay, get out of
the house and wait for us.
What? Hello?
Mom?
Hello?
Let's go.
Ash of the Hawthorn Tree.
The pattern?
A Druidic glyph.
I'm using a hybrid spell
of my own devise --
Book of the Damned
and Celtic magic.
Should give your vessel
the resiliency and strength
of the mightiest tree.
Oh.
There's a woody joke
in there somewhere.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
Let's get back to that nagging
little word -- “should.”
It's uncharted territory.
I-I can't promise
the spell with last forever.
There's no known magic
for that.
[ Inhales sharply ]
But it will last.
The final step.
?
Permission to speak,
Dark Lord?
If -- when the spell succeeds
and you are restored
to your full glory...
Will I just kill you?
[ Voice breaks ] I can be
of value beyond this spell.
We'll see.
Thank you, my Liege.
Festina.
[ Gasps ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Red, what did you do?
Sped up the decaying process,
my Lord.
[ Chuckles ] You thought
Keith Richards was bad?
Try Iggy Pop.
Oh, decapitation is
far too merciful for you,
Ginger Bitch!
Aah!
No!
[ Grunts ]
[ Objects clatter ]
You can't destroy me!
Not yet,
but I can send you
far, far away.
Try finding a new vessel at
the bottom of the bloody ocean.
Abi!
Aah!
[ Exhales sharply ]
What's keeping you here?
Him.
?
[ Ground rumbling,
structure rattling ]
[ Exhales ]
You're the father
of that little girl.
You killed them all,
all those ch--
[ Thud ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Shotgun thuds ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Ice crackling ]
[ Gasps loudly ]
Dean: Mom!
[ Whoosh ]
[ Groans, gasping ]
Mom. Hey. Come on.
Uhh!
Dean?
She's possessed.
?
[ Growls ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Distorted voice] My house.
[ Groans ]
My children.
[ Grunts ]
Forever.
[ Groans, chokes ]
[ Ice crackling ]
[ Strained voice ]
Mom?
You can fight this.
[ Crackling continues ]
[ Panting ]
Mom?
[ Dean groans ]
Aah!
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasping ]
Sam: Mom.
[ Grunting ] The basement.
Go!
?
[ Switch clicks ]
[ Grunting ]
Mom?
[ Distorted voice ] Mommy's gone.
[ Cocks shotgun ]
Don't. Don't make me.
[ Shotgun clatters ]
[ Growls ]
[ Grunts ] Aah!
Aah!
I got you, Mom.
[ Match strikes ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Screams ]
[ Panting ]
Aah!
[ Screaming ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Whooshing ]
?
[ Whoosh ]
[ Crow cowing ]
?
If you're looking for Lucifer,
you just missed him.
Cup of tea?
Until you forced me to get
back in the game,
I'd tried to forget
about Lucifer.
I loathe him,
and I loathe that I had
any part
in letting him out
of the pit he belongs in.
So you'll help us, then?
Good God, no.
[ Chuckles ]
That whole
FBI pantsuit look?
Not my hex bag.
But if you get Lucifer cornered
and find yourself in need,
I'm there.
[ Sighs ] Well, you gonna
take a shower? Take a nap?
You really went through it
today.
No, I'm okay.
And, um...
listen, apologies if, uh,
me and Sam hijacked
or sidelined you in any way.
I mean, this was your case,
you know?
And...well, you kicked ass.
[ Chuckles ] Again.
I kicked ass?
[ Scoffs ]
You saved me. I --
Yeah, but you were right.
You know, those kids
were innocent.
I mean, hell, we didn't even
know what Moriarty's deal was.
I do.
When he possessed me,
I saw...
I felt it.
All of it.
When Hugo lost his child,
he went mad.
Buried himself alive
in his basement
and walled himself in
and starved to death.
Damn.
But when new families
moved in,
families with children,
he coveted those children.
So he took them. Killed them.
And somehow that bound
their spirits to his.
What's where he got
his power.
He was so...greedy.
Twisted.
Mom, it's okay. All right?
You're home now.
No.
[ Sighs ] I'm not.
I miss John.
I miss my boys.
We're right here, Mom.
I know. In my head.
But I'm still mourning them
as I knew them.
My baby Sam.
My little boy Dean.
Just feels like yesterday,
we were together in heaven,
and now...
I'm here, and John is gone,
and they're gone.
And every moment
I spend with you reminds me
every moment I lost with them.
And I thought hunting, working,
would clear my head.
Mom...
[ Sighs heavily ]
w-what are you trying
to say?
I have to go.
I'm sorry.
I'm so...so sorry.
I just need a little time.
?
I love you.
I love you both.
?
[ Door opens, creaks ]
[ Door closes ]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man