You know, Claire,
you go down this path, our path,
it's not a long life.
I solemnly swear
not to hunt like a dumbass.
Claire, do your homework before
you do anything stupid, okay?
And we're here
if you need us, any time.
“Werewolves that are turned
up to four generations
“from pureblood are less feral
and can transform
before, during,
and after the lunar cycle”.
I mean,
werewolves are badass.
The old men want
the Winchesters,
so I made a play for Dean,
and it was working until
your operation went sideways.
I'm in.
You're changing the world,
and I wanna be a part of it.
Dean, because of Mick
and his guys,
the Alpha Vampire is dead.
What do you want me to say?
Do I like it? No.
Do I trust them?
Hell, no.
We work with people
we don't trust all the time.
So if you wanna give this
a shot, then fine.
“Are you calling me a liar?
Seriously?”
?
Yeah. Seriously.
You're so busted.
You are beyond lame,
you know that?
Let's just go back.
Please?
I'll get you in.
Ever had a Moscow Mule?
A Moscow Mule?
Will you just, for once,
act your age?
Says the guy who doesn't even
have his own car.
Stop hounding Mom about
buying us a car, all right?
She's doing the best
she can.
Two more years,
I am so gone.
Hold up!
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
They're called animals.
Let's just go back into town.
No, Hayden, we're going.
Have you, like, never seen
a horror movie?
Two kids, dark road,
creepy noise in the woods?
We keep walking...
and boom!
You are such a drama queen.
All right,
there's nothing there.
But I --
No, fine. I'll prove it.
?
Sucker.
See?
Told you.
Hayden!
- Hayden...
- No.
Oh, my God. Hay.
Help!
Hayden, Hayden, Hayden, Hayden.
Aah!
? Supernatural 12x16 ?
Ladies Drink Free
Original Air Date on March 20, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
All right, that's it.
I'm waiting in the car.
Dean, dude, wait a second.
No. You know what?
Getting jobs from these dicks
is one thing,
but I didn't sign up for
this reporting for duty crap,
especially when they're late.
Sorry I'm late.
My report to the home office
ran long.
We've had our hands full
since...
Well, best not to dwell
on that.
Wow. That is some
world-class repression.
You are British.
We prefer to call it
a stiff upper lip.
Okay, okay. Enough.
Mick, what's the deal
with the bat signal?
There was an incident
in Wisconsin.
“Animal attack.”
A girl named Hayden Foster's
in the hospital,
and her brother lost his heart.
Looks like a werewolf.
Well, they don't usually
leave behind survivors.
Freak probably got spooked
before it could finish the job.
Well, perhaps.
But it usually takes
more than a fright
to put your average werewolf
off his supper.
Oh, you'd know that, would you?
Actually, I would.
I did extensive research
into lycanthropy at Kendricks.
Kendricks?
The Kendricks School.
It's where
the British Men of Letters
train their operatives.
It's like our --
Hogwarts?
Exactly.
Kendricks is the largest
collection of occult lore
in the world.
Cool.
So when it comes to werewolves,
I'm not entirely ignorant.
For example, we know
that last night's attack
didn't happen on a full moon.
Therefore, we're looking
for a pureblood.
You think?
It's like a milk run to me.
Then you don't mind
if I tag along?
Mick, um...
Listen, I-I don't think...
I don't think it's really
your kind of thing.
Oh, no, maybe it should be.
I had the best team,
but most of us,
we were thinkers, not fighters.
And let's be honest --
your and your mum,
you're the only reason
I'm still alive.
So now you wanna be like us?
No.
I just want to be ready
for whatever's next.
Dude, he is dead weight,
and you know it.
Look, Mick's inexperienced,
sure.
But these people have
some serious knowledge.
So? Dude, what we do, you can't
learn this crap in a book.
You put on a flannel, you pick
up a gun, you go out there.
Either you get good fast
or you get dead faster.
We're working
with these people now
and -- and we're getting wins.
We're saving people.
The better they are,
the better we are.
Look, Mick held his own
with the Alpha.
Why not give him a shot?
Maybe he'll come in handy.
And what if
he gets himself killed?
I heard that.
Good.
If he's coming,
you're babysitting him.
?
In Luther's 27th thesis,
the word “jingle” is
an obvious nod
to a canny 15th century monk...
Had to let him listen
to his podcast, huh?
Dude, it's educational.
And besides, I've been wanting
to listen to this one.
You know,
monks like Martin Luther
are among the earliest Hunters.
He even wrote parts
of that book you're holding.
What? This lore dates back
to the 16th century?
Yeah. Well, in Europe,
everything's old.
Though we do have
our fair share of new tricks
for dealing with wolves --
sulfate gas,
silver nitrate lethal injection.
Take a handful of silver bullets
over any of that fancy crap.
Yes, well,
thanks to that “fancy crap,”
Britain's last werewolf outbreak
was in the '20s.
We rooted them out,
bitten and pureblood alike.
Wait a second.
You killed them all?
Even the ones that weren't
hurting anyone?
Sorry?
I mean, werewolves aren't
like most monsters.
Some can control it. I mean,
we -- we have a buddy got bit.
Nothing but beef hearts
ever since.
And you trust him?
Well, killing is a fundamental
need for werewolves.
And monsters don't just stop
being monsters.
Well, Garth did.
Oh, turn here.
?
This place, uh,
seems a little...
Shabby? Yeah.
Three stars was the best
I could do.
Least our bean counters
will be happy.
Booked us all suites.
Wait, you...
We're in separate rooms?
Yeah, of course.
You say three stars?
Yeah.
So we're talking fresh towels,
little baby shampoos?
Uh-huh.
And I believe there's a pool.
Welcome, sir. Mm-hmm.
Cheers, mate.
Get the bags.
?
Thanks.
Man. Those pillows, right?
The little chocolates
that they put on?
I mean, I'm ruined, Sam.
Those limey sons of bitches
ruined me.
I even took a swim
this morning.
You brought a swimsuit?
No.
Ugh.
What'd you get up to?
I read through more
of Mick's lore books.
Really? Wow. Those three stars
are wasted on you.
Anyways, listen to this.
It's crazy.
So apparently, back in the '30s,
they were working on
this treatment for werewolves.
This, like, blood therapy.
Plasma therapy.
Useless, I'm afraid.
So how were
your accommodations, lads?
I've had better nights sleep
in my baby.
Get in. Let's go.
Not gonna give him
the satisfaction.
Wait, wait. Let us.
Talking to a grieving family,
it's tougher than you think.
Oh, I'm a quick study.
Well, good for you.
Okay, stay here, keep watch.
Anything comes up...
I don't know, whistle.
Ms. Foster?
Sorry to bother you.
Agent McVie.
This is my partner,
Agent Fleetwood.
Um, we'd like to ask
your daughter a few questions.
She's sleeping.
We'll be quick. Promise.
I said no.
Hayden needs
her rest. She's...
Good morning.
And how is our patient today?
I'm sorry. Who are you?
Dr. Buckingham. Hayden's
attending doctor, Dr. Markum,
asked me to look in on her.
Um, would it be okay
to ask you just to step outside
for a moment?
I, um...Of course, Doctor.
Sure.
Thank you.
Here. Please.
No problem.
I'm sorry,
about all that.
Oh, please.
After what you've been through,
you have no reason to apologize.
Where's my mom?
Your mum's just outside.
Just gonna take a quick look,
make sure you're okay.
Brave girl.
I don't know what happened.
It was so fast.
You've had quite a shock.
I just -- I don't even know what
my kids were doing out there.
You know, Hayden was supposed
to be sleeping
at her friend's house,
and -- and Ben...
I just keep thinking
this is a nightmare, you know?
That I'm gonna wake up.
Okay.
I'm just glad
the FBI is here,
not those crazies.
Crazies?
Bigfoot truthers.
Calling, sending e-mails.
They thought Hayden was...
Like I said. Crazy.
Huh.
Some girl even came by here
saying she was from
the Fish and Wildlife Service.
Barely as old as Hayden.
I mean, like I'm gonna
buy that.
You remember
what she looked like?
Yeah. Blonde.
Bad attitude.
I actually -- I have her card
right here.
Good.
Ah.
Ohh. No.
Okay.
You're okay.
You relax, okay?
Oh.
Is she...
Wound's healing up nicely.
Nothing too serious.
Oh, that's so --
Thank you so much.
Pleasure.
Excuse me.
Doc?
So?
Was Hayden bit?
No. No, she's a lucky girl.
Good. What about, uh,
Fish and Wildlife Service?
Think it's another hunter?
Young, blonde, pissed off.
Sound like anybody we know?
?
“Campus is nice.”
Oh.
Hello? Uh, this is
Agent Beatrice Quimby.
Oh, thank God. There's a bear.
It's the size
of a freakin' tank!
I think
it wants my pic-a-nic basket!
Mm-hmm.
Hi, Dean.
So Fish and Wildlife?
Really?
Claire, what are you
doing here?
Same as you. Werewolf case.
Now. Beers all around.
Who are you?
Oh. Mick Davies.
Men of Letters. British.
Long story. And, like,
“Downton Abbey” boring, so...
No. Unh-unh.
Okay. Anyway...
I've been on this a day.
And guess what?
The girl, Hayden?
Her story about what happened
the night of the attack?
One big lie.
Her mom said the same thing.
Where was she?
She was at the local dive bar,
gettin' trashed.
I tracked her phone
and asked around and...
Bartenders love me.
It's a gift.
Right. You get anything else?
The guy I talked to
was a scumbag.
Tribal tat, motorcycle,
grabby.
Grabby?
I'm a big girl. I handled it.
Right.
Think I'm gonna call it a night.
D-dude, it's 5:30.
Yeah, but my report's due
at 6:00 sharp.
All work, no play.
Nice meeting ya.
So your foreign exchange student
is totally lame.
Yeah.
He's Sam's best friend.
They're like nerd soul mates.
Anyway, why are you alone?
Jody's busy
with sheriff stuff.
And she said to call if
I found anything.
So you called her?
You called first.
And she's great, by the way.
And so is Alex.
So should we go to
the morgue?
Take it easy, Clarice.
Morgue's closed.
By the way, when's the last time
you had a hot meal
that didn't come from
a-a Gas-n-Sip microwave?
Not that there's
anything wrong with that.
It's been a while.
Well...
Go nuts. It's on, uh,
Harry Potter.
Cool.
?
I'm sorry.
No!
Thanks for coming by
so quickly.
Ms. Foster gave us
your number.
You have any idea
what happened to her?
Autopsy's tomorrow,
but it could be
an arterial embolism,
cardiac arrest.
A heart attack at her age?
It gets weirder.
When we admitted her, she had
defensive wounds to her arms.
Now...
they're gone.
Just, uh, give me a second.
Sure.
Mm.
Okay...what the hell?
You checked Hayden out.
Did you notice anything weird?
No, but, uh, the girl could've
had internal injuries or...
But somehow, her external
injuries all healed? No way.
This is almost like, uh...
You know,
what if she turned?
What, like,
“wolfed out” turned?
Explains the whole
Wolverine healing factor thing.
Yeah, no,
but that'd be crazy
because that means
she would've been bit.
And Mick here says that
that didn't happen.
Right, Mick?
Uh...
Uh, no, not -- not that I saw.
Are you 100%?
Unless I made a mistake.
Hell of a mistake.
Dean...
No, I told you we shouldn't
have dragged him along.
I told you!
Don't!
Whatever got Hayden is
still out there.
Okay.
So let's say
the night of the attack,
wolf ices big bro,
chomps down on a little sis,
and then...poof, vanishes?
Does that make any sense?
Maybe he let her go.
On purpose? Why?
Perhaps he didn't want her dead.
He wanted her turned.
Right. Which means
this wasn't random.
Which means it would've been
somebody who knew her.
Friends, family.
Or someone from the bar.
Okay. All right, Sam,
you and Claire, you go talk
to the girl that she was
supposed to be crashing with,
and me and amateur hour will hit
the bar, see what shakes loose.
?
So... really?
Things are good?
Yeah. They're awesome.
Really? You sure?
Dude, take the yes.
Okay.
So you wait here.
What?
Sam, no offense,
but who do you think
the kids are gonna
wanna talk to?
Me, or some old skeezer?
Exactly.
Be right back.
Skeezer?
Dean,
what happened back there...
my mistake,
it won't happen again.
Better not.
Problem?
The old carpal tunnel.
Well, allow me,
your lordship.
Thanks.
Howdy.
Agent Strummer.
This is Agent Vai.
Uh, hi.
Do you recognize this girl?
She was here
three nights ago.
Yeah. Not really.
Yeah, I'd lie if I served
underage girls, too.
Look, man, I...
- I really need this job.
- I...
She started coming in
a few weeks ago
after Conner got hired.
Conner?
Yeah, the other bartender.
They're having a thing.
What kind of a thing?
Ask him.
Hi, Conner.
Oh. Nice ink.
So you like high school girls,
do you? Hmm?
You get older, they stay
the same age. Is that it?
That's not how it was.
Oh, so you weren't dating
Hayden Foster?
Dating? No, I let her in from
time to time.
She is stupid hot. Okay?
But that's it. I swear.
And the night she got attacked,
did you let her in
that night, too?
Look, I don't know
what happened.
I was behind the bar
the whole night.
I didn't even see her leave.
Hmm.
And then what'd you do?
Guess I went home.
You guess?
Well, it's a simple question,
Conner.
I ask what you were doing,
then you tell me.
For instance, what were
you doing last night?
?
Me?
Yeah.
Oh, I was writing my report.
?
And then?
Well, I watched an episode
of “The Great British Bake Off”
and went to bed.
Ha! See?
Simple.
I went home, man.
And I didn't do anything
to that girl, okay?
Yeah. Well, we'll see.
Oh, one more thing. Um...
Did you happen to meet a, uh,
blonde girl the other night?
About yay high. Feisty?
Yeah, yeah.
Said she was Hayden's cousin.
Crazy bitch
threw a beer at me.
Huh. Well, from what I heard,
you earned it.
What are you, her dad?
Dude, come on. Girls like that?
Yeah.
You ever touch her again,
I'll break your face.
Nice work in there.
Thank you.
Yeah, that alibi --
I almost bought it.
Sorry?
See, here's the thing
about 16-year-old girls,
especially 16-year-old
freshly minted werewolf girls --
they don't just die.
And you've been
acting sketchy all day.
Oh, I don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh!
What did you do to her?
I did what needed
to be done.
And that means?
Last night,
I injected her with
silver nitrate.
So you killed her?
Well, she attacked me.
She tore up my shoulder.
And...
I had orders.
You had a choice.
Did I?
Killing monsters is
what we do.
Or maybe palling around with
demons and witches,
you've forgotten.
Don't tell me how to do my job.
Well, then do it.
You think it's that simple, huh?
I really do.
Yeah?
I used to think
the same thing.
Well, here's a little tip.
Things aren't just
black and white out here.
All you have is a case
in front of you, like Hayden.
A few months ago, there was
this kid, this psychic.
She was killing people, but she
didn't mean to hurt anyone.
She was being abused.
So we gave her
a second chance
because it was
the right thing to do.
Well...
that's your luxury.
We have a code.
Thank you, Mr. Ketch.
Well, now Hayden's mom,
she gets to bury two kids
instead of one,
thanks to you
and thanks to your code.
Nice work.
I was kidding before,
but you really do look
like a creeper.
Funny. How'd it go?
BFF found. Beans spilled.
Hayden was hooking up with
this older guy on the DL,
and she was really into him,
but he was a total stalker.
Texting constantly,
ultra possessive.
Skeeved her friend out so much
she narc'd to Hayden's brother.
Guess that explains why
he was there.
I did good, right?
Claire, why does Jody think
you're in Madison
looking at colleges?
You called her?
Did you tell?
No. Not yet.
But why are you lying to her?
Look, I-I know, okay?
I know how much I owe Jody.
But we tried
the whole hunting thing,
and I just ended up
sitting in the car
while she does everything.
Guess she's taking it slow.
She wants me to be normal,
go to nursing school
like Alex.
Did she actually say that?
She doesn't have to.
I'm better off on my own.
This way, everybody's happy.
Claire, Jody's not gonna
be happy when she finds out.
And if something happened
to you...
I'm careful!
You need to tell her
the truth.
You know what?
Screw you.
I'm so sick of you guys
dive-bombing my life,
pretending like you care.
We do care.
Then stop treating me
like a stupid kid!
Then stop acting like one.
?
Claire...
? ...everything ?
? Opportunities for eternity ?
? And I could belong
to the night ?
? Then your eyes, your eyes ?
? I can see in your eyes ?
? Your eyes ?
? Everything in your eyes ?
? You make me wanna die ?
? I'll never be good enough ?
? ...you love
will burn up in the night ?
? Look inside your eyes ?
? You make me wanna die ?
Oh, my...
Oh!
?
Aah!
Claire. Claire.
Hey. Hey. Claire.
Hey, it's me. It's me.
It's me. I gotcha. I gotcha.
I gotcha. You're safe.
?
We gotta cool her off.
She's burning up.
No. No, no, keep her warm.
Back off.
Shut up.
Look, I understand
you're angry --
Mick, you killed a kid.
We're not angry. We're done!
How long have I got until...
Sometimes it takes a full moon.
Sometimes it just takes time.
Hey.
Hey, listen to me.
Look, nobody said this was
gonna be easy, okay?
But you can live with this.
No way.
Hey. Look, so you -- you have
to stay locked up
a few nights
out of the month, okay?
The rest of the time,
you're you.
Unless I break out.
Maybe some people can
control this,
but I can barely
keep it together on a good day.
So if there's any chance
I could hurt Jody
or Alex...
or anyone...
I'd rather die.
Claire, there may be
another way.
There's -- there's the blood
therapy that you talk about.
I told you, it doesn't work.
It says right here, uh,
1 out of 9 test subjects
was cured.
Cured?
Yes.
That study was on mice.
You want to tell me what
the hell he's talking about?
We experimented with the blood
of sire werewolves.
And we found
it was possible to reverse
the early stages of
lycanthropy...in rodents.
So you never tested on humans?
Once.
And?
The subject died in agony.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Maybe second time's a charm.
Hey, no, no.
You don't get a vote in this.
It's my life.
I get all the votes.
Sam, you wanna
back me up here?
It's her life.
I bet you think this is
a great solution. Hmm?
It works, or she dies.
Either way,
one less monster, right?
I don't think there's
any great solutions here.
Dean...
Please? I can't.
All right.
If we do this -- if...
how do we get it done?
We need blood, live blood,
from the werewolf that bit her.
Good. Great. Who we lookin' at?
Tribal tat.
Back at the bar.
We shook him down about Claire,
and right after, she gets bit.
That's not a coincidence.
Timeline fits,
connection to both victims.
Then we should go.
The full moon rises
in less than an hour.
And if she turns and feeds,
our cheery success rate
drops to zero.
Let's go.
Not you.
You stay with her.
You trust him?
Mick's a smart guy.
So when I say that
if anything happens to her,
and I mean anything...
You'll kill me.
Like I said, smart.
Sam, if you're not back...
We'll be back.
?
Yo.
All right, don't move,
don't move. It's silver.
He's human.
Let's give it time.
Aah! It burns!
?
You don't understand.
It's happening!
Give it to me!
No.
Then you do it, please!
It's happening!
And you don't understand
how this feels!
I know a man who would
shoot you right now
without a moment's thought.
And every instinct I have
says he's right...
that I ought to do my duty.
But...
But my instincts haven't
been so grand of late.
Sit down.
Now okay, here's what
we're gonna do.
Firstly, we're gonna
restrain you, right?
For my protection. Okay?
And then...
then we're gonna sedate you.
Also for my protection.
With any luck, when you wake up,
this will all be over.
If I wake up.
I gotta call Jody.
She's gonna be
so mad at me.
Claire, get back!
Aah!
Claire?
Where is she?
The wolf, he took her.
What did I tell you?!
I tried to stop him, okay?
I can find her.
I put a tracker
in her pocket.
You planted a bug on her?
Look, you can kill me later,
after we find Claire.
?
I know this is sudden,
but you and your friends, you
should've let me have Hayden.
She was miserable here.
She...
We had big plans.
Yeah? Was that before or after
you bit her?
I had to know if she could
survive the change.
Not everyone does.
See?
It hurts at first,
but eventually,
it's like the best drug ever
times a thousand.
Right. Eat me, Teen Wolf.
It's not like
I want to do this.
My pack, we were happy.
We didn't hurt anyone.
And then hunters with weapons
that I've never seen before,
they show up and...
Ah!
...take out 20 of us,
just like that.
The ones that made it,
we split up,
but we weren't meant
to live like that.
A werewolf needs his pack.
You'll see, I'm a nice guy.
Yeah? You know who says
they're a nice guy?
Clingy, insecure bitches
with mommy issues.
That's just the change
talking.
You'll feel better once you eat.
Try it. You'll like it.
As soon as I saw you, I knew...
you're just like me.
Alone.
Wrong.
I have a family,
and they love me.
Aah!
Claire?
Claire.
Hey, all right. Easy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa! Oh!
Mick, hurry!
Aah!
Ah! Sorry, kid.
?
Move, move, move, move, move.
Claire. Claire.
Okay, Claire, it's us.
You know us.
That thing ready yet?
It's ready. It's ready.
Go, go, go.
She wanted this, right?
Oh, yeah.
Ah!
Gonna get some air.
Claire?
Dean.
?
You guys look like crap.
All right, give this to you.
That girl is a walking miracle.
Yes, she is.
Listen, uh...thanks for
the win back there.
Yeah.
So we're good?
Not quite,
but we'll give you
a second chance.
Just don't mess it up.
There won't be a third.
Okay.
Hey. How you feeling?
Honestly?
I'm sort of craving
a Milk-Bone right now.
Look, um...
what I said before...
you guys are here
when I need you
and that's all that matters.
You gonna tell Jody
what happened?
I don't know.
Well, whatever you decide,
we got your back.
Leave
a message after the tone.
Hey.
It's me, Claire.
Okay, um, here it goes.
I've been hunting. Alone.
And I know it's not
what you want to hear.
And I know it sounds scary.
It scares me, too, sometimes,
but...
this is something
I have to do on my own.
Just for a little while.
But I'm ready,
and I never would've been
if it wasn't for you
being my mother.
Well, I better go. Um...
Tell Alex she better not
touch my stuff.
I love you guys.
? I'm a wild one ?
? Ooh, yeah, I'm a wild one ?
? Oh, yeah,
I'm a wild one ?
? Gotta break it loose,
gonna keep 'em movin' wild ?
? Gonna keep a-swingin', baby,
I'm a real wild child ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man