You must be one of us.
One of who?
One of the psychics.
I mean, there are others
like us out there and we're all
a part of something.
We both have
psychic abilities.
Sam, Max is a monster.
He's already killed two people,
now he's gunning for a third.
I think I'm here to help you.
[ Crying ] No one can help me.
[ Gunshot ]
There are people out there,
like me.
We all have some kind
of ability.
Ellen: Ability?
- Yeah.
Psychic ability.
These people out there,
these psychics,
they dangerous?
Not all of them.
But some are.
Some are very dangerous.
Who knows how many of 'em
are really out there?
Castiel,
after you left Heaven,
when did it start to feel
like...like you fit,
like you belonged here?
You do belong here.
It's just gonna take me
a second to catch up.
I can handle myself.
You were good at this, weren't you?
Very.
Mom, what are you trying
to say?
I have to go.
I just need a little time.
I love you both.
?
[ Church bell tolling ]
[ Parishioners
whispering indistinctly ]
[ Church bell
continues tolling ]
[ Crying ]
[ Squishing ]
[ Whimpers, gasps ]
?
[ Whimpers ]
[ Screams ]
[ Whip cracks ]
[ Gasps, crying ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Whip cracks ]
[ Sobs ]
Olivia?
[ Gasps ]
[ Sobs ]
Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw!
[ Whip cracks ]
[ Crying ]
Prok yaw-thi...
[ Sobbing ]
Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw!
?
? Supernatural 12x04 ?
American Nightmare
Original Air Date on October
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ Church bell tolling ]
Sam: Father Valdecantos?
I'm Father Penn
of the Dubuque Archdiocese.
This is --
Father DeNiro.
We're here to talk about
Olivia Sanchez.
I'm not talking about that
anymore.
You sure were chatty
with the press and the cops.
"Priest Claims Demons
Walk Among Us."
Boy, that's quite
the headline grabber.
I said I'm not talking about --
No, we heard you.
Don't care.
You'll think I'm lying,
like my bishop, like everyone.
But I knew Olivia.
She was a good person.
I watched her get flayed alive
by some invisible force.
That was the devil's work.
I've been told the church
doesn't want us
talking like that anymore --
too old fashioned.
But I know what I saw.
You see any black smoke?
What?
We don't think you're lying.
We just wanna ask you
a few questions, that's all.
Um...no. No smoke.
What about sulfur? Did you
smell, uh, rotten eggs?
No.
You told people that she was
speaking in tongues?
Yes.
It sounded like Hebrew.
Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw.
Sounds more like Aramaic
than Hebrew.
Hmm.
What kind of priests are you?
The old-fashioned kind.
[ Retreating footsteps ]
Thanks.
Dean: So no sulfur
means no demon.
You think the padre's right?
We talking about Lucifer here?
Little small-time for him.
I don't know.
Maybe a rogue angel?
Dean.
Yeah. Uh, I'll make a call.
Wait, wait, wait. What?
Are you serious?
Yes, Cass, that's weird.
It's really, really weird.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
All right, yeah. Um...
Thanks for the heads up.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Footsteps approaching ]
[ Horn honks in distance ]
Now I'm a 13-year-old girl.
Hey. So what's the word?
Cass have anything?
Yeah. Uh...
[ Clears throat ]
Well, good news, uh,
there's nothing on angel radio,
and Heaven's still on lockdown,
so rogue angel is out.
Bad news?
Cass is chumming it up
with Crowley.
Hmm.
They're hunting Lucifer
together.
That's right --
one's an angel, one's a demon,
and apparently,
they solve crimes.
Are they having any luck?
Kind of.
So Lucifer, the Lord of Evil,
Angel of Light,
is now
the Master of Butt Rock.
He jumped
into Vince Vincente.
The rock star?
The douchebag.
Guy used to roll with
purple hair down to his butt
and a spiked codpiece.
It -- it was the '80s.
The what?
Uh...
It was the '80s.
[ Chuckles ]
What, are you defending him?
No, I'm not... [ Sighs ]
I mean, his third album
was kind of...
not horrible.
I hate you so much right now.
Anyway, he's the Devil now?
Well, I mean, he was always
kind of the Devil,
but, yeah, now it's official.
Where is he?
Rowena blasted him
to the bottom of the ocean.
Why?
I don't know.
Why do you love Vince Vincente?
I don't love --
[ Clears throat ]
Anyways, uh,
looked at those words.
I was right.
They are Aramaic.
"Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw."
It means,
"Save me, oh, God."
Save me from what?
?
Body's right there, Agents.
I can get her prepped to your --
Dean: That's great, Carl.
Uh...
We'll take it from here.
Oh? Okay.
Um, but...it's a weird'un.
If you guys need
anything at all, I'm --
We won't. We won't. Thank you.
Are...you sure?
Yep.
Oh, okay.
Li  Le, uh, tough on Carl,
don't you think?
Ah, he's a big boy.
He can take it.
You okay?
Peachy.
You sure?
'Cause ever since Mom left,
you've been a little, uh...
[ Inhales deeply ] cranky.
Cranky, huh?
Yeah.
I mean,
to the priest, to Carl.
Heck, on the way here, you
wouldn't even make a pit stop.
So now your tiny bladder
is my problem?
I'm just saying --
Olivia Sanchez.
The body was found.
It had deep cuts on her back
as though she'd been whipped.
Holes punctured through
her hands and her feet,
and pinprick wounds around
the top of her skull.
What's that sound like to you?
Stigmata.
Bingo.
Gets weirder.
How?
"The victim's skull was filled
with a goopy mush."
That Carl paints
quite a picture, doesn't he?
All right.
What can do all that?
I got nothing.
Me neither.
Well, maybe we should focus
more on the case
and less on
the Dr. Phil crap.
?
[ Door opens ]
It's just over here.
This is --
was Olivia's office.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Sam: So...what is it now?
It's...kinda mine now.
So is that yours?
It's for positive energy.
I'm a Wiccan.
Cool.
So how well
did you know Olivia?
She was my boss.
Is it true
what they're saying,
that she, you know...
killed herself?
Well, we're working on that.
Um, now the day she died,
was Olivia acting strange?
Not really. I mean...
She was getting headaches.
Bad ones, like super migraines.
But we all knew
she was working too hard.
She have any enemies?
Somebody who held a grudge,
maybe wanted to do her harm?
[ Sighs ] Yeah.
[ Inhales deeply ]
I mean, Olivia was great,
but this is
Child Protective Services.
We get threats all the time.
From who?
Everyone.
You don't make a lot of friends
when sometimes
what's best for a family
is to split them up.
Right. Um, yeah,
can we see Olivia's case files?
Of course.
They're right over here.
Well, that was easy.
What?
What? The Wicca'd Witch
of the West in there.
Little Miss Positive Energy
Wanted a bigger office,
did a little hoodoo...
Boom.
I say we put a witch-killing cap
in her ass, call it a day.
Yeah, but we checked the church
and Olivia's house.
We didn't exactly find
any hex bags.
So she covered her tracks.
But we're not looking
at a witch.
I'm not saying it's not Beth.
I'm -- I'm just saying
we need proof.
And look, if it's her,
I'll shoot her myself.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, I'm definitely
shooting her.
[ Closes trunk ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Door creaks ]
[ Train whistle blows
in distance ]
?
[ Whip cracks ]
Aah!
Oh! Aah!
Ah! Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw!
[ Whip cracking ]
[ Screaming ]
Aah!
[ Grunts ]
[ Music continues playing ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
Dean: Coroner says
signs of stigmata
with a side of scrambled brains,
just like Olivia.
Great.
Did you find anything?
Maybe. Kid delivered groceries
all over town,
so I checked his route
against Olivia's case files.
And?
Got a match.
Dean:
Tell us about the Petersons.
They're weird.
How weird?
All the way. That family,
they're, like,
off the charts religious.
Old, old Testament.
I'm talking no cars,
no electricity, no nothing.
Kids are homeschooled.
Family like that, we try
to keep an eye on them, but...
[ Taps keys ]
[ Sighs ]
But what, Beth?
Their oldest, Magda --
a few years ago,
she got pneumonia,
and the family wouldn't let
a doctor treat her.
They said whatever happened
was God's will.
What happened?
She died.
All right. Um, thank you.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
So?
Weird, creepy, off the grid,
"Children of the Corn" people?
Yeah, I'm in.
[ Engine starts ]
?
[ Engine turns off ]
[ Doors creak ]
Guess we're walking
from here.
?
[ Grunting ]
Whoa. When they cut the cord,
they really cut the cord.
Yeah, no kidding.
How fast you think their buggy
goes? Like, top speed?
Hey, about yesterday...
Oh, all right.
Next time you gotta take a leak,
I'll pull over.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about you and Mom.
What about her?
What, she took some cash,
she took a cellphone she doesn't answer,
and she bailed on us.
I mean, think about
what she's going through.
After everything, she probably
just needs some space.
We've been there.
We've both had times
where we needed time apart.
And we both came back.
You don't think she's going to?
I don't know.
She hates the way
that we were raised.
She hates the fact that
we're hunters.
Maybe she starts walking
and she doesn't stop.
You know, she obviously
has zero interest
in keeping
this family together.
Well, you know, sometimes
families do better
after a little time apart.
Yeah, who? The Mansons?
[ Animals making
various sounds]
Can I help you?
Uh, Abraham Peterson?
I'm James Morrison.
This is my associate
Ray Manzarek.
Uh, we're your new case workers
with Child Protective Services.
Pleasure to meet you.
Yeah, thought you'd be, uh,
you know,
long beard, suspenders,
big hat.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Chuckles ] We're not
that kind of religious.
Ah.
[ Clock chiming ]
Sam: Mr. and Mrs. Peterson,
we're here because your previous
case worker, Olivia Sanchez,
has passed away.
What happened?
We're not sure yet.
How often did she visit?
Every few months.
We liked her better than
the other one --
that Beth.
And what was wrong with Beth?
She hated us
because of our faith.
Olivia Sanchez was a Papist,
but...
at least she believed
in God.
[ Exhales ]
Hmm.
Do you know God, gentlemen?
Oh, yeah.
[ Door opens ]
Yeah, we're -- we're besties.
[ Door closes ]
[ Whispering indistinctly ]
Okay.
Um...I'm a little embarrassed
to ask,
but do you think one of you boys
might help me with something?
[ Engine running ]
[ Engine revving ]
?
Dean: So what happens when, uh,
stuff like this goes wrong
and no one's around
to help you?
Pray harder.
See, I'm not good
with all this.
I was a computer programmer
till about five years ago.
What made you move out
to the middle of nowhere?
Oh, the world out there
is all distractions.
Consumerism, corporations.
And the people, if they're not
shopping or stuffing their face,
they're sitting in front
of some screen
watching fake people
do fake things,
while the real world just gets
more and more screwed up.
Gail and I, we didn't want that
for our kids, so...
so here we are,
sweatin' our butts off.
The things you do
for family.
Hmm.
It's ready.
All right,
let's get this wheel on.
On three.
One, two, three.
[ Grunts ]
Okay.
[ Clock chiming ]
We're out of coffee.
Hope lemonade's all right.
Oh, yeah. Great. Thank you.
Welcome.
Happy family.
No, they weren't.
The father was working
80 hours a week
to barely pay the mortgage.
And what little time he did
spend at home,
he spent in a bottle.
Children were on
four different kinds
of behavior-enhancing medication
and barely spoke.
Could text up a storm,
though.
And the mother,
she was the worst.
She was so pilled up,
she could barely think straight.
So what happened?
God showed them a better way.
I was in a car accident.
[ Sets down glass ]
Almost died.
Nerves in the lower half
of my body are damaged.
Wow.
I saw doctors.
No one could stop the pain.
Best they could do was
give me drugs,
which helped for a while.
[ Whispers ] Yeah.
But the more I took,
the more I needed.
And when I didn't
get them...
And then one night,
when things were
at their worst, I was...
lying in a puddle
of my own sick.
I heard a voice.
It was God's voice.
And he said, "Go, live a life
of simplicity and humility,
and all your pain
will be taken away."
So has the pain gone away?
I get by, with His grace.
Mrs. Peterson, um,
what can you tell me
about Ricky Copeland?
The delivery boy?
Yeah.
Comes by once a week,
brings us things
we can't grow ourselves.
Why?
[ Inhales deeply ]
Well...
[ Sets down glass ]
He's dead, too.
I see.
[ Clears throat ]
You see?
That's it?
God has a plan for us all.
So what happened to your
daughter, was that God's plan?
Yes.
She didn't have to die.
She was sick.
If you had taken her
to a doctor --
God does --
God doesn't care
what kind of life you live.
Trust me.
And God didn't kill
your daughter. You did.
Think you boys should go.
?
[ Door opens, closes ]
All right. We're clear
on what we gotta do, right?
Yeah, definitely.
What's that for?
To track down Magda's ghost.
What's...
Beth. The witch.
Dean, this isn't a witch.
Well, it's not a ghost.
Those people let
their daughter die.
She's angry and wants revenge.
Yeah, but they're alive.
Besides, how -- how she getting
around town, huh?
Ghosts are tied to one place.
Or -- or to a person
or to a thing.
Oh, you're reaching.
And you're not?
Beth didn't even know
the delivery boy.
Maybe, maybe not,
but I'm gonna find out.
Look, you didn't spend
alone time with that woman.
She is disturbed.
The family's weird,
but they're good people.
Look, Beth wanted the better job,
she killed to get it.
End of story.
You're wrong.
All right, look,
you got your ideas, I got mine.
You wanna stay here and, uh,
scan the farm for EMF,
you go right ahead.
I'm on Beth.
Fine. We'll see who's right.
Well, you'll see I'm right.
[ Gun thuds ]
?
[ Horse blusters ]
[ Abraham and Elijah
speaking indistinctly ]
?
[ Door creaks ]
[ Humming ]
[ Voice breaking ] ? I've got
the joy, joy, joy, joy ?
? Down in my heart ?
? Where? ?
? Down in my heart to stay ?
? And if the Devil doesn't
like it ?
? He can sit on a tack ?
? Ouch ?
? Sit on a tack ?
? And I'm so happy ?
? So very happy ?
[ Stairs creaks ]
[ Footsteps descending ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Chains rattle ]
What did you do?
Nothing. Nothing.
Liar.
That woman. That boy.
You killed them.
What? No.
[ Gasps ]
[ Crying ]
I have tried to keep
the Devil locked away,
and you let him out.
You couldn't let it rest.
And now...
Now the Devil is doing
his work through you.
Confess your sins.
Pray for forgiveness.
Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw
a-rum mayyaw mto 'ad naf-Shaw.
[ Cracks ]
[ Sobs ]
Tma-'ith bama-'a-ma-ke syawn
w-leth a-Thar lma'kum.
[ Cracks ]
[ Sobs ]
[ Magda sobs ]
Ishthal-hith bmik-ri.
[ Cracks ]
[ Cries ]
[ Animals making
various sounds ]
[ Horse blusters ]
[ Horse grunts ]
[ Door creaks ]
?
[ Feed shifts ]
[ Metal bucket clatters ]
[ Horse whinnies ]
Elijah?
What's wrong?
Mom's with Magda.
Your mother's doing
God's work.
She's hurting her.
Son, the Devil's a deceiver.
Don't let him sow doubt
in you.
[ Horse whinnies ]
If anyone found out about Magda,
they'd come for her.
And if that happened...
I love your sister...
but you know what
she can do.
Magda...
Magda's our cross to bear.
?
[ Cellphone beeping ]
Come on.
[ Mouse button clicking ]
Working late?
Oh. [ Sighs ] Sorry, Agent,
you surprised me.
No worries.
Can I help you?
How you liking the new gig?
I hate it.
What?
Yeah.
You make more,
but you work more.
And if somebody screws up,
that's on you.
If somebody blows a deadline,
And if somebody's photocopying
their ass in the breakroom,
you have to adult
and act all mad,
even though
it's kind of hilarious.
Being the boss sucks.
I don't know
how Olivia did it.
I-I thought you wanted
this job.
[ Chuckles ] No.
Nobody wants this job.
Oh.
So...why are you here?
Um...
Krav lwaw-thi prok yaw-thi.
[ Cracks ]
[ Whimpers ]
Hekh ksa-gi-uth Ra-chamawch
this-tha-kal lwaw-thi.
[ Cracks ]
W-Al this-tha-lak...
a-pawch me-'av-dawch.
A-Ni yaw-thi sar-hev a-rum 'yawk Li.
[ Sobbing ]
Again.
Again!
[ Continues sobbing ]
Ra-chamawch
this-tha-kal lwaw-thi.
Shezev-Ni mba'-Le dvawv-vay.
[ Cracks ]
A-Ni yaw-thi a-do-nay
a-rum tawv.
[ Cellphone buzzes ]
[ Magda continues sobbing ]
Hey.
Beth is not a witch.
You were right about
the whole ghost thing.
Listen, Magda is still alive.
Wait, what?
Yes, Magda's not dead.
She's alive!
[ Shotgun cocks ]
Sam.
Don't move.
Sammy?
Okay, listen to me.
I can help your sister,
okay?
I just need you
to trust me here.
?
[ Grunts ]
Sam?
Sammy?
?
[ Tires screech ]
[ Humming ]
? Joshua fought the battle
of Jericho ?
? And the walls
came tumbling down ?
[ Grunts ]
? You may talk about
your men of Gideon ?
? You may talk about your men of... ?
Magda?
[ Grunts ]
Magda Peterson.
That's not my name.
I'm not Magda.
I'm the Devil.
[ Exhales sharply ] No.
No, you're not.
You're really not.
[ Chains rattle ]
He's inside me.
I can hear him whispering.
He lets me hear
what people are thinking.
He lets me do things.
What kind of things?
Magda, I'm here...
I'm here to help you.
Show me.
Please.
[ Chains rattle ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
They'll come for us,
our children.
We need to leave tonight.
Magda...
You're not the Devil.
You're just psychic.
There are others out there
like you, like -- like me.
I have powers, too.
I'd get these visions sometimes
and -- and I could move things
with my mind.
You can do that?
Well, no, not anymore,
I don't think.
But that didn't make me
the Devil.
It -- it --
it just made me who I am.
Then you are evil.
[ Sighs ]
Mother says I'm evil,
'cause I hurt people.
Who did you hurt?
I didn't mean it.
She was pretty,
and she always smiled.
And I thought that maybe
she could help me.
I couldn't talk to her,
but I could hear her thoughts.
And I thought maybe I could
make her hear mine.
[ Speaking Aramaic ]
So I prayed.
Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw.
[ Cracks ]
[ Screams ]
Tma-'ith bama-'a-ma-ke syawn
w-leth a-Thar lma'kum.
And I reached out to her...
Ishthal-hith bmik-ri
ith-char-char 'inki.
...but she never came.
And I did it again
with the delivery boy.
Mother says I killed them.
Magda,
that wasn't your fault.
You are not the Devil.
You're not evil.
And it's scary.
I-I know it's scary.
But you can learn how
to control it.
You don't ever have to hurt
anyone ever again.
[ Door opens ]
[ Chains rattle ]
?
It's time for supper.
[ Clock chiming ]
Who's hungry?
Abraham...
your daughter needs help.
What do you think we've been
doing all these years?
You talk about knowing God,
but we know the Devil.
[ Scoffs ]
We've been wrestling with her
for years.
You have any idea what
she's done?
Those people, but...
That wasn't her fault.
You think they're the first?
Tell him.
Before we came here...
[ Sets down pot ]
I wanted a new cellphone,
but my mom wouldn't
buy me one.
We were driving home, and she
screamed at me to pull over.
And I felt the Devil
at my hands.
I yanked that wheel
right into oncoming traffic.
She did this to me.
She did this to us.
She has taken lives.
Don't you understand
that by keeping her here,
we're protecting you?
By doing what?
Beating the hell out of her?
Pain purges sin.
No, it doesn't. You're wrong.
Abraham.
It's time.
We thank you
for these bountiful gifts.
May they nourish
our body and soul.
And look after each one of us,
now and until our dying day.
Amen.
Gail and Elijah: Amen.
Mm.
Dig in, everyone.
Elijah.
[ Utensil clatters ]
[ Gags, gasps ]
Dad?
[ Choking ]
Abraham?
Dad?
Shh.
[ Gags, groans ]
What did you do?
Eat.
What did you do?!
This is how we will
stay together.
We will enter Heaven
as a family.
Eat!
Elijah, do not eat that.
Elijah!
[ Chair scrapes ]
Mom?
Eat.
Elijah, do not do it.
Eat!
No!
[ Spoon clatters ]
[ Chair scrapes ]
Devil.
[ Dishes shatter ]
Elijah: No!
[ Squish ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Groans ]
[ Thud ]
[ Grunts ]
I'm not the Devil.
You are.
[ Grunting ]
Magda, stop!
You don't have to do this.
You could control it.
Magda, nobody else has to die.
[ Whimpers ]
Please!
[ Crying ]
?
[ Cries ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Knife clatters ]
[ Panting ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Velcro rips ]
She's the Devil!
The Devil is among us!
[ Radio chatter continues ]
She must be cleansed!
[ Car door opens ]
She is the Devil!
Pray for us!
[ Radio chatter continues ]
[ Car door closes ]
Sorry I missed all the psycho.
[ Car door opens, closes ]
Hey, you thought our family
was crazy.
[ Engine starts ]
Yeah.
[ Siren whoops ]
Hey, Magda.
Are you holding up?
Beth called my aunt
in California.
I'm gonna be staying
with her.
She has a ranch.
Lots of wide open country.
Dean: Well, that's great.
You know, sometimes in order
to figure things out,
a person needs space.
Agent, can I talk to you?
Yeah, sure.
[ Police radio chatter ]
Magda, I-I know it doesn't
feel like it right now,
but...you're gonna be
all right.
You can do this.
You will do this.
Just remember,
that power...
it doesn't control you.
You control it.
I know.
If you ever need anything,
anything,
call me, okay?
I'll be there.
Think you made the right call
back there, letting her go?
I hope so.
I mean, Magda didn't know what
she was doing. She had no idea.
I think she deserves
a second chance.
What did Beth want?
She gave me her number,
her personal number.
You were gonna shoot her.
Yeah, I know.
Kinda weird. Kinda hot.
Pfft.
Hey, um...
did you mean what you said
back there?
Yeah, you were right.
This whole mom thing,
it's...
I mean, we get her back,
and then she leaves.
I hate it, but I get it.
I do.
I guess I just...still working
through some of that crap.
I'll try to be
less of a dick about it.
Deal.
[ Cellphone chimes ]
[ Car door closes ]
[ Beeps ]
What?
Nothing.
[ Car door opens ]
?
[ Brakes hiss ]
Woman: All right,
bathrooms to the right.
Soda machines to
the left.
You have 20 minutes, folks.
Then we're off to Cali.
?
[ Silenced gunshots ]
[ Thud ]
[ Cellphone rings, beeps ]
Man: What's your status?
I cleaned up
the Winchester's mess.
As suspected,
they couldn't finish the job.
Very well.
Thank you, Mr. Ketch.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man