Dad's on a hunting trip
and he hasn't been home
in a few days.
We could take care
of a few kitchen witches.
They get their power
from demons.
I mean, selling your soul
at the crossroads kind of deal?
So you guys were raised by
a witch, but you're hunters.
Yep.
Dr. Hess
wants to know everything
about our "friends"
the Winchesters --
their allies...
...their habits.
how does Sam get his hair
so shiny?
When I saw Dagon had
captured Kelly,
I thought the angels
could help.
And?
Time to take this
off the board.
No!
I know now that this child
must be born
with all of his power.
Hello?
You have to ring
the bell.
You startled me.
What a delicate constitution
you must have.
Uh, that is a lovely ring.
Ah. Yes.
And if it goes missing,
I'll know who to blame.
I could cleanse your aura
if you like.
Looks a little...muddy.
Mm.
Oh. Coming!
Sorry. Hi.
Hi.
Sorry for the wait.
- Are you Tasha?
- Tasha Banes, yes.
- I called and...
- Yes, right. I'm Andy.
We've got you set up
at the top of the stairs.
Fantastic.
So what brings you
to Rock River?
Business or pleasure?
Little bit of both.
Hmm.
?
Reveal.
Now.
?
Ugh.
Oh, God.
?
? Supernatural 12x20 ?
Twigs & Twine & Tasha Banes
Original Air Date on May 4, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Okay, so last night...
that Super Mario power-up crap?
That wasn't Cass.
That freaking baby
isn't even born yet
and it sock puppeted him.
Think about it.
Cass said that he had faith
in Lucifer Jr.?
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
I don't know.
I mean, look, this doesn't make
any sense to me either, Dean.
But if we wanna have some shot
at finding Cass,
then we have to...
I don't know.
Uh, try and think like him.
How?
Seriously, I mean up until now,
if Cass messed up,
if he did something wrong,
but he thought it was for
the right reasons, I got it.
Right?
But last night,
when I looked at him,
I did not recognize the guy
staring back at me.
?
Can you fix it?
I hope so.
It's not me.
Must be one of Mom's.
Hello?
Oh, uh...
Sam?
Uh, I didn't know y--
Uh, it's Alicia Banes.
Alicia?
Hey, what's going on?
Like Max and Alicia?
Yeah.
Yeah, sorry to, um...
Uh, Mary gave me
a couple different numbers
to reach her, and we thought --
No. No. Mnh-mnh.
I thought Mary would
be down to help.
Uh, be our backup
on this, um...
You sound crazy.
Hey, guys. It's Dean.
Uh, you okay?
Yeah, depends who you ask.
Um, Mom was hunting
this witch
who's killed people
all over Wyoming.
Uh, anyway, Mom usually
checks in with us,
but she's sort of disappeared.
Oh, my God.
She did not disappear.
She's busy.
Wait, so -- so your mom
is missing?
Where are you guys?
We're on our way
to Rock River, Wyoming.
But Max thinks
I'm overreacting, but I --
Because you're being dramatic.
Mom's fine.
Stop bothering them.
Fine. Okay.
Hey, we'll be okay.
Uh, never mind.
No, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Um...
Hey, why don't you text us
your address? We'll meet you.
You will?
They will what?
We'll see you soon.
What the hell, man?
What about Cass?
Dude, Cass ditched
his cellphone.
Look, Jody put an APB out
for Cass and Kelly
across three states.
Until that
shakes something loose
or we get some other break,
all we're doing is --
is sitting here,
banging our heads
against a brick wall.
Let's get out there. Let's...
Their mom's on a hunting trip
and hasn't been home in a week.
All right. Let's go.
?
Please be a dear
and shut that bloody thing off.
It's Dean.
And?
This is Mary. Leave a message.
Mom.
Hey, uh, just wanted
to let you know that, uh,
me and Sam, we're uh,
we're heading out on a case
with those witch twins,
uh, Max and Alicia.
Um, I'll text you the info,
but, uh...
I know the Brits have got you
running nonstop.
So if you can help out,
that'd be great.
Um...
And even if you can't swing by,
can you call me back?
Just some stuff
going down that's...
kind of got me spun out.
Be good to talk to you.
I suppose it amuses
you to take Mary's form,
or perhaps you believe
it will inspire
a bit of hesitation
on my part.
It will not.
Aah!
He's not gonna talk.
The shifter has killed people,
Mary.
This is the very beginning
of what it deserves.
And if it tells us where
its family is,
well, then this will
all stop.
Promise.
That eye of yours twitches
when you lie.
My eye twitches all the time.
Well, then,
I guess I know all about you.
Hmm.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
All right, well, we're here.
What do you got?
Our mom was after
a "borrower" witch.
So witch that gets their power
from a demon deal.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, so you tracked
your mom here?
And now we tracked her
to the only vegan restaurant
in town.
They told us where
she was staying.
Anything else?
I got the bartender's
phone number.
Ignore him.
Dean...
that car is still major.
You want the tour?
Definitely.
Come on.
Yeah.
Max isn't really
feelin' this.
Yeah, I hadn't noticed.
He always thinks he knows
Mom better,
but it's 'cause they're both
natural witches.
It's who they are.
Whoa.
Right?
Nice.
Yeah.
Is that a grenade launcher?
Yes, she is.
Yeah, but, uh, this is what
we need right now.
Witch killing bullets.
And what about you?
Uh, with magic.
Nah, I don't have it.
It's just kind of
a lot of noise to me.
Magic is definitely
their thing, you know?
Yeah.
When I was growing up,
Dean and my dad
had the same thing
with hunting, that bond.
What about with Mary?
I mean, she, uh,
she gets into a case
and just sort of vanishes.
Yeah.
No, Mary's a great hunter.
Uh, she doesn't seem like
much of a hugger.
Yeah.
Hey.
Let's go find your mom.
Well, her car's here.
Well, no one's trying
to hide it. That's good news.
Yeah.
?
Not weird. At all.
All right, look, anything happens,
you guys stay behind us.
Yeah. Sure.
Alicia...
Uh, hi.
Hey.
Can I help you?
Yes, please. We're, uh,
we're looking for, uh --
Max? Alicia?
What are you two doing here?
?
Mom!
Sam and Dean Winchester,
meet the great Tasha Banes.
The kids have told me
very nice things.
Alicia basically made them come
just in case you were in peril.
Well, that was unnecessary,
but very nice of you
all the same.
Andy, can we get
a couple rooms
for my children
and their friends?
Sure. It'll just be a minute.
Great. You can wait in my room.
I have wine.
Great.
Wine.
So Rock River's a dead end.
No witches here, unfortunately.
Thought this was the place --
Well, then why didn't you
call us?
I mean, we --
Ahem.
I called and texted a lot.
I'm sorry, baby. My phone
hasn't been charging all day.
Oh, but I did find
a fantastic acupuncturist.
Of course you did.
You want me to help with that?
Oh, I've got it.
No, but you always call
on the fourth day of a hunt,
no matter what.
Honestly, babe, it just
slipped my --
Mom? You okay?
I'm fine.
Sam, do the honors.
Of course.
Alicia, put some music on.
?
Oh.
I ordered food
from that vegan place,
but no deliveries.
Oh, I can get it.
Oh, I'll grab it.
Uh, you guys stay,
hang out, catch up.
Dean...drink.
Yes.
I must say, I am pumping
with adrenaline.
Perhaps we could find some
privacy and tire ourselves out.
It's not
illicit motel sex, but --
I remember us agreeing
that was a onetime thing.
Did we? Ah, well.
Ketch, it was a waste of time,
that little torture session.
Oh, you mean the information
gathering session?
Yeah, but we didn't get
any Intel.
That shifter was never gonna
betray his family,
and still you --
Sometimes pain works.
Sometimes it doesn't.
But anyone who tells you that
torture is never the answer,
they haven't been under
the knife.
But you enjoyed it,
because that...
I have never seen that side
of you.
Yes, well, Mary, I'm sad to say
that you won't become
the Jiminy Cricket of
the British Men of Letters.
We don't need a conscious.
Such a trite idea,
but we firmly believe
the ends do justify
the means.
They didn't this time.
Ah, but look,
you're still with us.
Feel free to call
Mick Davies.
Have him write me up.
Well, Mick's not answering
his phone.
And his e-mails have stopped.
I'm sure he's busy.
When you get called to London
by the old men,
it's not all pints of stout
and trips to Savile Row.
Oh, and you should probably
return Dean's call.
Wouldn't want him to think
Mummy doesn't love him.
?
Expecting a call?
Oh.
Alicia...
Guess not.
...let's say later, I...
hypothetically
might need your Jeep
to take it out
for maybe a little cruise.
Mm, let's not.
You know, I gotta say,
you did a bang up job
with those two.
You must be drunk.
Off of wine?
Not fair.
Yeah.
I did the best I could
for Max and Alicia.
No.
I got lucky.
I see how you are with them,
all right? It's good.
You know, they're --
they're happy.
Alicia said you grew up
in the life.
Yeah. Yeah, my dad raised
me and Sam to hunt.
And your mother?
That's complicated.
Yeah. Yeah.
Family's always complicated.
Parents always seem smart
and strong and perfect.
It's only when you grow up
that you realize
that they're just people.
...love your brother?
?
And even if you can't
swing by,
can you call me back?
Just some stuff going down
that's...
kind of got me spun out.
Be good to talk to you.
Well, I can't just send him
to you economy comfort,
now can I?
The package is
in the armory now.
We gave it a lot number.
1-2-2-5-7. Mm-hmm.
We'll speak when you get in.
Tra.
?
Hi.
You've made yourself
at home.
Uh...
Can I help you
with something?
I use Mick's computer
for e-mail.
Uh, uh, yeah, well,
have at it.
?
There's a message from Mick.
He says he's gonna be stuck
in London a few more weeks.
Hmm.
Well...there you are.
- Hey.
- Oh!
Food!
Ooh!
Oh! Who's hungry?
Me!
Oh, my goodness. Thank you.
All right.
Ooh, it smells so good.
All right, let's see what we've got.
- Here, I can set up over here. Okay.
- Hey.
We'll be right back, y'all.
Sure.
Ah, you two. Get it --
get it down. Grab some napkins.
I know that look. What's up?
This was posted outside
the restaurant.
That guy we saw earlier,
coming out of the cellar?
He's been missing
for a month.
Okay, that's weird.
Well, maybe Tasha's wrong.
Maybe there is something going on here.
Yeah. I'll let 'em know.
No, no, no. Let's...
We can handle it. Come on.
Hmm.
?
This is Dean's
other other cell,
so you must know what to do.
Hey. It's me.
Sorry I couldn't pick up before.
I've been on a hunt with Ketch.
And, Dean...
I'm sorry I haven't been there
for you and Sam.
But I wanna be.
I will be.
I just...
I need to finish this.
I miss you boys.
I love you.
...she made me get out of the car...
She did not.
...to make a phone call in the rain.
Oh, my God. Alicia.
He just got out to yell at me.
Ugh.
Smells like death.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
What? You.
All right.
?
Alicia...
Was it that serious?
Oh, man.
Ladies, I'm gonna leave
you alone now
to have some girl time.
Since when are you not
a part of girl time?
Since I've got a date
with that hot bartender
from that vegan restaurant.
We're gonna have some...
guy time.
Hey, don't do anything
I wouldn't do.
Right. Right.
And what exactly was that?
Max!
?
Sam.
Ugh.
Dean.
?
Son of a bitch.
Her heart's been ripped out.
So have theirs.
Wait, this is everybody
that's in the house.
Okay, well, if this is
the real Tasha,
then who the hell
was I talking to up there?
Hey.
Hey, Max. Uh...
I saw the light. You guys find
some trouble to get into?
Nah. No, no. We -- we --
we just, uh...
I just...
?
Ohh.
Mick.
?
Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
What the...
So now we're reporting
to low-rent Christian Bale?
Seriously?
I don't like that guy.
He creeps me out.
This is Dean's
other other cell,
so you must know what to do.
Dean, call me.
We've got a problem.
Hello, Mary.
Your handprint doesn't open
this room
because it's not for you.
What are you doing here?
Why is Mick's body in a box?
An unfortunate
werewolf mishap.
A werewolf
shot him in the head?
It's not impossible.
You're a psychopath.
Mary.
Did you kill him?
Mick was weak.
He wasn't one of us.
When will you realize that
we will do whatever it takes
to rid this world of the things
that go bump in the night?
Something that people like Mick
and your sons
are incapable of.
Uhh!
Aah!
Don't talk about my boys.
Why not?
I've been cleaning up
after them for months.
I took care
of those federal agents
they stupidly allowed
to live.
I killed a psychic girl
they thought was...human.
Honestly, they're damn sloppy.
I think you mean...
decent.
It's the end
for the American Hunters.
Their time has passed.
But I can keep you safe.
If you just play your part,
if you play nice...
I don't play nice.
Aah!
Are we done?
Those Enochian brass knuckles
only work on angels.
And sadly, I'm not an --
Aah!
Brass knuckles
are brass knuckles.
Uhh! Oh!
Oh, you bitch!
?
- No, I think he's really --
- Who are you?
Max?
What did you do to my mom?
Max! What are you --
Wait, wait, wait.
Tell me!
What are you doing?
Let her go!
That's not your mom.
- What?
- Shh.
What are you talking -- Mom!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's okay.
Max, what is wrong, sweetie?
Don't! Don't.
You are not my mom.
Max --
I don't know what kind
of thing you are,
but you are not my mom.
Ow!
Max! Stop!
Reveal. Now!
Reveal!
The...the room,
end of the hall.
Top of the stairs.
Magic.
Got him.
Max!
Mom!
Really?
People are trying to sleep.
All right, lady,
craft time's over.
Mom! Mom!
Sam, this magic,
what is this?
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh.
How lucky am I?
Such an impressive witch.
Maybe you'll take the deal
the last bitch wouldn't.
?
My mother...you killed her.
Did I?
What did you do
to those people?
Oh. Let me show you.
I'm reaching the end
of my very long life,
and it's a problem
'cause I sold my soul for power.
So when I pass,
my soul goes to Hell.
Unless I can find someone
to take the burden,
to take my magic.
Sam!
Mom! Mom!
When your mother found me,
and when I realized
what she was,
I offered to teach her.
I offered her my power.
But even dying,
she was rude.
So...
I made her into one of
my creatures.
That doll has all of
your mother's memories.
It's her. Mostly.
Just like the others.
Rick, Andy -- they do what
I want, when I want.
I'm old.
I like things a certain way.
No.
No!
Nice try.
If you kill me,
well, then all of them
just fall apart.
So here's the offer.
You take my power.
You take my burden,
and my doll -- your mother --
will stay with you
and your sister forever.
Just one big happy family.
Max, no. Listen to me.
Your mother is gone, okay?
It's awful and it sucks...
...but that's -- Aah!
So...
do we have a deal?
You okay?
Mom!
No!
Take it...
and the deal is done.
Take it.
?
Alicia. Hey. Hey.
Hey, hold on. Just -- just
take it easy. Take it easy.
We're gonna get you
some help.
Why did you...
Max, listen to me. Hey, hey.
I had to, okay?
That deal wasn't with her.
It was with a demon.
You even touch that magic,
you lose your soul.
Dean!
Come on.
Don't fight. Don't -- Shh, shh.
Just take it easy, okay?
Take a breath. Shh.
Alicia?
She, uh...
What? Please.
No, no, no.
Hey. Hey.
Hey!
Please, no. No, no, no!
Hey, Max, um, this is, uh...
Look, you -- you're probably
in shock right now,
but it's gonna pass.
And then it's gonna hurt.
I could've saved them...
My mom.
If I had just...
taken Alicia seriously.
Come on, man,
you can't think like that.
Just stop talking.
Please.
Sure.
We'll, uh, go get some supplies.
We have to, uh --
We gotta burn
the bodies, Max.
Like my dad.
I can do it.
I...
I should do it.
You two get out of here.
Max, we would --
Please.
Please just...
?
You did the right thing.
You saved him.
Yeah.
Yeah, he seemed
super saved.
You know, I was watching them,
this loving family.
The kind we should've had.
And now just like that,
it's gone.
Dean, you couldn't let Max
make some deal for his soul.
Sam, we do terrible things
all the time
to save each other.
I mean, that's what you do
for family.
Who am I to stop him?
?
Well, he's strong.
He'll be all right.
Yeah, I'm not so sure.
? Oh, them old hollows ?
? Hide the dark secrets ?
?
What happened? I feel...
Ugh, I feel
like I drank too much tequila.
?
What...w-what did you do?
What...
Are you hurt?
No, no, no, no. I-I...
I'll explain everything.
But we gotta go now. Okay?
Okay.
? Oh, them old hollows ?
? Hide the dark secrets ?
?
? Tell what they've seen ?
? You'd never sleep again ?
? In peaceful dreams ?
Hey, it's me. Sorry I
couldn't pick up before.
I've been on a hunt with Ketch.
I'm sorry I haven't been there
for you and Sam,
but I wanna be.
I will be.
I just...I need to finish this.
I miss you boys.
I love you.
Dean, call me.
We've got a problem.
Sam? Hey, it's Mom.
Something's wrong.
Sam!
Good of you to rejoin me.
A Taser?
Not really a fair fight.
If only you'd been
as ruthless as I hoped,
this could have worked out.
Remember, Mary,
I gave you a chance.
So now what?
You kill me?
Don't be silly.
You're an asset.
We have other plans for you.
Now, Mary...
?
Let's begin.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man