Book you for 9:00?
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Take the day off.
Thank you.
All right.
? House 7x18 ?
The Dig
Original Air Date on April 11, 2011
== Sync by elderman ==
Corrected by Addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
So what did you do?
You figured out I was in jail,
but you don't know why?
I've been busy.
Excessive prescribing.
Not that busy.
I know that you pled down
to excessive prescribing,
but the question was
"what did you do?"
36-year-old, non-smoking
junior high science teacher
started coughing blood
in the middle of homeroom.
House says he's gonna be out
for the next three days.
Sweet. If I go straight to the airport,
I can make Cabo
for the last call.
Um, he also said to call him
if we find a case.
Which we didn't.
What do you call this?
Could be a case. Could be nothing.
Sadly, we'll just never know.
He's coughing blood.
A lot of people are.
Right now I have
to get to Vernon
while there's still enough
powder to ski on.
This is where a lesser man
would make
a black-guy-skiing joke.
You owe me a body shot.
Make it fast.
I'm driving.
I don't want to end up
in jail like...
A person should who used their
phone illegally while driving.
36-year-old male with hemoptysis,
headaches, chills,
and chest pain.
Where are you?
On my way to the greater
Schenectady chili cook-off
and spud gun competition.
That's your honeymoon?
Nope, Dominika went to A.C.
with her boyfriend.
E.R. ruled out bronchitis,
pneumonia, and lung cancer.
So diagnosis...boring.
It's epistaxis.
It's a nosebleed.
Blood runs into his lungs,
he coughs it back up,
flu explains the rest
of the symptoms.
Going once, going twice...
Toxic exposure
to ammonia or sulfites
can traumatize the lungs,
cause neuralgias or fevers.
Fits better because
of his radiating chest pain.
Sold. To Masters.
Do a home search for toxins.
Draw cultures
for bacteria and fungi.
You're married?
You were gone so long.
Green card.
Thanks for not saying anything.
I just need some time to...
I didn't do it for you.
Some puzzles are just
too good to share.
This is my exit.
Chili?
I hate chili.
Love spud guns.
You get nosebleeds?
Yeah, yeah.
You think that's where
the blood came from?
I don't just think it.
I hope it.
When was the last time
it happened?
At the quarterfinals.
I coach volleyball,
and during warm-ups
I got hit in the nose
a few months ago.
You coach volleyball in a gym?
Yes.
With showers?
Clean showers?
Not particularly.
The blood you were
coughing up wasn't blood.
Dirty gym washroom means
serratia infection.
Your lungs are full
of red bacteria.
You were right.
That was an interesting case.
You start him on Levaquin.
I'll start looking
for my good flip-flops.
Think that might be blood.
What's this really all about, House?
As convincing as I find
your deep devotion
to vegetable trajectory.
First of all, it's a tuber.
And you're just jealous because
your potato-related plans
are more of the serving
up fries variety.
You did time.
Means your license
is suspended.
Which means your
leave of absence
is definitely indefinite.
What exactly
are you going back to?
I'd only have to serve up fries
until
the medical board hearing.
I stand corrected.
You obviously have a rich,
full life waiting for you.
I'll slow down the car
and you can roll out.
I don't even have
a change of clothes.
Damn. If only
I'd planned for that.
Okay, here's what I got.
One, you were in jail
for six months,
but you were gone about a year,
which means that when you left
you hadn't been arrested.
Two, you enjoy being known
as a number.
You don't want people
to know the real you,
because you think
the real you is weak.
You were running...
A bleeding-heart medical
consulting business
for illegals, or some other
sympathetic under-class.
No.
Over-class?
This interrogation thing
is getting annoying.
Studies have shown
that un-annoying interrogation
is 50% less effective.
Why are you so determined
to bring me to this competition?
Why don't you bring Wilson?
Wilson thinks it's stupid.
I think it's stupid.
Junior year of high school,
you placed fourth
in a West Virginia
all-county science fair.
Your project, clean combustion.
Yeah, I also
wore a training bra.
Things have changed.
Not that much.
I've been going to this contest
for four years.
For four years I've come second
to a pissant named Harold Lam.
This is serious?
Second.
Okay.
I can help you,
but I'm going to need
to make a personal stop
along the way.
What kind of stop?
Personal.
Did I not mention that?
You gonna tell me
where you were last night?
I ran into a friend.
We had 50 bucks on the Bulls.
I had to eat a large pizza
by myself.
You missed me.
Not as much as I miss my $50.
Where'd you meet her?
At the hospital.
If it's Masters,
just lie to me.
Oh.
It's the new CNA
on the third floor.
The redhead.
She's hot.
And I'm seeing her again
tomorrow night.
I don't know how you do it.
Is it the cute, harmless vibe,
the self-deprecating humor,
or just straight-up roofies?
If you're interested,
I do seminars.
No electric, no gas either.
It's cold in here.
The good thing is I found a guy
who makes you look
like a good roommate.
Maybe hoarding's a symptom.
Could be caused by brain injury
or early-onset Alzheimer's.
It's most likely that it's psychological.
As to what's making him
cough blood,
dealer's choice.
Declutter your home.
The hoarder's handbook.
He's hoarding books
on hoarding.
Ugh.
He doesn't have running water.
How does this guy live,
let alone make it to work every
day and teach a bunch of kids?
Fridge is on. He's hooked it up
to a neighbor or something.
Cat.
I might have to throw up.
He'll want to keep that too.
Aspergillosis.
Explains the coughing blood,
and if he's formed
small aspergillomas,
it could explain the headache
and chest pain.
I'll be in the car.
Okay, turn right.
You were writing
bogus prescriptions
for medical marijuana.
Please say no
because you have to be an idiot
to actually screw that up.
No.
I mean, I was,
but I didn't get caught.
I have to admit, you have
one of the best game faces
I've ever seen.
Also one
of the best game bodies.
Pull over.
Hang on a second.
Didn't know you were
a Jehovah's Witness.
Yeah, the weak lost faith
when Christ didn't return
in '75, but I still believe.
You're really not gonna tell me
what just happened?
I don't know about you,
but I am starving.
You broke into my home?
We slowly pushed
into your home.
So what did you find?
A compost heap in your fridge.
We think
you have aspergillosis.
It's treatable
with antifungals.
You do remarkably well
for living...
Like you live.
I use bottled water
and flashlights.
It's like camping.
Fun.
We're also gonna need
a psych consult.
I'm not a hoarder.
I'm just a major slob.
You save earwax.
You know,
I'm actually kind of hurt
that you don't know what I did.
I'm not worth bribing
a court official
or hacking into police records?
Where's the fun in that?
You could have at least hired
Cuddy's weird boyfriend.
Lucas?
Mm-hmm.
You don't know?
What, is he dead or something?
No.
Actually, until
a couple of weeks ago,
I was Cuddy's weird boyfriend.
You're gonna have to do
a lot better than that.
Are...are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
It's not a big deal.
I killed a man.
Psych eval gave us nothing.
So our patient
is just an average Joe
with a two-foot pile
of used q-tips?
Whatever he is,
he doesn't have aspergillosis.
Pain's intensified,
and now he needs oxygen.
There's got to be all kinds
of toxins in that place.
Exposure issues
don't make sense.
He's been here a full day.
He'd be getting better,
not worse.
Unless exposure was keeping him
from getting worse.
The gas was off at his place.
How does he stay warm?
Portable heater?
Or portable gas heater,
which emits carbon monoxide.
Which is a vasodilator.
The low-grade exposure
was actually improving
his lung capacity.
We bring him here,
he gets worse.
If we're right,
don't need House,
and we still get two days off.
We still have to prove it.
Someone's got to go back
into that place
and test for C.O.
Chase and I can go.
It's only fair.
Fairness is important.
You're awfully quiet.
Sorry.
That's just how I get
around people
who have recently killed a man.
It wasn't...
You know, I've had
a pretty rough year.
Do you think maybe we could just
give this whole thing a rest?
You killed a man.
But you pled out to drugs.
Hit-and-run
under the influence.
Guy you kneed in the groin
was your date
who dropped a dime on you.
I'm asking you to let it go.
And I really wish
I was the kind of person
who could do that.
Ruby, right?
Yeah.
Hey, how are you liking PPTH?
It's great.
Everyone's so friendly.
Yeah.
Especially Dr. Taub.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna bust your chops.
I just want to know one thing.
How did he get you
to go out with him?
Why?
Is...is there something...
No, no, no, no,
he's...he's great.
I'm...you know,
I'm just asking
because...
Well, he's...
Um...
You know what, never mind.
It's none of my business.
You guys have fun tonight.
I'm not seeing him tonight.
We had plans, but he canceled.
Dr. Stern to Radiology.
This thing's got no fuel valve.
Means you can't regulate
the input.
And what is this?
A barbecue lighter?
Your gun sucks.
We should treat this
like an archaeological dig.
Grid the site, excavate,
catalog, analyze.
You like it here.
You don't think
this is fascinating?
Not nearly as fascinating
as the fact
that you think
it's fascinating.
But this guy kept everything
he ever came into contact with.
An interactive life history.
It's an indiscriminate pile
of rubbish.
Well, for the most part,
so are our lives.
There's no carbon monoxide.
A bit of a blow to Foreman's
exposure hypothesis
and my plan to get out
of here quickly.
Maybe we don't just figure out
the what,
we figure out the why.
Then maybe...
From the size
and the undigested seeds,
I'm guessing this came
from a raccoon.
If you're thinking Q fever,
it fits.
So why are you still looking?
Well, you only found one thing.
It fits perfectly.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean...
Chase.
You missed something
at his place.
His wife.
Nina.
I didn't know where you were.
I'm so sorry.
I couldn't get home.
You okay?
We think you both have Q fever.
Found raccoon feces
in the kitchen cupboard.
We're gonna start you
on Doxycycline.
Why wouldn't you tell us
you're married?
The fewer people who know about her,
the easier it is.
When can I go back?
She gets anxious
when she's away
from her things.
She's the hoarder.
He just lives there.
On purpose?
She's my wife.
How do they not have
1/2-inch drill bits?
By the way, Harold's
probably gonna hit on you.
Everything I have, he wants.
Just turn him down flat.
Unless...
Yes.
Let's stop shopping.
I'll just do him and get him
to throw the contest.
I'm not sugges...
Would you do that?
How's this thing judged?
Hang time, distance,
and accuracy.
Okay, how about this?
You met a guy in a club,
you brought him home,
he O.D.'d,
so the guy now writhing
on his front porch
was the dealer who sold you
the faulty goods.
Categories weighted the same?
Yup.
Screw accuracy.
We're gonna double distance
and hang time,
beat Harold on points.
We need raw power.
Where's the fertilizer?
By all means, Kaczynski.
Hi.
You and Taub
sharing phones now?
He's seeing the redhead
on the third floor.
Please tell me
you're not talking
about the hot new CNA
with the dimples.
She confirmed it.
What she didn't confirm
was their date tonight.
He bailed on her.
If he's standing her up,
he must have something better
going on.
Better than sex
with a 22-year-old?
Who's artie92?
Presumably a 21-year-old.
Whoever it is,
Taub's meeting 'em
at my place at 8:00,
which is usually
when I go to the gym.
Guess you'll be missing
spin class.
Okay, contestants, the field
is now open for practice.
You've got one hour.
Have fun.
Schedule 80 PVC
is pressure rated
for 220 psi,
fuel valve 300.
We can easily push it to 250,
have your friend Harold
peeing in his pants.
Damn.
Be cool.
Harold.
House.
You look good.
I like that jacket on you.
Thanks.
You filled out a little.
Who's the babe?
She's the boot in your ass.
Perhaps you've heard
of famed Russian physicist
Olga Petrovich?
Olga Petrovich is 72 years old.
And her granddaughter
works at a little place
called JPL.
I did an internship there
last summer.
She killed a man.
No.
I'm guessing she didn't do it
with a spud gun.
Just a bad combustion valve.
Shut up.
On my sofa.
Oh. Uh.
Hey.
You remember my wife.
Hi, Eric.
Hey, rt92.
I hope you like rhubarb.
We're celebrating.
We're going rogue.
We rip out
the combustion valve,
replace it with disks.
With enough pressure,
it should blow out
at maximum velocity.
Turning the spud into spudnik.
What do we use for disks?
Well, here's a hint.
I actually hate rhubarb.
Pie tins.
You're a genius.
You know that I'm a doctor.
Any interest I have
in the human body
is purely clinical.
Yeah, that line never works
for me either.
That line always works for you.
So what did you do?
No more guessing?
I need to know.
I can make some phone calls,
see if we can speed up
your medical board hearing.
In the meantime,
no one could stop me
from hiring an assistant.
You were right this morning.
I met a guy at a coffee shop,
we went back to my place,
and he O.D.'d.
Damn.
I could have saved myself
a job offer.
We both acted like idiots.
And I ended up doing time.
Guess he did more.
When we first moved into the house,
we had people over
all the time.
Then she started
collecting things.
I figured it was a hobby.
Piles turned into art projects,
and art projects turned
into what you saw.
So why do you stay?
To everyone else,
the world is full of junk...
meaningless, ugly,
broken things.
But to Nina,
every shape,
every color, texture, smell,
they all tell a story.
They're all worth treasuring.
I wouldn't wish what she has
on anyone,
but every now and then
I get a glimpse
of what she sees, and...
It helps.
Your lungs
are clearing up nicely.
Respiratory rate's normal.
Temp's normal.
Looks like you're
gonna be fine.
She okay?
Something's wrong
with her heart.
The husband is fine.
The wife is worse.
She had a heart attack.
Her heart attack could be
from a complication.
Q fever would cause
congestive heart failure,
not myocardial infarction.
So she had Q fever and something else
that causes heart attack?
And the hoarding. Now that
the wife is the only patient,
hoard is back on the board.
Or we were wrong about Q fever.
I don't buy
it's just a coincidence.
It's not a coincidence.
Diagnosis X
caused the hoarding,
which caused the Q fever
when the raccoons came
to spend spring break
at her house.
Now all we have to do
is solve for x.
I remember somebody saying that
hoarding could be a symptom.
We should do an MRI.
Hydrogen sulfide.
It's given off by eggs
and rotting food.
Long-term exposure could cause
the pulmonary issues,
headaches...
Even the heart attack.
Hydrogen sulfide
is also a vasodilator.
Which my crack team
never tested the place for.
Of course, half my crack team
never tested
the place for people.
So we should go back,
check it out.
Might be safer
to just assume we're right
and start treatment.
Go with God.
And some air freshener.
You know, maybe Taub is right,
so I'm gonna stay here with him
and help him with the MRI.
Shine up your spuds, folks.
We're gonna start shooting
for hang time
in just a few minutes.
The wind's coming
from the southeast.
You have to aim five degrees
to the left.
We're gonna break 14 seconds.
I can feel it.
When I was 10 or 11,
my dad used to take us
to this county fair.
And there was this kid...
What?
Who's "us"?
My mom and me.
Your mom who had
advanced stage Huntington's.
You have a sibling
that you've never mentioned.
Why did you slip up now?
Not everything means something.
We're gonna be up soon.
I want to check the pressure.
You don't wake up in the middle
of the night to cry
over a dead stranger.
You don't confess
to killing a man
and then hide the details
unless the details reveal
more about you
than the crime itself.
You pled down to drugs.
You've got
a horrible genetic disease
and a sibling
who's suddenly on your mind.
You euthanized your brother.
And that guy back at the house
was the doctor
who wouldn't help you
cover it up.
The guy back at the house
is my cellmate's boyfriend.
He cheated on her
when she was inside.
But I was right
about everything else.
Congratulations.
You're mad.
No.
Actually, I'm impressed.
Messing around
on a 22-year-old hottie
with your wife on my sofa.
You're a full-throttle
head case.
I was doing you a solid
with the sofa.
Rachel wanted to do it
in your bed.
You've got the memory foam top.
Let's make this really simple:
If I own it, I don't
want you doing it on it.
You might want to get rid
of your kitchen table.
Look, I'm sorry,
but it was worth it.
Yeah, I bet.
You get to mess with her
physically and emotionally.
I still care about her.
Not enough to let her move on
with her life.
While we're talking
about your bad ideas,
MRI's clean.
There has to be some kind
of inciting
psychological incident.
This is perfect for you.
You get all
the human interaction you crave
without any actual
human interaction.
She was a cheerleader.
Huh.
You know when you're interested
in something
and nobody else is,
the polite thing
is to keep it to yourself.
Popular, beautiful,
gregarious.
Hydrogen sulfide's
about two parts per billion.
The size of a healthy fart.
I'll be back for you in July.
He couldn't do it himself.
He was...the disease
had progressed too far.
He was flailing.
He didn't have any control
over his own body.
He pretty much lost control
of his mind too,
but...
Every once in a while,
he would have a few seconds
of lucidity.
He turned to me, and he said,
"it's time."
I hooked up the I.V.
I used gloves.
I knew they'd get me
on the drugs,
but they couldn't prove
who pushed the plunger.
I put in the needle,
and he just...
Got quiet.
And it was over.
And I was alone.
And one day,
I will be that sick,
and there will be no one there
when it's time.
I didn't expect compassion
from you.
I would have taken
commiseration.
Hell, I would have taken
revulsion,
any emotional engagement
at all.
It's no wonder
Cuddy broke up with you.
Folks, Chad Lockerbie just won
first place
in the chili cook-off.
Congratulations, Chad.
That cocoa powder
really did it.
Dumped in a field in Schenectady.
Ouch.
You mind if I make a move?
I know she's out of my league,
but she's at a spud gun contest
with the soon-to-be
five-time runner-up,
so she's probably got
some self-esteem issues.
You wouldn't.
So?
Warning.
They gave you a warning?
Well, it turns out
our friend Harold
felt up the sheriff's daughter
last night
at the potato mash mixer,
so sheriff's feeling
kind of ambivalent.
You always get your way,
don't you?
Not always.
Today would have been
our one-year anniversary.
Which is an incredibly
arbitrary thing to celebrate.
If you want to get
to the bottom of something,
you literally have
to dig down to the bottom.
So stratigraphically,
the oldest stuff I found
was in the bedroom.
And the oldest stuff
in the bedroom
was in the closet.
And at the bottom
of the closet...
Tell me about this.
We have a new symptom.
Infertility.
They wanted kids
but couldn't have them.
She started collecting things
to fill the void.
We should run
a full hormone blood panel.
Hey, Harriet the Spy,
before you get too full
of yourself,
you might want to go back
to bio 101.
It takes two
to not-tango.
Hubby could be shooting blanks.
So either it's a new symptom
that will help us save her life
or it's a complete
waste of time.
Figure out which is fried,
the bacon or the eggs.
I'll start the hormone workup.
There's another option.
House, who's that?
Radio.
Sounded a lot like Thirteen.
It's a Thirteen tribute band
with their new song,
"I've got a better theory
than Masters."
She said they never had kids.
Oh, my God.
Where the hell have you been?
I think we've all got something
a little more important
to worry about than...
No, we don't.
She's been missing for a year.
You can ask her all about it
when she comes in on Monday.
Monday?
This Monday?
Can I talk?
She said they never had kids,
and you all jumped
to infertility.
You never considered
the other option.
And the bitch is back.
We think you have
Ehlers-Danlos syndrome.
It would explain the symptoms.
It also causes miscarriages.
Is that something
you think you might have?
Were you pregnant?
Three times.
The miscarriages
triggered the hoarding.
Hoarding eventually
made you sick too.
Can you cure her?
We can treat
the physical symptoms
as they arise,
make her life a lot better,
but the hoarding,
we're the wrong kind
of doctors.
You lied to me?
For nine years?
I was so afraid of losing you.
What have I ever done
to make you afraid of that?
I need to get some air.
I've been selfish.
I need to let you
move on.
I think we should stop
seeing each other.
No.
Um, I just want you
to be able to...
the last time
you got all noble on me,
we ended up dividing
our dishes.
This time, I want
to make the decision.
You don't feel weird
about this?
Of course
I feel weird about this.
It's confusing and messy
and dirty.
Dumb.
But we spent our whole lives
trying to do everything right,
and it sucked.
It wasn't all bad.
It sucked, Chris.
And this,
whatever it is,
it's fun.
So I'm not
taking advantage of you?
The fun is fading.
You know...
there's something
seriously wrong with us.
I know.
? don't leave ?
? 'cause I believe ?
? we were meant ?
? to sleep ?
? in the dirt ?
Home, sweet home.
You owe me 87 bucks for gas.
I'll kill you.
When the time comes,
if you want me to.
I'll do it now if you like.
I think I've got
a baseball bat in the back.
I'll see you Monday.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==