I don't know about you,
But i'm nervous.
Zel tov!
Mazel tov!
Many children.
This is a great thing,
Roz.
I am so happy for you.
Thank you, Mrs. Silver.
Yonatan is a good man
from a good family.
I know you chose well
for me.
I've been blessed.
±????»???©?§?°?»???¬???????????µ????
- =Http:/www. Ragbear. Com=-
House 412
- =?????????»??=-
?±????????°®??????s
Cross-Species mating.
If you like darwin
and the galapagos.
Amber and i
have a lot in common.
She's a cutthroat bitch.
You cry over dark victory.
Bette davis, another strong,
assertive woman.
You don't like strong.
You don't like assertive.
You like needy.
She's not dying, is she?
Yes. Go away.
I give it two months.
Hundred bucks.
Not really fair.
You're not objective.
But i'm all about
the teaching-
We're at four months.
You hid this from me?
I was wrong, okay?
I thought you'd be upset.
I thought you'd track me
down in hallways-
I shouldn't have
discounted the sex.
She's obviously limber enough
To put off the meltdown
for two months.
She's not needy.
I don't need needy.
She's scary.
Why does scary need pathetic?
Are you gonna talk
to her?
I don't see
that i have any choice.
You all right with that?
No impulse
to save her from me?
I've broken
the pattern, house.
Which is why
this has a chance.
I know
you're too suspicious
To accept that
without getting out your ruler,
And your calipers, and
your scanning equipment, so...
Go ahead.
Get it out of
your system.
38-Year-Old female
with loss of bladder control,
Blood in her urine,
and a broken leg
From collapsing
at her wedding.
Ampicillin for the uti.
Shiny cast for the leg.
You guys know
wilson's dating amber?
No.
Wilson and amber?
I knew.
I asked her out.
Said she'd just
started seeing someone.
Cultures were negative
for utis.
No signs of previous
trauma or stds.
- Kidney cancer.
- CT was clean for tumors and kidney stones.
I thought Amber
scared you guys.
She does.
But she also has legs that go
all the way up to canada.
So do canadians-Doesn't mean
i wanna date one.
Her sodium's low-Could be
endometriosis in the bladder.
Low sodium
could also be from low food.
Hasidic jews
fast on their wedding day.
Or sodium was absorbed by
a toxin already in her system.
Was it just the legs,
Or did you detect something
resembling a soul?
She grew on me.
If there's a toxin in her,
could be carbolic acid.
I'm talking
about the patient now.
That much carbolic acid,
Someone would have had
to poison her.
Could have been a cossack-
If this was 18th century poland
And cossacks were
into household cleansers.
Which is why it's more likely
that the poisoner was poisonee.
Suicide's a sin.
Corollary of "people lie"
is "people sin. "
And in my world,
people includes jews.
She was getting married.
Hasidic women marry young
So they can start pushing out
little hasidilings.
38 means a woman
not on anyone's hot list
Being pushed onto a guy
who's not on anyone's hot list.
No way out, no way out.
Endometriosis fits better
Than an epiphany
that her life is meaningless.
We should start her on a. I.S
and do a cystoscopy to confirm.
Fine, check her innards
for bad cells
And her home for bad karma.
Carbolic acid
should be on the shelf
Right next to the regret
and the self-Loathing.
These people are crazy.
Yeah. She should
be self-Hating.
I'm not self-Hating.
I hate religious people who are
out of touch with reality.
You only marry someone
you met three times
If they're carrying
a little mistake.
What's their divorce rate?
Cleaners are all organic.
Nothing with carbolic acid.
You like
how they hook up?
Romance is just
emotional foreplay.
Candlelight meals,
flowers.
It's as much a ritual
as anything these people do.
Why not go with someone
who's pre-Vetted,
Shares the same values?
Cut to the quick.
Values may give you
the big picture,
But time together
gives you the little picture-
Does she chew her food
too loud?
Will she leave you alone
during the final four?
You commit
to something deeper,
You let the little
surprises slide.
Surprises kill-
Which is why i only commit
When there are
no more surprises.
And you have no more surprises
for your wife.
Do you think this came up
on date number two?
You ever heard
of a hasidic jew into hard rock?
She's listed as a producer
on all of these.
Where there's rock and roll,
And sex...
Usually, there's drugs.
I'm baal teshuvah.
I became hasidic
about six months ago.
And before six months ago?
Music business isn't
exactly known for its holiness.
Heroin.
But i've been clean
for months.
Yonatan knows.
The broad strokes.
He never actually asks
the details.
Says what's important
is the person that i am now,
Not the person i was then.
How do you go
all the way from-
Just took a class.
Then i took another class.
And you just completely left
the music business?
Pop music is considered
frivolous.
Same reason we don't watch tv
or go to movies.
Your drug use may have caused
some long term damage.
We're gonna need
to take a hair sample
To test for latent toxins.
So you can never watch
star wars again.
You figured
that i'll hire you
If you promise
to dump wilson.
- How did you-
- Wilson had a key.
You figure that i'll make
your life hell at first,
But i'll eventually see
how good you are and keep you.
It's a good plan,
don't you think?
Perfectly tailored
to your personality.
No, it's not.
You know it's not.
Means you just wanna stay
in my orbit.
'Cause you figure
i'll eventually realize
That i made a mistake
And you're gonna be able
to rub my face in it.
I can't wait.
It's gonna be awesome.
No, it's not.
And you know it's not.
'Cause you know that even
if i made a mistake,
I'd never admit
that i made a mistake.
Which means that you're
just toying with wilson
To toy with me.
Your goal
is pure feral vengeance.
Innocent bystander,
But there's
a greater good.
No, that's not it.
Because a bag
of flaming poop
Bypasses the bystander.
So...
Which is it, house?
Am i in this for you...
Or am i in this for him?
Give him back
his sweatshirt.
Pit stains
don't become you.
Treatment had no effect.
Rules out endometriosis.
And her hair sample
was negative
For residue drugs.
This woman lived
in the fast lane
Till six months ago.
Maybe we're missing
something.
She admitted drug use.
Doubt she's holding out on her
days as an asbestos miner.
Cryoglobulinemia might account
for the symptoms.
Except for
the one you missed.
There's no change
in her condition.
I'm not talking
about a new symptom.
I'm talking about one
that presented six months ago.
Look, she's nuts,
but we can't just give her
10 ccs of atheism
and send her home.
Religion is a symptom
of irrational belief
And groundless hope.
Altered mental status,
on the other hand,
Is a symptom of porphyria.
She didn't develop
uncontrollable anger,
Crying, anxiety.
She just decided
to go to temple.
The woman didn't just
choose to keep kosher.
She went directly
to the extremes of hasidism,
A life of stringent rules.
She became a masochist.
She didn't like her old life,
so she changed it.
People don't change.
They want to.
They need to.
Taub gave up a six figure
plastic surgery career
For this job.
That mean he has
porphyria?
He switched jobs
to save his marriage.
He did it to avoid change.
He's right.
You don't suddenly
choose crazy
Without suddenly
being crazy.
No, no, if she walked
away from everything
To go base jumping
or live with apes,
We wouldn't be having
this discussion.
We would if she was
also tinkling blood
Out of her overexcited bladder.
Pump hadassah full of hematin
and give her a phlebotomy.
Bloodletting?
Porphyria is a rare
genetic disorder
That causes an overproduction
of a certain protein.
Draining the blood
relieves-
The hair test
for damage from drugs
Showed she has
a rare genetic disease?
Not-Not exactly.
We're testing her now
to confirm.
You're treating it
before you confirm it?
Blood test results
take 24 hours.
You must have seen something
that makes you suspect it.
Dr. House has
A theory.
A theory based on what?
We'd like
a different doctor.
I assure you
that dr. House is our best-
Then we will settle
for second-Best,
Someone who doesn't think
my wife is sick
Just because
she's religious.
If you prefer,
I can give your wife
my second-Best diagnosis.
Do you know wilson's
dating amber?
I have reviewed
the chart.
Someone on your team
must have pointed out
That cryoglobulinemia
also fits the symptoms.
Yes, it fits many
of the symptoms.
My wife's body is sick.
Her mind and soul are fine.
You live according to god's
600 commitments, right?
613.
You understand them all?
Takes a lifetime
of learning...
But you follow
the ones
You don't understand because
the ones you do understand
Make sense, and you believe
The guy who created them
knows what he's doing.
Of course.
So you will trust
my diagnosis
And you'll let me
treat her,
Because in this temple,
i am dr. Yahweh.
I want a new doctor.
I'm starting her
on indomethacin
For cryoglobulinemia.
People don't change.
For example, i'm gonna keep repeating
people don't change.
So alcoholics that successfully
Go through treatment
don't exist.
They're still alcoholics.
If they never take a drink
as long as they live,
It's only 'cause
they didn't live long enough.
If you're dissatisfied
with your life,
Changing it is a symptom
of mental health.
I get why that concept
is strange to you.
O2 sats are 85.
She's hypoxic.
We might need to intubate.
What's wrong with her?
It's definitely not
cryoglobulinemia.
Better ask him.
We kept her
on oxygen overnight.
Her respiratory rate
stabilized,
And her o-Sat's
back up to 95.
I saw amber drop off wilson
this morning.
Yes, the male
always drives the female.
So what caused
the breathing problem?
Pulmonary involvement
rules out porphyria.
She kiss him or he kiss her?
I missed it.
The lab tech with the tongue
stud also pulled up.
Wegener's would explain
her elevated sed rate.
Wegener's wouldn't explain
the changed mental status.
Actually, we've
been trying to ignore
That part
of the whiteboard.
I wrote it in black.
I'm always serious
when i use black.
- Lupus would explain-
- Maybe she didn't change.
Are you agreeing with me
or you making a point?
I'm making a point.
That's gonna take longer.
How do we know
that the real roz
Isn't who she is now
and who she was then?
Can't we say that
her previous life was true
Without making
her present one a fraud?
"Life is messy" argument.
Nice.
Explains everything
without explaining anything.
If it's lupus,
there's a heart problem
We don't know about yet.
Run her through
a stress test.
If she has a heart attack,
i'm right.
Or we could wait,
hope that-
You're afraid
to give her a heart attack.
Of course we're afraid-
No reason to be afraid.
Unless you think i'm right.
It's wegener's.
But we'll have the crash cart
just in case.
Oh, my god!
What are you guys doing here?
I had a sudden yen
for fusion.
I put a different restaurant
in my date book.
I'm firing my assistant.
That's okay.
Hi, greg.
And i call you Greg because
we're now social equals.
I call you
cutthroat bitch...
Well,
quod erat demonstrandum.
And i speak in latin
Because i don't try to hide
what an ass i am.
I assume you'd like
to join us?
It'll be easier
to observe our interaction
If you're at the same table.
If we ever get seated.
Excuse me.
No, no, i, uh-
We've been waiting for...
Any minute now,
She's gonna hit him
in the face
With your testicles.
She tends to treat e-
She tends to treat
every event
Like it's the last copter
out of saigon.
She's the anti-Wilson.
She's a force
for evil.
She has
an annoying quality.
Perhaps even two.
If i was perfect,
i would date perfect.
You like that!
It's annoying,
but she's good at it.
Wait a second.
This isn't just
about the sex.
You like her personality.
You like that she's conniving.
You like that she has
no regard for consequences.
You like that she can
humiliate someone if it serves-
Oh, my god.
You're sleeping with me.
I need you to go faster, roz.
A little harder.
I am going harder,
damn it.
What if dr. House
was right?
And roz did make
a radical change?
Lupus is chronic
but treatable.
And with the treatment,
it'd undo the change?
She'll be the way she was
before i knew her?
I don't think it's likely.
Then you don't know for sure.
You'd find someone else.
There isn't someone else.
You've had three dates.
How long have you
been married?
12 years.
And is she the one?
We wouldn't still be together
if she weren't.
I love her as much now
as the day-
Well, you should
love her more.
The more you know someone,
The more you
should love them.
Okay, that's enough, roz.
Okay, your heart's
as strong as a battleship.
Does this mean
dr. House was wrong?
Oh! Oh, my leg!
Heart's strong enough
to prove you wrong
About the change
in mental status.
Only proves
this isn't lupus.
Just as the leg pain proves
it isn't wegener's.
Leg pain can be
from nerve entrapment.
We're thinking
blood clot.
Do an mri
to look for the clot.
Then do an fmri.
- An mri alone...
- If the clot hasn't dissolved.
An fmri can show signs
of near-Ischemic stroke
In post-Ischemic parts
of the brain.
- Give me ten bucks.
- No.
I missed lunch.
- I thought you went-
- I missed lunch.
Good symmetrical activity
in both hemispheres.
Caudal structures look okay.
She hasn't changed?
Sex, drugs,
rock and roll,
The 600 rules of god
are all in there somewhere.
We oversimplify people.
It's how
the human mind works.
Everything's
on or off.
Everything's got a category.
You don't like it.
You don't wanna be
oversimplified.
Roz, move your right leg.
No one can describe themselves
in ten words.
Why would we want to hear
anyone else do it?
So you keep it a mystery.
No categories
if no one knows anything.
Do you think maybe
you're oversimplifying me now?
No.
I'm sure you have
many reasons
To keep yourself a mystery,
Besides the fact
that you're bisexual.
Uh... denial would have worked
before the long, vacant stare.
Roz, move your left leg
just an inch.
People who have a problem
with boxes
Are people
who don't fit in them.
You've been working
for house for a long time.
No need for name calling.
I would ask if this
was gonna be lunchtime gossip,
But lucky for me-
I don't give a damn.
How's our mental yentl?
Mri shows no sign
of clots.
Fmri shows
no problem areas.
Go restart her iv.
- What's wrong with it?
- Nothing.
But like so many procedures
we put patients through,
It hurts.
Which, if she's enjoying it,
will show up in pretty colors.
This is why you wanted
an fmri?
It showed she didn't
have a blood clot,
Which is diagnostically
relevant.
And it can show
if she's become a masochist-
Also diagnostically relevant.
And it'll be cool.
Either will explain which part
of my analysis makes sense.
Or go do it.
It isn't cool.
I'm sorry.
Heavens.
Look at her limbic system.
Pleasure centers are lighting
up like a hanukah bush.
Foreman must have
a touch like an elephant.
Okay, roz.
We've got what we need.
Yes, it was impressive.
Roz.
You all right?
I'm sorry.
I was praying.
All through
the procedure?
No.
When dr. Foreman
apologized,
I knew something bad
was gonna happen.
She was praying.
Could explain
the brain activity.
Bp, nd heart rate
are dropping.
She's crashing.
She's stabilizing.
Get her up.
All the way up.
On her feet.
Make her do that again.
We started her on
fludrocortisone and ephedrine.
It's planet of the apes.
Apes are the humans,
humans are the apes.
It's wacky wednesday,
opposite day.
When you stand up,
Your bp and heart rate
are supposed to go up, not-
Got it.
So what causes bloody urine,
Loss of bladder control,
leg pain, altered mental status,
And pressure-Blood
in direction-Wrong?
Pheochromocytoma.
Low catecholamines
in the urine
Means no pheochromocytoma
in the jewess.
Could be
systemic sclerosis.
Mental status.
She was praying.
She was in pain.
You no longer think she's crazy?
I can see why she'd be attracted
to that life.
You drank the
manishevitz-Flavored kool-Aid.
I'm not saying i agree.
I'm just saying-
That there's a rational basis
for the irrational.
They have something
we don't have.
Imaginary friends.
If the toaster's not working,
wiring could be bad.
Which debate is that metaphor
supposed to help us with?
Electrical problem
in the heart.
Arrhythmia messes with
the blood flow when she stands,
Causes low bp and heart rate.
Could also impact
mental status.
Everybody's happy.
Run an ep study of her heart.
Find where the wiring's
verklempt.
Went by your hotel
this morning.
They told me
you moved out.
Moved in with c. B.?
No, apparently,
i moved in with you.
The very fact
that you're resisting my insight
Proves to me-
House, you're right.
Why not?
Why not date you?
It's brilliant.
We've known each other
for years,
We've put up with all kinds
of crap from each other,
And we keep coming back.
We're a couple.
Are we still speaking
metaphorically?
Amber is exactly
what i need
And you would agree if you
weren't mired in self-Loathing
Topped with a thin crust
of megalomania.
Hey. That's my best friend's
girl you're talking about.
I was wrong.
House, you're right.
She's not me.
Well, she is me.
But that's not why
she's attractive.
She's a needy version
of me.
Hard to imagine
such a mythical creature.
You started seeing her
right after i fired her.
I started seeing her
four months ago.
She told kutner
it was four weeks.
You lied to me.
There was money
on the line.
Because i knew
how you'd react,
And i knew you
wouldn't pay me anyway.
You knew that i was right.
She wasn't needy.
She was in a...
bad situation.
There's a difference.
Not to your libido.
Wait a minute.
Why are you doing this?
Every time i agree with you,
you find a new argument.
What are you
trying to avoid?
Well, if you'd looked at me
with those flashing eyes
Before i was involved...
C'est la vie.
And... i use
the french because...
You're an ass.
Right atrium normal,
no arrhythmia.
You can become
a d'har master.
Does that require
further explanation?
Right ventricle normal.
In college, i was really
into science fiction-
Not like the guys
with the $600 prosthetic ears
Who could swear in romulan,
That was embarrassing
to the rest of us
Who just thought it was
good, smart literature.
Went to one convention.
By senior year, i was d'har
master in the klingon empire.
I'm not gonna become
hasidic.
I'm not even gonna become
slightly more reformed.
Coronary sinus normal.
You can't have your eyes opened
to something and not act on it.
I haven't had
my eyes opened.
I just... don't think
they're crazy anymore.
Then they have
something to offer.
She's living proof
That sane people
can make radical changes.
But house, he thinks
that he can bully-
No loshon hora.
I'm sorry?
I think she's telling you
to stop deflecting.
No loshon hora.
Evil tongue.
Gossip.
It's okay.
Thanks to the sedative,
you won't remember it.
Words are permanent.
Someday you'll say something
That you'll wish
you could take back.
This bundle's normal.
Pathways are all clean.
No arrhythmias.
If the toaster doesn't work
And the wiring
in the house is fine,
Problem's gotta be
in the city's power grid.
Autonomic nerve disorder
could be riley-Day syndrome.
Congratulations
on your wedding.
You have a rare and incurable
degenerative disease.
I'll set up for
a thermoregulatory sweat test.
She's a bisexual.
What?
I could hear them talking
from inside the mri.
Hear who?
I heard the word sex.
- It was interesting.
- What was interesting?
It doesn't matter.
We're doctors.
We never know
what's gonna matter.
She said sex.
If she wants to tell you
when she wakes up...
Yeah, these people
aren't gonna change you at all.
I need you to sleep
with wilson.
Good morning.
He's involved
with an inappropriate woman.
His people are sheepherders
and amber's are cattlemen?
He's combining two
of his worst qualities-
His love for me
and his love for need.
As administrator
of this hospital,
You have to save
your star oncologist.
Wish i could help,
but as administrator,
There are some people
in accounting
I'm scheduled
to sleep with first.
Wilson has a pattern
with women.
He saves them,
then he betrays them,
Which then causes guilt...
Which then causes him
to go save somebody else.
For example, a hospital
bureaucrat nearing 40
Who has no personal life.
I suggest
you go braless.
I get that "sleep with"
is your way of saying
I should talk to him?
No. I really mean
sleep with.
You're not worried
You're worried
it'll succeed.
That wilson will no longer be
at your beck and call 24/7.
That your best friend
will change.
People don't change just
because they wish they could.
And it bugs you
that he wishes he could!
You'll never lose
your friend, house.
You're the long-Distance runner
of neediness.
As the chamber heats up,
Roz's body temperature
should also rise,
Making her sweat
and turning the powder purple.
No change in color
means no sweating,
Which means her central
nervous system is damaged.
I shouldn't
see her like this.
We could have a diagnosis
As soon as she comes
out of the chamber.
It might be better
if you stayed.
It's disrespectful.
I'm sure sure she imagined
The first time
her husband would see her
Bare like this would be
celebrating the marriage.
Given the circumstances,
I think roz
would sacrifice modesty
To have you with her.
Please.
Don't do that.
What? I think it's nice
that you're here.
- I think-
- You think it's sweet...
That i care for her modesty,
But that it's archaic
and ultimately irrelevant.
Our traditions
aren't just blind rituals.
They... they mean something.
They have purpose.
I respect my wife.
And i respect her body.
Her body temperature's
stopped climbing.
What's going on?
She's having a seizure!
We need a crash cart!
Blankets too!
She's freezing.
She was supposed to sweat
and she froze.
Return to the planet
of the apes.
Hypothermia caused the seizure.
What caused the hypothermia?
It could be an infection.
Her white blood cell
count was fine.
When she was admitted.
She could have picked
something up here.
Complication
on a complication?
Body's doing the opposite
of what it's supposed to.
Her body's wilson.
How do we respond to that?
We accept
that he's happy.
We do the opposite.
So you want us to what,
send the patient home?
Infection... means that
Something's been added
to the body,
Something that should
be expelled.
What's the opposite
of that?
Something missing
from the body.
Could be an enzyme
or a hormone.
Cortisol.
Could be addison's.
It fits.
Every symptom.
I'll run a cortisol
stimulation test.
Are you sure
she doesn't wanna just
Take you back to her lair,
hang you upside down,
And deposit her eggs
in you?
Excellent disguise,
house.
You two are really
that serious?
She's pretty.
She's funny.
- Maybe she's a little more...
- Evil?
Aggressive than
you'd expect from me.
But i'm happy.
Can't i just enjoy what
that feels like for a while?
How many people have looked
at you trustingly
While you gave them
a fatal prognosis,
But you knew it was kinder
to tell them the truth?
Amber compulsively looks out
for number one.
You compulsively look out
for the person that you're with.
Your needs are gonna feed
her needs
Until all that's left
is a wilson chalk outline
On the floor.
Sorry.
Wow!
That cortisol stuff
is great.
Does it work
on everything?
I take it
you're feeling better.
Oh, still weak.
But yeah.
You must be so tired.
You should go home
and get some sleep.
I'll stay.
I never told you,
but you are much better looking
Than mrs. Silver
led me to expect.
She never liked me.
When i was eight,
I threw up on her shoes
at my uncle's wedding.
Your abdomen's
a little swollen.
Mm?
Is it serious?
It's hard to say.
Sometimes it can mean
a liver issue.
- We'll have to test.
- Oh...
Oh, dizziness
is getting-
She's going into shock.
I need another liter of saline.
Type and cross two units.
What's happening
to her?
She's bleeding internally.
She's saying the shema.
She thinks she's dying.
The mri shows
you're bleeding internally,
But not where
it's coming from.
The blood can only
keep you stable for so long.
Our best option
is to open you up and search.
But you can fix it?
If we find the leak.
You find the bleeding,
you find the disease?
No.
But it could keep you alive
long enough
So dr. House can find
what's wrong with you.
No.
I don't want to have
the surgery...
It's the only chance
you've got.
I don't want to have
the surgery
Until after sunset.
I'm probably
gonna die anyway.
I just wanna share
one shabbat with my husband.
Roz, please.
The torah commands us
to preserve life.
I waited 38 years
to find what i wanted.
I can wait
another eight hours.
I'll leave the rest
to god, okay?
I had a rabbi call.
She's adamant.
She's not a masochist.
She's suicidal.
Nice work, chase.
Yeah. I should have
had twin rabbis call.
Can i go?
We need you.
So instead of a few days
we now have a few hours
To figure this out.
- Nice work, chase.
- Why do you need me?
Saying, "nice work, chase"
when you're not here
Is pointless.
Seriously, we need you.
We should x-Ray
for malformations of the rib
That could cause
arterial twisting.
Malformations don't cause
bloody urine.
She's not suicidal.
She made a commitment
to a new life with her husband
And she wants one meaningful
experience in that life.
- She just met the guy.
- Taub just met her.
And he's already so in love,
he's ready to let her die
And take her back
to the home planet
For a burial
in the lava sea of tormiad.
It's who he might be.
She's connecting with all
the years she's not gonna have.
Better way of connecting
to those years
Is to actually have them.
You want more time?
Joshua got god to make
the sun stand still.
No reason
god can't speed it up.
And, by god,
i of course mean you.
Told you
we needed you.
It's sundown, roz.
We're taking you back
to your room
For your candlelight
dinner.
Ready?
One, two three.
It's too early.
Your sense of time is off
because of the medication.
Good shabbos, roz.
So you pray,
scarf down some challah,
Then we can do this?
You wanted
to see me?
And you came.
I feel pretty confident
It'll be
something interesting.
Solvis case
and the job is yours.
Is there a "drop wilson" clause
attached to this?
Standard contract
all employees sign.
Why do you have to believe
i have an ulterior motive?
For the same reason
i believe
That crack whores
can have sex for crack.
All my life
I thought
i had to choose
Between love
and respect.
And i chose respect.
And with wilson...
I know what it's like
to have both.
And that beats
a fellowship.
Could be d. I.C.
You've changed.
I hope so.
Normal platelet count
rules out d. I.C.
Good try though.
I read that a hydatid cyst
could-
Would affect the lungs,
not the bladder.
Tested her white cell
count again.
Normal.
How long till we
get to cut her open?
When i left, he was still
singing eshet something.
The husband's blessing
of his wife.
Woman of valor.
"Strength and honor
are her clothing.
She laughs at the future. "
Because she's an idiot.
Volvulus of the small intestine
could cause bleeding.
She would have had
constipation.
Her value
isn't "beyond pearls" either.
'Cause dead people
have no value.
Polycythemia vera.
Rbc count would be higher.
I need to bring
the light to my face.
Thrombocytopenia.
If it's autoimmune-
Titers were normal.
Parkinson's would explain
the hypothermia.
Not the bloody urine.
The woman's not just
a masochist, she's a hypocrite.
The commandment
to preserve life
Comes before all others.
Actually means she's
not a masochist.
She's not following
all the rules,
Just the ones
that please her.
Right, she walked in crazy
And explained how ritual
trumps living,
And you decide
it's a beautiful lifestyle.
I know.
She's wrong.
But if there's
nothing more-
Then the only meaning
is here.
But if she thinks
god is there for her,
If she lives her life
believing that god is there-
Then she dies.
Things aren't where
we want them to be
Just because
we want them to be there.
Of course, that doesn't mean
they're where they should be.
Hey!
Stop that jew.
Chase hates working
on shabbos.
Gonna make this easier for him.
Stand her up.
She doesn't do so well
on her feet.
Neither do i.
Stand her up.
You can tell all the ladies
at the mikvah about this.
What did you do?
What are you doing?
Put your hand here.
Press hard.
You have nephroptosis.
Also known as
"floating kidney. "
The kidney's
like a chandelier.
It's attached to a ceiling of
intestines and blood vessels.
But your contractor-
Think you know who he is-
He hung it
with a cheap chain.
It's been hanging sloppy
for years.
Finally something
shook it loose.
After that,
every time you stood,
Your kidney dropped
a few centimeters,
Caused all your symptoms.
None of the scans
picked it up.
Because we do scans
with patients lying down.
She'd have been lying down
in surgery too.
Never have found it.
Good chance
she'd never come out.
She'll be all right?
Ultrasound to confirm,
Then tell chase to put
the kidney back on the shelf.
The bleed will be nearby.
That's... it?
Mazel tov.
Couple hours surgery,
You'll be ready
to push out those 14 children.
You do it both ways,
right?
What?
The ultrasound-You do it
standing up and lying down.
What else would i mean?
I've decided
you could do worse
Than a female proxy
for me.
So you're going to acknowledge
that people can change?
No.
You think i've changed
or amber's changed?
Nope.
Then you've changed.
If you do change,
can it be the part of you
That chases me down halls,
trying to change me?
Do you know
what this means?
That you made
one go dating choice.
The fabric of the space/time
continuum could unravel.
My world could expand.
I could form
a long-Term connection
That isn't with you.
And since you put
The darkest possible
construction on everything,
You could end up
losing a friend.
You've thought
of all this.
And yet...
You're going along with it.
Are you being...
self-Sacrificing?
I'll sacrifice a lab rat,
I'll sacrifice a fly,
And i'll sacrifice $200
on a mudder at monmouth park.
I don't sacrifice self.
Shabbat shalom, wilson.
Shabbat shalom, house.
?????????»?? -
=Http:/www. Ragbear. Com=- »¶?­????