Chinese water torture cell
Was invented in 1911
by Harry Houdini.
Nothing like new material.
He was lowered head first
into the water.
His ankle was locked and
bolted to the top of the tank.
I'm going to need a volunteer.
The guy dislocating
his shoulder...
Yeah...
Could you tell the guy
next to you to come up?
Come on,
get up there, man.
Get up there, get up there!
Come on!
- Hi. Have we met before?
- No.
See, if you said yes, you could
have gone back to your seat.
Now, can you vouch
for this audience
That this is
a glass tank full of water?
- Yeah.
- No, you can't.
You haven't done anything yet.
Come on.
Knock on the glass.
Solid glass.
Knock on it.
It's real water too.
Ilana, splash the guy.
Does that feel wet
to you?
- Yeah.
- And you think that proves it's water?
I think we have met.
Do you know
the public washroom
Behind the truck stop
east of omaha?
No.
See, if you'd said yes,
that would have been so funny.
Hold out your arms
for me.
You've done this
before, right?
No.
Again, two choices, and
you went for the unfunny one.
Now, remember,
there's only one thing
You've got to be able to do-
Drag a screaming,
crying, shackled man
Out of a tank of water.
Up!
Hey, you can swim, right?
Whoa, whoa,
tell me you can swim.
Yeah.
Two answers, man.
Two answers!
Is that part of the act?
I'm new.
I think so.
Maybe not.
Get up here!
House MD
Season 4 Episode 8
"You don't want to know"
Five eager doctors,
And no sick people.
Let us try and fill
our spare time
With a new challenge.
The winner gets immunity.
I have a sick guy.
I saw this magician last night-
The girl's fine.
He didn't really cut her
in half.
His heart stopped
While he was hanging
upside down in the water tank.
A drowning man's
heart stopped.
That is a mystery.
Along with immunity,
The winner
gets to nominate two-
He lost consciousness
Almost as soon
as he hit the water.
You have to leave work
at 6:00 p. M.,
But you make time
for man dates?
What's the challenge?
Are we not allowed
to be friends?
No, i'm just hurt.
When i asked you
to come see Mama Mia-
No history of heart disease.
No angina.
- No-
- He's lying.
- About his history? ER confirmed.
- About everything. He's a magician.
That's what they do.
He screwed up the trick,
he started drowning,
He got a cardiac arrest.
You were talking
about a challenge?
The winner nominates...
Two of your competitors.
I will fire one of them.
Even if he was drowning,
It would have taken longer
to set off a cardiac incident
Without some underlying
problem that-
Fine. Go run your tests.
If you're wrong,
you're fired.
If i'm right, do i stay?
If i say no, are you
gonna let your patient die?
What's the challenge?
We can all applaud the doctor
Who's willing
to break all the rules.
But the real hero
is the unsung doctor,
Toiling in anonymity,
'Cause he broke the rules
without getting caught.
I need to know
you have these skills.
I need you...
To bring me the thong
of lisa cuddy.
Not kidding.
Thong. Cuddy. Go.
It's how i got hired.
You're actually
considering this?
If you want to stand
on principle,
I really
respect you for that.
It's childish, unprofessional,
and inappropriate.
The job is not worth it.
We should all beg off.
Tell him we failed.
No winners, no losers.
Fine.
You're gonna do it,
aren't you?
Of course
i'm gonna do it.
No valvular regurgitation,
No wall motion abnorbnbnormalities,
no structural defects.
If you didn't sound
so despondent,
I'd say
that was good news.
It is for you,
not for him.
Notice any heaviness in your legs
the last couple days?
Why isn't it
good news for you?
Because, if there's nothing
wrong with you, he gets fired.
Seriously?
Somewhat seriously.
Your legs?
Haven't noticed anything
out of the ordinary.
- Shortness of breath?
- Would it help if i puked?
Pick a card.
Any tightness
in your chest or arms?
- Pick a card.
- You don't seem too worried.
Would you please
pick a card?
Our boss thinks
your cardiac arrest
Was just a result of you
accidentally drowning.
Your boss is an idiot.
Put it back.
Shuffle 'em up.
So then why
aren't you worried?
Either i'm dying
or i'm not.
I mean, i don't want
the ride to be over,
But unless worrying
Is some new form
of treatment...
Your card.
No.
I'm gonna prep you
for a transesophageal echo.
You sure you shuffled these?
And i'm gonna need
to sedate you.
Might wanna check
your wallet first.
Would you check your wallet?
It's part of the trick.
Oh.
That's my card.
How did you do that?
Do it again.
Thought you weren't playing.
I'm not.
She'll fire you
if she catches you.
I don't think
she can fire me
For not trying
to steal her panties.
You trying
to will them off?
If i had a plan,
The first part would be not
telling you what the plan was.
You haven't touched
that coffee.
Yes, i have.
She can't keep her panties on
if they're wet.
We work together.
One wins,
protects the other.
Or i win by myself,
And then you try desperately
to convince me to spare you.
Dr. Cuddy.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
Dr. Taub, are you okay?
I- I just tripped.
I'm so sorry.
I have some extra time.
Do you need any help
in the clinic?
Uh... okay.
We found no apparent
cause for the arrest.
T.T.E. And T.E.E.
Revealed no-
Send the patient home.
You can give him a lift.
We checked for clots.
We checked for-
You're reporting to me because
you're scared to report to house
Because you found nothing,
because this isn't a case.
And you thought
i'd save your ass.
Yeah.
I thought he was sick.
What was i
supposed to do?
What about his lungs?
Decreased oxygen saturation
leads to heart failure.
E.R. Didn't find
anything.
E.R. Wasn't looking.
Too busy trying
to keep him alive.
Get an mri.
Clinic.
Yes, can you ask dr. Cuddy
To come to the nurse's station,
stat?
Right away.
I asked you to get
doctor-
Dr. Taub said
she'd be right out.
A fungus in my lungs?
How would i even get
something like that?
Right now,
it's just a theory.
We don't even know
if it's-
I knew i shouldn't have done
those mushrooms in college.
I'm sure
there's no connection.
It was a joke.
You really lose
your sense of humor
When your job's
on the line, huh?
Sorry. Most dying people
don't really like to-
Not that you're dying.
But a little sick
would be perfect, right?
Yeah.
Aah! My stomach!
Stabbing or throbbing?
Grey turner's sign.
He's got internal bleeding
I'll call surgery.
Surgeons have transfused
three units ab positive,
But they're still looking
for the source of the bleed.
No trauma.
Could be liver disease.
Vitamin k deficiency.
The only thing we know
for sure it's not... nothing.
And we would have noticed
something chronic
Like liver disease.
It's probably
an intestinal infarct-
I got it!
Ahem.
Eau de cuddy.
No way.
How did you get them?
Only one way.
These are not cuddy's panties.
- You don't think that i-
- No.
Also, she's wearing
a red bra today.
Like i'm the only one
who noticed.
Means the downstairs
will match.
Do your research,
people.
An intestinal infarct
Could be linked
to the cardiac arrest.
Hike up your skirt.
Wow, that's rude,
even for you.
Hike it down then.
You're wearing
a black bra.
Let's see the underwear.
No!
You two cut a deal.
If you're not cheating,
you're not trying hard enough.
Is she not wearing
any underwear?
Um, there's a guy
bleeding-
Foreman, she's not wearing
any underwear.
You used to be more fun.
She's not wearing
any underwear-Big deal.
When she stops
wearing clothes,
Then we can drop
the medical stuff.
Let me see the mri film.
Oh, we didn't
get any images.
He started screaming
as soon as i turned it on.
Define "soon. "
Uh... i didn't even get
a chance to sit down.
You guys ever wonder
How he was gonna get out
of that water tank?
You-Come.
Lacerations
in his digestive tract.
And his spleen
is shredded.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have nothing
in my hands,
Nothing up my sleeve.
I do have something
in my pants,
But it's not gonna help
with this particular trick.
Watch closely.
How ya been?
Fine. Till now.
Ta-Da!
Now you... disappear.
Look familiar?
The mri's magnet ripped this
through your intestine
Into your spleen.
Forgot about that.
On account
of almost dying.
Where's dr. Kutner?
He's no longer
on your case.
'Cause there's nothing
wrong with you.
I didn't screw up
that trick.
Everything that's happened
can be explained
By you being forgetful
and incompetent.
You screwed up,
you passed out-
Know my favorite time
to lie?
When my life hangs
in the balance.
Your life doesn't hang
You know your life
doesn't hang in the balance.
Your reputation
might hang-
You ever do magic
as a kid?
You seem like
the type-
Lonely, obsessive.
I outgrew it. You?
Pick a card.
Too much trouble.
Can i just pick my nose?
I'm not a hack.
If i tell you how it's done,
will you go home?
So you gonna make it magically
appear in my wallet?
You are a hack.
I don't screw up.
A nosebleed that major
means he's actually sick.
Means the cardiac arrest
was a symptom.
Stop gloating.
I'm not gloating.
Then what's that smirk?
No smirk.
This is how i look.
What about
the underwear challenge?
I declare it
officially on hold.
Not really fair,
but i get it.
It's cuddy's.
Pull down your pants.
You think i'm lying?
No. I wanna give you
a reward.
Yes, i think
you're lying.
Cardiac arrest
plus nose bleed-Go.
Uh, patient has no significant
family history,
No angina,
no prior attacks.
What if it
isn't his heart?
What if it's the vessels
around his heart?
Polyarteritis nodosa
causes cardiac symptoms
And hypertension,
which makes his nose bleed.
You know what else makes your
nose bleed and your heart race?
Cocaine. Guy works in a b-List
nightclub in atlantic city.
He's gotta be taking
regular rolls in the snow.
You, take the gloater
to the patient's drug den.
Make sure you pat down
his pockets before you leave.
You and big love,
Biopsy of blood vessel
from around the heart.
Test for
polyarteritis nodosa.
You...
In my office.
Those aren't my panties.
I know.
Hypothetical.
A young woman
does something clumsy in public.
And instead of
laughing it off,
She gets
irrationally upset.
Explain.
Maybe she's clumsy
'cause she's nervous,
'Cause she forgot to do
her spelling homework.
In my hypothetical,
she's eight.
But this girl's
not insecure.
Seems more like
she's afraid.
Do you have a point,
Or did you just get
a new book of riddles?
I think you're hiding
a medical condition.
I'm not.
I'm glad we had this talk.
Doctors often try to ignore
their symptoms
'Cause they think
they can't get sick.
If you got something
going on,
I need you
to take care of it.
And i take your compassion
entirely at face value.
It's not compassion.
It's self-Interest.
I want my team healthy.
It's not self-Interest.
It's curiosity.
I dropped a file, house.
I start bleeding
from the eyes,
I'll be sure
to make an appointment.
Okay.
Eh, found some pot.
Bag it.
I'm not sure it really fits
the symptoms.
Of course not,
But it'd be irresponsible
to leave it here.
You have a quarter?
No.
How did cole get those panties
off cuddy?
They were never
on her.
No way those are hers.
Uh-Huh.
Tularemia.
No, you'd have
to have rabbits.
True-Maybe a tick
Jumped from a rabbit
and landed
On one of these
white, fluffy alligators.
Then it jumps
onto our patient,
Transfers the bacteria,
causes pericarditis.
Explains everything.
What are you giving me?
How'd you do the trick?
Oh, if i explain,
it becomes mundane,
And you lose
the actual magic.
What do you mean,
the actual magic?
Think you're actually
sawing women in half?
You gonna tell me what's
wrong with me or not?
Magic is cool.
Actual magic
is oxymoronic.
Might not even be oxy.
You're not gonna tell me
unless i tell you?
You got a nurse
to plant the card.
I can't get a nurse
to help me pee.
You got a buddy
to plant the card.
The fun...
is in not knowing.
is in knowing.
Oh, my head. Oh!
I got a headache.
How bad?
Is it new?
It's not too bad.
I'll-I'll just
take one of these...
Vicodin.
You eat a lot of beets,
you have an electric toothbrush,
And you sleep
less than six hours a night.
That's impressive.
The red betamine
from the beets
Stains the plaque deposits
on your teeth,
Which are then swirled
by your spinning toothbrush.
Your heavy lids
and your prematurely aging skin
Tell me that you're carrying
a major sleep debt.
That was way cooler
before you explained it.
It was meaningless
until i explained it.
People come to my show
Because they want
a sense of wonder.
They want
to experience something
That they can't explain.
If the wonder's gone
when the truth is known,
There never was
any wonder.
You have tularemia
from your rabbits.
I've put you
on antibiotics.
You'll be better
in a couple of days.
Sorry to spoil
the mystery.
Thank you.
Because
it's very important
To actually do it well.
I'll get it.
Oh... my... god!
You're not wearing
underwear!
Of course, i'm-
Skirt that tight,
you got no secrets.
i can tell if you got an i. U.D.
You've seen dr. Cole?
No.
You're blushing.
I am not.
Look at me.
Oh... my...
God!
How'd you do it?
So i'm safe?
In this job, yeah.
Crotch,
on the other hand...
How'd you do it?
Prayer, mostly.
Just tell me.
Does cuddy have
her groove back?
It'd be rude of me
to discuss.
You handed over
her panties.
I don't think Gallantry's
Really an option
at this point.
If i tell you,
then where's the magic?
(Kutner)
he passed out.
Ultrasound revealed bleeding
around his heart.
We drained 100 ccs
before it stopped.
The antibiotics
aren't working.
It's obviously not tularemia
or any other infection.
Excuse me-
We were talking.
(Taub) bleeding around the
heart could meaned biopsy
When cole was looking
for the-
Why would you accuse
the man who decides your fate
Of screwing up?
(Taub) those really were her panties?
Cole has traveled through
the forest of crustaceans
And brought us
a treasure.
And he has earned
his reward.
If i could just get
the immunity, i-
No, sophie, you can't.
Use whatever criteria
you want.
Could be
a clotting issue.
(Amber) if he developed
d. I.C. After the surgery,
Even a normal biopsy bleeds
out of control.
So cardiac arrest
and d. I.C.
What's the common denominator?
Could be cancer.
We've been looking in his chest
since he got here-It's clean.
(Taub) so the main mass is
somewhere else-Throws up a clot,
Blocks an artery in his heart,
causes the arrest.
Good!
Go find out where
he's hiding his cancer.
(Cole) if you swallowed any more metal,
Now would be
a good time to tell us.
My hands feel
kind of numb.
You lost a lot of blood.
I'm gonna die.
Everybody gets scared
in a hospital.
You're sick,
you feel awful-
No.
This time tomorrow.
I'll be dead.
So who's going
on the block?
He thinks he's dying.
He's probably right.
Tomorrow.
You decide to put me up,
i totally get it.
Nothing personal.
I haven't decided anything.
But you don't like me.
I like you.
Some fluid in the lungs.
No masses.
I'm manipulative.
[Typing]
I play the game.
I can be a bitch.
There's a dark spot.
Damage from where the key
ripped through.
You're probably expecting me
to bash the others,
Give examples
of how they screwed up.
You know i can.
I'm a good doctor.
As good as anybody
around here.
Probably better.
You know that's
the only thing that matters.
(Cole)
what's that?
It's not a tumor.
It's another bleed.
This one's in his kidney.
And his thigh.
He's bleeding
all over the place.
His Time-Table might be right-on
(Cole)
it was creepy.
The patient predicted
his own death.
(House) would have been more impressive
If he'd predicted
that he wasn't gonna die.
Of course,
that takes longer to prove.
(Cole)
could be a symptom.
Sense of impending doom.
Yeah, could be
adrenal gland disorders,
Blood issues,
anaphylaxis.
If you're gonna kiss his ass
to protect your ass,
At least wait
until he's had a good idea.
It's a symptom
of him being a charlatan.
He's a second-Rate magician
with a mysterious illness.
Why wouldn't he
predict his own death?
If he's wrong,
we all forget it.
If he's right,
he goes out a legend.
(Kutner) he got scared
right after a transfusion.
Tainted blood
has been known to cause
A sense of
impending doom.
Could also explain
the d. I.C.
I predict all your pagers
go off... right now.
Oh!
But if it had happened...
Anyone bother
looking at his panel?
His immunoglobulin levels
are low.
That doesn't tell us
anything specific about-
Are you acting stupid 'cause
you know you're safe? Clever.
(Foreman)
low immunoglobulin
Plus failing heart,
plus fluid in the lungs,
Plus internal bleeding,
equals amyloidosis.
He's bleeding way too much
for amyloidosis.
Say anything about his hands
or feet feeling weak?
(Cole)
he said his hands felt numb,
But that's explained
by the blood loss.
No! Do not give me
credit for that.
Close doesn't count.
That's how people get sucked
into this stupidity.
He's seizing.
Somebody stabilize him.
Rest of you,
pull his medical records.
Go back ten years.
Look for joint pain,
fatigue,
Anything associated
with amyloidosis.
Mr Flynn, node if you can hear me.
You had
a grand mal seizure.
We're giving you liquids
and an anticonvulsant.
Just try to rest.
Pulse is dropping.
He's stabilizing.
You're not gonna put me
on the block, are you?
I haven't decided
who i'm gonna pick.
That's cool.
His legs look swollen
to you?
Slight swelling
could be renal.
I babysat for you.
I decided i'm gonna make
my decision
Based solely on who
deserves to be here.
That's admirable,
though stupid.
You shouldn't save
the strongest.
You should get r the strong
Eliminate your competition,
which is definitely not me.
And i'm your friend.
And how are you
gonna explain to your kid
That i can't take him
to the zoo next week
Because you got me fired?
Kutner.
He's gonna seize again.
Flank pain.
His kidneys are shutting down.
Also... amber's a racist.
(Wilson)
you knew they'd get paged?
I noticed a trend-
If nobody does anything,
Sick people
often get sicker.
You think it's
remotely possible they had sex?
They're both single.
It's still legal
in the blue states.
She barely knows him.
You know,
in some cultures,
Hiring people to steal
someone's underpants
Is considered wooing.
You should move there.
Because here it's just,
you know, creepy.
There was no woo.
This was
an effective test.
This is beneath my skills.
(Kutner)
kidneys are shutting down.
Led to a sodium deficiency.
Caused him to seize.
Kidney failure
means i was right
About amyloidosis.
Except that nothing
in his medical history
Remotely indicates
amyloidosis.
So kidney failure proves
i'm right about the bad blood.
Bad blood doesn't explain
the heart or the liver.
His major symptoms didn't start
until after we transfused him.
Is cardiac arrest no longer
considered a major symptom?
Not when it's caused
by drowning.
So your new theory
Is that you're an idiot
to take this case.
Yes. Can i go test
that theory now?
Waste of time.
He needs a bone marrow
transplant for the amyloidosis.
You'd have to
irradiate him first.
If they're right
about the blood,
You'd be destroying
his immune system for nothing.
Which could be a good thing.
Does he have
a really crappy life?
Go prove i'm right.
Do a subcutaneous
fat biopsy.
At least let us
eliminate the bad blood theory,
Check the blood banks for
mis-Marks and contamination.
You've got two hours.
That's completely arbitrary.
No, if i'd said that
you got three lunar months,
That'd be
completely arbitrary.
Two hours is how long
it's gonna take big love
To finish a biopsy
that you guys can't do
Because you're wasting two hours
checking blood.
9-3.
5- All.
Hey. Brought you
something from the cafeteria.
It's not a bribe.
This is a bribe.
How much?
$1 million.
$5,000.
This is so wrong.
House specifically said
You can use
whatever criteria you want.
I've got money.
You need money.
Hand me that slide.
Right now, you're earning
what i'm earning,
Which is miserable.
I know what school
your kid's at.
I know what it costs.
I've seen his picture.
He's gonna need braces.
(Kutner)
No R.B.C. Damage.
(Thirteen)
Nothing wrong with storage.
I'm gonna double-Check type
and start cultures.
(Foreman) We've still
got 32 minutes left.
Time flies.
What have you found?
You're checking up on them-
That means cole's finished
With the biopsy,
and it was negative.
Inconclusive.
Fat doesn't always
give you the answer.
Need to biopsy
his actual organs-
Lungs, kidneys, liver.
We stick another needle in him,
he'll hemorrhage.
Unless we start treatment
for amyloidosis.
Unless it's not
amyloidosis.
If he has an infection,
the radiation will kill him.
Show me evidence
of infection.
We need
more than two hours.
Some of these cultures will
take at least a day to grow.
He'll be dead in a day.
Like he predicted.
O. He'll be
half a day off.
Would it make you guys
feel any better
If i let you argue with me
for... three minutes
Before i order you to treat
for amyloidosis?
No. Just treat
for amyloidosis.
No. Don't.
You're playing
the cuddy card?
That's why i'm here.
Amyloidosis was your idea.
I was wrong.
Yeah, me too.
You were never fun.
Give me the blood.
I'm type ab.
(Kutner) whatever's in
there could be killing him.
In where?
How much tainted blood
do you think they keep in here?
How many people
would have gotten sick-
It would have to have been
the first batch,
The splenectomy-That's when
the symptoms started.
Okay. So transfuse blood
from those donors.
I'll be fine.
We move on.
Treat for amyloidosis.
Fill 'er up.
(House)
I have a new theory.
You're not stubborn.
You're not
getting it checked
'Cause you already
know the answer.
I found an old picture
in your wallet.
Of course you did.
I wasn't snooping.
I needed lunch money.
Figure it's your mom,
Except she looks
about 32 years old.
The only reason
not to update a photo
In 20-Odd years
is she's not talking to you,
Which would be interesting,
Or she's dead.
Which would also
be interesting.
She's dead.
So's grover cleveland.
Pretty young
to have a dead mom.
You were even younger
20 years ago.
I googled her obituary.
Said she died
at new haven presbyterian
After a long illness.
Parkinson's?
Huntington's chorea.
I'm sorry.
I'm leaving
when this case is over.
No, you're not.
You don't want a doctor
on your team
Who's slowly losing control
of her body and mind.
Huntington's isn't the only
thing that causes tremors.
You think
it's just a coincidence?
I think you're
the only one on the team
Who drinks decaf.
I've been switching it out
with regular
Ever since you dropped
that file.
You're trembling 'cause
you're hopped up on caffeine.
The first file
wasn't my fault.
Medical explanation
for that is...
People drop things.
I've been walking around
thinking i'm dying...
You are.
You don't know that.
With huntington's,
it's inevitable.
No, you don't know,
because i don't know.
How could you
not get tested?
If your mom had it,
it's a 50% chance
You're a bomb
waiting to explode.
Not knowing makes me do things
i think i'm scared to do-
Take flying lessons,
climb kilimanjaro,
Work for you.
'Cause if you knew,
You couldn't do
any of those things.
What?
You're sweating.
You're burning up.
House...
You?
(Kutner)
Could be pneumococcus.
That'd cause chest pain
and the stiff neck.
It's not pneumococcus.
Let me check
your lymph nodes.
I'm not the patient.
Patient is the one
whose body is shutting down.
I'm having a benign
transfusion reaction.
Pseudomonas would present
as an armpit rash.
Take off your shirt.
You first.
House, you gotta
let us do this.
We can't biopsy him
without bleeding him to death.
You are not
biopsying me.
How's your stomach?
Any diarrhea?
[Exhaling]
the more transfusions you have,
The greater the chance
of you reacting.
I've had three
in a decade.
Fever'll be gone
in a couple of hours.
(Thirteen) i heard somewhere
that doctors ignore symptoms
Because they think
they can't get sick.
(Kutner) you told us to give you
the blood so that you wouldn't-
I am not sick.
Fever is a symptom.
But not of what
the patient has!
My kidneys are working.
I'm not bleeding
out of every organ.
Yet.
This is a waste of time.
And it's distracting you
from the actual case.
What's wrong?
The room is spinning.
You okay?
No, i'm dizzy.
My mouth just went dry.
Could be a symptom
of any number-
It's a symptom of narcotics.
Who spiked my-
What'd you drug him
with?
Amber's nickname
is cutthroat bitch,
And you're pointing
at me.
Got the kidney sample.
You're the only one
with nothing to lose.
Could have been you.
You don't seem to care
if you get this job or not.
Yeah, i've been here
for eight weeks
'Cause my subscription
to masochism weekly ran out.
You're the only one
who hasn't asked me
Not to put them
on the block.
You're either gonna pick me
or you're not.
You're fair enough to try
to make the right decision,
And arrogant enough
That nothing i can say
will change your mind.
I don't want it
to be over, but...
Unless worrying about it
is gonna make a difference...
I'm gonna run
some stains.
He'll be less
of an ass to you.
Patient dead yet?
No.
That's a little much
for a first date.
Obviously,
you've never dated me.
Feels like you already
got the...
Lung and kidney samples.
Now i just need
a piece of your liver.
Hey, you might wanna use
a little lidocaine-
Oh, yeah, i forgot.
Oh!
Slight pinch.
You drugged me.
Stopped by the lab.
Your mutinous team
is starting to worry
About life
on pitcairn island.
All your biopsies
are clean.
Because there's
nothing wrong with me.
Did foreman finally okay
The amyloidosis treatment?
Patient's scheduled
for irradiation at 9:00.
You risked your life again.
You couldn't be sure
he had amyloidosis.
You can't be sure
that i couldn't be sure.
You did one test.
It was negative.
Inconclusive.
Well, then, by all means
Flood your body
with possibly lethal blood.
I usually like to give
the lethal blood to foreman,
But i'm the only one
who's type ab.
Of course.
You're type ab.
Universal recipient.
You take from everybody.
Course, you're type o-
Universal donor.
No wonder you're paying
three alimonies.
How do you know...
what blood type i am?
I don't.
Just seemed to fit the metaphor.
No, no, no, no, no.
Did you test my blood
for something?
Why would you test
my blood for something?
I didn't.
You must have...
told me what you were.
Who the hell chats
about their blood type?
You had to have
tested me.
There's no reason to ask
anyone their blood type.
You're about to run
out of here, aren't you?
Nurse, can i have
a moment with my patient?
He's due
in radiation.
It's too late.
He's dying.
Told you.
I'm sorry i doubted you.
Be a shame if your secrets
died with you.
Perhaps you've got that trick
written down somewhere?
Or maybe you wanna tell me,
and i'll write it down for you.
That way...
you can live on.
I'm taking it with me.
See, that way,
It stays magic.
You were wrong
about everything.
It was never magic,
and you're not dying.
What's your blood type?
T- Type a.
What?
Trust me.
It's way cooler to know.
(Coleman)
where's finn?
Up my sleeve.
It's not amyloidosis.
And his blood's fine.
We just gave him
the wrong type.
'Caused the DIC.,
explains the bleeding.
Multisystem failures.
But we tested his blood.
That's because
we don't test blood for type.
We test for antibodies.
'Cause your body
only makes those antibodies
When you actually have
that type of blood.
Apparently,
he has one more symptom.
His body's making
an extra antibody-Type b.
Combine that with his
natural type a,
And presto change-O,
he magically pulls
Blood type ab
out of his hat.
Would you stop that?
God, yes!
(Thirteen)
autoimmune diseases
Can make antibodies
go haywire, but still...
It's happened... and apparently,
it's happened again.
I finally
have a case of lupus.
Flush him with saline.
Transfuse four units type a.
Start him on steroids.
He'll be back
hoodwinking idiots in no time.
Use their power wisely,
my lord.
I nominate... amber.
Cutthroat bitch...
Rise.
You're surprised?
You're everyone's pick.
Next victim.
I nominate...
Kutner.
Now everyone's surprised.
Why?
You said i don't have
to justify my picks.
No. I said you could use
whatever criteria you want.
Doesn't mean
i don't wanna know.
He was right
about this being a real case.
about the botched transfusion.
And he's
your love nugget.
You got no reason
to pick him.
But somebody else does.
Kutner's a liability.
He electrocuted himself,
lit a patient on fire.
It's only a matter of time
Before he burns
the hospital down.
You made the deal
with cuddy.
That's how you got
her underwear.
She sold it to you
For the right to put
her choices on the block.
You said
get her underwear.
I got it.
Your scheme was brilliant.
And you're fired.
You're all about
breaking the rules.
Her rules, not mine.
The whole point of this
was to subvert cuddy.
You became her partner,
Gave her power
she didn't already have.
Let her greedy fingers
into my cookie jar,
Which, sadly, is not
as dirty as it sounds.
Thanks for playing.
What the hell is this?
Looks like an envelope
with the results
Of the genetic test
for huntington's inside.
Did you look?
I thought it'd be fun
to find out together.
I don't want to know.
No. You're afraid
to know.
I might die.
So could you.
You could get hit
by a bus tomorrow.
The only difference is you don't
have to know about it today,
So why should i?
I don't have to know
the lottery numbers.
But if someone offered
them to me, i'd take them.
You spend your whole life
looking for answers...
Because you think the next
answer will change something,
Maybe make you
a little less miserable.
And you know that when
you run out of questions,
You don't just
run out of answers.
You run out of hope.
You glad you know that?