Whoever thought walking in a circle
at two miles an hour would be draining?
Fresh air, exercise.
You know, some things do
have their negative sides.
Our income just got cut in half.
And we get to spend twice
as much time together.
More, if you don't leave
before your lunch hour is over.
Out of my way.
We have a legal right to
hold you up for 15 seconds.
Fifteen, fourteen...
One.
Eleven, ten...
Ow!
Just trying to do my job.
Hey, relax. Three more
seconds and you can go.
Are you telling me what to do?
It's okay.
Just take a breath.
Get the hell off me!
I think it's been 15...
You okay?
Oh, my God. Jeff?
Standby.
Place is a mess.
Welcome to a world without nurses.
Here, you can start with these.
It's not my fault. I don't use nurses.
Cuddy was looking for you,
said she'd send you down here.
I know. That's why I'm here.
Because Cuddy hasn't found you yet.
She's going to look everywhere
except the place she wants me to be.
Hey. I've got an aortic dissection here.
What's with the idiot?
Fainting spell and a
recent history of dysgeusia,
everything tastes like
lemon meringue pie.
You want to take him?
No.
Sir!
Why do you have two
lunches in front of you?
Been here for two meals.
And you're happy with that? No.
I just don't see much
use in complaining.
Seriously?
It's a pretty useful tool.
You complain, make people miserable.
Then they do what you want,
to make the misery go away.
We probably should say something.
Maybe I can call one of doctors...
They're doing their best.
Ow!
What the hell?
I'm sure it was an accident.
Is he Canadian?
He's a low priority.
Is that a yes?
He's just... Happy.
I've got to stop this,
before it spreads.
You guys are done.
Could be a metabolic
disorder, toxic exposure,
carcinoma of the tongue metastasized
to the brain, epilepsy, M.S.
Or it could be the flu and we
should all be back in the E.R.
No, you're ignoring the big symptom.
What if we were looking at both
the flu and decent parenting.
Okay, you two are perfectly healthy.
This guy wasn't pandering.
He wasn't vanilla nice.
He was nice without any
aspiration of personal gain.
I'm thinking genetic defect.
Niceness is a defect?
Three cavemen see a stranger
running towards them with a spear
one fights, one flees, one smiles
and invites him over for fondue.
That last guy didn't last
long enough to procreate.
And how long has the
patient been suffering?
At least as long as his wife
has known him, eleven years.
The chances of him having an
undiagnosed pathology for that long...
What are you saying?
Evolution is wrong?
Where do you think we
are? 21st century America?
He's saying that
statistics are true, too.
The world is a bell curve,
most of us fall within
the standard deviation.
But there are outliers.
And if we believe in the
existence of extreme jerkiness,
which I suspect that we do,
then we also have to accept the
existence of the opposite extreme.
You want it to be a symptom, because
then we're supposed to be jerks,
which means you don't even
have to try to be nice.
Okay, maybe I am biased.
Let's take a vote.
Who thinks niceness is not a symptom?
And who thinks that their vote counts?
You two, check out his home
for toxins. Taub and 31...
31?
Oh, I'm sorry, I thought that
either way was good with you.
Taub and Thirteen, MRI for
tumors, EEG for nerve damage
and test whatever comes out
of him for everything else.
Too much axis tilt.
Don't release until your thumb's
at the bottom of the ball.
I assume Wilson was busy.
Again.
No axis tilt.
With Amber?
Again.
Still. It was nice of you
to invite me. This is fun.
No, it wasn't. No, it isn't.
I didn't invite you to
be nice, I invited you
because bowling isn't one of the
two things guys do by themselves.
What's the second thing?
Other hand.
Well, if people are incapable of
being nice, why bother having the word?
The ontological proof of niceness.
The existence of the word proves
the existence of the concept.
Look out for those
minotaurs on your drive home.
And I thought motives don't
matter, only results mattered.
So what are you gonna do?
To screw up Wilson's relationship
so you don't have to listen to me
while you bowl.
I wish the best for them, and
their tragically deformed children.
She's good at being bad.
You might not be able to destroy her.
As long as I give it my best
shot, I can hold my head high.
Cameron had this one
insufferable friend.
She wasn't going to get rid of her,
and I sure wasn't going to join them.
So I just said, "See her on Thursdays. "
I know it's not as exciting
as an exploding birthday cake,
but, hell, I don't want to hang
out with her every night anyway.
That's amazing. Cameron only
has one insufferable friend?
Joint custody.
Of Wilson?
Unless we have another love child.
Deal with him.
He needs a mother figure.
I'm not saying you're not
entitled to spend time with him.
I'm just saying I'm entitled, too.
I don't know how to deal with
him when he's being reasonable.
This is reasonable? This is crazy.
You're not a child, you
can make your own plans.
No. Crazy is what House would
normally do in this situation,
swap your lubricant with super glue.
The man knows me.
This is his way of accepting us.
It's actually a very touching moment.
I'm proposing I get every other
day and every other weekend.
I have Yoga Wednesdays,
you can have him then,
but you have to have him home by 11:00.
We can swap weekends.
Mondays and Wednesdays. And midnight.
If he's not home till midnight, we
won't be asleep till almost 2:00.
Wilson, make a ruling.
No.
You two are like dogs circling
each other in the park.
And I say that with all
the love in the world.
You need to sniff each
other's butts, bare your teeth
and arrive at some strange d?tente.
Otherwise you'll end up
biting each other's eyes out.
Again, with all the love in the world.
I'll let you sniff first.
Take my deal or get out of my apartment.
Take my deal or I move in.
This guy worked for Habitat
for Humanity in Costa Rica.
And coaches handicapped kids.
You think we should do a
work up, on the other coaches?
It is possible he's too perfect.
I'm not saying he's perfect,
I'm saying he's trying to be.
It's what people do.
What?
That's not what people do.
People usually suck, but they
want to be good, want to be nice.
House?
Exception that proves the rule.
What sort of argument is that?
Bad one.
That might be relevant.
Hydrofluoric acid. Lowers his calcium,
causes the fainting and taste issue.
But not the niceness.
Wouldn't that be nice?
You are King Solomon.
If you want us to cut him in
half, we're cool with that.
My boyfriend's too much of a
wuss to make the call for himself.
And I mean that with all
the love in the world.
I'm gonna piss off one of
them. And they both scare me.
"Your treatment of
patients is reprehensible. "
You're reading his performance review?
I'm busy. We have a nurses' strike.
"Your management of
employees borders on abuse. "
Let's go.
No, I... I want to hear it.
"You are overtly contemptuous
of hospital hierarchy. "
And covertly.
But I suppose, you
didn't know about that.
"Your attitude towards supervisory
personnel is disrespectful.
"And a disturbingly large proportion
of your comments are racist or sexist. "
That top makes you look
like an Afghani prostitute.
Would be an example of that.
Sign this.
House, I got the... It can wait.
I will sign if you
will give us a ruling.
I will give you a ruling if
you do the reviews on your team.
I'd be happy to continue
the mockery of this process.
What did you offer him?
Wednesdays till 11:00,
and alternate weekends.
Yes! Wednesday nights are
Ladies' Nights at Cheetah's.
Calcium's normal.
Wow. It really could wait.
Everything's normal. And
you thought it wouldn't be?
He's a carpet cleaner, he's got
a home full of hydrofluoric acid.
Doesn't mean his calcium should be low.
Yeah, actually, it kind of does.
HF causes lower levels of...
Lower, not low. Lower than normal.
Lower than yesterday.
Yesterday might have been high.
What's lower than high?
He actually has hypercalcemia,
which is being lowered
to normal by the HF.
So what gives us elevated
calcium, bad taste and fainting?
I take it you know.
Get the team. This is gonna be fun.
Hello, again.
These people think you're not too nice.
Too nice? For what?
For life as we know it to have evolved
without an intelligent designer.
I'm going to prove them wrong.
Your wife is very ugly.
Get out of here. Deb...
He's obviously trying to prove a point.
I think I just did. You're
either perfect or you're sick.
And in my experience,
sick is much more common.
He's not sick. He's nice.
Nice in the sense that your toaster
is nice for making you breakfast.
It's the only thing his
wiring will let him do.
He has Williams Syndrome.
Your husband is missing the
genes that make him suspicious.
You're wrong, he's...
Relax, there's no cure.
He's gonna go right on
tasting lemon meringue pie,
fainting and being a sap.
What about the other symptoms?
He has no other symptoms.
But Williams does.
He's got the teeth, the glasses...
Williams cuts IQ by 20...
He doesn't work in
the physics department,
except when they spill a
black hole on their carpet.
Elfin appearance?
Yeah, he's more Legolas than Keebler.
Bet you he can still crack
off a batch of Pecan Sandies.
Perfect pitch?
You love to karaoke, right?
I suck. Modest.
Another symptom.
No, he really does suck.
Give us a warble. Know any Cher?
No, but I know Bread.
Baby, I'm-a want you
Baby, I'm-a need you
You're the only one I
care enough to hurt about
Maybe I'm-a...
What's the matter?
He's stroking!
Not a moment too soon.
You were wrong.
Why do people say that with such
pleasure? It's very hurtful, you know.
It means the patient gets to keep
being nice. Why does that offend you?
It's the way he said it.
He wasn't relieved, he was
excited. He was also wrong.
And I say that with
no sense of pleasure.
Patient tested negative for Williams,
which means the stroke and
everything else wasn't caused...
You have a friendly demeanor but
you sometimes get too involved.
You relate well to your peers and patients
and you complete tasks in a timely manner.
Please sign.
What the hell was that? I have to give
each of you performance reviews.
Plenty of other conditions can
cause debilitating niceness.
How is that supposed to help him?
I don't know, how was it
supposed to help Wilson?
Cross out Wilson's name and the
date and then fill in your own.
The point of a review is
to give feedback to help...
I'm thinking neurosyphilis.
Wouldn't show up on the
MRI without contrast.
I'll go run the tests.
He doesn't think it's syphilis but
he's gonna go run those tests anyway.
Because he doesn't know,
that's why we do tests.
Because he's a wimp.
Because he's afraid of you.
You want me to intimidate
him into not being afraid?
Not sure I know how to do
that. Reviews make a difference.
People have to listen,
so they have to learn...
I don't think the right time to tell the
dog not to pee on the rug is semi-annually.
You don't want to do the paperwork.
I am concerned about the rain forest.
I'll do it.
I know.
I don't have syphilis.
You don't know.
How many ways are there to get it?
You can know who you had sex
with, you can't know who she...
I do.
Not for sure.
It's a waste of time. I had a
stroke. You can't keep wasting time.
We were tested for the Peace Corps.
Ten years ago.
You haven't been with your
wife every minute of every day.
You think I'm naive, don't you?
I think you're... Yeah.
I know my wife.
She's not perfect.
I'm not perfect. But she loves me.
And she's always loved me.
Every minute, every day.
You're 15 minutes late.
Have you heard the good news?
Miley Cyrus is playing a
third night at the Spectrum?
Happiness is possible. And not just in
this life but in the next. Where you can...
Oh, you're selling religion! I'm
sorry, I bought some Islam yesterday.
Well, it's where your light
showed signs before mending...
Have a good evening.
You're late. Fifteen minutes.
Sixteen minutes. My sixteen minutes.
So keep him an extra sixteen minutes.
You hear that? She doesn't care.
You're going mini-golfing, what's
it matter? You've got a tee-off time?
It matters because you don't
get to decide what matters.
It was my fault. I had to take a shower.
Which was my fault.
I have to take a dump.
Anything else I don't need
to know before you leave?
Have fun on your play date.
You've got mommy's numbers, right?
Daddy needs a drink.
I was thinking, if we
discount the niceness issue...
Sit down.
I think it's a heart
defect. Nothing on the echo.
Could be a patent foramen ovale.
Explains the stroke and the syncope
and a PFO wouldn't show
up on a routine echo.
I'm going to do a bubble test.
You got a minute, first?
Sure.
I think you've shown remarkable
strength in a difficult situation.
Are you giving me a performance review?
A good one.
I'm gonna do a bubble test.
There was enough blood left over from
his admission work up to run the VDRL.
You doubted your patient?
No, what I thought didn't matter.
House said he wouldn't let us go
on until we ruled out neurosyphilis.
It's not neurosyphilis, it's a PFO.
It's neurosyphilis.
The tests were positive.
It's always the same conversation.
They tell you you must be mistaken,
which is why I always run the tests
twice. Then they blame the other guy.
Which makes sense if they're innocent.
But, obviously, half of them aren't.
They don't seem to get that they're
busted. Scientifically proven.
Unless your spouse cheated, too.
Exactly. That's what you're praying for
in that moment, that she cheated, too.
And then, if she doesn't kill
you, you know that she did.
You'd know she betrayed you.
And then you realize
that that sucks worse.
The test must be wrong.
I ran it twice.
Not that test. The one
I took 10 years ago.
What other explanation is there?
He really sees no other possibility.
Did you have an affair?
No.
Then why aren't you angry with him?
You ever know anybody
who's just too nice?
No. It's annoying.
Then you realize it's annoying because
they remind you of what you're not,
that you'll never be
as good as they are.
And then you think, why can't I?
And before you know it,
that naive idiot you laughed at
has made you a better person.
You really think I've been in love
all these years with a symptom?
If syphilis caused lesions in his brain,
and the lesions caused
personality changes...
You may notice a change in
him, as his condition improves.
I know my husband. He's
not going to change.
You should get yourself tested.
So much for the bell curve.
How can House be an ass
without it being an illness,
but niceness is a biological crime?
You got five bucks?
Yeah...
Niceness just cost you five bucks,
being an ass generally turns a profit.
Kutner, could you excuse us?
I need to do Taub's review.
You can stay.
I think it'd be better if
this was done privately.
This isn't going to be done.
What is with you guys? I've
given you advice before.
Not as our boss.
What's the difference? Advice is advice.
Fair enough. I'll go first.
"You demonstrate a great air of confidence,
which is really pissing me off. "
House authorized me to...
How long have you known him?
He's using you. I volunteered
because I knew he wouldn't...
He could care less about the paperwork.
He's using you to screw with you.
He knows it'll annoy us,
we'll stand up to you,
which will force you to
confront the fact that
even though you think
you're our superior,
you're no different from us.
He gave you authority,
to keep you in your place.
It's true.
Thanks.
Not him. What did he say?
Nothing. What's true?
If there's something
wrong with this guy,
it means there's
something wrong with House.
Are you trying to get me drunk?
What time is it?
10:30.
She'll kill you.
I'll get you home before lights out.
Great, then she'll kill me.
If I get any more drunk...
It might not work.
If you know what I mean.
Really?
You'd think one or more of your
ex-wives would have mentioned that to me.
They told you? Wait.
Why do you want to get Amber angry?
Because I'm your friend.
No, no, no, you said you approved.
You said you were taking the high road.
For how long, the first exit?
Hello, and thank you from saving
me from being righteous to death.
Patient's vomiting blood.
Hematemesis could indicate...
Don't put it on the board.
You don't think it's a symptom?
I think it's my marker.
He has syph and what?
And syph. It can cause hematemesis.
Not everyone agrees.
How could you...
Because if you all
thought it was just syph
you wouldn't have woken me
up in the middle of the night.
If it was just syph, he
wouldn't be getting worse.
He's already on penicillin.
The bleeding's probably
from liver damage,
probably caused by ethanol in
the cleansers or the penicillin.
Two more probablies than I like to hear.
Liver test and serologies,
are going to take a full day.
Full night, actually.
Guy might not make it to brunch.
Yes, I knew about your
issue with alcohol.
Yes, I intentionally got you drunk
to provoke an argument,
between you and Amber.
And why I'd do such a thing
is an interesting question.
But what's more interesting is
that you knew as much as I did,
and you're the one who's
pouring down the drinks. Why?
Because I thought I was out
having fun with a friend.
I didn't know these drinks had subtext.
I gotta get home.
GGT's normal, that rules out alcohol.
What about serum protein?
It's positive.
Kind of assumed he had protein.
It's how much protein he
has that we care about.
He's positive for syphilis.
Do you mind if I give
you a performance review?
Not the patient. House. He has syphilis.
What happened?
Every time I searched
my soul, I found Anna.
Are you going to tell Marie?
I have to.
It will destroy her!
Will it be any worse...
Yes?
You might want to turn the off TV.
I'm multitasking. Also
doing my taxes. And Cuddy.
What did you find out?
Patient has hepatitis.
I assume from your omission of
the word "viral" before the "hep"
that it's not another STD.
Put him on steroids and test him
for sarcoid before the liver failure
becomes liver failed.
We're all doing this.
There's more?
You have syphilis.
Love lasts forever.
No, I don't.
One of us found a vial of your
blood in the lab from when we...
Which one of you?
It's treatable.
We filled a prescription.
You okay?
So, this is why he is who he is.
We don't know.
We know. It's not just a coincidence.
Wilson says he's always been a jerk.
But he got worse.
After his leg.
The leg was a coincidence.
Did you sleep with him?
So what's going to happen?
What's gonna change?
Maybe he'll be less of a jerk.
Or less of a doctor.
You gotta be a jerk to be a good doctor?
I don't know. Maybe House does.
Why aren't you answering me?
Because it's none of their business.
It's none of your business.
I think the STD makes it my business.
Humans are complicated.
Humans are simple.
A million different
things make us who we are.
You change one, you change everything.
If Mozart was better adjusted,
decides to play catch one day,
maybe there's no Magic Flute.
You did, didn't you?
Something I need to tell you.
You returned him drunk.
On time. Drunk.
On time. No tag backs.
The purpose of the time
was to give me time.
So you didn't have sex...
I like sex. You can have it tonight.
The L Word is on.
You don't get to decide what matters.
Either you're genuinely afraid
I'm gonna make him miserable,
or you're afraid I'm gonna make him
happy, or you simply can't stop screwing
with anything that moves. It doesn't
really matter because, whatever the reason,
you'll only get worse. Until
either I stop seeing Wilson
or I stop you.
What do you think I'm going to choose?
If you terminate the agreement, that's
not gonna bring peace to the Mideast.
I'm not terminating the agreement.
I'm amending the agreement.
I'm adding penalty clauses.
Fine. Whoever violates it
gets their finger cut off.
I'm serious. So am I.
You want people to drive safer,
take out the airbags and attach
a machete pointing at their neck.
No one will drive over
three miles per hour.
I'm not cutting... We'll figure it out.
On your time.
You know she's certifiable,
right? I got forms in my desk.
Where is she wrong?
What were you going to tell me?
Nothing.
You're punishing me?
I needed to tell you
something privately.
I'm not gonna tell her.
You'll tell her. She's your
girlfriend. You should tell her.
You're my friend.
It's not the same.
Don't sulk.
Where am I wrong?
"Your management style
is counterproductive.
"You gave me authority over the
team just so they could undercut... "
Critiquing the clap-addled?
Sort of tasteless.
I don't feel like waiting
until your genitals cleared up.
You need to formalize my
authority over the team.
No, I don't.
You don't think I'm qualified?
Compared to those three?
You want to punish Cuddy
for hiring me without...
I like Cuddy.
Parts of her.
You want to crush the
team, by crushing me?
I want to empower them.
Those three idiots need to respect you.
They should respect you.
They should be afraid of you.
So I have to humiliate you.
See, if the team fears you,
they won't question you,
if they don't question you,
they won't get any answers,
if they don't get any
answers, they're useless.
Mocking me saves lives?
Hospital will probably
build you a statue one day.
You know, with a "kick me" sign on the back.
So when you think about
it, the more I mock you,
the more it shows that
I have respect for you.
Or you made up that B.S.
Because you like humiliating me.
Wouldn't rule that out completely.
You busy?
Almost done.
So just remember, the rabbit goes
around the tree and jumps down the hole.
Negative for sarcoidosis.
Run him for everything you can think of.
Lepto, schisto, hemo and the fourth
Marx Brother nobody ever heard of.
You bitch!
I just went to get us some
lunch. You were asleep.
You moved my book!
Jeff, calm down, it's just the drugs.
The drugs didn't move my...
Jeff?
My husband's having a heart attack!
Can somebody help me, please?
Somebody help me, please!
She saved his life.
Or she scabbed. Depends
on your point of view.
So, what do we think? New
symptom? Or just a wife beater?
Hey.
Time for you took this baby for a spin.
We loaded him full of prednisone
to try to fix the liver.
Good news is, he's running
out of organs to fail.
Prednisone could cause roid rage,
which could cause hypertension,
which results...
Roid rage after six hours?
That rate, by sundown,
he'll have eaten most of us.
Still could be the
penicillin, allergic reaction.
How does a fried liver
put him into a rage?
It's not frying his liver,
it's frying his syphilis.
The penicillin's working.
The real patient's emerging.
So syphilis prevents domestic violence.
I'm gonna be even more
attractive to the ladies.
I was about to test for a
heart issue before the syphilis.
PFO could explain the heart attack,
and reduced blood flow to the
brain could explain the rage.
Well, they're all good ideas.
Okay. Let's take a vote.
How many think it's the roids talking?
And who's for the penicillin?
And how about whatever she said?
Someone hasn't raised their hand.
Whatever I decide?
You're setting me up.
Why would I do that?
PFO.
PFOs have it.
I just hope the bubble test is
positive. Or it's no more Mr. Nice Guy.
We gave van Gogh chelation therapy.
Turned him into a house painter.
Maybe not. Maybe we just
put Hitler on Ritalin.
Are you comparing House to Hitler?
Oh, God.
Just because I don't think he's
Hitler doesn't mean I slept with him.
I don't sleep with everyone
who's better than Hitler.
Maybe Taub's right. Maybe this is good.
This is not good.
He respected our opinions, he mocked
himself, he was civil, he shared.
He didn't care.
He never cares.
He didn't vote. He always
cared about one thing,
solving the puzzle.
But he was irrelevant in that
diagnosis, he had no opinion of his own.
He now cares about nothing.
You had no choice, you had to
treat him. What's done is done.
You know that thing I was going
to tell you? I gotta tell you.
I got to tell someone. You
have to swear not to tell C.B.
Whatever. That's not
swearing, that's shrugging.
It's actually the opposite of swearing.
I won't tell Amber.
My team thinks that I have syphilis.
Do you? Not yet.
Why do they think you do?
Because I knew they had
access to an old blood sample.
I knew they'd test it
sometime for something.
Why would you swap your blood?
What are you afraid they'd find?
Shut up, you're missing the point.
Now they think that I'm on penicillin.
Is this some clever practical
joke that I'm not aware of?
And as I get better, I get nicer.
That's brilliant.
Foreman thinks I actually
value his opinion.
Thank God he said PFO or I'd
have had to do some dancing.
You got time for bowling?
Come on, it's work hours.
I'll get my shoes.
So we don't need to talk about... No.
You're gonna keep screwing... Yeah.
And you're gonna keep talking
about it. We are who we are.
I'll get my shoes.
Okay, got a good view of the heart.
What if we lower House's
dosage? Maybe stabilize him?
He doesn't get worse,
he doesn't get better.
Quite the line to walk. If we're
wrong, he dies of neurosyphilis.
If we don't, other people die.
Other people who aren't our boss.
People.
This sucks. The guy
had a gift. I killed...
Hi. What...
House doesn't have syphilis.
He switched the blood samples.
How do you know that?
House told Wilson.
I wanted to ruin House's day. See you.
We're idiots. We're not idiots.
Positive blood test
means positive blood test.
Apparently not.
There they are. Let's see if they...
What are you doing? We're not done.
He doesn't have syphilis.
I know.
Patient tested positive
for syphilis, right?
Is this some sort of recap?
But why did he test
positive for syphilis?
Oh, oh, I know this.
Either, one, he has syphilis.
I was gonna say that.
Or two, the test was wrong twice.
Or three, he gave us
someone else's blood.
Who? Amber.
Get that idiotic smile out of my
face, I got to go on a killing spree.
Or four, he has something that
tests positive for syphilis.
It's not Chagas. He
worked in Costa Rica,
before he was married.
Is two a spree or do
I have to kill you too?
Chagas wouldn't explain the niceness.
I've heard of remote tribes that
actually practice acts of kindness.
Or the Chagas caused encephalitis.
The MRI showed no signs...
Until we started him on steroids,
compromised the immune system
and let the infection flare up.
I did another one. It's not much.
It's plenty.
You figured this out because
I don't have syphilis?
Damn.
It should have been my epiphany.
Good news and bad news.
Good news is, we know what you have,
it's treatable, and
you're going to live.
Really?
What's the bad news?
The cure is a grueling course of pills.
It's like
one a day for a month.
Now you're just trying to make me laugh.
Yeah, like that's a challenge.
You have Chagas disease.
It's a parasite. It's been
asymptomatic for 10 years.
Not quite. Your brain's been
swollen, not enough to see,
but enough to alter your personality.
We're back to that?
He screamed at you, you
don't think he can change?
That was because of the drugs.
So you think drugs are more
powerful than parasites?
I mean, the ones we're gonna give you
to treat the parasites obviously are,
but I stand by the principle.
I'm not worried.
Neither am I.
Neither am I. But that's
because I don't care.
Reviews?
It was brought to my
attention that, on occasion,
I am not respectful
of hospital hierarchy.
The word was "contemptuous. "
Well phrased, thoughtful...
Identically phrased.
These are all the same.
Because underneath it
all, we are all the same.
And Foreman refused to type his up.
Well, it's more than I expected.
There's an extra one in there.
"Your treatment of
patients is nonexistent
"because you're not a doctor,
you're an administrator. "
Foreman convinced me that
these could be helpful.
"Your management of employees is,
well, let's face it, they're
outside carrying signs. "
The strike ended. The nurses have
been back for two shifts already.
You'd think I'd have noticed. What
exactly did they do around here?
"You act like employees should fear and
respect you, but your eyes tell us...
"Actually your eyes tell us nothing,
because we're looking at your boobs,
"which tell us that you're
desperate to have someone jump on you
"and tell you they love you
one grunted syllable at a time.
"What you want, you run away from.
What you need, you don't have a clue.
"What you've accomplished
makes you proud.
"But you're still miserable. "
Please sign.
I got a call from Amber today. Says
there's been a violation your contract.
You've been seeing Wilson on her time.
She breached confidentiality. You
can let it slide, Officer, we're even.
Yes, you are. You're
both losing fingers.
Look what I found.
Nice.
They think you might be
able to come home tomorrow.
Yeah? That's good.
What's the matter?
The ketchup. There's
something wrong with that.
Tastes fine. Is there anything else?
Everything else is great.
I just, I don't know, I guess
I don't like ketchup anymore.
Wonder what else I don't like.
Roll over.
We need a tougher punishment.
You want to come over to the poopy side?
So where are you two going Friday night?
Dinner at L'Auberge.
You're lying.
Of course I am.