Great.
Meredith.
Hello?
System disarmed.
System armed.
Hey, Meredith, it's Kristin.
You have to tell me what happened
last night. Call me.
Hey Meredith, it's Dereck.
Where have you been?
I've tried to get you all day
'cause I got maybe something's
gonna please you.
Guess what. Call me when you come back, ok?
So if you wanna solve that mystery,
call me. Alright. Bye.
Hey, Meredith. Listen,
All right, Dean,
this is the place.
I've got to say dad and me did just fine
without these stupid costumes.
I feel like a
high-school-drama dork.
What was that play that you did?
What was it... "Our Town".
Yeah, you were good.
It was cute.
Look, you want to pull this off or not?
I'm just saying these outfits
cost hard-earned money.
- Whose?
- Ours.
You think credit-card fraud is easy?
Thanks for letting us look around.
The police said they were done
with the place, so...
You guys said
you were with the alarm company?
That's right.
Well, no offense, but
your alarm is about
as useful as boobs on a man.
Well, that's why we're here,
to see what went wrong,
to stop it from happening again.
Now, ma'am, you found the body?
Yeah.
Right after it happened?
No, a few days later.
Meredith's work called.
She hadn't showed up.
I knocked on her door.
That's when I noticed...
the smell.
Any windows open?
Any sign of break-in?
Windows were locked.
Front door was bolted.
Chain was on the door.
We had to cut it to get in.
And the alarm was still on?
Like I said.
Bang-up job your company is doing.
Did you see any overturned furniture,
broken glass, signs of struggle?
Everything was in perfect condition...
except Meredith.
Well, what condition was Meredith in?
Meredith was all over,
in pieces.
The guy who killed her
must have been a whack job.
But I tell you,
if I didn't know any better,
I'd have said a wild animal did it.
Ma'am,
you mind if we take some time,
give this place a once-over?
Go right ahead.
Knock yourself out.
So the killer walks in and out
of the apartment...
- no weapons, no prints, nothing.
- I'm telling you,
the minute I found that article,
I knew this was our kind of gig.
I think I agree with you.
So, you talked to the cops?
Uh, yeah, I spoke to Amy...
a, uh, charming, perky officer of the law.
- What did you find out?
- Well, she's a sagittarius.
She loves tequila. I mean...
Oh, and she's got this little tattoo.
- Dean!
- What? Yeah.
Nothing we don't already know,
except for one thing they're
keeping out of the papers.
Meredith's heart was missing.
Her heart?
Yeah, her heart.
So, what do you think did it to her?
The landlady said
it looked like an animal attack.
Maybe it was.
- Werewolf?
- Not a werewolf.
The lunar cycle's not right.
Plus, if it was a creature, it would've left
some kind of trace.
It was probably a spirit.
See if you can find
any masking tape around.
Ever see that symbol before?
Never.
Me, neither.
I want to step on your hands
and cut the rope
and the twine tangled up
on your mind, love
On the outside.
On the hillside.
We can play with the paste all night.
I talked to the bartender.
Did you get anything...
besides her number?
Dude,
I'm a professional.
I'm offended that...
you would think that.
All right.
You mind doing a little bit of thinking
with your upstairs brain, Dean?
Hmm?
There's nothing to find out.
Meredith worked here.
She waited tables.
Everyone here is her friends.
Everyone says she's normal.
She didn't do or say anything
weird before she died. So...
What about that symbol?
Did you find anything?
Nope. Nothing.
It wasn't in dad's journal
or in any of the usual books.
I just have to
dig a little deeper, I guess.
There was a first victim, right,
before Meredith?
Right, yeah. His name was, uh...
his name was Ben Swardstrom.
Last month he was found mutilated
in his town house.
Same deal. The door was locked.
The alarm was on.
- Is there any connection between them?
- Nothing I could tell.
I mean not yet, at least.
Ben was a banker. Meredith was a waitress.
They never met, never knew anyone in common.
They were practically from different worlds.
So, to recap, the only successful intel we've scored
so far is the bartender's phone number.
What?
Sam!
Well, we talked about you and
we've heard about you...
Meg.
Sam!
Sam, is that you?
Oh, my gosh!
What are you doing here?
I'm just in town... visiting friends.
Where are they?
Well, they're not here right now,
but what about you, Meg?
I thought you were going to California.
I did.
I came. I saw. I conquered.
Oh, and I met what's his name...
something Michael Murray, at a bar.
Who?
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, the whole scene got old,
so I'm living here for a while.
- You're from Chicago?
- No, Massachusetts.
Andover.
Gosh, Sam,
what are the odds we'd run into each other?
I know. I thought I'd never see you again.
Well, I'm glad you were wrong.
Dude, cover your mouth.
Yeah, I'm sorry, Meg. This is, um...
This is my brother, Dean.
- This is Dean?
- Yeah.
So you've heard of me?
Oh, yeah, I've heard of you.
Nice,
the way you treat your brother like luggage.
- Sorry?
- Why don't you let him do what he wants to do?
Stop dragging him over god's green earth.
Meg... it's all right.
Okay. Awkward.
I'm gonna get a drink now.
Sam, I'm sorry.
It's just,
the way you told me he treats you,
- if it were me, I'd kill him.
- It's all right.
He means well.
- We should hook up while you're in town.
- Yeah.
- I could show you a hell of a time.
- That sounds great.
Why don't you give me your number?
312-555-0143.
You know what? I never got your last name.
- Masters.
- Masters?
So you better call.
Scout's honor.
I hope to see you around, Sam.
Who the hell was she?
I don't really know. I only met her once.
Meeting up with her again?
I don't know, man. It's weird.
What was she saying...
I treat you like luggage?
Were you bitching about me to some chick?
Look, I'm sorry, Dean.
It was when we had that huge fight
when I was in the bus stop in Indiana.
But that's not important.
Is there any truth to what she's saying?
Am I keeping you against your will, Sam?
No, of course not. Now, would you listen?
What?!
I think there's something strange
going on here, Dean.
Tell me about it. She wasn't even into me.
No, man, I mean, like our kind of strange.
- Like maybe even a lead.
- Why do you say that?
I met Meg weeks ago
literally on the side of the road.
Now I run into her in some random
Chicago bar...
the same bar where a waitress
was slaughtered by something supernatural.
You don't think that's a little weird?
I don't know, random coincidence,
it happens.
Well, yeah, it happens, but not to us.
Look, I could be wrong. I'm just saying
that there's something about this girl
that I can't quite put my finger on.
But I bet you'd like to.
But maybe she's not a suspect.
Maybe you got a thing for her, huh?
Maybe you're thinking too much with
your upstairs brain, huh?
Do me a favor.
Check and see if there's really
a Meg Masters from Andover, Massachusetts
and see if you can't dig anything up
on that symbol on Meredith's floor.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna watch Meg.
I just want to see what's what.
Better safe than sorry.
All right, you little pervert.
I'm going. I'm going.
Hey.
Let me guess. You're lurking outside that
poor girl's apartment, aren't you?
No.
Yes.
You've got a funny way of showing
your affection.
You find anything on her or what?
Sorry man, I should check this out.
There's a Meg Masters in the
Andover phone book.
I even pulled up her high-school photo.
Now, look, why don't you go
knock on her door
and invite her to a
poetry reading or whatever it is you do.
What about the symbol? Any luck?
Yeah, that I did have some luck with.
Turns out it's zoroastrian.
Very, very old-school,
like 2,000 years before Christ.
It's a sigil for a Daeva.
- What's a Daeva?
- It translates to "demon of darkness"...
zoroastrian demons,
and they're savage, animalistic,
nasty attitudes;
kind of like demonic pit bulls.
- How did you figure that out?
- Give me some credit, man.
You don't have a corner on paper
chasing around here.
Name the last book you read.
I called dad's friend, Caleb.
He told me, all right.
Anyway, here's the thing.
These Daevas, they have to be summoned.
Conjured.
So someone's controlling it?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
And from what I gather,
it's pretty risky business, too.
These suckers tend to bite the hand
that feeds them...
and the arm and the torsos.
- So what do they look like?
- Nobody knows.
Nobody's seen them for a couple
of millennia.
Summoning a demon that ancient,
someone really knows their stuff.
I think we've got a major player in town.
Why don't you go give that girl
a private strip-o-gram?
- Bite me.
- Bite her.
Don't leave teeth marks, though. It's not...
Sam?
- No, no, I'm just...
- Pervert!
I don't think you should come
because the brothers,
they're in town. I didn't know that...
Yes, sir.
Yes, I'll be here...
waiting for you.
What the hell?
Dude, I've got to talk to you.
So, hot little Meg is summoning the Daeva?
It looks like she was using that black altar
to control the thing.
So Sammy's got a thing for the bad girl.
- And what's the deal with that bowl again?
- She was talking into it...
the way witches used to scry
into crystal balls or animal entrails.
She was communicating with someone.
- With who? With the Daeva?
- No, you said those things were savages.
No, this was someone different,
someone who's giving her orders, someone
who's coming to that warehouse.
Holy crap.
What?
What I was gonna tell you earlier.
I pulled a favor with my...
friend Amy, over at the police department.
The complete records of the two victims.
We missed something the first time.
What?
The first victim, the old man?
He spent his whole life in Chicago,
but he wasn't born here.
Look where he was born.
Lawrence, Kansas.
Meredith, the second victim?
It turns out she was adopted.
And guess where she's from?
Holy crap.
Yeah.
I mean, that is where the demon killed mom.
That's where everything started.
You think Meg's tied up with the demon?
I think it's a definite possibility.
But I don't understand!
What's the significance of Lawrence?
And how do these Daeva things fit in?
I say we trash that black altar, grab Meg,
and have ourselves a friendly little interrogation.
No, we can't.
We shouldn't tip her off.
We've got to stake out that warehouse.
We've got to see who...
or what, is showing up to meet her.
I'll tell you one thing.
I don't think we should do this alone.
We think we've got a serious lead
on the thing that killed mom.
So, uh,
this warehouse... it's
1435 west erie.
Dad, if you get this,
get to Chicago as soon as you can.
Voice mail?
Yeah.
Jeez.
What'd you get?
I ransacked that trunk...
holy water, every weapon
that I could think of.
Exorcism rituals from about
a half-dozen religions.
I'm not sure what to expect, so I guess
we should just expect everything, huh?
It's a big night.
Yeah.
You nervous?
No.
Are you?
No. No way.
God, could you imagine if we actually
found that damn thing, that demon?
Let's not get ahead of ourselves,
all right?
I know. I'm just saying...
what if we did?
What if this whole thing was over tonight?
Man, I'd sleep for a month,
go back to school, just
be a person again.
- You want to go back to school?
- Yeah,
once we're done hunting the thing.
Huh.
Why? Is there something wrong with that?
No, no, it's great. Good for you.
I mean,
- what are you gonna do when it's all over?
- It's never gonna be over.
There's gonna be others.
There's always gonna be something to hunt.
But there's got to be something that
you want for yourself.
Yeah, I don't want you to leave the second
this is over, Sam.
Dude,
what's your problem?
Why do you think I drag you everywhere?
Why do you think I came and got you
at Stanford in the first place?
'Cause dad was in trouble.
'Cause you wanted to find the thing
that killed mom.
Yes, that, but it's more than that, man.
You and me and dad...
I want us to...
to be together again.
I want us to be a family again.
Dean,
we are a family.
I'd do anything for you.
But things will never be the way
they were before.
They could be.
I don't want them to be.
I'm not gonna live this life forever.
Dean, when this is all over,
you're gonna have to let me go
my own way.
Guys.
Hiding is a little bit childish,
don't you think?
That didn't work out like I'd planned.
Why don't you come out?
Sam,
I have to say, this puts a real crimp
in our relationship.
Yeah, tell me about it.
So,
where's your little Daeva friend?
Around.
And that shotgun's not gonna do much good.
Oh, don't worry, sweetheart.
The shotgun's not for the demon.
So, who is it, Meg?
Who's coming?
Who are you waiting for?
You.
Hey, Sam,
don't take this the wrong way,
but your girlfriend...
is a bitch.
This,
the whole thing, was a trap.
Running into you at the bar,
following you here,
hearing what you had to say...
it was all a set up, wasn't it?
And that the victims were from Lawrence.
It doesn't mean anything.
It was just to draw you in, that's all.
- You killed those two people for nothing.
- Baby, I've killed a lot more for a lot less.
You trapped us.
Good for you.
It's miller time.
Why don't you kill us already?
Not very quick on the up take, are we?
This trap isn't for you.
Dad.
It's a trap for dad.
Oh, sweetheart,
you're dumber than you look.
'Cause even if dad was in town,
which he is not,
he wouldn't walk into something like this.
He's too good.
He is pretty good, I'll give you that.
But you see...
he has one weakness.
What's that?
You.
He lets his guard down around his boys,
lets his emotions cloud his judgment.
I happen to know he is in town,
and he'll come
and try to save you.
And then the Daevas will kill everybody...
nice and slow...
and messy.
Well, I've got news for you.
It's gonna take a lot more than some...
shadow to kill him.
Oh, the Daevas are in the room here.
They're invisible.
Their shadows are just the only part
you can see.
Why are you doing this, Meg?
What kind of deal you got worked out
here, huh...
- and with who?
- I'm doing this for the same reasons you do what you do.
Loyalty,
love.
Like the love you had for mommy...
and Jess.
Go to hell.
Baby, I'm already there.
Come on, Sam.
There's no need to be nasty.
I think we both know...
how you really feel about me.
You know...
I saw you...
watching me...
changing in my apartment.
It turned you on, didn't it?
- Get a room, you two.
- I didn't mind.
I liked that you were watching me.
Come on, Sammy,
you and I can still have a little dirty fun.
You want to have fun?
Go ahead, then.
I'm a little tied up right now.
Now, were you just trying to distract me
while your brother cuts free?
No.
It was because I have a knife of my own.
Sam! Get the altar!
So, I guess the Daevas
didn't like being bossed around.
I guess not.
Hey, Sam?
The next time you want to get laid,
find a girl that's not
so buckets of crazy, huh?
Why don't you just leave that stuff
in the car?
I said it before, and I'll say it again...
better safe than sorry.
Hey!
Dad.
Hey, boys.
Hi, Sam.
Hi, dad.
Dad, it was a trap.
I didn't know. I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I thought it might have been.
Were you there?
I got there just in time to see the girl
take the swan dive.
She was the bad guy, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Well,
it doesn't surprise me.
It's tried to stop me before.
- The demon has?
- It knows I'm close.
It knows I'm gonna kill it.
Not just exorcise it or send it
back to Hell,
actually kill it.
How?
I'm working on that.
Let us come with you. We'll help.
No, Sam.
Not yet.
Listen, try to understand.
This demon is a scary son of a bitch.
I don't want you caught in the crossfire.
- I don't want you hurt.
- You don't have to worry about us.
Of course I do.
I'm your father.
Listen, Sammy,
the last time we were together,
we had one hell of a fight.
Yes, sir.
It's good to see you again.
It's been a long time.
Too long.
No!
Shot your ass!
These things are shadow demons,
so let's light 'em up!
Dad!
Over here!
Come on!
All right, come on. We don't have much time.
As soon as the flare's out, they'll be back.
Wait, wait!
Sam, wait.
- Dad, you can't come with us.
- What?
What are you talking about?
You boys...
- you're beat to hell.
- We'll be all right.
Dean, we should stick together!
- We'll go after those...
- Sam, listen to me!
We almost got dad killed in there.
Don't you understand?
They're not gonna stop.
They're gonna try again.
They're gonna use us to get to him.
I mean, Meg was right.
Dad's vulnerable when he's with us.
He...
he's stronger without us around.
Dad...
no.
After everything,
after all the time we spent looking for you,
please.
- I've got to be a part of this fight.
- Sammy, this fight is just starting,
and we are all gonna have a part to play.
For now, you've got to trust me, son.
Okay? You've got to let me go.
Be careful, boys.
Come on.