M. Elkins?
M. Elkins.
Would you like another?
Yeah. Thanks, Beth.
I thought they caught
the unabomber.
Yeah, poor M. Elkins lives
all alone up in the canyon.
Same seat every day,
going through his papers,
making his little notes.
He's a nice old man.
He's just a nut.
Here you go.
What'll you have?
Jack all around.
Leave the bottle.
You hungry?
We have dinner plans.
Can I get you something else,
M. Elkins?
It's been a while.
I got to say,
you look old.
- What do you want?
- What do you think?
Damn.
You can do better than that.
Come on, come on.
Nice gun.
Wouldn't do you much good,
of course.
Boys...
We're eating in tonight.
All right, dude,
not a decent lead in all of Nebraska.
What do you got?
Well, I been scanning Wyoming,
Colorado, south Dakota.
Here.
A woman in Iowa fell 10,000 feet
from an airplane and survived.
Sounds more like "that's incredible!"
than "the twilight zone".
Yeah.
Hey, you know, we could
just keep heading east...
New York, upstate.
Could stop by
and see Sarah again. Huh?
She's a cool chick, man.
Smokin'.
You two seemed pretty friendly.
What do you say?
Yeah. Maybe someday.
But in the meantime,
we got a lot of work to do,
Dean, and you know that.
Yeah, you're right.
What else you got?
Uh, man in Colorado.
Local man by the name of
Daniel Elkins
who was found mauled in his home.
Elkins. I know that name.
Doesn't ring a bell.
It sounds like the police
don't know what to think.
At first they said
it was some sort of bear attack,
and now they found
signs of robbery.
Yeah.
Here. Check it out.
You think
it's the same Elkins?
It's a Colorado area code.
Looks like the maid
didn't come today.
Hey, there's salt over here,
right inside the door.
You mean, like,
protection-against-demon salt
or "oops, I spilled
the popcorn" salt?
It's clearly a ring.
You think this guy Elkins
was a player?
Definitely.
That looks a hell of a lot
like dad's.
Except this dates back
to the '60s.
Whatever attacked him,
looks like there was more than one.
Looks like he put up
a hell of a fight, too.
Yeah.
You got something?
I don't know.
Some scratches in the floor.
Death throes maybe?
Maybe.
Or maybe a message.
Look familiar?
Three letters, six digits...
The location and combination
of a post office box.
It's a mail drop.
That's just the way
dad does it.
"J.W."... You think?
John Winchester?
I don't know.
Should we open it?
Dad?
Dad, what are you doing here?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Look, I read the news
about Daniel.
I got here
as fast as I could.
I saw you two up at his place.
Why didn't you come in, dad?
You know why.
Because I had to make sure
you weren't followed...
By anyone...
Or anything.
Nice job of covering your tracks,
by the way.
Yeah, well, we learned
from the best.
Wait, so you came all the way
out here for this Elkins guy?
Yeah.
He was...
He was a good man.
He taught me a hell of a lot
about hunting.
You never mentioned him
to us.
We had a...
We had kind of a falling out.
I hadn't seen him in years.
I should look at that.
"If you're reading this,
I'm already dead".
- That son of a bitch.
- What is it?
- He had it the whole time.
- Dad, what?
When you searched the place,
did you see a gun, an antique,
a colt revolver?
Did you see it?
Uh, there was an old case,
but it was empty.
They have it.
- You mean whatever killed Elkins?
- We got to pick up their trail.
Wait.
You want us
to come with you?
If Elkins is telling the truth,
we've got to find this gun.
- The gun? why?
- Because it's important, that's why.
Dad, we don't even know
what these things are yet.
They were what Danny Elkins
killed best...
Vampires.
Vampires?
I thought there was
no such thing.
You never even
mentioned them, dad.
I thought they were extinct.
I thought Elkins and others
had wiped them out.
I was wrong.
Most vampire lore is crap.
A cross won't repel them.
Sunlight won't kill them
and neither will
a stake to the heart.
But the bloodlust...
that part's true.
They need fresh human blood
to survive.
They were once people,
So you won't know it's a vampire
until it's too late.
All yours, baby.
What?
Well, I guess
you showed that guy.
What guy?
The guy who bet you
you wouldn't buy that shirt.
I love this shirt.
Look out!
What happened to him?
Call 911.
22, I'm going out there.
Copy that.
Sam, Dean, let's go.
I picked up a police call.
What happened?
A couple called 911.
They found a body in the street.
Cops got there.
Everyone was missing.
It's the vampires.
How do you know?
Just follow me, okay?
Vampires.
It's funny every time I hear it.
I don't see why we couldn't have
gone over with him.
Oh, don't tell me
it's already starting.
What's starting?
- What do you got?
- It was them all right.
It looks like
they're heading west.
We have to double back
to get around that detour.
- How can you be so sure?
- Sam!
I just want to know we're going
in the right direction.
- We are.
- How do you know?
I found this.
It's a... vampire fang?
No fangs... Teeth. The second
set descends when they attack.
Any more questions?
Let's get out of here.
We're losing daylight.
And, Dean, why don't you touch up
your car before you get rust?
I wouldn't have given you
the damn thing
if I thought
you were gonna ruin it.
Vampires nest
in groups of 8 to 10.
Smaller packs are sent out
to hunt for food.
Victims are taken to the nest,
where the pack keeps them alive,
bleeding them
for days or weeks.
I wonder if that's what happened
to that 911 couple.
That's probably
what dad's thinking.
Of course, it would be nice if
he just told us what he thinks.
So it is starting.
What?
Sam, we've been looking for dad
all year.
Now we're not with him
for more than a couple of hours
and there's static already.
No.
Look, I'm happy he's okay,
all right,
and I'm happy that we're all
working together.
Good.
It's just the way he treats us
like we're children.
He barks orders at us, Dean.
He expects us to follow him
without question.
He keeps us on some crap
need-to-know deal.
He does what he does
for a reason.
- What reason?
- Our job!
There's no time to argue.
There's no margin for error.
It's just the way the old man
runs things.
Yeah, well, maybe that worked when
we were kids, but not anymore, all right?
Not after everything you and I
have been through, Dean.
Are you telling me you're cool
with just falling into line
and letting him
run the whole show?
If that's what it takes.
Have some beer, buddy.
It'll calm your nerves.
No, thanks.
Oh, come on.
You drink enough,
I can taste it in your blood.
That's gross.
Well, how about you, babe?
Attagirl.
Bo! Wait for Luther.
I missed you, too, baby.
We've got presents.
She looks interesting.
He doesn't.
Lock him up.
Let's go.
On second thought,
go ahead and treat yourself.
No!
There's something else.
- This all theirs?
- No.
It's from an old friend
of yours...
Daniel Elkins.
I caught his scent.
I thought I'd surprise you.
Kate, what did you do?
- I made him suffer.
- You shouldn't have done that.
There are others like him.
They'll know the signs
and come looking for us.
- We have to be careful.
- Luther, I did it for you,
For what he did to your family.
Revenge isn't worth much
if you end up dead.
I'm sorry, babe.
I'm sorry.
I thought you might
like that.
Looks like it was made
around the time you were born.
I've seen this before.
Elkins died with it
in his hands.
He should have known better...
Using a gun!
This is no ordinary gun.
Yeah, dad.
All right, got it.
- Pull off the next exit.
- Why?
'Cause dad thinks we got
the vampires' trail.
How?
I don't know.
He didn't say.
Oh, crap. Here we go.
- Sam, what the hell was that?
- We need to talk.
- About what?
- About everything.
Where we going, dad?
What's the big deal
about this gun?
Sammy, come on. We can q&a after
we kill all the vampires.
Your brother's right.
We don't have time for this.
Last we saw you, you said it was
too dangerous to be together.
Now, out of the blue,
you need our help.
Obviously something big's going down,
and we want to know what!
- Get back in the car.
- No.
I said get back
in the damn car.
Yeah, and I said no.
All right, you made your point,
tough guy.
Look, we're all tired.
We can talk about this later.
Sammy, I mean it.
Come on.
This is why I left
in the first place.
- What'd you say?
- You heard me.
Yeah, you left.
Your brother and me...
We needed you.
You walked away, Sam.
You walked away!
- Stop it, both of you!
- You're the one who said, "don't come back", dad.
You're the one who closed
that door, not me!
You were just pissed off
you couldn't control me anymore!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
That's enough!
That means you, too.
Terrific.
You like to watch, huh?
Me too.
Ready, baby?
Are you gonna kill me?
I'm gonna take you so high
you're never gonna come down.
Welcome home, baby.
I know what time it is.
Get in.
Son of a bitch.
So they're really not
afraid of the sun?
No, direct sunlight hurts
like a nasty sunburn.
The only way to kill them
is by beheading.
And, yeah,
they sleep during the day.
It doesn't mean
they won't wake up.
So I guess walking right in's
not our best option.
Actually...
that's the plan.
Dad, I've got an extra machete
if you need one.
Think I'm okay.
Thanks.
Wow.
So...
You boys really want to know
about this colt?
Yes, sir.
It's just a story...
A legend, really.
Well, I thought it was.
Never really believed it
until I read Daniel's letter.
Back in 1835, when
Halley's comet was overhead,
the same night those men died
at the alamo,
they say Samuel Colt
made a gun...
A special gun.
He made it for a hunter...
A man like us,
only on horseback.
The story goes
he made 13 bullets.
This hunter used the gun
a half dozen times
before he disappeared,
the gun along with him.
Somehow,
Daniel got his hands on it.
They say...
they say this gun
can kill anything.
Kill anything,
like supernatural anything?
Like the demon.
Yeah, the demon.
Ever since I picked up its trail,
I've been looking for a way
to destroy that thing.
Find the gun...
we may have it.
Dean.
There's more.
Hey.
Hey, hey, shh.
I'm here to help you.
Boys, run!
Dad!
Dad?!
They won't follow.
They'll wait till tonight.
Once a vampire gets your scent,
it's for life.
What the hell do we do now?
You got to find
the nearest funeral home.
It shouldn't be taking
this long.
I should go help.
Dean's got it.
Sammy.
Yeah?
I don't think
I ever told you this, but...
the day you were born,
you know what I did?
No.
I put 100 bucks into
a savings account for you.
I did the same thing
for your brother.
It was a college fund.
And every month, I'd put in
another $100 until...
Anyway, my point is, Sam,
that...
This is never the life
that I wanted for you.
Then why'd you get so mad
when I left?
You got to understand
something.
After your mother passed,
all I saw was evil,
everywhere.
And all I cared about
was keeping you boys alive.
I wanted you prepared...
ready.
So somewhere along the line,
I, uh...
I stopped being your father.
And I...
I became your drill sergeant.
So when you said you wanted to
go away to school,
all I could think about,
my only thought was
that you were gonna be alone...
Vulnerable.
Sammy, it just...
It never occurred to me
what you wanted.
I just couldn't accept the fact
that you and me...
we're just different.
What?
We're not different.
Not anymore.
With what happened to
mom and Jess...
We probably have a lot more
in common than just about anyone.
I guess you're right, son.
Hey, dad?
What happened to
that college fund?
Spent it on the ammo.
Whoo!
Man, there's some heavy security
to protect a bunch of dead guys.
Did you get it?
You know what to do.
Car trouble?
Let me give you a lift...
Take you back to my place.
I'll pass.
I usually draw the line
at necrophilia.
I don't normally get this friendly
till the second date.
You know,
we could have some fun.
I always like
to make new friends.
Oh, sorry.
I never really stay with a chick
that long.
Definitely not eternity.
Damn it.
Barely even stings.
Give it time, sweetheart.
That arrow's soaked
in dead man's blood.
It's like poison to you,
isn't it?
Load her up.
I'll take care of this one.
Toss this on the fire.
Saffron, skunks, cabbage,
and trillium,
it'll block our scent and hers
until we're ready.
- Stuff stinks.
- Well, that's the idea.
Dust your clothes
with the ashes
and you'll stand a chance
of not being detected.
You sure
they'll come after her?
Yeah. Vampires mate for life.
She means more to the leader
than the gun.
But the blood sickness
is gonna wear off soon,
so you don't
have a lot of time.
Half-hour ought to do it.
And then I want you out
of the area as fast as you can.
- But...
- You can't take care of them all yourself.
I'll have her
and the colt.
But after,
we're gonna meet up, right?
Use the gun together,
right?
You're leaving again,
aren't you?
You still want to go after
the demon alone?
You know, I don't get you.
- You can't treat us like this.
- Like what?
- Like children.
- You are my children.
I'm trying to keep you safe.
Dad, all due respect,
but that's a bunch of crap.
Excuse me?
You know what Sammy and I
have been hunting.
Hell, you sent us on
a few hunting trips yourself.
You can't be that worried
about keeping us safe.
It's not the same thing,
Dean.
Then what is it?
Why do you want us
out of the big fight?
This demon...
It's a bad son of a bitch.
I can't make the same moves
if I'm worried
about keeping you alive.
You can't be as reckless.
Look...
I don't expect to make it out
of this fight in one piece.
Your mother's death...
It almost killed me.
I can't watch
my children die, too.
I won't.
What happens if you die?
Dad, what happens if you die
and we could have
done something about it?
You know, I've been thinking.
I think maybe Sammy's right
about this one.
We should do this together.
We're stronger as a family, dad.
We just are. You know it.
We're running out of time.
You do your job,
and you get out of the area.
That's an order.
Is there any sign
of those three?
No. Something else.
- What?
- Luther, they cut off Hank's head.
And Kate?
I don't know.
She wasn't there.
What are we gonna do?
It's just a truck
up on the highway.
Kate.
She's in that truck.
Boo.
I told you I'd come back.
Get out!
Who are you?
My name's Winchester.
Where are your friends?
Cleaning out your nest.
Where's Kate?
Come here, sweetheart.
Kate, you all right?
Dead man's blood.
You son of a bitch.
I want the colt...
Elkins' gun.
Trade.
Is that what this
is all about?
I mean, you can't shoot us all,
right?
We'll kill you.
Oh, I don't need it for you.
I'm saving it
for something else.
Now, put the colt down
or she goes first.
All right.
Just don't hurt her.
Back up.
Further.
That's a nice move.
You almost made it.
Don't!
I'll break his neck.
Put the blade down.
You people.
Why can't you
just leave us alone?
We have as much right to live
as you do.
I don't think so.
Luther!
Kate, don't!
So, boys...
Yes, sir?
You ignored a direct order
back there.
- Yes, sir.
- But we saved your ass.
You're right.
I am?
It scares the hell
out of me.
You two are all I've got.
But I guess we are stronger
as a family.
So...
we go after this damn thing...
together.
Yes, sir.