NARRATOR:
Previously on Supernatural:
MARY:
Sammy.
Take your brother outside
as fast as you can. Now, Dean. Go!
Dad's on a hunting trip.
He hasn't been home
in a few days.
-l swore I was done hunting.
-l can't do this alone.
No! Jess!
I think Dad wants us to pick up
where he left off.
You know, saving people,
hunting things.
No. I gotta find Jessica's killer.
[WOMAN WHlMPERlNG]
MAN 1 [ON WALKlE-TALKIE]:
Roger that.
[BLAST]
MAN 1 :
Be advised, we found the victim.
She's alive.
It's okay. It's okay.
WOMAN:
In there. There. ln there.
MAN 1 :
Choke Team, let's go.
-Freeze! Don't move!
MAN 2: Drop the knife.
-Keep your hands where I see them!
MAN 1 : Drop it.
-Hold it right there! Come on, come on!
MAN 2: Now.
MAN 3:
Nice and easy.
MAN 1 :
Do it.
All right. l figure we hit Tucumcari
by lunch, then head south...
...then Bisbee by midnight.
Sam wears women's underwear.
-l've been listening, l'm just busy.
-Busy doing what?
Reading e-mails.
-E-mails from who?
-From my friends at Stanford.
You're kidding. You still keep in touch
with your college buddies?
-Why not?
-Well...
...what exactly do you tell them?
You know? About where you've been,
what you've been doing.
I tell them l'm on a road trip
with my big brother.
I tell them l needed
some time off after Jess.
-Oh, so you lie to them.
-No. I just don't tell them everything.
Yeah, that's called lying.
I get it. Telling them the truth
is far worse.
So, what am l supposed to do?
Just cut everybody out of my life?
-You're serious?
-Look, it sucks, but...
...a job like this, you can't
get close to people.
You're kind of antisocial,
you know that?
Yeah, whatever.
Unbelievable.
-God.
-What?
This e-mail from this girl Rebecca
Warren, one of those friends of mine.
She hot?
I went to school with her
and her brother Zach.
She says Zach's been
charged with murder.
Arrested for killing his girlfriend.
Rebecca says he didn't do it...
...but it sounds like the cops
have a pretty good case.
Dude, what kind of people
you hanging out with?
No, I know Zach. He's no killer.
Yeah, well, maybe you know Zach
as well as he knows you.
They're in St. Louis. We're going.
Look, sorry about your buddy, okay?
This does not sound like
our kind of problem.
It is. They're my friends.
St. Louis is 400 miles
behind us, Sam.
-Oh, my God. Sam.
-Well, if it isn't little Becky.
And you know what you can do
with that "little Becky" crap.
-l got your e-mail.
-l didn't think that you would come.
Dean. Older brother.
-Hi.
We're here to help.
Whatever we can do.
Come in.
DEAN: Nice place.
BECKY: It's my parents'.
I was crashing here for the long
weekend when everything happened.
I decided to take the semester off.
I'm gonna stay until Zach's free.
-Where are your folks?
-They live in Paris for half the year...
...so they're on their way
home now for the trial.
You guys want a beer?
-Hey.
-No thanks.
So tell us what happened.
Well.... Zach, he came home,
and he found Emily tied to a chair.
And she was beaten up and bloody,
and she wasn't breathing, and so he--
He called 91 1 and the police,
they showed up and--
And they arrested him.
But the thing is, the only way
that Zach could have killed Emily...
...is if he was in two places
at the same time.
The police, they have a video. lt's from
the security tape from across the street.
And it shows Zach
coming home at 1 0:30.
Now, Emily was killed just after that.
But l swear, he was here with me having
a few beers until at least after midnight.
You know, maybe we could
see the crime scene.
-Zach's house.
-We could.
I mean, why?
I mean, what could you do?
Well, me, not much. But Dean's a cop.
[CHUCKLES]
-A detective, actually.
-Really? Where?
Bisbee, Arizona.
But l'm off duty now.
You guys, it's so nice to offer,
but I just-- l don't know.
Beck, look, l know Zach didn't do this.
Now, we have to find a way
to prove that he's innocent.
Okay.
I'm gonna go get the keys.
[DEAN WHISTLES]
You're a real straight shooter
with your friends.
-Look, Zach and Becky need our help.
-l don't think this is our kind of problem.
Two places at once?
We've looked into less.
You're sure this is okay?
Yeah. l am an officer of the law.
Beck, you wanna wait outside?
No, I wanna help.
Tell us what else the police said.
Well, there's no sign of a break-in.
They say that Emily let her attacker in.
The lawyers, they're already
talking about plea-bargain.
Oh, God.
Look, Beck, if Zach didn't do this,
it means someone else did.
Any idea who?
There was something. About a week
before, somebody broke in here.
They stole some clothes. Zach's clothes.
The police,
they don't think it's anything.
I mean, we're not that far
from downtown.
Sometimes people get robbed.
[DOG BARKlNG]
You know, that used to be
the sweetest dog.
DEAN: What happened?
BECKY: He just changed.
DEAN:
Do you remember when he changed?
I guess around the time of the murder.
So the neighbor's dog went psycho...
...right around the time
Zach's girlfriend was killed.
Animals can sense the paranormal.
Yeah, maybe Fido saw something.
So you think maybe
this is our kind of problem?
No, probably not. But we should look at
the security tape just to make sure.
-Yeah.
So the tape, the security footage?
Think your lawyers could get it?
I don't have that jurisdiction.
I've already got it. l didn't wanna say
something in front of the cop.
I stole it off the lawyer's desk.
I just had to see it for myself.
All right.
LlNDSAY:
I'm gonna miss you.
-Why do they always have to send you?
-Because I'm the best.
Well, l know. That's why
I want you to stay home.
It's just Kansas City.
Be home tomorrow night
and make it up to you.
LlNDSAY:
You'd better.
Here he comes.
2204, that's just after 1 0.
You said time of death
was about 1 0:30.
Our lawyers hired
some kind of video expert.
He says the tape's authentic.
It wasn't tampered with.
-Beck, can we take those beers now?
-Oh, sure.
Hey.... Maybe some sandwiches too?
What do you think this is, Hooters?
-l wish. What is it?
-Check this out.
DEAN: Maybe it's just a camera flare.
-That's not like any flare l've ever seen.
A lot of cultures believe a photo
can catch a glimpse of the soul.
-Right.
-Remember that dog? Maybe he saw this.
Maybe this is a dark double of Zach's,
something that looks like him but isn't.
-Like a doppelg?nger.
SAM: Yeah.
That would sure explain how
he was in two places at once.
Honey? It's me.
The client cancelled at the last minute.
I called. Why didn't you answer?
Lindsay?
It's okay, Lindsay. It's me.
Please don't hurt me anymore.
Leave me alone.
All right. So, what are we doing
here at 5:30 in the morning?
I realized something.
The videotape shows the killer
going in, but not coming out.
-So he came out the back door?
SAM: Right.
So there should be a trail to follow.
A trail the police would never pursue.
DEAN: Because they think the killer never
left. They caught your friend Zach inside.
I still don't know what we're
doing here at 5:30 in the morning.
Blood. Somebody came this way.
Maybe the trail ends.
I don't see anything here.
[SIRENS WAlLlNG]
-What happened?
-He tried to kill his wife.
-Tied her up and beat her.
-Really?
I used to see him going to work
in the morning. He'd wave, say hello.
He seemed like such a nice guy.
Hey. Remember when l said...
-...this wasn't our kind of problem?
-Yeah.
-Definitely our kind of problem.
-What did you find out?
I just talked to the patrolman
who heard this guy Alex's story.
The dude was driving home from a trip
when his wife was attacked.
-So he was two places at once?
-Exactly.
Then he sees himself in the house.
Cops say he's a nut job.
Two dark doubles attacking
loved ones in exactly the same way.
Could be the same thing doing it too.
Shapeshifter? Something that
can make itself look like anyone?
Every culture has a shapeshifter lore.
Legends of creatures who transform
themselves into animals or other men.
Right. Skinwalkers, werewolves.
We got two attacks
within blocks of each other.
I'm guessing we got
a shapeshifter problem.
Let me ask you this:
In all this shapeshifter lore,
can any of them fly?
-Not that I know of.
SAM: l picked up a trail here.
Someone ran out of the back of this
building, headed off this way.
-Just like your friend's house.
-Yeah. And just like at Zach's house...
...the trail suddenly ends.
I mean, whatever it is just disappeared.
Well, there's another way to go.
Down.
I bet this runs right by Zach's house too.
The shapeshifter could be using
the sewer system to get around.
DEAN:
I think you're right.
Look at this.
SAM:
Is this from his victims?
DEAN:
I just had a sick thought.
When the shapeshifter
changes shape, maybe it sheds.
That is sick.
One thing I learned from Dad:
No matter what kind of shapeshifter
it is, there's one sure way to kill it.
-Silver bullet to the heart.
-That's right.
[CELL PHONE RlNGS]
This is Sam.
Where are you?
SAM:
Near Zach's, checking some things out.
Sam, just stop, because l really...
-...don't need your help anymore.
-What?
I told the lawyers that
we went to the crime scene.
-Why would you do that?
-I said we were with a policeman...
...and they checked it out and said
there is no Detective Dean Winchester.
-Beck--
-I don't get why you would lie to me.
-We're trying to help.
-Oh, trying to help?
Do you realize that was
a sealed crime scene?
-This could have ruined Zach's case.
-l'm sorry, but--
No. Goodbye, Sam.
I hate to say it, but that's exactly
what I'm talking about.
You lie to your friends because if they
knew the real you, they'd be freaked.
-lt's just-- lt'd be easier if--
-lf I was like you.
Hey, like it or not,
we are not like other people.
But l'll tell you one thing,
this whole gig...
...it ain't without perks.
DEAN: Think we're close to its lair.
-Why do you say that?
Because there's another
puke-inducing pile next to your face.
Oh, God.
DEAN: Looks like it's lived
here for a while.
Who knows how many murders
he's gotten away with.
Dean!
Get the son of a bitch!
-All right, let's split up.
-All right. I'll meet you on the other side.
[CHATTERlNG]
-Yes.
-Oh, I know.
DEAN:
Hey.
-Anything?
-No, he's gone.
All right, let's get back to the car.
[HORN HONKlNG]
SAM: You think he found
another way underground?
Yeah, probably. You got the keys?
Hey, didn't Dad once face a
shapeshifter in San Antonio?
No, it was Austin.
And it turned out not to be a
shapeshifter. lt was a thought-form.
A psychic projection, remember?
Oh, right.
Here you go.
Don't move!
What have you done with him?
Dude, chill.
-lt's me, all right?
-l don't think so.
-Where's my brother?
-You're about to shoot him.
-Calm down.
-You caught those keys with your left.
-Your shoulder was hurt.
-Yeah, it's better. You want me to cry?
You're not my brother.
Why don't you pull the trigger, then.
Because you're not sure.
Dude, you know me.
Don't.
Where is he?
Where's Dean?
SHAPESHIFTER:
I wouldn't worry about him.
-l'd worry about you.
-Where is he?
You don't really wanna know.
I swear, the more l learn
about your family....
I thought I came from
a bad background.
What do you mean, learn?
[CHATTERlNG lN
SHAPESHIFTER'S HEAD]
[SHAPESHIFTER GRUNTS]
He sure got issues with you.
You got to go to college.
He had to stay home.
I mean, l had to stay home.
With Dad.
You don't think l had
dreams of my own?
But Dad needed me.
-Where the hell were you?
-Where...
-...is my brother?
-l'm your brother.
See, deep down, l'm just jealous.
You got friends. You could have a life.
Me? l know I'm a freak.
And sooner or later,
everybody's gonna leave me.
-What are you talking about?
-You left.
Hell, I did everything Dad asked me to,
and he ditched me too.
No explanation, nothing. Just:
Left me with your sorry ass.
But still, this life...
...it's not without its perks.
I meet the nicest people.
Like little Becky. You know Dean
would bang her if he had the chance.
Let's see what happens.
[KNOCKlNG ON DOOR]
-Oh, hi.
-l know what you're gonna say.
-Oh, you do?
-Well, no, not exactly.
But l can take a guess:
"Get off my porch"?
That's about right.
I admit it, we lied.
Thought l'd try to explain myself.
Sam told me not to come,
but I thought:
"What the hell? I have to try."
Damn it.
[DEAN COUGHING]
That better be you, Sam,
and not that freak of nature.
Yeah, it's me. He went to Rebecca's,
looking like you.
Well, he's not stupid.
He picked the handsome one.
So you're saying
that there's something...
...out there that made itself
look like my brother.
Mm-hmm.
-What did you call it?
-A shapeshifter.
Yeah. Maybe we're crazy.
But what if we're not?
Look, you said it yourself that
Zach was in two places at once.
-Tell me how that could happen.
-Okay, so this thing...
...it can make itself look like anybody?
That's right.
Well, what is it? Like a genetic freak?
[CHUCKLES]
Maybe.
Evolution is about mutation, right?
So maybe this thing was born human...
...but was different.
Hideous and hated.
Until he learned to
become someone else.
SAM:
Yeah, that's the thing.
He didn't just look like you,
he was you...
-...or he was becoming you.
-What do you mean?
It's like he was downloading
your thoughts and memories.
-You mean like the Vulcan Mind Meld?
-Yes, something like that.
Maybe that's why
he doesn't just kill us.
Maybe he needs to keep us alive...
-...for the psychic connection.
-Hands.
Yeah. Come on, we gotta go.
He's probably at Rebecca's already.
SAM: Come on. We gotta find a phone,
call the police.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're gonna put an APB out on me.
SAM: Sorry.
DEAN: This way.
SHAPESHIFTER:
It's funny.
I kind of understand him.
He's all alone.
Close to no one.
All he wants is for someone to love him.
He's like me.
Everybody needs a little
human touch now and then.
-lt's so hard to be different.
-You should go.
You are disgusting!
Just get out of here!
-Rebecca, just calm down.
-Oh, calm down.
-What is wrong with you?
-What's wrong with me?
-What's wrong with you?
BECKY: I'm calling the police.
[SCREAMlNG]
SHAPESHIFTER:
Give me your hands!
Shut up!
You're a nice girl, Rebecca.
I mean, l liked you.
Believe me, it makes this harder.
But l gotta do what I gotta do.
[BLAST]
[SCREAMlNG]
SHAPESHIFTER:
Shh.
MAN 1 : Freeze! Drop the knife.
Drop the knife!
[GUNSHOTS]
MAN 2:
Come on, come on!
MAN 3:
Go! Go!
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNTlNG]
[ON TV]: An anonymous
tip led police to a home...
...in the Central West End
where a SWAT team discovered...
...a local woman bound and gagged.
Her attacker,
a white male approximately...
...24 to 30 years of age,
was discovered hiding in the home.
-Shots were fired....
-Man, that's not even a good picture.
It's good enough.
MAN [ON TV]:
He may be armed and is dangerous.
DEAN:
Man.
Come on.
They said attempted murder.
At least we know--
-l didn't kill her.
-l'll check on Rebecca in the morning.
First l'm gonna find that handsome devil
and kick the crap out of him.
We have no weapons,
no silver bullets.
The guy's walking around with my face.
It's personal. l wanna find him.
-Okay. Where do we look?
-We could start with the sewers.
We have no weapons.
He stole our guns. We need more.
-The car?
-l bet he drove over to Rebecca's.
The news said he fled on foot,
I bet it's still parked there.
-The thought of him driving my car.
-Come on.
-That's killing me.
SAM: Let it go.
DEAN:
There she is.
Finally something went right tonight.
[SIREN WAILlNG]
Crap.
This way! This way!
-Go, I'll hold them.
-They'll catch you.
They can't hold me! Just go, keep out
of sight. Meet me at Rebecca's.
Dean! Stay out of the sewers alone!
-l mean it!
DEAN: Yeah, yeah.
MAN: Don't move! Keep your hands
where l can see them.
I'm sorry, Sam.
You know me, l just can't wait.
-Becca?
-So say this...
...shapeshifter is real.
By the way, you know you're crazy.
But say it is real.
How do you stop it?
Thanks. Silver bullet to the heart.
You are crazy.
What happened?
I was walking home,
and everything just went white.
Someone hit me over the head
and l wound up here...
...in time to see that thing
turn into me.
-How is that even possible?
-Okay, okay. lt's okay.
Come on. Can you walk?
Okay, we gotta hurry.
Sam went to see you.
What are you gonna do to me?
I'm not gonna do anything.
Dean will, though.
-They'll never catch him.
-Oh, it doesn't matter.
Murder in the first of his own brother?
He'll be hunted the rest of his life.
I must say...
...l will be sorry to lose this skin.
Your brother's got a lot
of good qualities.
You should appreciate him
more than you do.
Cheers.
You son of a bitch.
SHAPESHIFTER: Not bad, little brother.
SAM: You're not him.
SHAPESHIFTER:
Even when we were kids...
...l always kicked your ass.
DEAN:
Hey!
BECKY:
Sam.
So this is what you do.
You and your brother,
you hunt down these kinds of things?
-Yeah, pretty much.
-l can't believe it.
I mean, l saw it
with my own eyes, and....
I mean, does everybody at school--?
Nobody knows that you do this?
No.
Did Jessica know?
No, she didn't.
-Must be lonely.
-Oh, no. No, it's not so bad.
Anyway, it-- What can I do?
It's my family.
Well, you know, Zach and me and
everybody at school, we really miss you.
Yeah, me too.
Well, will you call sometime?
It might not be for a little while.
DEAN:
So, what about your friend Zach?
Cops are blaming this Dean Winchester
guy for Emily's murder.
They found the murder weapon
in the guy's lair...
...Zach's clothes
stained with her blood.
Now they're thinking maybe the
surveillance tape was tampered with.
Yeah, Becca says Zach will be
released soon.
Sorry, man.
About what?
I really wish things could be different.
I wish you could just be...
-...Joe College.
-lt's okay.
You know, truth is, even at Stanford,
deep down, l never really fit in.
-Well, that's because you're a freak.
-Yeah, thanks.
Well, l'm a freak too.
I'm right there with you all the way.
Yeah, l know you are.
You know, I gotta say,
I'm sorry I'm gonna miss it.
Miss what?
How many chances am l gonna have
to see my own funeral?
[ENGLISH SDH]