- What do you got those amped up to?
- A hundred thousand volts.
- Damn.
- Yeah, I want this rawhead extra frickin’ crispy.
- And remember, you only get one shot with these things.
- So make it count.
- On three. One. Two. Three.
- Is it still here? Ok. Grab your sister’s
hand, come on, we gotta get you out of here.
- Alright, go!
- Sam!
- Sam, get ‘em outta here!
- You take this!
- Come on.
- Dean!
- Dean, hey.
- Hey.
- Sir, I’m so sorry to ask. There doesn’t seem
to be any insurance on file.
- Right. Uh, ok.
- Okay, Mr. Burkovitz.
- Look, we can finish this up later.
- No, no, it’s okay.
- We were just taking a shortcut through the neighborhood.
And, um, the windows were rolled down, we heard some screaming.
- We drove past the house, and we stopped. Ran in.
- And you found the kids in the basement?
- Yeah.
- Well, thank God you did.
- Excuse me.
- Sure. Thanks for your help.
- Hey, Doc. Is he—
- He’s resting.
- And?
- The electrocution triggered a heart attack. Pretty massive, I’m afraid.
- His heart—it’s damaged.
- How damaged?
- We’ve done all we can.
- We can try and keep him comfortable at this point.
But, I’d give him a couple weeks, at most, maybe a month.
- No, no. There’s—there’s gotta be something
you can do, some kind of treatment.
- We can’t work miracles.
I really am sorry.
- Have you ever actually watched
daytime TV? It’s terrible.
- I talked to your doctor.
- That fabric softener teddy bear. Oh, I’m gonna hunt that little bitch down.
- Dean.
- Yeah. Alright, well, looks like you’re gonna leave town without me.
- What are you talking about?
I’m not gonna leave you here.
- Hey, you better take care of that car.
Or, I swear, I’ll haunt your ass.
- I don’t think that’s funny.
- Oh, come on, it’s a little funny.
- Look, Sammy, what can I say, man,
it’s a dangerous gig.
- I drew the short straw.
That’s it, end of story.
- Don’t talk like that, alright?
We still have options.
- What options?
- Yeah, burial or cremation.
- And I know it’s not easy. But I’m
gonna die. And you can’t stop it.
- Watch me.
- This is John Winchester. I can’t be reached. If this is
an emergency, call my son, Dean. 866-907-3235. He can help.
- Hey, Dad. It’s Sam. Uh….you probably
won’t even get this, but, uh….It’s Dean.
- He’s sick, and uh….the doctors say there’s nothing they can do.
- Um….but, uh, they don’t know the things we know, right?
- So, don’t worry, cause, uh….
I’m gonna do whatever it takes to get him better.
- Alright….just wanted you to know.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- I checked myself out.
- What, are you crazy?
- Well, I’m not gonna die in a hospital where the nurses aren’t even hot.
- You know, this whole I- laugh-in-the-face-of-death
thing? It’s crap. I can see right through it.
- Yeah, whatever, dude. Have you even slept?
You look worse than me.
- I’ve been scouring the Internet
for the last three days.
- Calling every contact in Dad’s journal.
- For what?
- For a way to help you.
- One of Dad’s friends, Joshua,
he called me back.
- Told me about a guy in Nebraska. A specialist.
- You’re not gonna let me die in peace, are you?
- I’m not gonna let you die, period.
- We’re going.
- I got it. Man, you are a lying bastard.
Thought you said we were going to see a doctor.
- I believe I said a specialist. Look, Dean,
this guy’s supposed to be the real deal.
- I can’t believe you brought me here to
see some guy who heals people out of a tent.
- Reverend LeGrange is a great man.
- Yeah, that’s nice.
- I have a right to protest. This man is a fraud. And he’s bilking all these people out of their hard
- earned money.
- I take it he’s not part of the flock.
- But when people see something they can’t explain, there’s controversy.
- Come on, Sam, a faith healer?
- Maybe it’s time to have
a little faith, Dean.
- You know what I’ve got faith in?
Reality. Knowing what’s really going on.
- How can you be a skeptic? With the things we see everyday?
- We see them, we know they’re real.
- But if you know evil’s out there, how
can you not believe good’s out there, too?
- Because I’ve seen what evil does to good people.
- Maybe God works in mysterious ways.
- Maybe he does.
- I think you just turned me around on the subject.
- Yeah, I’m sure.
- I’m Dean. This is Sam.
- Layla.
- So, if you’re not a believer,
then why are you here?
- Apparently my brother here
believes enough for the both of us.
- Come on, Layla. It’s about to start.
- Well, I bet you she can
work in some mysterious ways.
- Yeah, peace, love, and trust all over.
- Come on. - What are you doing? Let’s
sit here. - We’re sitting up front.
- What? Why? Oh, come on, Sam.
This is ridiculous. I’m good, dude, get off me.
- Perfect.
- Yeah, perfect.
- Each morning, my wife,
Sue Ann, reads me the news.
- Never seems good, does it?
- Seems like there’s always someone
committing some immoral, unspeakable act.
- But, I say to you, God is watching.
- God rewards the good,
and He punishes the corrupt.
- Who does the healing here, friends? The Lord who guides me
in choosing who to heal by helping me see into people’s hearts.
- Yeah, or into their wallets.
- You think so, young man?
- Sorry.
- No, no. Don’t be.
- Just watch what you say around
a blind man, we’ve got real sharp ears.
- What’s your name, son?
- Dean.
- Dean. I want—I want you
to come up here with me.
- No, that’s ok.
- What are you doing?
- You’ve come here to be healed, haven’t you?
- Well, yeah, but—
- No, maybe you should
just pick someone else.
- Oh, no, I didn’t pick you,
Dean, the Lord did.
- Get up there!
- You ready?
- Look, no disrespect, but I’m not exactly a believer.
- You will be, son. You will be.
- Pray with me, friends.
- Alright, now.
- Dean!
- Say something.
- So, you really feel okay?
- I feel fine, Sam.
- Well, according to all your tests,
there’s nothing wrong with your heart.
- No sign there ever was.
- Not that a man your age should be having heart
trouble, but, still it’s strange it does happen.
- What do you mean, strange?
- Just yesterday, a young guy like you, 27, athletic. Out of nowhere, heart attack.
- Thanks, Doc.
- Oh, no problem.
- That’s odd.
- Maybe it’s a coincidence. People’s hearts give out all the time, man.
- No, they don’t.
- Look, Dean, do we really have to look this one in the mouth?
- Why can’t we just be thankful that
the guy saved your life and move on?
- Because I can’t shake this feeling, that’s why.
- What feeling?
- When I was healed, I just—I felt wrong.
- I felt cold. And for a second, I saw someone. This, uh,
this old man. And I’m telling you, Sam, it was a spirit.
- But if there was something there, Dean, I think I would’ve seen
it, too. I mean, I’ve been seeing an awful lot of things lately.
- Well, excuse me, psychic wonder. But you’re
just gonna need a little faith on this one.
- Sam, I’ve been hunting long enough
to trust a feeling like this.
- Yeah, alright.
- So, what do you wanna do?
- I want you to go check out the heart attack guy. I’m gonna visit the reverend.
- I feel great. Just trying to, you know,
make sense of what happened.
- A miracle is what happened.
- Well, miracles come so often around Roy.
- When did they start? The miracles.
- Woke up one morning, stone blind.
Doctors figured out I had cancer.
- Told me I had maybe a month.
So, uh, we prayed for a miracle.
- Now, I was weak, but I told Sue Ann:
You just keep right on praying. ”
- I went into a coma. Doctors said
I wouldn’t wake up, but I did.
- And the cancer was gone.
- If it wasn’t for these eyes,
no one would believe I’d ever had it.
- And suddenly you could heal people.
- I discovered it afterward, yes.
- God’s blessed me in many ways.
- And his flock just swelled overnight.
- And this is just the beginning.
- Can I ask you one last question?
- Of course you can.
- Why? Why me?
- Out of all the sick people, why save me?
- Well, like I said before, the Lord guides me.
- I looked into your heart, and
you just stood out from all the rest.
- What did you see in my heart?
- A young man with an
important purpose. A job to do.
- And it isn’t finished.
- I’m telling you, he seemed healthy.
Swam every day, didn’t smoke.
- So, a heart attack just
kind of seemed, well, bizarre.
- And you said he was running, right before he collapsed?
- Yeah, yeah, he was freaking out.
- He said that something was, uh, was after him.
- Did he say what?
- Well, thin air is what.
I mean, it wasn’t anything.
- Alright, thanks.
- Hey, buddy? Your, uh, your clock’s busted.
- Oh, yeah, we, uh, can’t get it workin’.
Just froze at 4:17.
- Is that the same time Marshall died?
- How’d you know?
- Dean, hey.
- Hey.
- How you feeling?
- I feel good. Cured, I guess.
- What are you doing here?
- You know, my mom, she wanted
to talk to the reverend.
- Layla?
- Yes, I’m here again.
- Well, I’m sorry, but Roy is resting, and
he won’t be seeing anyone else right now.
- Sue Ann, please. This is our
sixth time, he’s got to see us.
- Roy is well aware of Layla’s situation. And he very
much wants to help just as soon as the Lord allows.
- Have faith, Mrs. Rourke.
- Why are you still even here? You got what you wanted.
- Mom. Stop.
- No, Layla, this is too much.
- We’ve been to every single service. If Roy
would stop choosing these strangers over you.
- Strangers who don’t even believe.
I just can’t pray any harder.
- Layla, what’s wrong?
- I have this thing….
- It’s a brain tumor.
- It’s inoperable.
In six months, the doctors say...
- I’m sorry.
- It’s okay.
- No. It isn’t.
- Why do you deserve to live
more than my daughter?
- What’d you find out?
- I’m sorry.
- Sorry about what?
- Marshall Hall died at 4:17.
- The exact time I was healed.
- Yeah.
- So, I put together a list of everyone
Roy’s healed, six people over the past year
- And I cross-checked them with the local obits.
Every time someone was healed, someone else died.
- And each time, the victim died of the same
symptom LeGrange was healing at the time.
- Someone’s healed of cancer, someone else dies of cancer?
- Somehow.
- LeGrange—he’s trading a life for another.
- Hello?
- Wait, wait, wait. So,
Marshall Hall died to save me?
- Dean, the guy probably
would’ve died anyway.
- And someone else would’ve been healed.
- You never should’ve brought me here.
- Dean, I was just trying to save your life.
- But, Sam, some guy
is dead now because of me.
- I didn’t know.
- Pray with me, friends.
- The thing I don’t understand is how is Roy
doing it? How’s he trading a life for a life?
- Oh, he’s not doing it.
Something else is doing it for him.
- What do you mean?
- The old man I saw on stage.
- I didn’t wanna believe it, but deep down I knew it.
- What are you talking about?
- There’s only one thing that
can give and take life like that.
- We’re dealing with a reaper.
- You really think it’s the Grim Reaper?
Angel of death, collect your soul, the whole deal?
- No, no, no. Not the Reaper, a reaper.
- There’s reaper lore in pretty much every
culture on Earth. Go by a hundred different names.
- It’s possible that there’s more than one of ‘em.
- But you said you saw a dude in a suit.
- Well, what, do you think he should’ve
been workin’ the whole black robe thing?
- You said it yourself that the clock stopped, right?
- Reapers stop time. And you can only see ‘em when they’re
comin’ at you, which is why I could see it and you couldn’t.
- There’s nothing else it could be, Sam.
The question is how’s Roy controllin’ the damn thing?
- That cross.
- What?
- There was this cross. I noticed it in the
church tent, I knew I had seen it before.
- Here.
- A tarot? It makes sense. I mean, tarot
dates back to the early Christian era, right?
- When some priests were still using magic?
And a few of them veered into the dark stuff.
- Necromancy, and how to push
death away, how to cause it.
- So, Roy is using black magic to bind the reaper?
- If he is, he’s riding the whirlwind.
It’s like putting a dog leash on a Great White.
- Ok, then we stop Roy.
- How?
- You know how.
- Wait, what the hell are you talking about, Dean? We can’t kill Roy.
- Sam, the guy’s playing God, he’s deciding who
lives and who dies, that’s a monster in my book.
- No, we’re not gonna kill a human being, Dean.
- We do that, we’re no better than he is.
- Okay, so we can’t kill Roy, we can’t
kill death. Any bright ideas, college boy?
- Okay, uh, if Roy is using some kind of black spell
on the reaper, we’ve gotta figure out what it is.
- And how to break it.
- If Roy is using a spell, there might be a spell book.
- See if you can find it.
- Hurry up, too, the service starts in fifteen minutes.
I’ll try to stall Roy.
- Roy LeGrange is a fraud. He’s no healer.
- Amen, brother.
- You keep up the good word.
- What do you got?
- Roy’s choosing victims he sees as immoral.
And I think I know who’s next on his list.
- Remember that protestor?
- The guy in the parking lot?
- Yeah. Yeah, I’ll find him.
But you can’t let Roy heal anyone, alright?
- Layla. Layla Rourke,
come up here, child.
- Oh, man.
- Layla, listen to me, you can’t go up there.
- Why not? We’ve waited for months.
- You can’t let Roy heal you.
- I don’t understand. I mean, Roy healed you,
didn’t he? Why wouldn’t I at least let him try?
- Because if you do, something bad is gonna happen.
I can’t explain, I just need you to believe me.
- Layla.
- Please.
- I’m sorry.
- Layla. Layla!
- Help!
- Pray with me, friends.
- I hope you’re ready.
- I am.
- Help! Help me, please!
- Where is it?
- It’s right there!
- Alright, come on!
- Fire!
- Hey, tent’s on fire!
- Everybody, get out of here!
- No! No, please!
- Please, don’t stop! Please!
Reverend, please! Please!
- Friends, if you’d all just leave the tent in an orderly
fashion, then we can figure out what’s going on out there.
- I did it. I stopped Roy.
- David, I think it’s okay.
- No!
- Dean, it didn’t work! The reaper’s still comin’!
- I’m tellin’ you! I’m tellin’ you, it must not
have worked. Roy must not be controlling this thing!
- Well, then who the hell is?
- Sue Ann.
- Help! Help me! Help!
- I got ya. I got ya.
- Thank God.
- I just don’t understand. After everything
we’ve done for you, after Roy healed you.
- We’re very, very disappointed, Dean.
- You can let him go, I’m not gonna press charges.
The Lord will deal with him as he sees fit.
- We catch you around here again, son, we’ll put the fear of God in you, understand?
- Yes, sir. Fear of God. Got it.
- Layla.
- Why would you do that, Dean?
When it could’ve been my only chance.
- He’s not a healer.
- He healed you.
- I know it doesn’t seem fair. And I wish I could
explain, but Roy is not the answer. I’m sorry.
- Goodbye, Dean.
- I wish you luck. I really do.
- Same to you.
- You deserve it a lot more than me.
- Private session tonight. No interruptions.
I give you my word. I’ll heal your daughter.
- Thank you, Reverend.
God bless you.
- So Roy really believes?
- I don’t think he has any
idea what his wife’s doing.
- Well, I found this hidden in their library.
- It’s ancient. Written by
a priest who went dark side.
- There’s a binding spell in
here for trapping a reaper.
- Must be a hell of a spell.
- Yeah. You’ve got to build a black altar.
- With seriously dark stuff. Bones, human blood.
- To cross the line like that, that
preacher’s wife. Black magic, murder.
- Evil.
- Desperate.
- Her husband was dying,
she’d have done anything to save him.
- She was using the binding spell
to keep the reaper away from Roy.
- Cheating death. Literally.
- Yeah, but Roy’s alive,
so why’s she still using the spell?
- Right. To force the reaper
to kill people she thinks are immoral.
- May God save us from half the
people who think they’re doing God’s work.
- We’ve gotta break
that binding spell, Dean.
- You know, Sue Ann had a Coptic cross like this.
And when she dropped it, the reaper backed off.
- So, you think we’ve gotta find the cross or destroy the altar?
- Maybe both.
- Whatever we do, we better do it soon.
- Roy’s healing Layla tonight.
- That’s Layla’s car. She’s already here.
- Yeah.
- Dean.
- You know, if Roy would have picked Layla instead of me, she’d be healed right now.
- Dean, don’t.
- And if she’s not healed tonight, she’s gonna die in a couple months.
- What’s happening to her is horrible. But, what
are you gonna do? Let somebody else die to save her?
- You said it yourself, Dean.
You can’t play God.
- Where’s Sue Ann?
- House.
- Go find Sue Ann. I’ll catch up.
- What are you—?
- Hey.
- You gonna put that fear of God in me?
- You see him?
- No.
- Psycho mutt.
- I gave your brother life,
and I can take it away.
- Sam, can’t you see?
- The Lord chose me to reward
the just and punish the wicked.
- And your brother is wicked. And he deserves
to die just as Layla deserves to live.
- It's God’s will.
- Goodbye, Sam.
- Mrs. Rourke, pray with me.
- Pray with me, friends.
- Alright, now.
- No!
- I don’t understand.
- I don’t feel different.
- My God! What have you done?!
- He’s not your God.
- Reverend?
- Sue Ann?
- You okay?
- A little bit weak.
- Yeah.
- Alright, come on,
we should get going.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
- We did the right thing here, didn’t we?
- Of course we did.
- Didn’t feel like it.
- I got it.
- Hey, Layla. Come on in.
- Hey.
- How’d you know we were here?
- Sam called. He said you wanted to say goodbye.
- I’m gonna grab a soda.
- So, um, where are you going?
- Don’t know yet. Our work
kind of takes us all over.
- You know, I went back to see Roy.
- What happened?
- Nothing.
- I mean, he laid his hand on
my forehead, but nothing happened.
- I’m sorry.
- I’m sorry it didn’t work.
- And Sue Ann. She’s dead, you know? Stroke.
- Yeah, I heard.
- I mean, Roy’s a good man.
- He doesn’t deserve what’s happened.
- It must be rough.
- To believe in something so much,
and have it disappoint you like that.
- You wanna hear something weird?
- Hm?
- I’m okay. Really.
- I guess, if you're gonna have faith, you
can’t just have it when the miracles happen.
- You have to have it when they don’t.
- So, what now?
- God works in mysterious ways.
- Goodbye, Dean.
- Hey.
- Uh, you know, I’m not
much of the prayin’ type.
- But I’m gonna pray for you.
- Well. There’s a miracle right there.