Okay,
i think i found a way
we can bypass that construction
just east of here.
We might even make pennsylvania
faster than we thought.
Yeah.
Problem is
we're not going to pennsylvania.
Wait... what?
I just got a call
from an old friend.
Her father was killed
last night.
She thinks it might be
our kind of thing.
What?
Yeah, believe me,
she never would've called,
never, if she didn't need us.
Come on.
You coming or what?
By "old friend,"
you mean...
a friend
that's not new.
Yeah, thanks.
So, her name's cassie,
huh?
You never mentioned her.
Didn't i?
No.
Yeah, we went out.
You mean you dated someone?
For more than one night?
Am i speaking a language
you're not getting here?
Dad and i were working
a job in athens, ohio.
She was finishing up college.
We went out for a couple weeks.
And?
Look, it's terrible
about her dad,
but it kind of sounds
like a standard car accident.
I'm not seeing how it fits
with what we do.
Which, by the way,
how does she know what we do?
You told her.
You told her the secret.
Our big family rule
number one...
we do what we do
and we shut up about it.
For a year and a half,
i do nothing but lie to jessica,
and you go out with this chick
in ohio a couple of times
and you tell her
everything?
Dean!
Yeah, looks like.
Anderson: It's a newspaper
we put out here,
not a bulletin
for the mayor's office.
Get off your soapbox,
jimmy.
I'm urging a little discretion
is all.
No, i think you're telling us
what you want us to print
and what you want us
to sit on.
I know you're upset,
cassie.
I liked your dad a lot.
But i think your grief
is clouding your judgment.
Two black people were killed
on the same stretch of road
in the same way
in three weeks.
Jimmy, you're too close
to this.
Those guys were friends
of yours.
Again, i'm very sorry
for your loss.
Dean.
Hey, cassie.
This is my brother, sam.
I'm sorry about your dad.
Yeah, me, too.
My mother's
in pretty bad shape.
I've been staying with her.
I wish she wouldn't go off
by herself.
She's been snervous
and frightened.
She was worried about dad.
Why?
He was scared.
He was seeing things.
Like what?
He swore he saw an awful-looking
black truck following him.
A truck?
Who was the driver?
He didn't talk about a driver,
just the truck.
He said it would appear
and disappear.
And in the accident,
dad's truck was dented
like it had been slammed into
by something big.
Thanks.
Now, you're sure this dent
wasn't there before?
He sold cars,
always drove a new one.
There wasn't a scratch
on that thing.
It had rained hard that night.
There was mud everywhere.
There was a distinct set
of muddy tracks from dad's car
leading right...
to the edge
where he went over.
One set of tracks... his.
And the first person killed
was a friend of your father's?
Best friend...
clayton solmes.
They owned
a car dealership together.
Same thing...
dent, no tracks.
And the cops said exactly
what they said about dad...
"he lost control
of his car. "
Can you think of why your father
and partner might be targets?
No.
You think this vanishing truck
ran him off the road?
When you say it
aloud like that...
listen, i'm a little skeptical
about this ghost stuff
or whatever it
is you guys are into.
Skeptical.
If i remember,
i think you said i was nuts.
That was then.
Hmm.
I just know that i can't explain
what happened up there,
so i called you.
Mom.
Where have you been?
I had no idea
you'd invited friends over.
Mom, this is dean,
a friend of mine from... college,
and his brother, sam.
Well,
I- I-I-i won't interrupt you.
Mrs. Robinson?
Hmm?
We're sorry for your loss.
We'd like to talk to you for
a minute, if you don't mind.
I'm really not up
to that just now.
Dd: Jimmy meant something
to this town.
He was one of our best.
It won't be the same
without him.
Our best seem to be dropping
like flies.
Clayton, my father, jimmy.
What is it exactly
you want me to do?
Well, how about closing this
section of road for starters?
Close the main road, the only
road in and out of town?
Accidents happen, cassie. That's
what they are... accidents.
Did the cops check
for denting on jimmy's car
to see if it was pushed?
Who's this?
Dean and sam winchester,
family friends.
This is mayor harold todd.
There's one set of tracks...
one. Doesn't point to foul play.
Mayor, the police
and town officials
take their cues from you...
if you're indifferent about...
indifferent?
Would you close the road
if the victims were white?
You're suggesting
i'm racist, cassie.
I'm the last person
you should talk to like that.
Why is that?
Why don't you k
your mother?
I'll say this for her...
she's fearless.
Mm-hmm.
Bet she kicked your ass
a coupleimes.
What's interesting is you guys
never really look at each other
at the same time.
You look at her
when she's not looking.
She checks you out
when you look away.
It's just a... just an
interesting observation
in a, you know,
observationally interesting way.
You think we might have some
more pressing issues here?
Hey, if i'm hitting
a nerve...
oh, let's go.
Excuse me.
Are you ron stubbins?
Friends with jimmy anderson?
Who are you?
We're with mr. Anderson's
insurance company.
Just here to dot some i's
and cross some t's.
We were just wondering,
had the deceased mentioned
any unusual
recent experiences?
What do you mean,
"unusual"?
Well, visions,
hallucinations.
It's all part of a medical
examination kind of thing.
What company
you say you were with?
All tional mutual.
Tell me, did he ever mention
seeing a truck,
a big black truck?
What the hell you talking about?
You even speaking english?
Son, this truck, a big, scary,
monster-looking thing?
Yeah, actually,
i think so.
Hmm.
What?
I have heard
of a truck like that.
You have?
Where?
Not where... when.
Back in the '60s,
there was a string of deaths.
Black men.
Stores they disappeared
in a big, nasty black truck.
They ever catch
the guy who did it?
Never found him.
Hell, not sure
they even really looked.
See, there was a time
this town wasn't too friendly
to all its citizens.
Thank you.
Truck.
Keeps coming up,
doesn't it?
I was thinking. You heard
of the flying dutchman?
Yeah, a ghost ship infused
with the captain's evil spirit.
It was basically
a part of him.
So, what if we're dealing
with the same thing?
A phantom truck who's the
extension of some bastard ghost,
re-enacting past crimes.
The victims have
all been black men.
I think it's more
than that.
They all seem connected
to cassie and her family.
All right, well,
you work that angle.
Go talk to her.
Yeah, i will.
Oh, and you might also want
to mention that other thing.
What other thing?
That serious unfinished
business.
Dean, what is going on
between you two?
So maybe we were a little bit
more involved than i said.
Oh, okay, yeah.
Okay, a lot more... maybe.
I told her the secret about what
we do, and i shouldn't have.
Look, man, everybody's got
to open up to someone sometime.
Yeah, i don't.
It was stupid to get that close.
I mean, look how it ended.
Would you stop?
Blink or something.
You loved her.
Oh, god.
You were in love with her,
but you dumped her.
Oh, wow.
She dumped you.
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
Dean.
Hey. Hey.
Come on in.
So, you busy?
The paper is doing
a tribute to jimmy.
I was just going
through his stuff, his awards,
trying to find the words.
That's got to be tough.
For years this family owned
the paper, the dorians.
They had a whites-only
staff policy.
After they sold it, jimmy became
the first black reporter.
He became editor.
He taught me everything.
Where's your brother?
Not here.
All right,
so, what brings you here?
I'm trying to find
the connection
between the three victims.
By the way,
did you talk to your mom
about what todd said
about not being a racist?
I did.
She didn't want
to talk about it.
So, just then, why did you ask
where my brother was?
Nothing. Not important.
Could it be because without him
here it'just you and me
and not you, me, and sam,
which would be easier?
It's not easier.
Look...
no, forget it.
It's fine.
Keep it strictly business.
I forgot you do that.
Do what?
Oh, whenever we get...
what's the word, close?...
anywhere in the neighborhood
of emotional vulnerability,
you back off
or make some joke
or find any way
to shut the door on me.
Oh, that's hilarious.
See, i'm not the one
who took that big, final door
and slammed it behind me,
and i'm not the one
who took
the key and buried it.
Are we done
with this metaphor?
All i'm saying is i was totally
up front with you back then
and you nailed me with it.
The guy i'm hoping
might be in my future
tells me he professionally
pops ghosts.
Those weren't
the words i used.
And he has to leave too
work with his father. I did.
All i could think was,
if you want out, fine.
But don't tell me
this insane story.
It was the truth,
cassie,
it didn't sound so insane the
minute you thought i could help.
Back then i thought you just
wanted to dump me.
Whoa, let's not forget
who dumped who, okay?
I thought it was
what you wanted.
Well, it wasn't.
I didn't mean
to hurt you.
Well, you did.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me, too.
Absolutely.
Actually, we were always
pretty good at fighting.
This, we were good at.
It's all the other stuff,
not so much.
Hey, i tried.
I told you who i really was.
It was a big first for me.
Why'd you tell me?
I don't know.
I guess
i couldn't lie to you.
Dean...
when you told me
that story,
it scared the hell
out of me.
I thought you were nuts,
dangerous even.
Actually...
maybe i was looking
for a reason to walk away.
In my work
i see some horrible things,
things that
can't be explained.
I deal with them.
But working things out
with you?
I'm a scary one,
all right.
Hmm.
Well, usually thgs
get worked out
when you really
want them to.
Yeah, but i'm still really
involved in my dad's work.
No more excuses, okay?
From you or me.
Okay.
Yeah
you're kidding.
And he's with me.
Where were you
last night?
You didn't make it back
to the motel.
Nope.
I'm guessing you guys
worked things out.
We'll be working things out
when we're 90.
So, what happened?
Every bone crushed, internal
organs turned to pudding.
The cops are all stumped,
but it's almost like
something ran him over.
Something like a truck?
Yep.
Tracks?
Nope.
What was the mayor
doing here anyway?
He owned the property.
Bought it a few weeks ago.
Yeah, but he's white.
Doesn't fit the pattern.
Killings didn't happen up
on the road.
That doesn't fit, either.
Thanks.
I'm trying to find some link
between those killings
in the '60s
and what's going on now.
There wasn't a lot about it
in the paper.
Not surprising. Probably
minimal-police-work deal.
Back then,
equal justice under the law
wasn't too literal
around here.
Yeah?
Sam:
Okay, the courthouse records
show that mr. And mrs. Mayor
bought an abandoned property.
The previous owner
was the dorian family,
for like 150 years.
Dorian?
Yeah.
Didn't you say the dorian family
used to own this paper?
Along with most everything else
around here.
Real pillars of the town.
Right, right.
That's interesting.
What?
This cyrus dorian,
he vanished in april of '63.
The case was investigated
but never solved.
It was the time the string
of murders was going on.
Well, i pulled a bunch of paper
up on the dorian place.
It must've been in bad shape
when the mayor bought it.
Why is that?
The first thing he did
was bulldoze the place.
Mayor todd knocked down
the dorianlace?
It was a big deal. One of
the oldest local houses left.
It made the front page.
You got a date?
Uh... the 3rd
of last month.
Mayor todd bulldozed the
dorian family home on the 3rd.
The first killing
was the very next day.
Dean!
Maybe you could throw
a couple shots in that.
You didn't see
who was driving the truck?
It seemed to be no one.
Everything was moving
so fast.
And then it was just gone.
Why didn't it kill us?
Whatever is controlling the
truck wants you afraid first.
Mrs. Robinson, cassie said
that your husband saw the truck
before he died.
Mom?
Hmm?
Martin was under
a lot of stress.
You can't be sure
about what he was seeing.
Well, after tonight i think
we can be reasonably sure
that he was seeing
a truck.
What happened tonight,
you and cassie are marked, okay?
Your daughter could die,
so if you know something,
now would be a really good time
to tell us about it.
Dean...
yes.
Yes, he said
he saw a truck.
Did he know
who it belonged to?
He thought he did.
Who was that?
Cyrus...
a man named cyrus.
Is this cyrus?
Cyrus dorian died
more than 40 years ago.
How do you know he died,
mrs. Robinson?
The paper said
he went missing.
How do you know
he died?
We were all very young.
I dated cyrus a while.
I was also seeing martin,
in secret of course
'cause interracial couples
didn't go over too well then.
When i broke it off
with cyrus,
and when he found out
about martin...
i don't know...
he changed.
His hatred...
his hatred was frightening.
The string of murders.
There were rumors,
people of color disappearing
into some kind oa truck.
Nothing was ever done.
Martin and...
martin and i,
we were gonna be married
in that little church near here,
but last minute,
we decided to elope
'cause we didn't want
all the attention.
And cyrus?
The day we set for the wedding
was the day
someone set fire to the church.
There was a children's choir
practicing in there.
They all died.
Did the attacks stop
after that?
No, there was one more.
One night that truck came
for martin.
Cyrus beat him
something terrible,
but martin...
you see, martin got loose
and he started hitting cyrus
and he just kept hitting him
and hitting him.
Why didn't you call
the cops?
This was 40 years ago.
He called on his friends...
clayton, solmes,
and jimmy anderson...
and they put cyrus' body
into the truck
and then rolled it into the
swamp at the edge of his land
and all three of them kept
that secret all these years.
And now all three are gone.
So is mayor todd.
Now, he said
that you of all people
would know
that he is not a racist.
Why would he say that?
He was a good man.
He was a young deputy
back then,
investigating
cyrus's disappearance.
Once he figured out what martin
and the others had done,
he he did nothing
because he also knew
what cyrus had done.
Why didn't you tell me?
I thought
i was protecting them.
And now there's no one
left to protect.
Yes, there is.
Oh, my life was so simple.
Just school, exams,
papers on polycentric
cultural norms.
So i guess i saved you
from a boring existence.
Occasionally i miss boring.
So, this killer truck...
i miss conversations that didn't
start with "this killer truck. "
Ah...
all right, well,
this cyrus guy,
evil on a level
that infected even his truck.
When he died,
the swamp became his tomb
and his spirit was dormant
for 40 years.
So, what woke it up?
The construction on his house
or the destructi.
Right.
Demolition or remodeling
can awaken spirits,
make them restless.
Like that theater
in illinois.
Yeah.
And the guy who tears down
the family homestead,
harold todd,
is the same guy
that kept cyrus's murder quiet
and unsolved.
So now his spirit is awakened
and out for blood.
I guess. Who knows what ghosts
are thinking anyway.
You know we're gonna have to
dredge that body from the swamp?
Maman.
You said it.
Yeah.
Hey.
She's asleep.
Now what?
And we'll be back.
Don't leave the house.
Don't go getting
all authoritative on me.
I hate it.
Don't leave
the house, please?
You coming or what?
Sam: All right,
let's get her up.
All right.
Little more.
Litt more.
All right, stop.
Nice.
Hell yeah.
Now i know
what she sees in you.
What?
Come on, you can admit it.
You're still in love with her.
Can we focus, please?
I'm just saying, dean.
Hold that.
All right.
What am i getting?
Gas, flashlight.
Got it, got it.
All right,
let's get this done.
All right.
Got it.
All right,
let's get to it.
Think that'll do it?
I guess not.
So burning the body
had no effect on that thing?
Sure it did.
Now it's really pissed.
But cyrus's ghost
is gone, right, dean?
Apparently not the part
that's fused with the truck.
Where you going?
Going for a little ride.
Gonna lead that thing away.
That rusted piece of crap,
you got to burn it.
How the hell am i supposed
to burn a truck, dean?
I don't know.
Figure something out.
Figure something...
Hey, you got to give me
a minute.
I don't have a minute!
What are we doing?!
Uh... let me get back
to you.
Hey, cassie?
Hey, it's sam.
Okay, i need some information
and it has to be exactly right.
All right, dean.
This better be good!
Where are you? I'm in the middle of
nowhere with a killer truck on my ass!
It's like it knows
i put the torch to cyrus!
Dean, listen to me.
It's important.
I have to know exactly
where you are.
Decatur road,
about two miles off the highway.
Okay, headed east?
Yes!
Oh, you son of a bitch.
Okay, uh, turn right.
You make the turn?
Yeah, i made the turn!
Move this thing along
a little faster!
All right,
you see a road up ahead?
No!
Wait, yes, i see it!
Okay, turn left.
What?!
All right, now what?
Go exactly 7/10ths of a mile
and stop.
Stop?
Exactly 7/10ths, dean.
7/10ths, 7/10ths.
Dean,
are you still there?
Yeah.
What's happening?
It's just staring at me.
What do i do?
Just what you are doing...
bringing it to you.
Wh...
Come on, come on.
Dean?
You still there?
Where'd it go?
Dean,
you're where the church was.
What church?
The place cyrus burned down
and murdered all those kids.
There's not
a whole lot left.
Church ground
is hallowed ground
whether the church
is still there or not.
Evil spirits cross over
hallowed ground,
sometimes they're destroyed.
So i figured
maybe that would get rid of it.
Maybe?
Maybe?!
What if you were wrong?!
Honestly, that thought hadn't
occurred to me.
"Well, that honestly
didn't occur to me. "
I'm gonna kill him.
my mother says
to tell you thanks again.
This was a better goodbye
than the last time.
Yeah, well,
maybe this time
it'll be
a little less permanent.
You know what?
I'm a realist.
I don't see much hope
for us, dean.
Well, i've seen
stranger things happen.
Hell of a lot stranger.
Goodbye, dean.
I'll see you, cassie.
I will.
I like her.
Yeah.
You meet someone like her,
ever make you wonder
if it's worth it...
putting everything else on hold,
doing what we do?
Why don't you wake me up
when it's my turn to drive?