Dad's missing. I need you help me find him.
I can't do this alone.
Dad's given us a job to do.
He wants us to pick up what he left off.
Saving people, hunting things.
This demon killed mom and Jess.
I've got to find dad.
I've got to find Jessica's killer.
- I'm Meg.
- So, where are you headed?
No way I'm telling you.
You could be some kind of freak.
Dad?
Just to get a glimpse beyond this illusion
In 1835, Samuel Colt
made a special gun.
They say this gun can kill anything.
Though my eyes could see
I still was a blind man
Though my mind could think
I still was a mad man
I hear the voices when I'm dreaming
I have these nightmares
and sometimes, they come true.
Carry on my wayward son
You two are all I've got.
But I guess we are stronger
as a family.
We go after this damn thing,
together.
- Yes, Sir.
Don't you cry no more...
Good morning.
Can I help you?
I kinda...
I need to talk.
Well, that's what I'm here for.
I've done some things...
Not good things.
Well, there's always forgiveness
for us if we seek it.
For everyone?
Are you sure?
I like to say salvation was created
for sinners.
Tell me what's on your mind.
Well, I've lied...
A lot.
I've stolen.
I've lusted.
And the other day, I've met this man.
A nice guy, you know?
We had a really good chat...
Sort of like this.
Then I slit his throat and
ripped his heart out through his chest.
Does that make me a bad person?
I know what you are.
You can't be here.
This is hallowed ground!
Please.
Maybe that works in the minor leagues.
But not with me.
You throw like a girl.
What do you want?
The Winchesters.
I haven't spoken to John Winchester
in over a year.
You're wasting your time.
Even if I did know where they were,
I'd never tell you.
I know.
So this is it.
This is everything I know.
We got our all lives been searching for
this demon, right?
Not a trace. Just...
nothing.
Until about a year ago.
For the first time, I picked up a trail.
- That's when you took off.
- Yeah.
That's right. The demon must have
come out of hiding or hibernation.
So, what's this trail you found?
It starts in Arizona, then
New Jersey, California.
Houses burnt down at the ground.
It's going after families.
Just like it went after us.
Families with infants?
Yeah,
the night of kids' 6 month birthday.
I was 6 months old that night?
Exactly 6 months.
So basically this demon is going after
these kids for some reason.
The same why he came for me.
So mom's death...
Jessica...
It's all 'cause of me?
- We don't know that, Sam.
- Oh really?
'Cause I'd say we're pretty damn sure, Dean.
For the last time, what happened to them
is not your fault.
Yeah, you're right, it's not my fault.
But it's my problem.
No, it's not your problem.
It's our problem.
Ok,
that's enough.
So why is it doing?
What does it want?
I'd wish I had more answers.
I do.
I've always been one step behind it.
Look, I've never got there
in time to save...
So how do we find it before it hits again?
There are signs.
Look, it took me a while
to see the pattern.
But in the days before these fires,
signs crop up in the area.
Cattle death, temperature fluctuations,
electrical storms.
And then I went back and checked and...
The same thing happened in Lawrence.
A week before your mother died.
And in Palo Alto.
Before Jessica.
And these signs...
they're starting again.
Where?
Salvation, Iowa.
- Damnit!
- What is it?
- Son of a bitch!
I just got a call from Caleb.
- Is he okay?
- He's fine.
Jim Murphy is dead.
Pastor Jim?
How?
His throat was slit.
He bled out.
Caleb says they found traces of sulphur
in Jim's place.
A demon.
The demon?
I don't know.
It could be...
Caleb...
Maybe the demon knows
we're getting close.
What do you wanna do?
Now we act like every second counts.
There's two hospitals and
a house nursery in this county.
We split up.
We cover more ground.
I want records.
I want a list of every infant
that's gonna be 6 months old
the next week.
Dad, that can be dozens of kids.
How the hell are we gonna know
which one is the right one?
We'lle check them all.
That's how.
Or you got better ideas?
No, Sir.
Dad?
Yeah...
It's Jim.
I can't...
This ends. Now...
I'm ending it.
I don't care what it takes.
- Here we go, officer.
- Thank you.
Hi. Is there anything I could do for you?
Oh god, yes!
Only I, uh...
I'm working right now, so...
A train.
Hi, here, let me hold that.
I think you don't need that anymore.
Thanks.
She's gorgeous. Is she yours?
- Yeah.
- Oh wow, hi.
I'm sorry, I'm rude.
I'm Sam.
I just move end up the block.
Oh, hey, I'm Monica.
- This is Rosie.
- Rosie? Hey Rosie.
- So... Welcome to the neighbourhood.
- Thank you.
- She's such a good baby.
- I know. She... I mean, she never cries.
She just stares at everybody.
Sometimes she looks, and I swear it's...
It's like she's reading your mind.
What about you, Monica, you live here alone?
Oh my husband and I, we bought our place
just before Rosie was born.
- How old is Rosie?
- She's 6 months today.
She's big, right?
Growing like a weed!
Yeah...
Monica...
Yeah?
- Just... Just take care of yourself, okay?
- Yeah, you too, Sam.
- We'll see around.
- Yeah, definitely.
Here is daddy!
What do you...
Rosie!
A vision?
Yes.
I saw the demon burning a woman
on the ceiling.
And you think it's gonna happen to
this woman you met because...
Because these things happen exactly
the way I see them.
He started having these nightmares.
And he started having them
when he was awake.
That's like... I don't know.
It's like closer I get
to anything involving the demon,
the stronger the visions get.
Right. When would you wanna
tell me about this?
Tonight.
Something like this such happens
to your brother,
you pick up the phone and you call me.
Call you?
Are you kidding me?
Dad, I called you from Lawrence.
Alright, Sam called you
when I was dying.
I mean, getting you on the phone,
I got a better chance of
winning the lottery.
You're right.
Although I'm not real crazy about
this new tone of yours, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Look guys, vision or no vision,
the fact is
we know the demon is coming tonight.
And this family is gonna go through
the same hell that we went through.
No, they're not.
No one is. Ever again.
Hello?
Sam...
Who is this?
Think real hard. It will come to you.
Meg.
The last time I saw you,
you have fell out of a window.
Yeah, thanks to you.
That really hurt my feelings by the way.
Just your feelings?
That was a 7 story drop.
Let me speak to your dad.
My dad?
I don't know where my dad is.
It's time for the growing ups
to talk, Sam.
Let me speak to him now.
- This is John.
- Hi dear John, I'm Meg.
I'm a friend of your boys.
I'm also the one who watched Jim Murphy,
chokep up in his own blood.
Still there John Boy?
I'm here.
But that was yesterday.
Today I'm in Lincoln...
Visiting an other old friend of yours.
He wants to say hi.
John, whatever they do,
don't give...
Caleb?
You listen to me,
he's got nothing to do with anything.
You let him go.
We know you have the colt, John.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, okay.
So listen to this.
Caleb?
Caleb?!
Can you hear that?
That's the sound of your friend dying.
Now let's try this again.
We know you have the gun, John.
Words travel fast.
So as far as we're concerned,
you just declared war.
And this is what war looks like.
It has casualties.
I'm gonna kill you, you know that?
Oh, John, please.
Mind your blood pressure.
So this is the thing.
We're gonna keep doing what we're doing.
And your friends...
Anyone who's ever helped you
or gave you shelter...
Anyone you ever loved.
They'll all die.
Unless you give us that gun.
I'm waiting, Johnny.
Better answer before the buzzer.
Okay.
Sorry?
I didn't clearly get that.
I said okay.
I'll bring you the colt.
There's a warehouse in Lincoln.
In the corner of Walbash and Lake.
You're gonna meet me there.
It's gonna take me about
a day as drive to get there.
Meet me there at midnight, tonight.
That's impossible.
I can't get there in time.
And I can't just carry a gun on a plane.
The I guess your friends die, don't they?
If you do decide to make it,
come alone.
What the hell are you looking at?
So you think Meg is a demon?
Either that or she's possessed by one.
It doesn't really matter.
- What do we do?
- I'm going to Lincoln.
- What?
- It doesn't seem like I have a choice.
If I don't go,
a lot of people'll die.
Our friends'll die.
Dad, the demon is coming tonight.
For Monica and her family,
that gun is all we've got.
You can't just hand it over!
Who said anybody would hand it over?
Look, besides us and a couple of vampires,
no one's really seen the gun.
No one knows what it looks like.
So what? You're just gonna pick up
ringer at a pawn shop?
Antique store.
You're gonna hand Meg a fake gun
and hope she doesn't notice?
Look, as long as it's close...
she shouldn't be able
to tell the difference.
Yeah, but for how long?
What happens when she figures this out?
I just... I just need to buy
a few hours. That's all.
You mean for Dean and me.
You want us to stay here.
And kill this demon by ourselves.
No, Sam.
I wanna stop losing people we love.
I want you to go to school.
I want Dean to have a home.
I want Mary alive.
I just...
I just want this to be over.
Did you get it?
You know this is a trap, don't you?
That's why Meg wants you to come alone.
I can handle her.
I got a whole arsenal loaded.
Holy water, amulets...
- Dad.
- What?
- Promise me something.
- What's that?
If things go suck, just...
get the hell out.
Don't get yourself killed, alright?
You're no good to us dead.
The same goes for you.
Alright, listen to me.
They made the bullet special for this colt.
Only 4 of them are left.
Without them, this gun is useless.
Make every shot count.
Yes, Sir.
I've been waiting a long time
for this fight.
Now it's to you.
I'm not gonna be in it.
It's up to you boys now.
It's your fight.
You finish this.
You finish what I started.
You understand?
We'll see you soon, dad.
I'll see you later.
Later.
Maybe we could tell them there's a gas leak.
That might get them out of the house
for a few hours.
Yeah, and how many times has that
actually worked for us?
Yeah...
We could always tell them the truth.
Naah...
I know. I know, it's just...
What's coming after for these people?
Sam, we'll only got one move
and you know it, right?
We're gonna wait for this demon
to show itself...
And we get it before it gets them.
I wonder how Dad’s doing.
I’d feel a lot better
if we were there backing him up.
if he were here backing us up.
Au nom de J?sus, b?nis cette eau.
"In nomine de patris, in de patentis,"
"en de virtute, espiriti santi".
That's weird.
What?
After all these years, we're finally here.
That doesn't seem real.
We're just gonna keep our heads,
do our job, like always.
Yeah, but this isn't like always.
True.
Dean, uh...
I want to thank you.
For what?
For everything.
You've always had my back, you know.
Even when I couldn't count on anyone,
I could always count on you.
And uh...
I just wanted to let you know.
Just in case...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, you kidding me?
What?
Don't say
"just in case something happens to you".
I don't want to hear that freaking speech,
man.
Nobody's dying tonight.
Not us, not that family.
Nobody.
Except that demon.
That evil son of a bitch ain't getting
any older than tonight, understand me?
John, you made it.
Too bad really,
I was hoping to kill more of your friends.
Sorry to desappoint.
I can see where your boys
got their good looks.
Though I must admit, considering what
they say about you...
I thought you'd be...
taller.
Well, aren't you the chatty one?
You wanna get to business?
Fine.
Why don't you hand over the gun?
If I give you the gun,
how do I get out of here?
If you're good as they say you are,
I'm sure you'll figure something out.
Maybe I'll just shoot you.
You wanna shoot me, baby?
Go ahead.
It won't end anything.
There are more where I came from.
Who the hell is that?
He's not nearly as much fun as I am.
I can tell you that.
So I suggest you give us the gun.
Now!
This is the colt?
What do you think?
You shot me!
I can't believe you just shot me!
It's a fake!
You're dead, John.
Your boys are dead.
I never used the gun.
How could I know it wouldn't work?
I am so not in the mood for this,
I've just been shot!
Well then, I guess you're lucky
the gun wasn't real.
That's funny, John.
We're gonna strip the skin from your bones,
but that was funny.
Holy water, John?
Real cute.
Dad's not answering.
Maybe Meg was late.
- Maybe cell reception's bad.
- Yeah, well...
Dean, wait.
Listen.
It's coming.
Damnit!
Get out of my house!
- Mr. Holt, please.
- Be quiet and listen to me.
Be quiet and listen to me.
We're trying to help you.
- Charlie?
- Okay?
Is everything okay down there?
- Monica, get the baby!
- Don't go to the nursery!
You stay away from her...
What do you...
Where the hell did he go?
- My baby!
- No, wait.
I got her. I got her.
- My baby!
- He's got her.
You get away from my family!
Charlie, don't, they saved us.
I mean, they saved us.
Thank you.
It's still in there.
- Sam, Sam! No.
- Dean, let me go!
- It's still in there!
- It’s burning to the ground! It’s suicide!
- I don't care!
- I do!
Come on, dad. Answer your phone, damnit!
Something's wrong.
You hear me? Something happened.
If you had just let me go in there...
I could have ended all this...
Sam,
the only thing you would end was your life.
You don't know that.
So what? You're just willing
to sacrify yourself? Is that it?
Yeah. Yeah you're damn right.
I am.
Well, that's not gonna happen.
Not as long as I'm around.
What the hell are you talking about, Dean?
We've been searching for this demon
our whole life.
It's the only thing we've ever cared about.
Sam, I wanna waste it.
I do. Okay?
But it's not worth dying over.
- What?
- I mean it.
If hunting this demon means you
getting yourself killed...
Then I hope we never find the damn thing.
That thing killed Jess.
That thing killed mom.
You said yourself once...
that no matter what we do, they're gone.
And they're never coming back.
Don't you say that, not you...
Not after all this, don't you say that!
Sam, look...
The three of us,
that's all we have.
And it's all I have.
Sometimes I feel like I'm barely holding it
together, man.
And without you or Dad...
Dad...
He should have called by now.
Try again.
You boys really screwed up this time.
Where is he?
You're never gonna see your father again.