Take your brother outside
as fast as you can!
Now, Dean! Go!
Mary! No!
Dad is on a hunting trip...
and he hasn't been home
in a few days.
I swore I was done hunting.
I can't do this alone.
No!
We've got work to do.
This is dad's single,
most valuable possession
everything he knows about
every evil thing, it is in here.
I think he wants us to pick up
where he left off.
You know, saving people,
hunting things.
Family business.
No.
I gotta find Jessica's killer.
This is the only thing
I can think about.
Sam, you know that
we're gonna find dad, yeah?
Yeah, I know.
Nervous flyer?
Is it that obvious, huh?
You know what are the odds
of dying in a plane crash?
I mean what,
twenty thousands to one?
Oh, it's really reassuring,
thank you.
Thanks.
Amanda, how are you today?
I'm doing just fine, Chuck.
Welcome aboard.
15-C towards the back of the plane
on the right.
Have a nice flight, sir.
Oh, I'm counting on it.
11-F, that's at the middle
of the plane on...
Thank you.
...the left.
Excuse me. Do you know
how long we have been up?
About forty minutes.
Wow! Time really does fly, huh?
Excuse me.
I've got to stretch my legs.
Hey, what the hell are you doing?!
Oh, my god!
Morning, sunshine!
What time is it?
Oh, it's about 5:45.
- In the morning?
- Yap.
Where does the day go?
Did you get any sleep last night?
- Yeah, I got a couple of hours.
- You liar.
See, I was up at 3,
and you were watching
George Foreman informercials.
What can I say?
Riveting TV!
When's the last time
you got a good night sleep?
I don't know. A little while I guess.
It's not a big deal.
Yeah, it is!
- Okay, I appreciate your concern...
- Oh, I'm not concerned about you.
It's your job to keep my ass alive!
So I need you sharp.
Seriously you're still having
nightmares about Jess?
Yeah.
But it's not just her, it's everything.
I just forgot, you know, this job...
man, it gets to you.
Well you can't let it.
You can't bring it home like that.
So what?
All this it never keeps you up at night?
Never?!
You never afraid?
No, not really.
That's not fear.
That's precaution.
All right, whatever.
I'm too tired to argue.
- Hallo?
- Dean?
It's huh... It's Jerry Panowski.
You and your dad helped me out
a couple of years back.
Oh, right.
Yeah, up in Kittanning, Pensylvania.
The poltergeist thing.
- It's not back, is it?
- No.
No.
Thank God, no.
But it's something else
and I think it could be a lot worse.
What is it?
Can we talk in person?
Thanks for making
the trip so quick.
I ought to be doing you guys a favour,
not the other way around.
Dean and your dad
really helped me out.
Yeah, he told me.
It was a poltergeist?
Poltergeist?
Man, I loved that movie.
Hey, nobody is talking to you,
keep walking.
Damn right it was a poltergeist
practically it tore our house apart.
I'll tell you something.
If it wasn't for you and your dad
I probably wouldn't be alive.
Your dad said you are off
to college, that's right?
Yeah, I was. I'm...
taking some time off.
He was really proud of you,
I could tell.
He talked about you all the time.
- He did?
- Yeah, you bet he did.
Oh, hey, you know I tried to get
hold of him but I couldn't.
How is he doing anyway?
He is...
wrapped up in a job right now.
Well, we're missing the old man,
we get a Sam.
Even trade, huh?
No, not by a long shot.
I've got something I want
you guys to hear.
I listened to this.
Well, sounded like
it was appear on?
Normally, I wouldn't have
access to this.
It's the cockpit voice recorder
for the United Britannian flight 2485.
It was one of ours.
Mayday! Mayday! Repeat!
It's the United Britannian flight 2485...
We wants you to give immediately instructions.
We need help...
United Britannian Flight 2485,
we copy your mayday.
maybe we are experiencing some...
mechanical failure...
Took off from here...
crashed about two hundred miles up.
Others saying mechanical failure.
Cabin depressurized somehow,
nobody knows why.
Over a hundred people onboard,
only seven we got alive.
The pilot was one.
His name is Chuck Lambert,
he is a good friend of mine.
Chuck is a...
Well, he's pretty broken up about it.
Like it was his fault.
- You don't think it was?
- No, I don't.
Jerry, we're gonna need
passenger manifests,
a list of the survivors...
Right, and a...
We'll need take a look at the wreckage.
The other stuff is no problem,
but the wreckage...
Fellows in NTSB has it lockdown
in an evidence warehouse.
No way I've got that clearance.
No problem.
- Hey!
- Hi.
You have been there forever.
You can't rush perfection!
Homeland security?
It's pretty illegal.
Even for us.
Hell, well?
Something new.
You know, people
have seen it a thousand times.
All right, so what you got?
Well, there is definitely EVP
on the cockpit voice recorder.
- Yeah?
- Listen.
No survivors!
No survivors?
What's that supposed to mean?
There were seven survivors.
Got me.
So what you think?
A haunted flight?
There is long history of
spirits and death omens
on planes, on ships
like phantom travelers.
Or, do you remember flight 401?
Right, the one that crasher,
and the airlines salvaged
some of its parts put in other planes.
And the spirits of the pilot and
co-pilot haunted those parts.
- Right.
- Yeah?
Maybe we've similar deal.
All right, so the survivors.
Which one we have to talk to first?
Third on the list.
Max Jaffe.
Why him?
For one, he lives around here...
and two, if anyone saw
anything weird, he did.
What makes you say that?
Oh, I spoke to his mother,
and she told me where we find him.
I don't understand.
I already spoke with homeland security.
Right.
As new information has come up,
so if you could just answer
a couple of questions.
Just before the plain went down,
did you notice anything unusual?
Like what?
Strange lights,
weird noises maybe?
Voices?
No, nothing.
Mister Jaffe...
- Jaffee.
- Jaffee...
You checked yourself in here, right?
Can I ask why?
I was a little stressed,
I survived a plain crash.
And that's what terrified you?
And that's what you afraid of?
I... I don't wanna talk
about this anymore.
I think maybe you did
see something up there.
We need to know what.
No. No, I was delusional.
Seeing things.
He seeing things.
It's okay.
Then just tell us
what you thought you saw, please.
There was this man.
And... he had these... eyes.
These...
black eyes.
I saw him...
I thought I saw him...
What?
He opened the emergency exit.
And that's... that's impossible.
Right? I mean, I looked that up.
There is something like
two tons of pressure on that door.
Yeah.
This man, uh, did he seemed
to appear and disappear?
Rapidly, he would looked
something like a mirage?
What are you, nuts?!
He was a passanger,
he was sitting right in front of me.
So here we are.
George Phelps.
Seat 20-C.
Hm. Man, I don't care
how strong you are.
Even you hopped up on PCP
or something...
No way you can open up
an emergency door during the flight.
No, if you're a human.
But maybe this guy, George,
is something else.
Some kind of a creature maybe,
in human form?
Is this look like
where a creature's lair to you?
This is your late husband?
Yes, that was my George.
And you said, he was a... dentist?
He was headed to
a convention in Denver.
Do you know, that he was
petrified to fly?
For him to go like that.
How long have you been married?
13 years.
And all that time, did you ever noticed
anything strange about him?
Anything out of ordinary?
Well...
He had acid reflux,
if that's what you mean?
I mean it goes without saying
it's doesn't make any sense.
A middle-aged dentist with an ulcers
is not exactly evil-personified.
You know what we need to do
is getting inside
the NTSB warehouse
check out the wreckage.
Okay.
But if we're gonna go down around,
we better look depart.
Man, I look like
one of the "Blues Brothers".
No, you don't.
You look more like a seventh grader
at his first dance.
I hate this thing.
Hey, you want to go in
that warehouse or not?
What is that?
It's an EMF meter.
It metes electromagnetic frequencies.
Dean, I know what
an EMF meter is,
but why is that it looks like
as a busted up walkman?
That's why I made it out of.
It's homamade.
Yeah, I can see that.
Check out the emergency door handle.
- What is this stuff?
- We are going to find out.
Gentlemen.
Homeland security?
Why?
One of you two guys isn't enough?
What are you talking about?
Two of your budies went inside
not 5 minutes ago.
Well, these Mort's suits
do come in handy.
Listen, Chuck.
Let's get back on the horse.
Only in this case,
it's a little twin engine.
Not even a horse,
more like a pony.
And I'll be right there with you, too.
Anytime you feel
you don't want the wheel, I'll take over.
Look, Chuck.
You don't have to do this today.
I'm not try to rush you.
No... the waiting is worse.
Okay, they fueled up the tank.
There we go.
This stuff is covered in sulphur.
You sure?
Take a look for yourself.
If you fellas would excuse me,
I have an idiot to fire.
Hey, Einstein! Hey, you!
What the hell you doing?!
Put the wrench down!
Yeah, there is
not too many things
that leave behind
sulphuric residue.
Demonic possession?
That would explain how a mortal man
would've the strength to open up
the emergency hatch.
If he got possessed, it's possible.
You know, this goes way beyond
floating over a bed,
or barf from pea soup,
it's one thing to possess a person,
but to use him
to take down an entire airplane?
You ever heard
something like this before?
Never.
I'm ready.
Let's do this.
How are you feeling?
I feel great.
You'll be back flying jumbos
before you know it.
I hope so.
How long we've been up?
Almost forty minutes.
Wow! The time really does fly.
What are you doing?!
So... every religion and
every world culture...
has the concept of demons and
demonic possession, right?
Let them christian, native american,
hindu, you name it.
Yeah but not one described
anything like this.
Well that's not exactly true.
You see, according
japanese believes
certain demons are
behind some disasters,
both natural and man made.
One causes earthquake,
and other causes desease.
And this causes plane crashes?
All right, so what?
We have a demon
that's evolved with the times,
and found a way to
ratchet up the body count?
Yeah.
And you know, who knows how many planes
he's brought down before this one.
What?
I don't know,
I mean this is not a normal gig.
I mean, demons,
they don't want anything,
just death and destruction
for their own sake.
This is big.
I wish that dad was here.
Yeah, me too.
- Hello?
- Dean, it's Jerry.
- Oh, hi, Jerry.
- My pilot friend...
Chuck Lambert is dead.
Jerry, I'm sorry.
What happened?
He and his buddy went up
in a small twin,
but an hour ago
the plain went down.
Where this happened?
That's 60 miles west of here,
in Nazareth.
I will try to ignore the irony in that.
Sorry?
Nothing.
Jerry, hang on there.
I will catch up with you soon.
- Another crash?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Where?
Nazareth.
Sulphur?
Oh, that's great.
All right, so there're two
plane crashes involving Chuck Lambert.
This demon sounds like
goes after him.
Whit all respect to Chuck,
if that's the case,
that would be a good news.
What's the bad news?
Chuck's plane went down
exactly forty minutes on the fly.
And get this,
so the flight 2485.
40 minutes?
What is that mean?
It's biblical numerology.
You know, Noah's ark,
it rained for forty days.
That number means death.
I went back and there were six
plane crashes over the last decade
that all went down exactly forty minutes on.
Any survivors?
No. Or it not until now at least,
until 2485 for some reason.
On the cockpit voice recorder
remember what the evp said?
No survivors.
It's going after all the survivors.
It should finish the job.
Really?
Well, we thank you taking our survey
and if you do plan a flight
please don't forget your friends
at United Britannia Airlines.
Thanks.
All right. That takes care of
Blane Sanderson and Dennis Holloway.
They're not flying any time soon.
So the only wild card is
the fly attendant, Amanda Walker.
Right. Her sister Karen said
her flight leaves in Minneapolis at 8pm,
that's her first night back on the job.
It sounds like we just our luck.
Dean, this is an 5 hour drive, man.
Even with you by the wheel.
Why don't you call
Amanda's cellphone again,
see if we can head her off the pass.
I already left her three voice messages,
she just turned her cellphone off.
- God! We never gonna make it.
- We'll make it.
Right there.
It will boarding in thirty minutes.
Okay, we still left some cards to play.
We gonna need find a phone.
Airport services.
- I'm at gate 13.
- Who you wanna call, sir?
I'm trying contact with
an Amanda Walker,
she is a flight attendant on
a flight hm... flight 424.
Amanda Walker.
Amanda Walker, you have
a phone call flight crew six from gate 13.
Come on!
This is Amanda Walker.
Miss Walker?
Hi, this is Dr. James Hetfield from
St. Francis Memorial Hospital.
- We have a Karen Walker here.
- My Karen?!
Nothing serious just a minor car accident,
but she was injured  so...
Wait, wait, that's impossible.
I just got off the phone with her.
- You what?
- Five minutes ago.
She's at her house cramming
for a final...
Who is this?
That's must be some mistake.
How would do you even know
I was here?
Is this one of Vince's friends?
Guilties charged.
This is unbelievable!
He is really sorry.
Well, you tell him
to mind his own business
and stay out of my life. Okay?
Yes. But, he really needs
to see you tonight.
- So...
- No, I'm sorry, it's too late.
Don't be like that! Come on,
the guy's a mess, really, a pathetic.
Really?
Oh, yeah!
Look, I gotta go...
tell him to call me when I landed.
No, no, wait, Amanda...
Amanda!
How are you?
- Hey, Bob.
- Hey.
Damn it!
So close!
All right, it's time for plan B.
We're getting on that plane.
Just hold on a second.
Dean, that plane is leaving with over
a hundred passengers on board,
and if we're right,
that plane is gonna crash.
I know!
Okay. Then we're getting on that plane,
we need to find that demon and exorcise it.
Look, I'll get the tickets, you just go
get whatever you can out of the trunk,
whatever will make it through security,
meet me back here in 5 minutes.
Are you okay?
No, not really.
Why? What's wrong?
I kind of have this problem with...
Flying?
It's never been an issue until now.
Are you joking, right?
Do I look like I'm joking?!
Why do you think
I drive everywhere, Sam?!
All right. I'll go.
- What?
- I'll do this one my own.
Are you nuts?!
You said yourself
that's plane gonna crash!
Look, Dean, we can do it together,
I can do this one by myself,
I'm not seeing a third option here.
Come on!
Really?
Man...
- Just try to relax.
- Just try to shut up!
- Are you humming Metallica?
- Calms me down.
Look, man, I get you're nervous, all right?
But you got to stay focused.
Okay.
I mean, we got 32 minutes
and counting
to track this thing down
or whoever it's possessing anyway
and perform a full exorcism.
Yeah, on a crowded airplane
that's gonna be easy.
Just take one step at a time, all right?
Now... who is it possessing?
Well, it's usually gonna be somebody
with some sort of weakness you know,
a chink in the armor
that the demon can worm through.
Somebody with an addiction,
or some sort of emotional distress.
Well this is Amanda's first flight
after the crash,
if I were her I'd be messed up.
Excuse me.
Are you Amanda?
No, I'm not.
Oh, my mistake.
All right, well, it's got to be Amanda back there,
so I could talk to her.
And uh...
I'll get a read on her mental state.
What if she is already possessed?
There is a way to test that.
I brought holy water.
No.
I think we can go more settled.
If she's possessed,
she'll flinch at the name of God.
Uh, nice.
Hey?
- What?
- Say it in latin.
I know!
Hey?
- What?!
- In latin it's Christo.
Dude, I know! I'm not an idiot!
Ladies and gentlemen
this is the first officer speak...
- Hi.
- Can I help you in something?
- Oh, no. I'm just a bit of an uneasy flier.
Makes me feel better
to walk around a little bit.
Oh, it happens with the best of us.
Of course, you being a stewardess,
I guess flying comes easy to you.
Oh, you'd be surprised.
Really? You...
you're a nervous flyer?
Yeah, maybe. A little bit.
How is it though being a stewardes
you're scared to fly?
Kind of a long story.
All right, I'm sorry for asking.
Okay.
You never considered
other employment?
No.
Look, everybody scared of something.
I just... I'm not gonna let it hold me back.
Christo.
I'm sorry, did you say something?
Christo?
I didn't... I didn't...
Oh, nothing, never mind.
Okay.
All right, she is gotta be the most
well-adjusted person on the planet.
You said Christo?
- Yeah.
- And?
There is no demon in her.
There is no demon getting in her.
So it is on the plane
could be anyone, anywhere.
Come on, that can be normal?!
Hey! Hey... just a little turbulance.
Sam, this plane is going to crash, okay?
So quit treating me like I'm freaking fool!
- You need to calm down.
- Well, I'm sorry I can't!
Yes, you can.
Dude, stow the touchy-feely,
self-help-yoga crap. It's not helping!
Listen, you're panicked,
you're wide open to demonic possession,
so you need to calm yourself down,
right now.
Good.
Now, I found an exorcism in here
that I think is gonna work.
The Rituale Romanum.
What we have to do?
It's two parts. The first part is
spells the demon from the victim's body
and makes it manifest
which actually makes him more powerful.
- More powerful?
- Yeah.
How?
Well, it doesn't need to
possess someone anymore,
it can just break out and go on it's own.
Oh, and why is that a good thing?
Well, because the second part
sends the bastard back to hell.
Once and for all.
First things first we gotta find it.
- Man! Don't do that!
- Anything?
No, nothing,
how much time we got?
15 minutes.
Maybe we missed somebody.
Maybe the thing is
just not on the plane.
You believe that?
Well, I will, if you will.
What is it?!
Christo!
She is not gonna believe this.
12 minutes, dude!
Oh, hi!
The flight's not too bumpy for you I hope.
Actually that's kind of
what we need to talk to you about.
Okay. What can I do for you?
This is going to sound nuts, but...
we just don't have time for
"The Truth is Out There" speach right now...
Look, we know
you were on the flight 2485.
Who are you guys?
Now, we spoken
some of the other survivors,
and we know something
brought down that plane,
and it wasn't mechanical failure.
We need your help,
because we need to stop
from happening again, here, now.
I'm sorry...
I'm very busy, I have to go back...
Wait, wait a second.
We will not hurt you, okay?
But listen to me.
The pilot on 2485, Chuck Lambert,
he is dead.
What?!
Chuck is dead?
He died in a plane crach.
And that's two plane crashes in two months.
That doesn't strike you a little strange?
Look, there was something wrong with 2485
now maybe you sensed it, maybe you didn't,
but there's something wrong
with this flight, too.
Mandy, you have to believe us.
On 2485 there was this man...
he have this eyes...
Yes, that's exactly
what we're talking about!
I don't understand
what are you asking me to do?!
Get the co-pilot,
we need you to bring him back here.
Why?
What does he have to do with anything?
We don't have time to explain,
we just need to talk to him, okay?
How am I supposed to going to
the cockpit and get the co-pilot...
Whatever it takes! Do whatever it takes,
just tell that something's broken back here,
whatever that'll get him out of that cockpit.
You know that I can lose my job?
You'll lose lot more than that
if you don't help us out!
Okay.
Now what's the problem?
Wait, what are you doing with him?
You said you just wanna talk to him!
We are gonna talk to him!
No!
Oh my God!
What's wrong with him?
Look, we need you to calm down,
we need you outside of the curtain.
Don't let anybody in, okay?
Can you do that?
Amanda?
Okay. Okay.
Hurry up, Sam. I don't know
how much longer I can hold him.
Regna terrae cantate Deo:
psallite Domino...
qui vehitur per caelus,
caelos antiquos...
Okay, I get him!
Ecce, edit vocem suam, vocem potentem
Agnoscite potentiam Dei!
I know what happened to your girlfriend!
She must have died screaming!
Even now, she burns!
Sam!
...et potentia ejus in nubibus.
I got him!
- Where it go?
- It's on the plane.
Hurry up!
We gotta finish it!
Nooo!
Timendus est Deus e sancto suo...
ipse potentiam dat et...
Gloria Patri.
You sure you can't tell me
what happened?
I don't know. I was working at the airport,
then it all goes blank.
I don't even know how I get on that plane.
Anything else?
No, that's all.
Thank you.
Let's get out of here.
Are you okay?
Dean.
It knew about Jessica.
Sam, these things, they read minds.
They lie.
All right? Thats all it was.
Yeah.
Come on.
Nobody knows
what you guys did, but I do.
Lot of people could have been killed.
Your dad is gonna be real proud.
I'll see you around, Jerry.
- Hey, Jerry!
- Yeah?
I wanted to ask you, how did you get
my cellphone number anyway?
I only have it from like six months.
Your dad gave it to me.
- What?
- When did you talk to him?
Well, I didn't exactly talked to him but...
I called his number, his voice message
said to give you a call.
Thanks again, guys.
This doesn't make any sense, man.
I called dad's number like fifty times.
It's been out of service.
This is John Winchester.
I can't be reached.
If this is an emergency,
call my son, Dean.
866-907-3235.
He can help.
English script by Mammut
Thanks to Donnie and Pocok for the help
Special thanks to XTC