Dad's on a hunting trip.
And he hasn't been homein a few days.
I sworeI was done hunting.
I can't do this alone.
No!
I think dad wants us to pick upwhere he left off --
saving people,hunting things.
No, I got to findjessica's killer.
okay, what do you think?
Um...
oh, god.Too martha stewart?
Here, wear this.
Um...I don't knowif this is really me.
Lori, there's a hot chickburied somewhere in there.
Okay, okay.
so?
Damn, girl!
He's not gonna knowwhat hit him.
okay, I thinkhe's probably downstairs.
I'll see you later.
Don't do anythingI wouldn't do.
There's nothingyou wouldn't do.
It's true.
Lori: I thought we weregoing to the party.
Rich: Well, we can't arriveon time.
You know,if I didn't know any better,
I'd think you brought me hereon purpose.
What? I'm offended.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Do you want to get that?
Definitely not.
No.
It's okay.
Hey, I mean it.
What was that?
I don't know.
What is that?
Rich, no!
Just wait here.
What the hell?
Rich, let's go.
Aah!
Rich?
Rich, Where are you ?
Okay.
All right.
Thank you for your time.
Your half-caff
double venti vanilla latte
is getting cold over here,
francis.
Byte me.
So, anything?
I had them check the fbi's
missing-persons databank.
No "john does"
fitting that description.
I even ran his plates
for traffic violations.
I'm telling you, I don't think
dad wants to be found.
Check this out.
News item
out of plains courier,
ankeny, iowa.
It's about 100 miles
from here.
"Mutilated body was found
near the victim's car
parked on 9 mile road."
Keep reading.
"Authorities are unable
to provide
"a realistic description
of the killer.
"The sole eyewitness,
whose name has been withheld,
is quoted as saying
the attacker was invisible."
Could be something
interesting.
It could be nothing.
One witness
who didn't see anything
doesn't mean
it's the invisible man.
But what if it is?
Dad would check it out.
Why are we here?
Victim lived here.
Nice wheels.
We're your fraternity brothersfrom ohio.
We're new in town --transfers.
Looking for a place to stay.
Who are you?
We're your new roommates.
Do me a favor?Get my back.
Big game today.
He's the artist.
Things he can dowith a brush...
so...
murph, is it true?
What?
We heard one of the guys heregot killed last week.
Yeah.
What happened?
They're saying some psychowith a knife,
maybe a drifterpassing through.
Rich was a good guy.
Rich was with somebody?
Not just somebody --lori sorenson.
Who's lori sorenson?
You missed a spotdown on the back.
Lori's a freshman.She's a local.
Super hot.
And get this --she's a reverend's daughter.
You wouldn't happen to knowwhich church, would you?
Our hearts go out to the familyof the young man who perished,
and my personal prayersof thanks go out, as well,
because I believe he diedtrying to protect my daughter.
And now, as time healsall our wounds,
we should reflect onwhat this tragedy means to us
as a church.H...
.as a community,and as a family.
The loss of a young personis particularly tragic.
A life unlived is the saddestof passings.
So, please,let us pray for peace,
for guidance,
and for the powerto protect our children.
I can'T.It's sunday night.
It's just us girls.
We're gonna do tequila shotsand watch "reality bites."
My dad makes dinnerevery sunday night.
Come on, lori.
I know this has been hard,
but you are allowedto have fun.
I'll try.
Okay.
Are you lori?
Yeah.
My name is sam.
This is my brother, dean.
We just transferred hereto the university.
I saw you inside.
We don't want to bother you.We heard about what happened.
We wanted to sayhow sorry we were.
I kind of knowwhat you're going through.
I -- I saw someoneget hurt once.
It's somethingyou don't forget.
Dad, this is sam and dean.They're new students.
It's a pleasure to meet you,sir.
I must say that wasan inspiring sermon.
Thank you very much.
It's so niceto find young people
who are opento the lord's message.
Listen, we're new in town,actually,
and we're looking for A...
tell me, lori,what are the police saying?
Well, they don't have a lotto go on.
I think they blame mefor that.
What do you mean?
My story.
I was so scared,I guess I was seeing things.
That doesn't meanit wasn't real.
Dean:So you believe her?
I do.
I think she's hot, too.
No, man, there's somethingin her eyes.
And listen to this.
She heard scratchingon the roof
and found the bloody body
suspended upside downover the car.
Bloody body suspended?That sounds like --
the hookman legend.
That's one of the most famousurban legends.
You don't think that we'redealing with the hookman.
Every urban legendhas a source,
a place where it all began.
What about the scratchesand the tire punctures
and the invisible killer?
Maybe the hookmanisn't a man at all.
What if it's some kindof spirit?
Here you go.
Arrest recordsgoing back to 1851.
[ Coughs ] Thanks.
Okay.
This is how you spent fourgood years of your life, huh?
Welcome to higher education.
Hey, check this out.
1862 --
a preacher named jacob karnswas arrested for murder.
He was so angry overthe red-light district in town
that one nighthe killed 13 prostitutes.
"Some of the deceasedwere found in their beds,
"sheets soaked with blood,
"others suspended upside downfrom the limbs of trees
as a warning against sinsof the flesh."
Get this --the murder weapon?
Looks like the preacherlost his hand in an accident,
had it replacedwith a silver hook.
Look whereall this happened.
9 mile road.
Same place where the frat boywas killed.
Nice job, dr. Venkman.
Let's check it out.
I know this is your first timereally living alone
since mom died.
That's not it.I worry about you.
There are 22 girls in there.I'm perfectly safe.
That's whatI'm worried about.
You don't think I knowwhat goes on in there?
Dad, do we have to havethis argument again?
I'm over 18.I can live my own life.
Which means partyingwith that roommate of yours.
I'm an adult.I can take care of myself.
Good night.
Lori.Lori, come --
lori.
Taylor, are you awake?
Here you go.
If it is a spirit,buckshot won't do much good.
Yeah. Rock salt.
Hmm. Salt beinga spirit deterrent.
Yeah.
It won't kill 'em,but it'll slow 'em down.
That's pretty good.You and dad think of this?
I told you,
you don't have to be a collegegraduate to be a genius.
Over there, over there.
Put the gun down now!Now!
Hands behind your head!
Wait, wait, wait!Okay, okay.
Get down on your knees!Come on, do it!
On your knees.
Get down on your bellies.Come on, do it.
He had the gun.
[ Gasps ]Oh, my god!
Saved your ass.
Talked the sheriff downto a fine, dude.
I'm matlock.But how?
Told him you werea dumb-ass pledge
and that we were hazing you.
What about the shotgun?
I said that you werehunting ghosts
and that spiritsare repelled by rock salt.
You know,typical hell week prank.
And he believed you?
Well, you look likea dumb-ass pledge.
I just wantto take her home.
I understand, reverend,
but lori's now connectedto two murders
and I can't ignore that.
Listen to me.
Arrest her nowor let me take her home.
Make sure she's availablefor questioning.
Thank you.
Why would the hookmanhave come here?
This is a long wayfrom 9 mile road.
Maybe he's not hauntingthe scene of his crime.
Maybe it's aboutsomething else.
Dude, sorority girls.
Think we'll seea naked pillow fight?
Try and be quiet,will you?
Me be quiet?You be quiet.
"Aren't you gladyou didn't turn on the light?"
That's right outof the legend.
Yeah, that's classic hookman,all right.
It's definitely a spirit.
Yeah. I've never smelled ozonethis strong before.
Hey, come here.
Does that look familiarto you?
It's the same symbol.
Seems like it is the spiritof jacob karns.
Let's findthe dude's grave,
salt and burn the bones,and put him down.
"After execution,jacob karns was laid to rest
in old north cemeteryin an unmarked grave."
Super.
Okay, so,we know it's jacob karns,
but we still don't knowwhere he'll manifest next.
Or why.
I'll take a wild guessabout why.
I think your friend lorihas something to do with this.
You've been holding outon me.
This college thingis awesome!
This wasn't reallymy experience.
Let me guess --
library, studying,straight as.
What a geek.
Did you do your homework?
Yeah, it was bugging me.
How is the hookman tiedwith lori?
I think I came upwith something.
1932 -- "clergyman arrestedfor murder."
1967 -- "seminarian heldin hippie rampage."
There's a pattern here.
In both cases, the suspectwas a man of religion
who openly preachedagainst immorality
and then found himselfwanted for killings
he claimed were the workof an invisible force,
killings carried out --get this --
with a sharp instrument.
What's the connectionto lori?
A man of religion who openlypreaches against immorality.
Except this time insteadof saving the whole town,
he's trying to savehis only daughter.
Reverend sorenson.
Do you thinkhe's summoning the spirit?
Maybe.
Or you knowhow a poltergeist
can haunt a person insteadof a place?
The spirit latches onto thereverend's repressed emotions,
feeds off them.
Without the reverendever even knowing it.
Either way, you should keepan eye on lori tonight.
What about you?
I'm gonna go see if I can findthat unmarked grave.
Here we go.
That's it.
Next time, I get to watchthe cute girl's house.
Hello, preacher.
I saw you from upstairs.
What are you doing here?
I'm keeping an eyeon the place.
I was worried.
About me?
Yeah, sorry.
No, it's cool.
I already called the cops.
No, seriously,I think you're sweet,
which is probably whyyou should run away from me
as fast as you can.
Why would you say that?
It's like I'm cursedor something.
People around mekeep dying.
I thinkI know how you feel.
Goodbye, preacher.
No one willtalk to me anymore...
except you.
The sheriff thinksI'm a suspect.
And you knowwhat my dad will say?
"Pave faith."
What does he knowabout faith?
I heard you guysfighting before.
He's seeing a woman,a married woman.
I just found out.
She comes to our churchwith her husband,
I know her kids,
and he talks to me aboutreligion, about morality?
It's like on one hand,you know,
just do what you wantand be happy,
but he taught me --
raised me to believe thatif you do something wrong,
you will get punished.
I just don't knowwhat to think anymore.
Sam?
Lori, I can'T.
That someone you lost?
I'm sorry.
Lori.
Come inside, please.
I'll come inwhen I'm ready.
Ack! Aah!
No! No!
Dad!
It's okay.It's all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
We were just talking.
Then lori's dad came out,and then he appeared.
Man: A big man carryinga weapon, some kind of a hook?
Yes, sir.
Ever seen him before?
No, sir.
Son, it seems every timeI turn around, I'm seeing you.
I suggest you tryto stay out of trouble.
Yes, sir.
It's all right.I'm with him.
That's my brother.Hey, brother.
Let him through.
Thanks.
Go ahead.
You okay?
Yeah.
What the hell happened?
Hookman.
You saw him?
Damn right.
Why didn't you torchthe bones?
I did. Are you sure it'sthe spirit of jacob karns?
Sure as hell looked like him.And that's not all.
I don't think the spiritis latching onto the reverend.
Yeah, the guy wouldn't sendthe hookman after himself.
I thinkit's latching onto lori.
Last night she found outthat her father
is having an affairwith a married woman.
So what?
So, she's upset about it.
She's upset aboutthe immorality of it.
She was raised to believe
that if you do somethingwrong, you get punished.
Okay, so shehe's conflicted,
and the spiritof preacher karns
is latching ontoher emotions
and doingthe punishing for her.
Right.
Rich comes on too strong.
Taylor tries to make herinto a party girl.
Dad has an affair.
Remind me not to pissthis girl off.
But I burned those bones.I buried them in salt.
Why didn't that stop him?
You must've missedsomething.
No, I burned everythingin that coffin.
Did you get the hook?
The hook?
It was the murder weapon,
and in a wayit was part of him.
So, like the bones,
the hook is a sourceof his power.
So, if we find the hook...
both:We stop the hookman.
Here's something,I think.
Logbook,iowa state penitentiary.
"Karns, jacob --
personal affects,disposition thereof."
Does it mention the hook?
"Upon execution, all earthlyitems shall be remanded
"to the prisoner's houseof worship,
st. Barnabas church."
Isn't that where lori'sfather preaches?
Yeah.
Where lori lives?
That's why the hookman'sbeen haunting reverends
and reverends' daughtersfor the past 200 years.
But if the hook were atthe church or lori's house,
don't you think someonemight've seen it?
I mean, a blood-stained,silver-handled hook?
Check the church records.
"St. Barnabas donations,1862.
"Received --silver-handled hook
"from state penitentiary.
Reforged."
They melted it down,made it into something else.
All right.We can't take any chances.
Anything silvergoes in the fire.
I agree.
Lori's still atthe hospital.
We'll have to break in.
All right,take your pick.
I'll take the house.
Okay.
Hey.
Stay out of herunderwear drawer.
I got everythingthat even looks silver.
Better safe than sorry.
Move, move.
Lori?
What are you doing here?
What is it?
I've been trying to understandwhat's been happening, why.
Now I know, so I'm prayingfor forgiveness.
Forgiveness for what?
Don't you see?
I'm to blame for all this.
I've read in the bibleabout avenging angels.
Trust me.
This guy -- he's no angel.
I was so angry atmy father.
Part of me wanted himpunished,
and then he cameand he punished him.
It's not your fault.
Yes, it is.
I don't know how,but it is.
I killed rich.
Taylor, too.
I nearly killed my father.
Lori.
I can see it now.
They didn't deserveto be punished.
I do.
Come on.We got to go.
Go!
Come on!
No!
Come on, get up.
Sam, drop!
I thoughtwe got all the silver.
Why is he still here?
Maybe we missed something.
Lori, where did you getthat chain?
My father gave it to me.
Where'd your dad get it?
It was a church heirloom.He gave it to me.
Is it silver?
Yes.
Sam.
And you saw him, too,the man with the hook?
Yes, I told you.We all saw him.
We fought him off,and then he ran.
And that's all?
Yeah, that's all.
Listen,you and your brother --
oh, don't worry.We're leaving town.
You gonna be okay?
Yeah.
I still don't knowwhat happened,
but I do knowyou saved my life.
My father's, too.
Thank you.
We could stay.