sammy!
take your brother outside
as fast as you can!
go!
dad's on a hunting trip.
and he hasn't been home
in a few days.
this is dad's book.
i think he wants us to pick up
where he left off -
saving people, hunting things,
the family business.
i got to find dad. it's the only
think i can think about.
bethany:
now i lay me down to sleep.
i pray the lord my soul to keep.
thy angels watch me
through the night
and keep me safe
till morning light.
amen.
night, monkeypuss.
daddy?
is mommy coming home?
no, honey.
she's spending the night at
the hospital with your sister.
hey.
you sleep tight now.
dean: yeah,
you probably missed something.
dude, i ran lexisnexis,
local police reports,
newspapers - i couldn't find
a single red flag.
are you sure you got
the coordinates right?
yeah, i double-checked.
it's fitchburg, wisconsin.
dad wouldn't have sent us
coordinates
if it wasn't important,
sammy.
well, i'm telling you,
i looked,
and all i could find was a big,
steamy pile of nothing.
if dad's sending us
hunting for something,
i don't know what.
well, maybe he's gonna
meet us there.
yeah, 'cause he's been so easy
to find up to this point.
you're a real smartass,
you know that?
don't worry.
i'm sure there's something
in fitchburg worth killing.
yeah?
what makes you so sure?
because i'm the oldest,
which means i'm always right.
no, it doesn't.
it totally does.
well, the waitress thinks
that the local freemasons are up
to something sneaky,
but other than that,
nobody's heard
about anything weird going on.
dean, you got the time?
10 after 4:00.
why?
what's wrong
with this picture?
school's out, isn't it?
yeah.
so where is everybody?
this place should be crawling
with kids right now.
it sure is quiet
out here.
yeah, it's a shame.
why is that?
you know, kids getting sick.
it's a terrible thing.
how many?
just five or six,
but serious, hospital serious.
a lot of parents are getting
pretty anxious.
they think it's catching.
dude, dude,
i am not using this i.d.
why not?
because it says
"bikini inspector" on it.
don't worry.
she won't look that close.
hell,
she won't even ask to see it.
it's all about confidence,
sammy.
hi.
i'm dr. jerry kaplan,
center for disease control.
can i see some i.d.?
yeah, of course.
now, could you direct me
to the pediatrics ward?
okay, just go down that hall,
turn left, up the stairs.
you'll see them.
right.
thank you.
see?
told you it would work.
follow me.
it's upstairs.
sam: dean.
thanks for seeing us,
dr. hydaker.
oh, i'm glad you guys
are here.
i was just about to call
the cdc myself.
how did you find out
anyway?
oh, some g.p. -
i forget his name -
he called atlanta and must have
beat you to the punch.
so you say you got six cases
so far?
yeah, in five weeks.
at first i thought
it was bacterial pneumonia,
not that newsworthy.
but now...
now, what?
the kids aren't responding
to antibiotics.
their white-cell counts
keep going down.
their immune systems
just aren't doing their job.
it's like their bodies
are wearing out.
betty:
excuse me, dr. hydaker.
you ever see anything
like this before?
never this severe.
the way it spreads -
that's a new one for me.
what do you mean?
it works its way
through families,
but only the children,
one sibling after another.
you mind if we interview
a few of the kids?
they're not conscious.
none of them?
no.
can we talk
to the parents?
if you think it'll help.
yeah, yeah. who was your most
recent admission?
i should get back
to my girls.
we understand that,
and we really appreciate
you talking to us.
now, you say
mary's the oldest?
13.
okay, and she came down
with it first, right?
and then...
bethany the next night.
within 24 hours?
i guess.
look, i already went through
all this with the doctor.
right. just a few more
questions, if you don't mind.
how do you think
they caught pneumonia?
were they out in the cold,
anything like that?
no, we think
it was an open window.
both times?
the first time,
i don't really remember,
but the second time
for sure,
and i know i closed it
before i put bethany to bed.
so you think
she opened it?
it's a second-story window,
no ledge.
no one else could have.
you know this might not be
anything supernatural.
it might just be
pneumonia.
maybe. or maybe something
opened that window.
i don't know, man. look, dad
sent us down here for a reason.
i think we might be barking up
the right tree.
i'll tell you one thing.
what?
that guy
we just talked to -
i'm betting it'll be a while
before he goes home.
you got anything
over there?
no, nothing.
yeah, me neither.
hey, dean.
dean: yeah?
you were right.
it's not pneumonia.
it's rotted.
what the hell
leaves a handprint like that?
man: cheetara.
woman:
i am sorry to wake you,
but jaga bids me
to bring you to him.
john: all right.
you know the drill, dean.
if anyone calls,
you don't pick up.
if it's me, i'll ring once
and then call back.
you got that?
mm-hmm. don't answer the phone
unless it rings once first.
come on, dude. look alive.
this stuff's important.
i know, it's just,
we've done it
like a million times,
and you know
i'm not stupid.
i know you're not,
but it only takes one mistake.
you got that?
it's important that he join
jaga on the flight deck.
all right,
if i'm not back sunday night...
call pastor jim.
lock the doors and windows,
close the shades,
and most important -
watch out for sammy.
responsible for lion-o's
welfare, snarf is.
i know.
all right, if something
tries to bust in...
shoot first,
ask questions later.
that's my man.
what's up, jaga?
come closer.
what's happening to her?
what was that?
dean: i know why dad
sent us here.
he's faced this thing
before.
he wants us
to finish the job.
so what the hell is
a shtriga?
it's kind of like a witch,
i think.
i don't know much
about them.
well,
i've never heard of it,
and it's not
in dad's journal.
dad hunted one
in fort douglas, wisconsin,
about 16, 17 years ago.
you were there.
you don't remember?
no.
i guess he caught wind that
the thing's in fitchburg now
and kicked us
the coordinates.
so wait, this...
shtriga.
right, you think it's the same
one dad hunted before?
yeah, maybe.
if dad went after it,
why is it still breathing air?
because it got away.
got away?
yeah, sammy, it happens.
not very often.
i don't know
what to tell you.
maybe dad didn't have
his wheaties that morning.
what else do you remember?
nothing.
i was a kid, all right?
king or two queens?
two queens.
yeah, i bet.
what'd you say?
nice car.
hi. checking in?
yeah.
uh, do me a favor.
go get your brother some dinner.
i'm helping a guest.
two queens.
funny kid.
oh, yeah, he thinks so.
will that be cash
or credit?
do you take mastercard?
mm-hmm.
perfect.
there you go.
thank you.
when's dad gonna
get back?
tomorrow.
when?
i don't know.
he usually comes in late,
though.
now, eat your dinner.
i'm sick of "scabetti-os."
well, you're the one
who wanted them.
i want lucky charms.
there's no more
lucky charms.
i saw the box.
okay, maybe there is,
but there's only enough left
for one bowl,
and i haven't had any yet.
do you want the prize?
sir?
thanks.
well, you were right.
it wasn't very easy to find,
but you were right.
a shtriga is
a kind of witch.
they're albanian,
but legends about them
date back to ancient rome.
they feed off
of spiritus vitae.
spirit what?
vitae.
it's latin.
it translates
to "breath of life,"
kind of like your life force
or essence.
didn't the doctor say the kids'
bodies were wearing out?
it's a thought.
you know,
she takes your vitality,
maybe your immunity goes
to hell, pneumonia takes hold.
anyway, shtrigas can feed off
anyone, but they prefer -
children.
yeah.
probably because they have
stronger life force.
and get this -
shtrigas are invulnerable
to all weapons
devised by god and man.
no, that's not right.
she's vulnerable
when she feeds.
what?
if you catch her
when she's eating,
you can blast her with
consecrated wrought irons,
buckshots or rounds
i think.
how do you know that?
dad told me.
i remember.
oh.
so, uh, anything else
dad might have mentioned?
no, that's it.
what?
nothing.
okay, so, assuming we can kill
it when it eats,
we've still got to find
the thing first,
which ain't gonna be
a cakewalk.
shtrigas take on
a human disguise when
they're not hunting.
what kind of human disguise?
historically,
something innocuous.
it could be anything, but it's
usually a feeble old woman,
which may be how the witches-as-
old-crones legend got started.
hang on.
what?
check this out.
i marked down all the addresses
of the victims.
now, these are the houses
that have been hit so far,
and dead center -
the hospital.
when we were there,
i saw a patient, an old woman.
an old person, huh?
yeah.
in the hospital?
whew!
better call the coast guard.
well, listen, smartass,
she had an inverted cross
hanging on her wall.
betty:
good night, dr. hydaker.
see you tomorrow, betty.
try to get some sleep,
aaron.
come on.
who the hell are you?
who's there?
you trying to steal my stuff?
they're always
stealing around here.
no, ma'am, we're maintenance.
we're sorry.
we thought
you were sleeping.
ah, nonsense.
i was sleeping
with my peepers open.
and fix that crucifix,
would you?
i've asked four damn times
already.
"i was sleeping
with my peepers open."
i almost smoked that old gal,
i swear.
it's not funny.
oh, man, you should have seen
your face, dean.
oh, yeah, laugh it on, man.
we're back to square one.
hang on.
hey, what's wrong?
my brother's sick.
the little guy?
pneumonia.
he's in the hospital.
it's my fault.
no, come on. how?
i should have made sure
the window was latched.
he wouldn't have
gotten pneumonia
if the window was latched.
listen to me.
i can promise you that
this is not your fault, okay?
it's my job
to look after him.
michael.
turn on the "no vacancy" sign
while i'm gone.
i've got denise covering
room service,
so don't bother
with the rooms.
i'm going with you.
not now, michael.
but i got to see asher.
dean: hey, michael.
hey.
i know how you feel.
i'm a big brother, too.
but you got to go easy
on your mom right now, okay?
aw, damn it.
i got it.
thanks.
you're in
no condition to drive.
why don't you let me give you
a lift to the hospital?
no, no,
i couldn't possibly -
no, no trouble.
i insist.
be good.
we're gonna
kill this thing.
i want it dead.
you hear me?
dean: hey.
hey, how's the kid?
he's not good.
where you at?
i'm at the library,
trying to find out as much
as i can about this shtriga.
yeah, what do you got?
well, bad news.
i started
with fort douglas
around the time
you said dad was there.
and?
same deal.
before that,
there was ogdenville.
before that, north haverbrook
and brockway.
every 15 to 20 years,
it hits a new town.
dean, this thing is just getting
started in fitchburg.
in all these other places,
it goes on for months,
dozens of kids, before
the shtriga finally moves on.
kids just languish in comas,
and then they die.
how far back
does this thing go?
i don't know.
the earliest mention i could
find is this place
called black river falls
back in the 1890s.
talk about a horror show.
whoa.
sam?
hold on.
i'm looking at a photograph
right now
of a bunch of doctors
standing around a kid's bed.
one of the doctors
is hydaker.
and?
and this picture was taken
in 1893.
you sure?
yeah.
yeah, absolutely.
don't worry.
your son's in good hands.
i'm gonna take care
of him.
so what's the cdc come up
with so far?
we're still working
on a few theories.
you'll know something as soon
as we do.
well, nothing's more important
to me than these kids.
hmm.
just let me know
if i can help.
i'll do that.
sam: we should have
thought of this before.
doctor's a perfect disguise.
you're trusted.
you can control
the whole thing.
huh.
that son of a bitch.
i'm surprised you didn't draw
on him right there.
yeah, well...
first of all,
i'm not gonna open fire
in a freakin' pediatrics ward.
good call.
second, it wouldn't have done
any good
because the bastard's
bulletproof
unless he's chowing down
on something.
and third,
i wasn't packing,
which is probably
a really good thing
'cause i probably would have
just burned a clip in him
off of principle alone.
you're getting wise
in your old age, dean.
you're damn right.
'cause now i know
how we're gonna get it.
what do you mean?
the shtriga - it works
through siblings, right?
right.
well, last night...
it went after asher.
tonight it's probably gonna come
after michael.
then we got to get him
out of here.
no. no, that would blow
the whole deal.
what?
yeah.
then you want to use
the kid as bait?
are you nuts? no. forget it.
that's out of the question.
sam, it's the only way -
if this thing disappears,
it could be years
before we get another chance.
michael's a kid,
and i'm not gonna dangle him
in front of that thing
like a worm on a hook.
dad did not send me here
to walk away.
send you here?
he didn't send you here.
he sent us here.
this isn't about you, sam.
i'm the one that screwed up.
it's my fault.
there's no telling
how many kids have gotten hurt
because of me.
what are you saying, dean?
how is it your fault?
dean.
you've been hiding something
from the get-go.
since when does dad bail
on a hunt?
since when does
he let something get away?
now, talk to me, man.
tell me what's going on.
fort douglas, wisconsin.
it was the third night
in this crap room,
and i was climbing the walls,
man.
i needed to get some air.
...if ever i saw one.
command performance.
hey, kid.
we're closing up.
get out of the way!
sammy. sammy.
sammy.
you okay?
sam:
dad, what's going on?
are you all right?
what happened?
i- i just went out.
what?
j- just for a second.
i'm sorry.
i told you not to leave
this room.
i told you not to let him
out of your sight.
dad just grabbed us and booked,
dropped us off at pastor jim's
about three hours away.
by the time he got back
to fort douglas,
the shtriga had disappeared.
it was just gone.
it never resurfaced until now.
dad never spoke about it again.
i didn't ask.
but he, uh...
he looked at me different,
you know, which was worse.
not that i blame him.
he gave me an order,
and i didn't listen,
and i almost
got you killed.
you were just a kid.
don't.
dad knew this was
unfinished business for me.
he sent me here
to finish it.
but using michael -
i don't know, dean.
i mean, how about one of us
hides under the cover?
you know,
we'll be the bait.
no, that won't work.
it's got to get close enough
to feed. it'll see us.
believe me, i don't like it,
but it's got to be the kid.
michael: you're crazy!
just go away
or i'm calling the cops.
hang on a second.
just listen to me.
you have to believe me,
okay?
this thing came through
the window
and attacked your brother.
i've seen it.
i know what it looks like
'cause it attacked
my brother once, too.
this thing -
is it, like...
it has this long,
black robe?
you saw it last night,
didn't you?
i thought i was having
a nightmare.
i'd give anything
not to tell you this,
but sometimes nightmares
are real.
so why are you
telling me?
because we need your help.
my help?
we can kill it, me and him.
it's what we do.
but we can't do it
without you.
what? no.
michael, listen to me.
this thing hurt asher,
and it's gonna keep hurting kids
unless we stop it.
do you understand me?
well, that went crappy.
now what?
what did you expect?
you can't ask an adult
to do something like that,
much less a kid.
if you kill it,
will asher get better?
honestly, we don't know.
you said
you're a big brother.
yeah.
you'd take care
of your little brother?
you'd do anything
for him?
yeah, i would.
me too.
i'll help.
this camera has night vision
on it,
so we'll be able to see you
as clear as day.
are we good?
hair to the right.
there, there.
michael:
what do i do?
just stay under
the covers.
and if it shows up?
well, we'll be right
in the next room.
we're gonna come in with guns,
so as soon as we do,
you roll off this bed
and you crawl under it.
what if you shoot me?
we won't shoot you.
we're good shots.
we're not gonna fire
until you're clear, okay?
have you heard
a gunshot before?
like in the movies?
it's gonna be a lot louder
than in the movies.
so i want you to stay
under the bed, cover your ears,
and do not come out until
we say so, you understand?
michael, are you sure
you want to do this?
you don't have to.
it's okay. i won't be mad.
no, i'm okay.
just don't shoot me.
we're not gonna let anything
happen to you.
i promise.
what time is it?
3:00.
you sure these iron rounds
are gonna work?
consecrated iron rounds.
and yeah,
it's what dad used last time.
hey, dean, i'm sorry.
for what?
you know...
i've really given you
a lot of crap
for always following
dad's orders,
but i know why you do it.
oh, god.
kill me now.
wait, look.
now?
not yet.
michael, down!
mike, you all right?
yeah.
just sit tight.
dean!
dean: hey!
you okay, little brother?
it's okay, michael.
you can come on out.
hey, joanna,
how's asher doing?
have you seen michael?
michael: mom! mom!
hey!
how's ash?
i've got some good news.
your brother's gonna be fine.
really?
yeah, really.
no one can explain it.
it's, uh, it's a miracle.
they're gonna keep him
in overnight for observation,
but after that,
he's coming home.
that's great.
how are all
the other kids doing?
good, real good.
a bunch of them should be
checking out in a few days.
dr. travis says the ward's
gonna be like a ghost town.
dr. travis?
what about dr. hydaker?
oh, he wasn't in today.
he must have been sick
or something.
yeah, yeah, must have.
so did anything happen
while i was gone?
no, same old stuff.
okay.
you can go see ash.
now?
only if you want to.
i better get going
before he hot-wires the car
and drives himself.
it's too bad.
no, they'll be fine.
that's not what i meant.
i meant michael.
he'll always know there are
things out there in the dark.
he'll never be the same,
you know?
sometimes i wish that...
what?
i wish i could have
that kind of innocence.
if it means anything,
sometimes i wish you could, too.
* i was looking back
on my life *
* and all the things
i've done to me *
* i'm still looking
for the answers *
* i'm still searching
for the key *
* the road to nowhere...