Take your brother outside as fast as you can!
Now Dean! Go!
Mary!
No!
Dad's on a hunting trip.
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
Jess excuse us.
I swore I was done hunting,
for good.
I can't do this alone.
Now you're taking off the middle of the
night to spend the week-end with them.
Hey, everything's gonna be OK.
I promise.
You think mom would have wanted this for us?
Dean, we were raised like warriors.
- You have a responsability.
- To dad and his cruisade.
Even if you do find the thing that killed her, mom's gone
and she isn't coming back.
Don't talk about her like that.
Dad's gone.
I've got his journal. He left me a message.
It's coordinates he left us. It's weird, man.
Hey, Dean,
what I said earlier,
I'm sorry.
No chick-flick moments.
Yes.
No!
We got work to do.
Dude, you're cheating.
No, you just suck.
Hey, Hailey. Day six. We're still
out near Black Water Ridge.
We're fine, keeping safe,
so don't worry. Talk to you tomorrow.
Hey, where you going?
My moment of victory.
Nature calls.
Brad?
Gary, what's going on?
I am, um...
You always said roses were lame, so,
I brought you, uh...
Jess...
Oh, god.
I should have protected you.
I should have told you the truth.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Another nightmare?
Want to drive for a while?
In your whole life,
you never once asked me that.
Just thought you might want to.
Never mind.
Look, man,
you're worried about me.
I get it, and...
thank you, but I'm perfectly okay.
All right. Where are we?
We are just outside of Grand Junction.
You know what? Maybe we shouldn't
have left Stanford so soon.
Sam, we dug around there for
a week. We came up with nothing.
- If you want to find the thing that killed Jessica...
- Got to find dad first.
Dad disappearing, and this thing showing up
again after 20 years?
It's no coincidence.
- Dad will have answers. He'll know what to do.
- It's weird, man.
These coordinates he left us,
this Black Water Ridge...
- What about it?
- There's nothing there.
It's just woods.
Why is he sending us
to the middle of nowhere?
So Black Water Ridge
is pretty remote.
It's cut off by these canyons here -rough terrain, dense forest,
abandoned silver and gold mines all over the place...
Dude, check out the size
of this friggin' bear.
...And a dozen or more
grizzlies in the area.
It's no nature hike,
that's for sure.
You boys aren't planning to go out near
Black Water Ridge, by any chance?
Oh, no, sir. We're environmental-study majors
from U.C. Boulder- just working on a paper.
Recycle, man.
Bull.
You're friends with that Hailey girl, right?
Yes.
Yes, we are.
Ranger... Wilkinson.
Well, I will tell you exactly what I told her.
Her brother filled out a backcountry permit saying
he wouldn't be back from Black Water until the 24th.
So it's not exactly a missing persons now, is it?
Tell that girl to quit worrying.
I'm sure her brother's just fine.
We will.
Well, that Hailey girl's
quite a pistol, huh?
That is putting it mildly.
Actually, you know what would help is if I could
show her a copy of that backcountry permit.
You know, so she could see her brother's return date.
Yeah.
Heh heh.
What, are you cruising
for a hookup or something?
What do you mean?
The coordinates point to Black Water Ridge.
So what are we waiting for?
Let's just go find dad. Why even talk to this girl?
I don't know, maybe we should know what we're
walking into before we actually walk into it.
What?
Since when are you all "shoot first,
ask questions later" anyway?
Since now.
Oh, really?
You must be Hailey Collins.
I'm Dean, this is Sam. We're rangers with the park service.
Ranger Wilkinson sent us over.
We wanted to ask you
some questions about your brother Tommy.
Let me see some I.D.
There you go.
- Come on in.
- Thanks.
That yours?
Yeah.
Nice car.
So, if Tommy's not due back for a while,
how do you know something's wrong?
He checks in every day by cell. He e-mails
photos, stupid little videos.
But we haven't heard anything
in over three days now.
Well, maybe he can't get cell reception.
He's got a satellite phone, too.
- Could it be he's just having fun and forgot to check in?
- He wouldn't do that.
Our parents are gone.
It's just my two brothers and me.
We all keep pretty close tabs on each other.
- Can I see the pictures he sent you?
- Yeah.
That's Tommy.
Hey, Hailey. Day six.
We're still out near Black Water Ridge.
We're fine, keeping safe, so don't worry, okay?
Talk to you tomorrow.
We'll find your brother. We're heading out
to Black Water Ridge first thing.
Then maybe I'll see you there.
Look.
I can't sit around here anymore,
so I hired a guide. I'm heading out in the morning,
and I'm gonna find Tommy myself.
I think I know how you feel.
Hey, you mind forwarding these to me?
Sure.
So, Black Water Ridge doesn't get
a lot of traffic- local campers mostly-
but, still, this past april, two hikers went
missing out there. They were never found.
Any before that?
Yeah.
In 1982, eight different people
all vanished in the same year.
Authorities said it was a grizzly attack.
And, again, in 1959, and again,
before that, in 1936.
Every 23 years, just like clockwork.
Okay, watch this.
Here's the clincher.
I downloaded that guy Tommy's video to the laptop.
Check this out.
Do it again.
That's three frames. It's a fraction of a second.
Whatever that thing is, it can move.
I told you something weird was going on.
Yeah. I got one more thing.
In '59, one camper survived the supposed
grizzly attack, just a kid
barely crawled
out of the woods alive.
Is there a name?
Look, ranger, I don't know why
you're asking me about this.
It's public record.
I was a kid.
- My parents got mauled by a...
- grizzly?
That's what attacked them?
The other people that went missing that year,
those bear attacks, too?
What about all the people
that went missing this year?
Same thing?
If we knew what we were dealing with,
we might be able to stop it.
I seriously doubt that.
Anyways,
I don't see the difference it would make.
You wouldn't believe me.
Nobody ever did.
Mr. Shaw...
...what did you see?
Nothing.
It moved too fast to see.
It hid too well.
I heard it, though.
A roar...
...like...
no man or animal I ever heard.
It came at night?
Got inside your tent?
It got inside our cabin.
I was sleeping in front of
the fireplace when it came in.
It didn't smash a window
or break the door,
it unlocked it.
Do you know of a bear that
could do something like that?
I didn't even wake up until
I heard my parents screaming.
It killed them?
Dragged them off into the night.
Why it left me alive -I've been asking myself that ever since.
It did leave me this, though.
There's something evil in those woods.
It was some sort of a demon.
Spirits and demons don't have to unlock doors.
They just go through the walls.
So it's probably something
else - something corporeal.
"Corporeal"?
Excuse me, professor.
Shut up. So, what do you think?
The claws, the speed that it moves.
It could be a skinwalker,
maybe a black dog
Whatever we're talking about, we're talking
about a creature, and it's corporeal,
which means we can kill it.
We cannot let that Hailey girl go out there.
Oh yeah, what are we gonna tell her she can't go
into the woods because of a big, scary monster?
Yeah.
Her brother's missing, Sam.
She's not just gonna sit this out.
No, we go with her, we protect her, and we keep
our eyes peeled for our fuzzy predator friend
So finding dad's not enough?
Now we got to babysit, too?
What?
Nothing.
I'll tell you again.
I don't think ben should come.
Roy...
Look, you're paying me good money to keep
everybody safe. I think Ben's safest at home.
You guys got room for two more?
You want to come with us?
Who are these guys?
Apparently, this is all the park service could muster up.
You're rangers?
That's right.
And you're hiking out
in biker boots and jeans?
Well, sweet heart, I don't do shorts.
Oh, you think this is funny? It's dangerous
backcountry out there. Her brother might be hurt.
Believe me, I know how dangerous it can be.
We just want to help them find their brother.
That's all.
Roy, you said you did a little hunting.
Yeah, more than a little.
What kind of furry critters do you hunt?
Mostly buck. Sometimes bear.
Tell me, uh, Bambi or Yogi ever hunt you back?
What you doing, Roy?
You should watch where you're stepping... ranger.
It's a bear trap.
You didn't pack any provisions.
You guys are carrying a duffel bag.
You're not rangers, so who the hell are you?
Sam and I are brothers,
and we're looking for our father.
He might be here. We don't know.
I just figured that you and me, we're in the same boat.
- Why didn't you just tell me that from the start?
- I'm telling you now.
Besides, it's probably the most honest
I've ever been with a woman...
ever.
So, we okay?
Yeah, okay.
And what do you mean I didn't pack provisions?
This is it.
Black Water Ridge.
What coordinates are we at?
35 and minus 111.
You hear that?
Yeah.
Not even crickets.
I'm gonna go take a look around.
You shouldn't go off by yourself.
That's sweet. Don't worry about me.
All right, everybody stays together.
Let's go.
Hailey! Over here!
Oh, my god.
Looks like a grizzly.
Tommy?
Tommy!
- Tommy!
- Shh... Shh...
Why?
Something might still be out there.
Sam.
The bodies were dragged from the campsite.
But here, the tracks just vanish.
It's weird.
I tell you what.
It's no skinwalker or black dog.
Hey, he could still be alive.
Help!
It seemed like it was coming from around here, didn't it?
Everybody back to camp.
Our packs!
So much for my GPS and my satellite phone.
What the hell's going on?
It's smart.
It wants to cut us off so we can't call for help.
You mean someone -some nut job out there just stole all our gear.
I need to speak with you... in private.
Okay, let me see dad's journal.
All right.
Check that out.
Oh, come on.
Windigos are in the Minnesota woods or Northern
Michigan. I've never even heard of one this far west.
Think about it, Dean - the claws, the way it can mimic a human voice.
Great.
Well, then this is useless.
We got to get these people to safety.
All right, listen up. It's time to go.
Things have gotten more complicated.
What?
Whatever's out there, I think I can handle it.
If you shoot this thing, you're just gonna make it mad.
We have to leave now.
One, you're talking nonsense, two,
you're in no position to give anybody orders.
Relax.
We never should have let you
come out in the first place, all right?
I'm trying to protect you.
You protect me?
I was hunting these woods when your mommy
was still kissing you good night.
Yeah.
It's a damn-near-perfect hunter.
It's smarter than you.
And it's gonna hunt you down and eat you alive
unless we get your stupid sorry ass out of here.
- You know you're crazy, right?
- Yeah?
You ever hunt - chill out.
Stop! Stop it. Everybody just stop.
Look.
Tommy might still be alive.
And I'm not leaving here without him.
It's getting late.
This thing is a good hunter in the day,
but an unbelievable hunter at night.
We'll never beat it -not in the dark.
We need to settle inand protect ourselves.
How?
- One more time. That's...?
- Anasazi symbols.
It's for protection.
The windigo can't cross over them.
Nobody likes a skeptic, Roy.
You want to tell me what's going on
in that freaky head of yours?
- Dean...
- No, you're not fine.
You're like a powder keg, man. It's not like you.
I'm supposed to be the belligerent one, remember?
Dad's not here.
I mean, that much we know for sure, right?
He would have left us a message, a sign, right?
Yeah, you're probably right.
To tell you the truth, I don't think
dad's ever been to Lost Creek.
Then let's get these people back to town,
and let's hit the road...
Go find dad. I mean, why are we still even here?
This is why...
This book.
This is dad's single most valuable possession.
Everything he knows about every evil thing is in here.
And he's passed it on to us.
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
You know, saving people, hunting things...
The family business.
That makes no sense.
Why- why doesn't he just call us? Why doesn't
he tell us what he wants, tell us where he is?
I don't know.
But the way I see it,
dad's given us a job to do, and I intend to do it.
Dean...
no.
I gotta find dad.
I gotta find Jessica's killer.
- It's the only thing I can think about.
- Okay. All right. Sam, we'll find them. I promise.
Listen to me.
You've got to prepare yourself.
I mean, this search could take a while.
And all that anger,
you can't keep it burning over the long haul.
It's gonna kill you.
You got to have patience, man.
How do you do it?
How does dad do it?
Well, for one, them.
I mean, I figure our family's so screwed to hell,
maybe we can help some others.
It makes things a little bit more bearable.
And I'll tell you what else helps...
Killing as many evil sons of
bitches as I possibly can.
Help me!
Please...!
Help!
It's trying to draw us out.
Just stay cool. Stay put.
Inside the magic circle?
Help!
Help me!
Okay, that's no grizzly.
It's okay.
We'll be all right. I promise.
It's here.
I hit it!
Roy, no!
Roy!
Don't move.
It's over here. Ugh!
Roy?!
I don't...
I mean, these types of things-
they aren't supposed to be real.
I wish I could tell you different.
How do we know it's not out there watching us?
We don't.
But we're safe for now.
How do you know about this stuff?
It kind of runs in the family.
Hey.
So, we've got half a chance in the daylight.
And I, for one...
want to kill this evil son of a bitch.
Well, hell, you know I'm in.
Windigo is a cree indian word.
It means, "evil that devours. "
They're hundreds of years old.
Each one was once a man, sometimes an indian
or other times a frontiers manor a miner or hunter.
- How's a man turn into one of those things?
- Well, it's always the same.
During some harsh winter,
a guy finds himself starving,
cut off from supplies or help
becomes a cannibal to survive,
eating other members of his tribe or camp.
Like the donner party.
Cultures all over the world believe that eating
human flesh gives a person certain abilities-
speed, strength, immortality.
If you eat enough of it,
over years, you become this...
less-than-human thing.
You're always hungry.
So, if that's true, how can Tommy still be alive?
- You're not gonna like it.
- Tell me.
More than anything, a windigo knows
how to last long winters without food.
It hibernates for years at a time.
When it's awake,
it keeps its victims alive.
It stores them
so it can feed whenever it wants.
If your brother's alive, it's keeping him
somewhere dark, hidden, and safe
And we got to track it back there.
And then how do we stop it?
Well,
guns are useless- so are knives.
Basically...
we gotta torch the sucker.
Dean.
What is it?
You know,
I was thinking that those claw prints,
so clear and distinct...
...They were almost too easy to follow.
- You okay?
- His neck's broken.
Run, run! Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on. I got you. I got you.
Hailey!
Dean!
if it keeps its victims alive,
why would it kill Roy?
Honestly?
I think because Roy shot at it,
he pissed it off.
They went this way.
It's better than bread crumbs.
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Dean.
You. Wake up.
Hey. You okay?
Yeah.
Hailey... Hailey.
Wake up. Wake up.
Gotcha.
- You sure you're all right?
- Yeah, yeah. Where is it?
It's gone for now.
Tommy.
Cut him down.
We're gonna get you home.
Check it out.
Flare guns. Those will work.
Looks like someone's home for supper.
We'll never out run it.
- You thinking what I'm thinking?
- Yeah, I think so.
All right, listen to me. Stay with Sam.
He's gonna get you out of here.
What are you gonna do?
It's chow time, you freakin' bastard!
Yeah, that's right! Bring it on, baby!
I taste good!
All right, come on. Hurry!
Hey!
Hey, you want some white meat, bitch?!
I'm right here!
- Get him out of here.
- Sam, no.
Go. Go!
Go.
Come on.
Sam!
Come on. Hurry, hurry, hurry! Go!
Get behind me.
Not bad, huh?
That's when it circled the campsite. I mean,
this grizzly must have weighed 800, 900 pounds.
So, really, I don't know how to thank you.
- Must you cheapen the moment?
- Yeah!
- You riding with your brother?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
I hope you find your father.
Thanks, Sam.
Man, I hate camping.
Me too.
Sam, you know we're gonna find dad, right?
Yeah, I know.
But in the meantime...
...I'm driving.