I know you're just doing your job
but the police have been here a week already.
I don't see why we have
to go through this again.
The more he tells the story
the more he believes it's true.
Mrs. McKay.
We know you spoke with the local authorities.
But this seems like a matter
for the State Police. So...
Don't worry about how crazy it sounds Evan.
You just tell us what you saw.
I was up late...
watching TV.
When I heard this...
Weird noise.
What did it sound like?
It sounded like a monster.
Tell the officers what you were watching on TV.
Um...
Godzilla versus Mothra.
That's my favorite Godzilla movie.
So much better than the original?
Totally.
Yeah, he likes the remake.
Yuck.
That's what I mean.
Evan?
Did you see what this thing was?
No, but I saw it grab Mr. Jenkins.
It pulled him underneath the car.
Then what?
It took him away.
I heard the monster leaving.
It made this really scary sound.
What did it sound like, Evan?
Like this whining growl.
Thanks for your time.
So the local police have novel out foul play.
Apparently there were signs of struggle.
You know, they could be right.
Could just be a kidnapping.
Maybe this isn't our kind of gig.
Yeah, maybe not.
Except for this.
Dad marked the area, Dean.
Possible hunting grounds of a phantom attacker.
Why would he even do that?
Well, he found a lot of local folk law
about a dog figure that comes out at night,
grabs people then vanishes.
He found this too.
This county has more missing persons per
capital than anywhere else in the state.
It is weird.
Yeah.
Don't phantom attackers usually
snatch people from their beds?
Jenkins was taken from a parking lot.
Well, there are all kinds, you know.
Spring Hill Jack, Spanworm Gases,
they take people anywhere, anytime.
Look, Dean. I don't know if
this is our kind of gig either...
Yeah, you're right. We should
ask around more tomorrow.
Right.
I saw a motel about five miles back.
Whoa, whoa, easy.
Let's have another round?
We should get an early start.
Now, you really know how to
have fun, don't you Grandma?
You're right.
I'll meet you outside. I'm gonna take a leak.
Hey, hey.
Have you guys been outside? Around
here like the last hour or so?
Sam?
Sammy!
Sam...
So, what can we do for you Officer Washington?
I'm working a missing persons.
I didn't know the Jenkins case was
being covered by the State Police?
Uh, no, no. It's someone else.
Actually it's my cousin.
We were having a few laughs at
this bar down by the highway.
And I haven't seen him since.
Did your cousin have a drinking problem?
Sam? Two beers and he's doing Karaoke.
No, he wasn't drunk. He was taken.
All right. What's his name?
Winchester.
Sam Winchester.
Like the riffle?
Like the riffle.
Winchester, Sam
Samuel Winchester.
So you know that his brother
Dean Winchester died in St. Louis.
And it was excepted a murder.
Yeah, Dean.
Kind of the black sheep of the family.
Handsome though.
Well, he's not showing up
at any current field reports.
I already have a lead.
I saw surveillance camera above the highway.
County traffic cam.
Right, yeah.
I'm thinking the camera
picked up whatever took him.
Oh, whoever.
Well, I have access to the traffic cam footage
down at the county works department, but...
Well... Let me tell you this the right way.
Won't you fill out...
A missing persons report.
And sit tight over here.
Officer, look uh...
He's family.
And I kind of...
look out for the kid.
You got to let me go with you.
I'm sorry, I can't do that.
Well, tell me something.
Your county has a fair
share of missing persons.
Any of them come back?
Sam's my responsibility. And he's coming back.
I'm bringing him back.
Greg.
I think we've got something.
These traffic cam take an
image every three seconds.
It's part of the amber alert program.
These images were all taken around
the time your cousin Sam disappeared.
This really isn't what I'm looking for.
Just wait, wait.
Next one.
This one was taken right
after Sam left the bar.
Look at the back in at that thing.
Now, look at the plates.
The plates look new. Probably stolen.
So, whoever's driving that
rust bucket must be involved.
Do you hear that engine?
Yeah.
Kind of a whining growl, isn't it?
Sure.
I'll be damned.
You're alive?
Hey, you okay?
Does it look like I'm doing okay?
Where are we?
I don't know.
Country, I think.
Smells like the country.
You're Jenkins, aren't you?
Yeah.
Wow, I was looking for you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Well, no offense. But
this is a piss poor rescue.
Well, my brother's out there right
now too. He's looking for us. So...
So, he's not gonna find us.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
Waiting for them to come back
and do God knows what to us.
What are they?
Have you seen them?
What are you talking about?
Whatever grabbed us, what did they look like?
See for yourself.
Leave me alone.
Don't touch me. Leave me alone!
I'll be damned.
They're just people.
Yeah, what did you expect?
How often do they feed you?
Once a day.
They use that thing over
there to open the cage.
And that's the only time you see them?
So far. But I'm waiting.
Waiting for what?
Their baiting time, man.
I think that's the least
of your worries right now.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
What do you they want then?
Depends on who they are.
They're bunch of psycho
hill-billy red neck if you ask me.
Looking for love in all the wrong places.
Okay, the next traffic cam
is fifty miles from here and your
pickup didn't pass that one. So...
So, it must have pulled up somewhere.
I don't see any other roads here.
Well, a lot of these back woods
properties have their own private roads.
Great.
So, Gregory.
Yeah.
I ran your badge number.
It's routine when working
A case with State Police
for county purposes when we have you.
And they just got back to me...
Says here your badge was stolen.
And there's a picture of you.
I lost some weight.
And I got that Michael Jackson skin disease...
Okay.
Would you step out of the car please?
Look, look, look.
If you want to arrest me that's fine.
I'll cooperate. I swear.
But first please...
Let me find Sam.
I don't even know who you are.
Or if this Sam person is missing.
Look into my eyes and tell
me if I'm lying about this.
Identity theft. You're
impersonating an officer.
Here's the thing. When...
When we were young...
I pretty much pulled him from a fire.
And ever since then I felt responsible for him.
You know, like it's my job to keep him safe.
I'm just afraid if we don't find him fast.
Please...
He's my family.
I'm sorry.
You've given me no choice.
I have to take you in.
After we find Sam Winchester.
What's your name again?
It's Sam.
Why won't you give it up
Sammy. There's no way out.
Don't...
Call me...
Sammy.
What is it?
It's a bracket.
Well, thank God a bracket.
Now we got them, huh?
Must have been a short.
Maybe you knocked something loose.
I think you should get back in there Jenkins.
What?
This isn't right.
Do you want to get out of here?
Yeah, but that was too easy.
Look, I'm gonna get out of
here. I'm gonna send help. Okay?
Okay. Don't worry.
No.
I'm serious, Jenkins. This might be a trap.
Bye, Sammy.
Jenkins!
Thank you.
Okay, officer.
Look I'm gonna press my luck.
Your luck is so pressed.
Right.
I was wondering...
Why are you helping me out anyway?
Why don't you just lock me up?
My brother Riley disappeared three years ago.
A lot like Sam.
We searched for him but...
Nothing.
I know what it's like to
feel responsible for someone.
And for them...
Come on, let's keep at it.
Wait, wait. Pull over here. Pull over.
It's the first turn off I've seen so far.
You stay here, I'll check it out.
No way.
Hey...
You're a civilian.
And a felon, I think.
I'm not taking you with me.
You're not going without me.
All right. You promise...
You won't get involved. You let me handle it.
Yeah, I promise.
Shake on it.
Oh, come on.
This is ridiculous.
Katherine, I really think
you're gonna need my help.
I'll manage. Thank you.
I got to start carrying paper clips.
Hello?
Anybody home?
Hi.
How are you?
Who are you?
I'm Katherine. I'm a deputy.
What's your name?
Missy.
Missy? That's a pretty name.
Missy, is your mom home?
She's dead.
I'm sorry, what about your dad?
No?
Can I come in for a minute?
I just want you look at a picture.
Have you seen that guy?
Look at that picture.
What?
That's gonna hurt.
Missy, sweetheart.
Go tell your brothers, I want to see them.
Yes, daddy.
Son of a bitch.
But I've never seen him so angry before.
Never been followed by the police before.
You all right?
Are you Sam Winchester? Aren't you?
Yeah.
You're...
You're cousin's looking for you.
Thank God.
Where is he?
He uh...
I cuffed him to my car.
Sam?
Are you hurt?
No.
Damn, it's good to see you.
How did you get out of the cuffs?
I know a trick or two.
All right.
Oh.
These locks they're gonna be a bitch.
Well, there's some kind of
automatic control. Right there.
Have you seen them?
Yeah.
Dude, they're just people.
And they jumped you?
Must be getting a little rusty there, kiddo.
What do they want?
I don't know.
They let Jenkins go, but...
That was some sort of trap.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
Oh, well that's the point.
You know with...
Our usual play mates there's rules,
here's patterns. But with people...
They're just crazy.
You see anything else out there?
He has about a dozen junk cars
out back. Plates from all over.
So, I'm thinking when they take
someone they take their car too.
Did you see a black mustang?
Out there about ten years old?
Yeah, actually I did.
Your brothers?
I'm sorry.
Let's get you guys out of here. Then
we'll take care of those bastards.
It takes a key, key?
I don't know.
All right, I better go find it.
Hey.
Be careful.
Yeah.
Well, I'll say it again.
Demons I get.
People are crazy.
What the...
It's okay. I'm not gonna hurt you.
I know.
Daddy!
I'm gonna kick your ass first.
Then yours.
Come on.
Let's hunt.
Yeah, this one's a fighter.
Sure be fun to hunt.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
This is what this is about? You...
You yahoos hunt people?
You ever killed before?
What?
Well, it depends on what you mean.
I've hunted all my life.
Just like my father, his before him.
I've hunted deer...
and bear...
I even got a coo-coo once. Oh boy.
But the best hunt...
is human.
Oh, there's nothing like it.
Holding their life in your hands.
Seeing the fear in their
eyes just before they go dark.
Makes you feel powerful alive.
You're a sick puppy.
We give them a weapon.
Give him a fighting chance.
It's kind of like...
Our tradition passed down
father to son, cost only one or two a year.
Never enough to bring the lot
down we've never been that sloppy.
Yeah, well. Don't save yourself short.
You're plenty of sloppy.
So what? You're with that pretty cop?
Are you a cop?
If I tell you...
You promise not to make me into an ash tray?
Only reason I don't let my
boys take you right here now
is that there's something I need to know.
Yeah, how about it's not
nice to marry your sister.
Tell me, any of the cops
go come looking for you?
Oh, eat me.
No, no, no. Wait. You actually might.
You think this is funny?
You've brought this down on my family.
All right?
You want to play games?
We'll play some games.
Looks like we're gonna have a
hunt tonight after all, boys.
And you get to pick the animal.
The boy or the cop.
Okay, wait, wait.
Look, nobody's coming for
me. All right? It's just us.
You don't choose, I will.
Oh, you son of a bitch!
Next time, I'll take an eye.
All right, all right. The
guy. The guy. Take the guy!
Lee.
Go do it.
Don't let him out though.
Shoot him in the cage.
What?
I thought you said you were gonna hunt him.
You're gonna give him a chance!
Lee!
When you're done with the boy.
Shoot the bitch too.
We're cleaning this mess up before
any more cops come running out here.
What are you doing?
Hey!
You hurt my brother, I'll kill you. I swear.
I'll kill you all.
I will kill you all!
Lee!
Damn.
Jack, you come with me.
Missy.
You watch him now.
Lee?
Where are you?
Damn it. Jack, hit the lights.
They must have pulled the fuses.
You stupid...
Hey!
I'll watch this one. You go ahead.
Go ahead.
You hurt my family.
I'm gonna bleed you bitch.
You killed my brother.
Your brother?
Now I see.
Just tell me why.
Because it's fun.
Where's the girl?
I locked her in the closet.
What about the dad?
Shot. Trying to escape.
I think the car's at the police station.
Backup units on route to your location.
So...
State Police and the FBI are
gonna be here within the hour.
They're gonna want to talk to you.
I suggest that you're both long gone by then.
Thanks.
Hey, listen. I don't mean to press our luck.
But we're kind of in the middle of nowhere.
You think we could catch a ride?
Start walking.
Duck if you see a SWAT car.
Sounds great to me. Thanks.
Listen...
I'm sorry about your brother.
Thank you.
It was really hard not
knowing what happened to him.
I thought it would be easier
once I knew the truth. But...
It isn't really.
Anyway you should go.
Don't ever do that again.
Do what?
Go missing like that.
You were worried about me.
I'm saying, you vanish like that
again I'm not looking for you.
Sure you will.
I'm not.
So you got saddled on by
a 13 year old girl, huh?
Oh, shut up!
Just saying getting rusty there, kiddo.
Shut up!