Ok, right about there...
I think that's it!
I can't believe we actually bought
this thing.
There's a reason charity auctions
have an open bar.
Don't you think...
I don't know. It's kind of... creepy?
It's okay.
I'll keep you safe.
Maybe you're the one I ought
to be scared of.
Let's go upstairs.
Give me ten minutes to lock up.
Make that one minute.
If you don't hurry up,
I'm gonna start without you.
Babe, get the lights.
I can't see a thing.
Did you spill something?
Ann?
Ann?!
...3-4-2-0.
Alright. You're in there.
Perfect.
So, is that Brandi with a
"y" or a "i"?
Alright, listen. I gotta go.
Hold that thought,
I'll be right back, ok?
Alright. So, I think I've got something.
Oh, yeah, me too.
I think we need
to take a little shore leave,
just a little bit.
What do you think, huh?
I'm so in the door with this one.
So what are we today, Dean?
Are we rockstars?
We're Army rangers?
We're LA tv scouts, looking for people
with special skills.
But, hey, it's not that far off, right?
By the way, she's got a friend over there.
I can probably hook you up.
What do you think?
Dean, uh, no thanks.
I can get my own dates.
Yeah, you can, but you don't.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing. What do you got?
Mark and Ann Telesca
of New Paltz, New York,
were both found dead in their home,
just a few days ago.
Sloats were slit,
there were no prints,
no murder weapons, all... Dean?
No prints, no murder weapons.
All doors and windows were locked
from the inside.
Could just be
a garden-variety murder.
- You know, not our department.
- No, dad says different.
- What do you mean?
- Look.
Dad noted three murders
in the same area of upstate New York.
The first one, right here, in 1912.
The second one in 1945,
and the third in 1970.
The same M.O. as the Telescas...
the throats were slit,
the houses were locked from the inside.
Now, so much time passed
between the murders,
that nobody checked the pattern
except for dad.
He always kept his eyes peeled
for another one.
- And now we got one.
- Exactly.
Alright, I'm with you.
It's worth checking out.
We can't pick this up till
first thing, though, right?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Dean...
Ladies, did you miss me?
I'm just kidding.
Listen, I talked to my producer
and it is looking good...
Oh, man, it's so not cool.
I just swept the Telesca's house
with the EMF.
It's clean.
And last night, while you were...
out...
- Oh, good times.
- I checked the history of the house.
No hantings, no violent crimes.
Nothing strange
about the Telescas themselves either.
Alright, so if it's not the people
and it's not the house,
then maybe it's the contents.
- A cursed object or something.
- The house is clean.
Yeah, I know, you said that.
No, I mean it's empty.
No furniture, nothing.
Where's all their stuff?
Consignement auctions, estate sales...
lit's like a garage sale for WASPs
if you ask me.
Can I help you, gentlemen?
I'd like some champagne, please.
He's not a waiter.
I'm Sam Connors.
That's my brother, Dean.
We are art dealers with Connors Limited.
- You're art dealers?
- That's right.
I'm Daniel Blake.
This is my auction house.
Now, gentlemen, this is a private showing,
and I don't remember seeing you
on the guest list.
We are there, chuckles.
You just need to take another look.
Oh, finally.
Cheers!
A fine example of american primitive,
wouldn't you say?
Oh, I'd say it's more Grant Wood
than Grandma Moses...
But you knew that.
You just wanted to see if I did.
Guilty.
And clumsy, I apologize.
I'm Sarah Blake.
Sam.
This is my...
brother, Dean.
Can we get you some more mini-quiche?
Gnnbfffm, I'm good. Thanks.
So, can I help you with something?
Yeah, actually.
What can you tell us
about the Telesca estate?
The whole thing is pretty grisly
if you ask me,
selling their things as soon.
But dad's right about one thing...
sensational is to bring out the crowds.
Even the rich ones.
Is it possible to see the provenances?
I'm afraid there is any chance of that.
- Why not?
- You're not on the guest list.
And I think it's time to leave.
- Well, we don't have to be told twice.
- Apparently you do.
Ok, it's alright.
We don't want any trouble.
We'll go.
Dad, that was rude.
Grant Wood, Grandma Moses... what?
Art History course.
It's good for meeting girls.
It's like I don't even know you.
And what was the providence?
Provenance.
It's the certificate of origin,
like a biography, you know.
We can use them to track the history
of the pieces,
see if anything's got a freaky past.
We're not getting anything
out of chuckles,
- But uh, Sarah...
- Yeah.
Maybe you can get her to write it all down
on a cocktail napkin.
Not me.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Pickups are your thing, Dean.
It wasn't my butt she was checking out.
In other words, you want me to use her
to get information.
Sometimes, you've got to take one
for the team.
Call her.
Nice place.
Yeah.
Glad you called.
Surprised, but glad.
Yeah?
Although you seem to have a hard time
getting out the words
"would you like to have dinner"?
Yeah.
I haven't really been on a date
in a while.
Welcome to the club.
You're kidding me.
- Here we are.
- Thanks.
The wine list.
I don't know about Romeo here,
but I'll have a beer.
And you?
I will too.
Certainly.
So, you studied Art in school, huh?
It's true.
I was an artist...
a terrible, terrible artist.
That's why I'm in the auction business.
And you were in pre-law?
Yeah.
But you didn't go to law school.
How come?
Uh, it's a really long story
for another time.
You're not like any art dealer
I've ever met.
So... what did you mean when you said
you hadn't been on a date in a while?
Tried to make me feel like
I'm not such a "loser"?
I'm sure you're many things, Sam.
I'm also sure "loser" isn't one of them.
It was my mom.
She died about a year ago.
Totally unexpected.
It really threw me.
I went into a shell...
a nice, warn, safe shell.
But lately I've been thinking...
it's not what she would have wanted
for me.
So...
So, what about you?
You're a reasonably attractive guy.
Reasonably?
Why haven't you been out and about?
Another long story for another time.
So she just handed the providences
over to you?
Provenances.
- Pro-ve-nan-ces?
- Yeah, we went back to her place,
I got a copy of the papers.
And?
And nothing. That's it.
I left.
You didn't have to con her or
do any special favors?
Would you get your mind out of the gutter,
please?
When this whole thing's done,
we could stick around for a little bit.
- Why?
- So you can take her out again.
It's obvious you're into her.
Even I can see that.
Hey, alright, I think
I've got something here.
"Portrait of Isaiah Merchant's family,
painted in 1910."
Now, compare the names of the owners
with dad's journal.
"First purchased in 1912, to Peter Sims".
Peter Sims was murdered in 1912.
Same thing in 1945.
Oh, same thing in 1970.
Then stored,
until it was donated to a charity auction
last month,
where the Telescas bought it.
So what do you think?
It's haunted or cursed?
Eitherway, it's toast.
Go ahead.
Ugly ass thing.
If you ask me, we're doing
the art world a favor.
We've got a problem.
I can't find my wallet.
How is that my problem?
'Cause I think I dropped it
in the warehouse last night.
You're kidding, right?
I mean, it's got my prints, my ID...
well my fake ID anyway but
we've got to get it before
somebody else finds it. Come on.
How did you lose your wallet, Dean?
Hey guys.
Sarah. Hey.
What are you doing here?
We... we are leaving town,
and you know,
we came to say goodbye.
What are you talking about, Sam?
We're sticking around for at least
another day or two.
Oh, Sam, by the way,
I wanted to give you
that 20 bucks I owe you.
I always forget.
There you go.
Well, I leave you two crazy kids alone.
I got to go do...
something... somewhere...
So...
I had a good time last night.
Yeah, yeah. I did too.
Maybe we should do it again sometime.
You know, I'd love to,
I really would
but Dean...
he was just screwing around.
We really are taking off today.
That's too bad.
- Oh, my god!
- What?
The...
That painting...
looks so good.
If you can call that monstruosity good,
then yeah, I guess.
Sarah, what do you know
about that painting?
Not much.
Just that it creeps me out.
We sold it to the Telescas at a charity auction
the night they were murdered.
And now you're just gonna sell it again?
As much as my dad wants to, no.
I won't let him.
I think it'd be in bad taste.
Yeah. Good. You know what?
Don't. Don't.
- Make sure you don't, ok?
- Why?
Don't tell me you're interested in that?
No, god, no.
Not buying. No.
You know what?
I gotta go. I gotta take care of something.
But uh... I will call you back.
- I'll see you later.
- Wait. So,
you're not leaving tonight?
No, I guess not.
I'll see you.
Ok.
I don't understand, Dean.
We burned the damn thing!
Yeah, thank you, Captain Obvious.
Alright, we just need to figure out
another way to get rid of it.
- Any ideas?
- Ok, alright.
In almost all the lore
about haunted paintings
it's always the painting subject
that haunts them.
Yeah.
So we need to figure out everything
there is to know
about that creepy ass family
in that creepy ass painting.
What were their names again?
You said the Isaiah Merchant family,
right?
Yeah, that's right.
I dug up every scrap of the local history
I could find.
So, uh,are you boys crime buffs?
Kind of...
Why do you ask?
W ell...
Yes. That sounds about right.
The whole family was killed?
It seems that this Isaiah,
he slits his kids' throats
then his wife, then himself.
He was a barber by trade.
He used a straight razor.
- Why'd he do it?
- Well, let's look.
"People who knew him describe Isaiah
"as having a stern and harsh temperament,
to control his family with iron fist".
A wife, two sons,
adopted daughter... Yeah, yeah.
There were whispers that the wife
was gonna take the kids
and leave, which, of course,
you know, in that day and age...
So instead, old man Isaiah,
he gave them all a shave.
Couic!
Does it say what happened to the bodies?
Just that they were cremated.
- Anything else?
- Yeah.
Actually I found a picture of the family.
It's right here, somewhere.
Right. Here it is.
Hey, could we get a copy of this, please?
Sure.
Dad...
You promised you wouldn't sell
that painting.
I know sweetie, but Evelyn's offered
a persuasive amount of money.
You're shameless, you know that?
For that kind of money, I can afford to be.
I'm telling you, man. I'm sure of it.
The painting at the auctionhouse,
daddy's looking down.
The painting here, dad's looking out.
The painting has changed, Dean.
Alright, so you think daddy dearest
is trapped in the painting
and he’s handing out Colombian neckties
- like he did with his family?
- Yeah, it seems like it.
But if his bones are already dusted,
then how are we gonna stop him?
If Isaiah's position changed, then maybe
some other things in the painting changed as well.
- It could give us some clues.
- What, like a "DaVinci Code" deal?
I don't know.
I'm still waiting for the movie on that one.
Anyway, we gotta get back in
to see that painting.
Which is a good thing 'cause
you can get some more time
to crush on your girlfriend.
Dude!
Enough already.
- What?
- "What"?!
Every since we got here,
you've been trying to pimp me out to Sarah.
- Juste back off, alright?
- Well, you like her, don't you?
Alright, you like her; she likes you.
You're both consenting adults.
What's the point, Dean?
We'll just leave. We always leave.
Well, I'm not talking about marriage, Sam.
You know, I don't get it.
What do you care if I hook up?
Because then maybe you wouldn't be
so cranky all the time.
You know, seriously, Sam,
this isn't about just kooking up, ok?
I think that this
Sarah girl could be good for you.
And I don't mean nay disrespect, but I...
I'm sure this is about Jessica, right?
Now, I don't know what it's like
to lose somebody like that...
but...
I would think that she would want you
to be happy.
God forbid have fun once in a while.
Wouldn't she?
Yeah, I know she would.
Yeah, you're right. A part of this
is about Jessica.
But not the main part.
What's about?
Yeah, alright.
Well, we still gotta see that painting,
which means
you still gotta call Sarah, so...
Sarah, hey. It's Sam.
Good, good, yeah.
What about you?
- Yeah, good, good, really good.
- Smooth.
So, uh... So listen.
Me and my brother we were thinking
that maybe we'd like to come back in
and look at the painting again.
I think maybe we are interested
in buying it.
Wait, what?
Who did you sell it to?
Sarah, I need her adress right now.
Sam, what's happening?
I told you,
you shouldn't have come.
Hello! Anybody home?!
You said Evelyn might be in danger.
What kind of danger?
I can't knock this sucker down.
I've got to pick it.
What are you guys, burglars?
I wish that was that simple.
Look, you really should wait in the car.
It's for your own good.
The hell I would!
Evelyn is a friend.
Evelyn?
It's Sarah Blake.
- Are you alright?
- Sarah, don't! Sarah!
Oh, my god!
Hey.
- You're alright?
- No, actually.
I just lied to the cops and told them
I went to Evelyn's, alone,
and found her like that.
- Thank you.
- Don't thank me.
I'm about to call them right back if
you don't tell me what the hell is going on.
Who is killing these people?
"What".
What?
It's not "who".
It's "what" is killing those people.
Sarah, you saw that painting move.
No.
No, I was... I was seeing things.
It's impossible.
Yeah, well, welcome to our world.
Sarah, I know this sounds crazy...
But we think that this painting is haunted.
You're jocking?
You're not jocking.
- God! The guys I go out with!
- Sarah, think about it.
Evelyn, the Telescas...
They both had the painting.
And there have been others before that.
Wherever this thing goes, people die.
And we're just trying to stop it...
And that's the truth.
Well, then I guess you'd better show me.
I'm coming with you.
What? No.
Sarah, no.
You should just go home.
This stuff can get dangerous and...
And I don't want you to get hurt.
Look, you guys are probably crazy,
but if you're right about this,
when me and my dad sold that painting,
we might have got those people killed.
Look, I'm not saying I'm not scared,
because I am scared as hell,
but I'm not going to run and hide, either.
So, are we going or what?
Sam...
Marry that girl.
Uh...
isn’t this a crime scene?
Well, you’ve already lied to the cops.
What’s another infraction?
Aren't you worried that it's gonna...
you know, kill us?
No, it seems doing things at night.
I think we're alright in daylight.
Sam, check it out.
The razor, it's closed in this one
- but it's open in that one.
- What are you guys looking for?
Well if the spirit's changing aspects
of the painting,
maybe it's doing so for a reason.
Hey, look at this.
The painting in the painting.
It looks like a crypt or a mausoleum
or something.
"Merchant".
It's the third bone yard we've checked.
I think this ghost is jerking us around.
So, this is what you guys do
for a living?
Not exactly.
We don't get paid.
Well, mazel tov.
Over there.
Ok, that right there is the creepiest thing
I've ever seen.
That was sort of a tradition
at the time.
Whenever a child died,
sometimes they preserved
the kid's favourite toy
in a glass case, put it next to
the headstone in the crypt.
Notice any strange here?
Uh, where do I start?
No, it's not what I mean.
Look at the urns.
- Yeah, they're only 4.
- Yeah, mom and the 3 kids.
Daddy deariest isn't here.
So where is he?
So what exactly is your brother
doing in there?
Searching county death certificates,
trying to find out what happened to
Isaiah's body.
How could he even get in the door?
Lying and subterfuges mostly.
You have uh...
You have an eyelash on your...
You have it, right. No... You know what?
Do you mind if I...
- No.
- Ok.
Ok, I got it.
Make a wish.
Sam, can I ask you something?
- Yeah, sure.
- I don't mean to be forward,
but... "a girl could wait here forever".
Is there something here, between us,
or am I delusional?
You're not delusional.
But, there is a "but" coming.
But...
I don't think this would be
a good idea.
Can I ask why?
Because I like you.
Wait, you lost me.
Look, it's hard to explain.
It's just that when
people are around me...
I don't know, they get hurt.
What do you mean?
I mean like physically hurt.
With what my brother and I do, it's...
Sarah,
I had a grilfriend.
And she died.
And my mom died too.
I don't know, it's like...
It's like I'm cursed or something...
Like death just follows me around.
Look, I'm not scared that much,
but if I let myself
have feelings for anybody...
You're scared they get hurt too.
That's very sweet, and very archaic.
- Sorry?
- Look, I'm a big girl, Sam.
It's not your job
to make decisions for me.
- There's always a chance of getting hurt.
- I'm not talking about a broken heart
and a tub of haagen-dazs.
I'm talking about life and death.
And tomorrow I could get hit
by a bus.
That's what life is.
Look, I know losing somebody
you love is terrible,
You shut yourself off.
Believe me, I know.
But when you shut out pain...
you shut out everything else too.
Sarah, you don't understand.
The pain that I went through...
I can't go through it again.
I can't.
Am I interrupting something?
- No.
- Not at all.
Apparently.
So, what did you get?
Apparently, the surviving relatives
of the Merchant family
were so ashamed of Isaiah
that they didn't want him interred
with the rest of the family.
So they handed him over to the county.
County gave him a pauper's funeral.
Economic style.
Turns out he wasn't cremated.
He was buried in a pine box.
So, there are bones to burn.
- There are bones to burn.
- Tell me you know where.
You guys seem to be...
uncomfortably comfortable with this.
Well, this isn't exactly the first grave
we've dug.
You still think I'm a catch?
I think I've got something.
You've been a real pain in the ass,
Isaiah.
Good riddance!
Dean, keep the motor running.
I thought the paint was harmless now.
Better safe than sorry.
We're gonna bury the sucker.
- I wanna come with you.
- Are you sure?
I stay here. You go make your move.
Sam, I'm serious!
I'm in love with a girl
I'm talking about
I can't live without
I'm in love, but I feel like
I'm wearing it out
Uh, Sam...
You're the expert on all this ghost stuff.
Is that painting supposed to look
like that?
Where is the little girl?
And the razor.
Dean!
Hey, is that you?!
Sammy, you're alright?!
Tell me you slammed the front door.
No, it wasn't me.
I think it was the little girl.
- Girl? What girl?
- Yeah, she's out of the painting.
I think it might have been her all along.
Wasn't the dad looking down at her?
Maybe he was trying to warn us.
Let's recap later, alright?
Just get us out of here.
I'm trying to pick the lock,
but the door won't budge.
- Well break it down!
- Ok, genious.
- Let me grap my battering ram!
- The damn thing is coming!
Well you're gonna have to hold her off
until I figure something out.
- Get some salt or iron.
- Come on!
What kind of house doesn't have salt?
- Hey, you find any iron?
- No, what's it for?
Iron repels evil spirits,
but it's gotta be pure.
Hurry.
Dean, give me a sec.
Don't go anywhere.
Look at the chairs.
Sometimes, the seats...
Sam...
It's just so wrong.
Iron?
Yeah.
Sam, you're ok?
Yeah, for now.
How are we gonna waste her?
I don't know.
She was already cremated.
- There's nothing left to burn.
- Well then why she's still around?
There must be something else.
Sam, wait.
We used to handle antique dolls
at the auction.
Well, that's fascinating, Sarah,
but important right now?
Back then, they used to make
the dolls in the kids' image.
I mean, everything.
Like the... they would use
the kids' real hair.
Dean?
Sarah says the doll might have
the girl's hair.
Humans remains...
Same as bones.
The mausoleum.
Come on, Dean.
Come on, come on!
Sam, are you good?
Not bad.
It was archived in the county records.
The Merchants' adoptive daughter,
M?lanie.
Know why she was up for adoption?
'Cause her real family was murdered
in their beds.
She killed them?
Yeah, who'd suspect her?
A sweet little girl.
So when she killes Isaiah
and his family,
the old man takes the blame.
His spirit was trying to warn people
ever since.
Where is this one go?
Take it out back and burn it.
I'm serious, guys. Thanks.
So why'd the girl do it?
Killing others, killing herself...
Some people are just born tortured.
So when they die,
the spirits are just as dark.
Maybe. I don't really care.
It's over. We move on.
I guess it means you're leaving.
I'll go wait in the car.
See you, Sarah.
I'm the one who burnt the doll,
I destroyed the spirit,
but don't thank me or anything.
There are million things
that I want to say to you,
but for the life of me,
I can't think of one.
Yeah, I'll miss you too.
You know, there's a lesson
in all of this.
What's that?
We all got through this in one piece.
I didn't get hurt.
Yeah, I'm glad for that.
So, maybe you're not cursed.
Maybe...
Maybe you'lle come back and see me.
I will.
That's my boy.