Look, our whole lives we've been
searching for this demon.
We finally know where
this demon's gonna be...
...and now we know how to kill him.
This ends now. I'm ending it.
I don't care what it takes.
-A vision.
-Visions or no visions, the fact is...
...the demon is coming tonight.
And this family's gonna go through
the same hell we went through.
We know you have the gun, John.
-You just declared war.
-l'll bring you the Colt.
The demon is coming.
That gun is all we got.
Hand Meg a fake gun,
hope she doesn't notice?
I've been waiting
a long time for this fight.
Nobody's dying tonight.
Not us, not that family.
-Why don't you hand over the gun?
-Maybe l'll just shoot you.
There's more where l came from.
It's coming.
I can't believe you just shot me!
It's a fake.
-Sam, no.
-Let me go. It's still in there.
It's suicide.
-l don't care.
-l do.
That thing killed Jess.
That thing killed Mom.
They're gone.
And they're never coming back.
Don't you say that.
Not after all this.
You boys really screwed up this time.
Where is he?
You're never gonna see
your father again.
-They've got Dad.
-Meg?
-What'd she say?
-l just told you, Sammy.
Okay.
-What are you doing, Dean?
-We gotta go.
-Why?
-The demon knows we're in Salvation.
It knows we've got the Colt.
-lt's got Dad. lt's coming for us.
-Good. We've got three bullets left.
Listen, we're not ready. We don't know
how many of them are out there.
Now, we're no good to anybody dead.
We're leaving. Now.
-l'm telling you, we could've taken them.
-What we need is a plan.
They're probably keeping Dad alive.
Just gotta...
...figure out where.
They'll wanna trade him for the gun.
-What?
-Dean, if that were true...
...why didn't Meg mention a trade?
-Dad, he might be--
-Don't.
Look, l don't wanna believe it
any more than you...
...but if he is, all the more reason
to kill this damn thing.
We still have the Colt.
We can finish the job.
Screw the job, Sam.
I'm just trying to do what he'd want.
He would want us to keep going.
Quit talking about him like he's dead.
Listen to me, everything stops
until we get him back.
Do you understand me? Everything.
-- So how do we find him?
- We go to Lincoln.
Start at the warehouse
where he was taken.
Come on. You really think
these demons are gonna leave a trail?
You're right.
We need help.
Here you go.
-What is this, holy water?
-That one is. This is whiskey.
Bobby, thanks. Thanks for everything.
-l wasn't sure if we should come.
-Nonsense. Your daddy needs help.
Yeah, but last time we saw you,
I mean, you did threaten to blast him.
You cocked the shotgun
and everything.
Yeah, well, what can I say?
-John just has that effect on people.
-Yeah, I guess he does.
None of that matters now. All that
matters is that you get him back.
Bobby, this book....
-l've never seen anything like it.
-Key of Solomon?
It's the real deal, all right.
And these-- These protective circles,
they really work?
Hell, yeah. You get a demon in one,
they're trapped. Powerless.
It's like a satanic roach motel.
Man knows his stuff.
I'll tell you something else too.
This is some serious crap
you boys stepped in.
Oh, yeah?
-How's that?
-Normal year, I hear of...
...say, three demonic possessions.
-Maybe four, tops.
-Yeah?
This year, I heard of 27 so far.
You get what l'm saying?
More and more demons
are walking among us.
-A lot more.
-Do you know why?
No, but I know it's something big.
Storm's coming.
And you boys and your daddy...
...you are smack in the middle of it.
Rumsfeld.
What is it?
Something's wrong.
No more crap, okay?
I want the Colt, Sam.
The real Colt.
Right now.
-We don't have it on us. We buried it.
-Didn't I say, "No more crap"?
I swear, after everything l heard
about you Winchesters...
...l gotta tell you,
I'm a little underwhelmed.
First Johnny tries to
pawn off a fake gun...
...and then he leaves the real gun
with you two chuckleheads.
Lackluster, man.
I mean, did you really think
I wouldn't find you?
Actually, we were counting on it.
Gotcha.
You know, if you wanted to tie me up,
all you had to do was ask.
I salted the doors and windows.
If there are any demons out there,
they ain't getting in.
-Where's our father, Meg?
-You didn't ask very nice.
Where's our father, bitch?
Jeez, you kiss your mother
with that mouth?
-Oh, I forgot. You don't.
-Hey, you think this is a frigging game?
-Where is he? What did you do to him?
-He died screaming.
I killed him myself.
That's kind of a turn on,
you hitting a girl.
You're no girl.
Dean.
-You okay?
-She's lying. He's not dead.
Dean, you gotta be careful with her.
Don't hurt her.
-Why?
-Because she really is a girl, that's why.
-What are you talking about?
-She's possessed.
That's a human possessed
by a demon. Can't you tell?
You trying to tell me there's an innocent
girl trapped somewhere in there?
That's actually good news.
You gonna read me a story?
Something like that. Hit it, Sam.
An exorcism? Are you serious?
We're going for it, baby. Head spinning,
projectile vomiting, the whole nine yards.
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna rip the bones
from your body.
No, you're gonna burn in hell.
Unless you tell us where our dad is.
Well, at least you'll get a nice tan.
He begged for his life
with tears in his eyes.
He begged to see his sons
one last time.
That's when I slit his throat.
For your sake, I hope you're lying.
Because if it's true, I swear to God...
...l will march into hell myself
and l will slaughter...
...each and every one of you
evil sons of bitches, so help me, God.
Where is he?
-You just won't take dead for an answer.
-Where is he?
-Dead.
-No, he's not!
He's not dead. He can't be!
What are you looking at?
Keep reading.
-He will be!
-Wait! What?
He's not dead.
But he will be
after what we do to him.
-How do we know you're telling the truth?
-You don't.
-Sam--!
-A building, okay?
-A building in Jefferson City.
-Missouri? Where, where? An address.
-l don't know.
-And the demon. Where is it?
I don't know. l swear.
That's everything. That's all I know.
-Finish it.
-What?
-l told you the truth!
-l don't care.
-You son of a bitch, you promised.
-l lied!
Sam.
Sam!
Read.
Maybe we can still use her.
Find out where the demon is.
-She doesn't know.
-She lied!
Sam, there's an innocent girl trapped
in there and we've gotta help her.
-You're gonna kill her.
-What?
You said she fell from a building.
That girl's body is broken.
The only thing keeping her alive
is that demon inside.
You exorcise it, the girl is gonna die.
We are not gonna leave her like that.
-She is a human being.
-We're gonna put her out of her misery.
Sam, finish it.
Finish it.
She's still alive. Call 911.
Get some water and blankets.
-Thank you.
-Just take it easy, all right?
Come on, let's-- Let's get her down.
Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
I gotcha. Gotcha.
It's okay. It's okay.
-A year.
-What?
-lt's been a year.
-Just take it easy.
I've been awake for some of it.
I couldn't move my own body.
And things looked-- It--
It's a nightmare.
-Was it telling the truth about our dad?
-Dean.
-We need to know.
-Yes.
But it wants you to know.
They want you to come for him.
If Dad's still alive,
none of that matters.
Where is the demon we're looking for?
Not there.
Other ones. Awful ones.
Where are they keeping our dad?
By the riv-- River.
-Sunrise.
-Sunrise? What does that mean?
What does that mean?
You better hurry up and beat it
before the paramedics get here.
What are you gonna tell them?
You think you guys invented
lying to the cops?
I'll figure something out.
Here, take this.
-You might need it.
-Thanks.
Thanks for everything.
-Be careful, all right?
-You just go find your dad.
And when you do,
you bring him around, would you?
I won't even try to shoot him
this time.
You've been quiet.
Just getting ready.
He's gonna be fine, Dean.
Dude, what are you drawing
on my car?
It's called a devil's trap.
-Demons can't get through it or inside it.
-So?
Basically turns the trunk
into a lockbox.
So?
So we have a place to hide the Colt
while we go get Dad.
-We're bringing the Colt with us.
-Can't, Dean.
We only got three bullets left.
We can't just use them on any demon.
-We gotta use them on the demon.
-No, we have to save Dad, Sam.
Okay, we need
all the help we can get.
Do you know how pissed Dad would be
if we used all the bullets?
-He wouldn't want us to bring the gun.
-l don't care.
I don't care what Dad wants. Since
when do you care what Dad wants?
We wanna kill this demon.
You used to want that too.
Hell, you're the one
who came and got me at school.
You're the one who dragged me back
into this. I'm just trying to finish it.
You and Dad are more alike
than l thought, you know that?
You both can't wait
to sacrifice yourself.
But you know what?
I'm gonna be the one to bury you.
It's selfish, you know that?
You don't care about anything
but revenge.
That's not true, Dean.
I want Dad back.
They are expecting us to bring this gun.
They get the gun, they will kill us all.
That Colt is our only leverage
and you know it, Dean.
We cannot bring that gun.
-We can't.
-Fine.
-l'm serious, Dean.
-l said fine, Sam.
Hey, hey.
I think I know what
Meg meant by "sunrise."
Son of a bitch. lt's pretty smart.
If these demons can possess people,
they can possess anybody inside.
Yeah, and make anybody attack us.
Yeah, so we can't kill them.
A building full of human shields.
They probably know what we look like
too. And they could look like anybody.
-Man, this sucks out loud.
-Yeah, tell me about it.
All right, so how the hell
are we gonna get in?
Pull the fire alarm.
Get out all the civilians.
Okay, but then the city responds
in what, seven minutes?
Seven minutes exactly.
Hey, what--? What's happening?
Is it a fire?
We're figuring that out now, sir.
Just stay back.
Well, l got a Yorkie upstairs.
-He pees when he's nervous.
-Sir, you have to stay back.
l always wanted
to be a fireman when l grew up.
You never told me that.
This is the fire department.
We need you to evacuate.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Come on. Dad.
Dad.
He's still breathing.
Dad, wake up. Dad!
-Wait. Wait.
-What?
He could be possessed,
for all we know.
-Are you nuts?
-Dean.
We gotta be sure.
Sam?
Why are you splashing water on me?
-Dad, you okay?
-They've been drugging me.
-Where's the Colt?
-Don't worry, Dad.
It's safe.
Good boys. Good boys.
Hey, buddy. You can't go in.
Go. Go. Come on. Back, back. Go.
Sam, let's go.
Sam. Sam, come on.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
We gotta get out of here.
-How is he?
-He just needed a little rest, that's all.
How are you?
I'll survive.
Hey, you don't think we were
followed here, do you?
I don't know. l don't think so.
I mean, we couldn't have found
a more out-of-the-way place to hole up.
Yeah.
Hey, Dean, you--
You saved my life back there.
So l guess you're glad
I brought the gun, huh?
Man, l'm trying to thank you here.
You're welcome.
-- Hey, Sam.
- Yeah?
You know that guy l shot?
There was a person in there.
You didn't have a choice, Dean.
Yeah, l know.
That's not what bothers me.
Then what does?
Killing that guy, killing Meg...
...l didn't hesitate.
I didn't even flinch.
I mean, for you or Dad, the things
I'm willing to do or kill, it's just....
It scares me sometimes.
It shouldn't. You did good.
You're not mad?
-For what?
-Using a bullet.
Mad? I'm proud of you.
You know, Sam and l,
we can get pretty obsessed.
But you-- You--
You watch out for this family.
You always have.
Thanks.
-lt found us. lt's here.
-The demon.
Sam, lines of salt.
In front of every window, every door.
-l already did it.
-Well, check it.
-Okay?
-Okay.
-Dean, you got the gun?
-Yeah.
-Give it to me.
-Sam tried to shoot the demon...
-...and it vanished.
-This is me. I won't miss.
Now, the gun. Hurry.
Son, please.
Give me the gun. What are you doing?
-He'd be furious.
-What?
That I wasted a bullet.
He wouldn't be proud of me.
He'd tear me a new one.
You're not my dad.
-Dean, it's me.
-l know my dad better than anyone.
-You ain't him.
-What's gotten into you?
I could ask you the same thing.
Stay back.
Dean. What the hell's going on?
Your brother's lost his mind.
-He's not Dad.
-What?
I think he's possessed. He's been
possessed since we rescued him.
-Don't listen.
-Dean, how do you know?
-He's-- He's different.
-You know, we don't have time for this.
Sam, you wanna kill this demon,
you gotta trust me.
Sam.
No.
Fine.
You're both so sure.
Go ahead.
Kill me.
I thought so.
What a pain in the ass
this thing's been.
It's you, isn't it?
-We've been looking for you a long time.
-Well, you found me.
But the holy water....
You think something like that
works on something like me?
I'm gonna kill you.
Oh, that would be a neat trick.
In fact, here.
Make the gun float to you there,
psychic boy.
You know, this is fun.
I could've killed you
a hundred times today, but this--
This is worth the wait.
Your dad, he's in here with me.
Trapped inside his own meat suit.
He says hi, by the way.
He's gonna tear you apart.
-He's gonna taste the iron in your blood.
-Let him go.
-Or l swear to God--
-What?
What are you and God gonna do?
You see, as far as I'm concerned,
this is justice.
You know that little exorcism
of yours?
That was my daughter.
-Who, Meg?
-The one in the alley...
...that was my boy.
You understand?
-You gotta be kidding me.
-What?
You're the only one
that can have a family?
You destroyed my children.
How would you feel if
I killed your family?
Oh, that's right.
I forgot, l did.
Still, two wrongs don't make a right.
-You son of a bitch.
-l wanna know why.
-Why did you do it?
-You mean, why did I kill Mommy...
-...and pretty little Jess?
-Yeah.
You know, I never told you this, but
Sam was gonna ask her to marry him.
Been shopping for rings
and everything.
You wanna know why?
-They got in the way.
-ln the way of what?
My plans for you, Sammy.
You and all of the children like you.
Listen, you mind just
getting this over with, huh?
-l really can't stand the monologuing.
-Funny.
But that's all part of
your m.o., isn't it?
Masks all that nasty pain.
Masks the truth.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
You know, you fight and you fight
for this family, but the truth is...
...they don't need you.
Not like you need them.
Sam, he's clearly John's favorite.
Even when they fight, it's more concern
than he's ever shown you.
I'll bet you're real proud
of your kids too, huh?
Oh, wait, l forgot.
I wasted them.
Dean.
No!
Dad. Dad.
-Dad.
Don't you let it kill me.
Dean!
Dad, please.
-No! Don't!
-Stop.
Stop it.
You kill me, you kill Daddy.
I know.
Dean. Dean. Hey.
Oh, God. You lost a lot of blood.
-Where's Dad?
-He's right here.
-He's right here, Dean.
-Go check on him.
-Dean.
Dad.
Sammy! lt's still alive.
It's inside me. I can feel it.
Just shoot me. You shoot me.
You shoot me in the heart, son.
-Do it now!
-Sam, don't you do it. Don't you do it.
You gotta hurry.
I can't hold onto it much longer.
Just shoot me, son. Shoot me!
Son, l'm begging you.
We can end this, here and now.
Sammy!
-Sam, no.
-You do this!
Sammy!
Sam.
Look, just hold on, all right?
The hospital's only 10 minutes away.
I'm surprised at you, Sammy.
Why didn't you kill it?
I thought we saw eye to eye on this.
Killing this demon comes first.
Before me, before everything.
No, sir.
Not before everything.
Look, we still got the Colt.
We still have the one bullet left.
We should start over, all right? l mean,
we already found the demon once--