My name is Dean Winchester.
That big fella's my brother Sam.
- We kill monsters.
- Oh, this is boring.
Is there...
I don't know, music?
? Carry on, my wayward son ?
? There'll be peace
when you are done ?
? Lay your weary head to rest ?
? Don't you cry no more ?
We've got portals
to apocalyptic worlds.
We've got
shape-shifting demons.
Dealing with a whole new set
of tiddlywinks.
So much for simple.
Your mother, she's alive.
We're gonna save
Jack and Mom, together.
? Once I rose above ?
? The noise and confusion ?
Bobby.
? Just to get a glimpse
beyond this illusion ?
Michael wants to come
to Earth and destroy it,
- and we need your help.
- Let's go.
? But I flew too high ?
- Welcome to the team.
- Hmm, hmm.
? Though my eyes could see,
I still was a blind man ?
We grab Satan
and we use his grace
to open up a door
between two universes.
Then we get Mom, we get Jack,
and we get out.
Team Free Will 2.0.
Here we go.
? I can hear them say ?
? Carry on, my wayward son ?
We're running out of time.
Let's pick up the pace.
? When you are done ?
Aah!
? Lay your weary head to rest ?
No!
? Don't you cry no more ?
That was awesome.
The ice caps are melting.
People marching.
A little bit of, uh,
craziness in the movie world.
Businessman billionaire mogul
turned President,
embroiled in yet another
controversy.
And that...
is pretty much the world --
uh, our world -- right now.
Let me get this right --
the ice caps are melting,
a movie where a girl
goes all the way
with a fish...
wins Best Picture,
and that damn fool idjit
from “The Apprentice”,
is President.
- Yeah.
And you call where we come
from “Apocalypse World”.
Good point.
Sorry.
Oh. Excuse me.
- Dean.
- Hey, Sam. Got something.
All right. I'm on my way.
All right,
gang's all here.
How many are inside?
I can hear three.
Wait, maybe -- maybe four.
They're talking about
whether Kylie Jenner
would make a good mother.
The consensus is no.
Yeah, well, that's why
I'm a Khlo? man.
All right, we're talking
werewolves, which means...
Silver bullets.
That's right.
So...
you know the play.
Let's do it to it.
And that...
that is why
I'm a Khlo? man.
So you really like
the rain?
When it's
this beautiful, I do.
So what are you gonna
do now?
Honestly, I got no clue.
Everyone seems to be
settling in okay in town.
Ketch is out doing
Ketch things.
Rowena and Charlie
are road tripping it
through the Southwest.
That's trouble.
Ginger trouble --
the worst kind.
Anyways...
without an archangel, it's not
like we can go back home.
And I'm not sure
I'd want to.
I...I like it here.
Is that...
Blood.
Maggie.
? Supernatural 13x23 ?
Let the Good Times Roll
Original Air Date on May
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Kid did great.
Yeah, no kidding.
I mean, he keeps this up,
and...
And what?
I don't know.
Hey, you remember...
remember when you asked
if we could stop it?
All the evil in the world?
Yeah.
If we could...
really change things?
Well, maybe with Jack,
we can.
Maybe you're right.
But then
what will we do?
Mm. Yeah.
This.
A whole lot of this.
But on a beach somewhere,
you know?
Can you imagine?
You, me, Cass,
toes in the sand,
couple of them
little umbrella drinks.
Matching Hawaiian shirts,
obviously.
Some hula girls.
You talking about retiring?
You?
If I knew the world was safe?
Hell, yeah.
And you know why?
'Cause we freaking
earned it, man.
- I'll drink to that.
- Yeah.
Hell, yeah.
Stop!
No!
Jack? Hey.
Hey, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Easy.
You're just having
a bad dream.
Sorry.
It's okay. You don't
have to apologize.
I have 'em, too. All the time.
You do?
Sure.
You, um...
What do you see?
Well, depends.
Mostly...
mostly people I couldn't save.
Me, too.
Over there
in the other world,
I said I'd protect
those people.
But...
I saw so many of them die.
And...I tried to save them.
I...I tried,
but...
I'm sorry.
I wasn't strong enough.
Jack...
it's not about being strong.
I mean...
Look, I don't know
what you saw over there
and I don't know
what you went through.
I know it was bad.
But I also know that
you came out the other side
because you are strong.
But even when we're strong,
man, things are gonna
happen.
We're gonna make mistakes.
Nobody's perfect. Right?
But we can get better.
Every day,
we can get better.
So whatever you're dealing with,
you know, whatever...
whatever comes at us,
we'll figure out a way
to deal with it, together.
You're family, kid,
and we look after our own.
Dean?
What's wrong?
I-I...
I said I'd protect her,
and, Sam...
Stop, Jack.
This isn't your fault.
What happened to her?
I don't know.
Doesn't look supernatural.
Looks like some son of a bitch
beat on her until...
Who would do
something like this?
Word is, you're friends
with Maggie.
Uh, yeah, since we came over.
Me and her,
we didn't have anybody else,
so we kinda stuck together.
So I'm sure you know
she went out last night.
Well, she didn't come home.
Um...
is Maggie in trouble?
She's dead.
She...
No, that's not...
We were supposed
to be safe here.
We need to know
where Maggie went,
who she was talking to.
I don't...
There was a boy.
What boy?
Nate.
He works at that store
out on Route 281.
Maggie, she had a crush.
That's why she snuck out
last night.
She was going to meet him.
All right, well, let's go talk
to this boy, Jack.
Jack?
Why'd you do it?!
Tell me!
I-I didn't.
Liar!
Jack! No!
Jack?
- Let him go.
- All right.
Jack!
You...you shot me.
To get your attention.
You're acting like a psycho!
- Jack.
- He killed Maggie.
Maggie?
Maggie's dead?
Jack, listen to me.
He didn't kill Maggie.
Look at him.
I'm sorry.
Jack!
No, hey, just --
just let him go.
You keep hurting people!
You keep...
Aah! Uhh!
hurting...
Aah!
Why do you keep hurting people?!
You shot him.
Uh...rubber bullets.
Yeah,
a training exercise.
We're FBI.
I'm Agent Rowland.
This is Agent Knowles
and Agent Williams.
You need to go. Now.
Hi, son.
Run!
Aah!
- It's not possible.
- Yeah, tell him that.
Hey, fellas.
Miss me?
No, no, no, Cass. Don't!
No, Cass. Do. Please.
Run!
Go, go, go, go!
Is this...
Are you real?
Always.
Sam said you're dead.
He said
Michael killed you.
Yeah, I don't like
to speak ill of people,
but Sam is a big fat liar
and he's a bad person
and...
like, freakishly tall, so...
I-I don't understand.
No, Michael didn't...
Sam was the one
who left me behind.
- What?
- Yep.
I mean, I think he thought
I'd be trapped over there
in “Giant Litter Box World”
forever,
'cause that worked so well
the first time.
I don't blame him,
though, okay?
I mean...
for everything that
I've done to him, I think, uh,
I had it coming, you know?
But you know what?
I'm moving on.
But if the rift is closed,
then how are you here?
Oh, no. Not “how.”
“Why.”
I'm here for you, Jack.
Because, you know, even though
the Three Amigos --
Sam, Dean,
and the other one --
won't admit it,
you need me.
You do,
'cause we're blood.
And we're not human, no matter
how much we pretend to be.
See, humans are...
limited and fragile.
And I'll admit, they bring out
the worst in me, I gotta say.
It seems like, you know,
no matter how much
you try to do right around them,
something always goes wrong.
Follow?
I...
I know.
Right? And that's not
their fault, or ours.
It's just, us and humans,
we're like oil and water.
You know, sardines
and strawberries.
It's just
a bad combination.
What do we do?
Leave.
I mean...
there's a whole universe
out there, buddy.
Planets. Stars. Galaxies.
Why should we stay here
on Earth
when we can
go anywhere else?
Heck, everywhere else.
Like, um,
like "Star Wars"?
Exactly like "Star Wars."
You want a lightsaber?
I can make you a lightsaber.
Heck, I can make you
a Wookiee.
But...no.
Sam, Dean, and Castiel,
they'll miss me.
Yes, they will.
They will. It'll be hard.
But you have to
live your life for you.
Right?
This is our second chance,
kiddo.
This is our opportunity
to escape our past
and our sins
and start over.
What do you say?
Father, son.
You up for
an adventure, buddy?
I...
I'd like that.
But there's something
you need to do first.
Talked to the other refugees.
No one's got any idea
who'd wanna hurt Maggie.
Maybe it wasn't
one of them.
Maybe...
there are monsters in this world
that aren't monsters.
Jack! Hey --
Hey.
Kid, what the Sam Hell?
It's all right, okay?
He's here to help.
- He is?
- You know it, Longmire.
Call Sam. Now.
Hmm.
So you're leaving dead bodies
on tables now.
Nice.
We were waiting,
to give her
a Hunter's funeral.
You won't have to.
My father, he's gonna
bring Maggie back to life.
I am?
Yeah, boys, we got a problem.
Jack, what are you doing?
What I have to.
This...
it's my second chance.
Yeah, uh, Jack, about this, uh,
resurrection stuff --
It's not always a great idea
because, uh...
you know,
people come back...different.
Well, Sam didn't.
Right. Well, Sam's always
been...
sort of different.
You know what I mean?
Some would say "special."
No offense.
You said you'd do anything.
Fine.
Has he done
something to you?
I heard that. Heard it.
Mary, everything's
gonna be fine.
Okay.
Jack?
Jack!
He's not...
He's gone.
How did Michael and Lucifer
both get here?
How did they open a rift?
You know what? It doesn't --
We -- we've gotta find Jack
before Michael does
whatever the hell
he's gonna do, okay?
I-I'll call Jody
and everybody else.
You're gonna put out an APB
on the Devil?
Yeah, I am.
I'll check angel radio.
Sam, even if
we find Lucifer,
how we gonna stop him?
Maggie? Hey, sorry.
You okay?
I'm alive, so...
yes?
Right.
Listen, I-I know this is
weird -- so...weird --
but, um,
before you...died,
do you remember anything about
the person that killed you?
Does it matter?
Kinda seems like you have
bigger, you know,
Satan-y problems.
Yeah, but -- but we're --
we're dealing with those.
Mostly. Um...
But yes, it does matter.
It matters to me.
I...
I never saw his face,
but, uh...
I saw his eyes.
Magnificent, isn't it?
It really is.
All right, Jody's lookin'.
So far, Nada.
Yeah, angel radio
is nothing but static,
which is disturbing.
Great. Well, we'll just
add that to the list.
So what do we do now?
What's happening?
What the hell?
Oh, no.
What the hell is that?
Mom, Bobby, take Maggie,
get her out of here.
Go through the garage.
We'll buy you some time.
No!
- Mom!
- Please!
- Go.
Aah!
You really thought
you could run from me?
Aah! Uhh!
Yeah, how did you --
?Get here?
Easy. I made a deal.
I saw they do the spell.
I know what it takes.
It's some blood,
some fruit,
a glowy rock, and then...
Bam. We step through,
both of us.
And now,
this world is mine.
I can save it,
purge it of sin.
Oh, yeah, 'cause that
really worked on your rock.
?I'm not perfect.
Yes, I made mistakes.
But second time's the charm.
And you...
?Aah!
Dean Winchester, will be
the first life that I take
in this world,
first soul I save.
Some would consider that
an honor.
Well, as Shakespeare
once said,
eat me, dickbag.
?
Jack, Jack.
Jack, I don't know
where you are,
and I don't even know
if you can hear this prayer,
but we need you.
We need you.
Look at
all those worlds, Jack.
We're gonna take
the grand tour, buddy.
We're gonna explore every nook
and cranny of creation.
We might even
learn something,
maybe come up
with some improvements.
Improvements?
Yeah, yeah. We'll --
we'll talk about that later.
Jack, Jack,
I don't know where you are,
and I don't even know
if you can hear this prayer.
We need you.
What's up, buddy?
You all right?
Could've done this quick,
but I wanted to enjoy it,
that moment when the soul
leaves the body... ?
it's beautiful.
Aah!
Jack.
I heard your prayer.
Yeah, it's me.
Yay!
Uh, we done, buddy?
Buddy?
You hurt my friends.
You hurt my family!
Whoa.
Lucifer,
we -- we had a deal!
Okay, game over.
Hey, buddy, let's, uh, let's, uh...
split, okay?
What does he mean?
I-I-I don't know.
I didn't -- I didn't hear.
They had a deal.
Lucifer gets you,
and Michael
gets everything else.
He's gonna nuke our world, Jack,
just like he did his.
- Is that true?
- ?No! It's not.
Is that why
you wanted us to leave?
Leave?
He said -- he said
we'd go to the stars.
What,
and you're just gonna
leave the rest of us
here to burn?
Okay. Hold on a second.
Let's slow down, 'cause I...
I'm not currently
the bad guy here.
Yeah, tell that to Maggie.
What about Maggie?
Maggie saw the eyes
of the person who killed her --
the glowing, red eyes.
You're gonna --
you're gonna believe this guy?
- Come on, man! Sam's a hater!
-Tell me.
He would say anything
to get you on his side.
Tell me the truth!
She saw me when I was
scouting out the bunker.
She saw me and she screamed,
and then...
so I crushed her skull
with my bare hands.
And it was warm and wet,
and I liked it.
You're not my father.
You're a monster.
Come on, man!
Okay.
I tried with you.
I really tried with you.
Everything you told me
was a lie.
Because I told you what
you wanted to hear, man.
So what?! I killed the girl!
Big deal!
She's a -- she's a human!
She doesn't matter!
So am I!
Yeah?
And that's your problem.
You're too much like
your mother.
Jack...
Stay back.
I'll handle him.
Will you?
Oh, buddy.
We could've been something,
you and me.
We could've remade the universe.
It would've been great.
We could've been
better gods than Dad.
And I really wanted that, pal.
I wanted that.
But now if I can't
have it with you, I...
I don't need ya.
I just need your power.
?- Jack! - ?No!
Ahh.
- Jack.
- Sammy!
- Jack!
- ?
Sammy!
What just happened?
I don't know.
The Devil won.
That's what happened.
Really, Sam? Hitching a ride?
I mean, do you ever quit?
- Go to hell.
- ?Hell, yeah.
Been there. Done that.
?Aah!
How do we stop him?
You don't.
After consuming the nephilim's
grace, Lucifer's juiced up.
He's super-charged.
He'll kill the boy,
your brother.
Hell, he could
end the whole universe
if he put his mind to it.
And you thought I was bad.
No. No, you beat him. I saw you.
When he was weaker,
and I was stronger.
Believe me,
I'd love to rip
my brother apart.
But now in this banged up
meatsuit...
not happening.
This is the end,
of everything.
No.
What if...
what if you had your sword?
You know...
it's been real fun.
I really had a great time
with you,
but I think we should see
other people.
- What do you say?
- ?
Aah!
?
Stop!
Now why should I listen to you?
Because...
- I'm your son.
?- Oh, yeah.
Well, you had a chance
with that, but...
?Now?
As for kids...
Ah, I can make more of those.
Wow, Daddy Sammy
coming to the rescue.
But your little Jackie,
the nougat-loving boy
that you had before,
he's killed people.
He's got lots of blood
on his hands.
I don't care.
He's family.
Ha!
What's family done for anybody?
My dad left me.
My brothers tried to kill me.
A lot.
Family blows.
And I'm gonna prove it to you.
What, by killing me?
Go ahead.
No, I'm not gonna kill you.
He is.
Dean, no.
I am your sword.
It's you.
?You're the Michael sword.
Your perfect vessel.
Why do you think you two
are the vessels?
Michael
and Lucifer.
You were
born to this, boys.
With me, you'd be stronger
than you've ever been.
Oh, I know what you are.
If we work together,
can we beat Lucifer?
- Dean --
?- Can we?!
We'd have a chance.
Dean, you can't.
Lucifer has Sam.
He has Jack.
Cass, I don't have a choice!
If we do this,
it's a onetime deal.
I'm in charge.
You're the engine,
but I'm behind the wheel.
Understand?
Now I could -- I probably
should -- execute you.
I mean, really, really use
my imagination.
But I'm feeling generous today.
So one of you is gonna
walk out that door,
and the other one will be
laying dead on the ground.
You choose.
No.
Or you could do that,
and I can murder you both
and end all life
in the universe.
Remake it in my image,
better than Dad ever could.
I'm thinkin'...
mm...
fire-breathing dragons,
sassy talking robots.
I might give humans another
chance if they know their place
and worship me,
'cause I've earned it.
But hey, it'll probably take a few days to
unravel the universe,
Maybe, uh, 7, 10 days tops.
So maybe, just maybe,
one of you could stop me.
Maybe.
Well, let's see.
Clock's ticking, guys.
Kill me.
- What?
?- Kill me.
You can stop him, Jack.
You can get your power back.
No, I-I c-can't.
I can't beat him.
But you can.
?What?
I know you can.
No, no, no, no, no. Jack.
Don't! Jack!
Jack!
I love you.
I love all of you.
Jack, don't! Don't!
Dean?
Hiya, Sammy.
You let my brother in.
Well, turns out, he and I
have something in common.
We both wanna gut your ass.
Aah!
?
Well...
?Uhh!
Good try, Dean.
?I'll give you that, buddy.
I'm not just powerful now.
I am power.
And I don't need a blade
to end you, pal.
Dean!
Bye-bye, Dean.
Is he...
He...
he's dead.
Holy crap.
You did it.
No.
No, we did it.
We did it.
Dean?
Dean!
We had a deal!
Michael.
Thanks for the suit.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
? @elder_man ?