Azazel was a fanatic.
Dagon has her toys.
If anyone bothers
a Prince of Hell...
you don't wanna know
what happens.
Crowley's dead. Kelly's dead.
Cass is...
- Mom's gone.
- Aah!
And apparently, the Devil's kid
hit puberty in 30 seconds flat.
No!
Jack is not evil.
He's just a kid.
My mother, she said
the world was a dangerous place.
That's why
I had to grow up fast.
She said Castiel,
he would keep me safe.
I think we should take him
back to the bunker.
I agree.
Until I figure out a way
to end him,
we'll bring him home.
Protect the throne, Drexel?
Face it, we're done.
Lord Lucifer promised
he would return.
He'll pull us out of chaos.
He will
make Hell great again.
Do you even hear yourself?
What did I tell you? Hmm?
?
On your feet.
Um...
who'd you say you were?
I am Asmodeus...
Fourth Prince of Hell.
...here to rule until
such time
as Lucifer returns
with his son.
And there are gonna be
some changes.
The underperforming
and ineffective,
the corporate lackeys
in the Crowley era
are being purged.
The grand old days
of fire and brimstone are back.
The following will
step forward --
Mr. Drexel.
Mr. Harrington.
Mr. Sierra.
As for the rest of y'all...
?
There's a new sheriff in town.
? Supernatural 13x02 ?
The Rising Son
Original Air Date on October 19, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey, we still got probably
12 hours until we're home.
You want me to drive?
Do I ever want you to drive?
Look...
losing Mom and Cass,
that's a lot to process, Dean,
especially on no sleep.
And the kid --
“The kid”?
Come on, man. You know how
this plays out.
Look, when we try
to bend the rules,
pretend that the bad guys
aren't so bad
or that things will
get fixed,
that's when people that
we care about get hurt.
And then we end up doing
what we should've done
in the first place,
which is end the problem.
So this time, let's start
with the obvious.
Soon as I find a way
to take care of...It.
Dean, “the problem”
might be our only shot
at saving Mom.
?
Mom's gone.
There's no fixing that.
?
Mary, not to be critical,
but if we are ever gonna
find a way out of here, uh,
you gotta pick up the pace.
We got a lot of ground
to cover, okay?
Not sure I see the point,
since...
no matter how this plays out,
you're going to kill me.
Why would I kill you?
- Oh. That's right.
- 'Cause I'm evil.
Yeah, let me tell
you a couple things, all right?
You don't get to defy God
and beat the Cage
without having a modicum
of intelligence, all right?
A game plan, i.e.,
I don't want you dead
because I need you alive.
All right, look, yeah,
in a perfect world,
I would probably kill you
and your plodding sons.
But life isn't fair.
Your sons have my boy.
So I'm gonna exchange you
for my son.
You can't possibly care
about raising a child.
Oh, you have no idea
what I care about.
Aah!
?
What the hell?
Mary?!
No trace of Lucifer.
Indeed.
We scoured all of Hell.
Even checked the Cage.
Nothing.
At this point, we must
focus on the son.
There's no sign of him
either, sir.
Maybe a Sudden Infant Death?
He is not an infant.
New to this world, yes,
but he is full
of timeless knowledge
and unschooled power.
He lives. I know it.
With Lucifer gone, I want him
found and trained to rule.
With me as his humble advisor,
of course.
Okay.
“Find son,
but continue
to search for Lucifer.”
Because if we didn't,
he'd be upset,
and I-I can assure you,
from personal experience,
that an upset Lucifer
has a, uh,
short fuse.
Are you equating your paltry acquaintance
with our lord to mine?
- Uh...
- Mine, which is born
from eons of service
and sacrifice?
?
Ah.
I know the perils
of Lucifer's disappointment.
He...he did that?
Long ago.
Eager to please,
I freed the Shedim.
You...
Oh, I've heard stories
about --
Oh, I'm sure you have.
Hell's most savage.
Things so dark and base,
God himself would not
allow them into the light.
But I, in my pride, believed
that I could train them.
Use them.
But Lucifer feared them,
as well he should,
so he forbade it,
locked them up again.
He was...
“disappointed” in me.
Mm. Mm.
The pain, the, uh,
the total humiliation...
it forged an eternal bond
between us.
I am his to command,
as you are mine.
Write that down.
This is a bad idea.
We should've just kept driving.
Dude... you were
hallucinating sheep on the road.
We need a few hours.
This is nice.
Let's ward the room,
get a bite,
get a few hours of sleep,
hit the road first thing.
It's...wonderful.
Hey. No.
But...
Y--
?
No.
And you're on the couch,
sport.
All right?
So why don't you go
over there?
Sit down and...
here.
Read a book.
We're out of here
in a few hours.
Jack, hey, I can take
the couch. Why don't --
No, no. It's fine.
?
You can slow down, you know.
That stuff's not gonna
disappear.
Ever seen you eat, Dean?
Wait, wait, wait. How old
do you think you are?
3 days, 17 hours,
and 42 minutes.
This book, it mentions
my father.
Not Castiel, but Lucifer.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, he's --
he's big in the Bible.
Lotta screen time.
And you...knew him?
Well, he's not really
an easy guy to know.
He's, um, he's kind of rough
around the edges.
He's Satan.
And that's...that's bad.
Damn straight.
See...he turned
on his father, God.
God. He's in here, too.
Is he famous or something?
Yeah. Um, God basically...
created everything.
Yeah, and then he skipped out,
leaving guys like us to clean up
his messes like Lucifer.
So God's like my grandfather.
He's family, and that's...
that's good.
Sometimes.
Okay, all right, will you stop?
So, Jack, we know Kelly taught
you things before you were born.
And obviously, you can,
you know,
make people or things move
with your mind.
But, um...
what else can you do?
I...
don't know.
Okay.
For instance,
say you wanted to --
to be someplace else
right now.
Could you?
Can you teleport?
“Teleport.”
Yes.
If you wanted to be on
the other side of that door
right this instant,
what would you do?
What...
Great.
You know, it's possible
he's more human than we thought.
Mm-hmm.
Like that?
Come on.
You're trying to tell me
you didn't pick up anything
before you were born?
That your father never
reached out to you?
?
What?
Jack? Hey.
You all right?
Yeah. Uh, good.
I'm good.
?
All right, I say we, uh...
get some rest.
It's been a long day.
We're startin' early tomorrow.
?
Uhh!
Donatello?
Sam? Dean?
Is God with you?
?
You okay?
Ah, pretty much.
No soul of course,
thanks to Amara.
It's kinda like
losing your appendix.
You never really noticed it
when you had it.
But now, when I come
to a moral crossroad,
I ask myself,
“What would Mr. Rogers do?”
And as soon as I nail that,
I'm usually good.
Why are you here?
Yes.
That is the question
we all must ask.
Why are you in Wyoming?
Oh. Uh, Well...
after God left,
I said to myself,
“Donatello, you are so retired”"
I mean, who needs
a prophet of God
when there is no God?
So... a few days ago,
I'm online,
checking out condos in Boca,
and I am knocked off my feet by
this weird wave of power.
Not exactly like God's.
More like...something new,
something fresh.
I was drawn to it.
It's here.
Wow.
Right here.
It's...
you.
Who are you?
I'm...Jack.
Jack is a nephilim.
A child
of a human and an angel.
Archangel, actually.
Um...Lucifer.
Lucifer?
And Donatello here
is a prophet.
Which means he has a direct line
to God, or Heaven.
Yes, well, not so much anymore.
But, uh...
Look at you.
The waves of power...
so intense.
Maybe less human than
we thought.
Fascinating.
You know, I've met
your father.
Your power's nothing like his.
Not dark, not toxic.
That so?
Not yet.
If Jack is sending out
a signal strong enough
to get Donatello
all the way out here...
The angels are still
out there.
I mean, who knows what else
might be listening?
He needs protection.
?
All right, so, uh...
I'm thinking something
like this, right about here.
Uh, you know what?
Exactly like that.
And you're cool with this?
Yeah.
Turn the damn thing on
and start buzzin'.
W-we're brothers. It's kind of
like a family crest.
?
So you heard Donatello.
No evil vibes from Jack.
Proves nothing,
except you're way too attached
to this kid.
You need to see this
for what it is, okay?
I mean, what do you need,
a sign?
Dean, whatever his powers
are or will be...
...if we train him properly,
they could be used for good.
Aah!
Uhh!
Well, there's your sign.
Did you do that?
I'm not sure.
Hey. You all right?
It hurt.
Okay, see, sometimes,
things hurt,
so you just man up
and deal with it.
Yes. I understand.
Pain is a part of
the complete human experience.
Accepting it is
a sign of maturity.
All right.
I think your, uh, machine
might've fritzed out there.
You might wanna
get that looked at.
Uh...
Yeah.
Okeydokey.
Looks good, Jack.
?
Well, there's your second sign.
It was a reflex.
He didn't do it on purpose.
Who cares if he didn't do
it on purpose? He did it.
I mean, you didn't see Cass
smiting someone
every time he got his teeth cleaned.
I'm right here, you know.
Yeah, and what about
the vanishing tattoo?
An archangel healing itself.
Another reflex.
Or maybe he didn't want
to be warded.
Okay, look, yeah, Jack is on
Lucifer's family tree.
But we don't know if that DNA
is stronger than Kelly's,
or his connection
with Cass.
Oh, you mean the connection
that got Cass killed?
I'm just saying,
Jack doesn't have to be evil.
We can teach him not to be.
Ah.
- The nature versus nurture conundrum.
- Hey.
Mnh-mnh.
Dude...
Oh. Speaking not as a prophet
but as a scientist,
I don't think teaching him
is in the cards.
It's like asking a lion
not to be a lion.
But this isn't
a lion! This is a human!
With a strong dose
of God juice.
Okay. that's it.
I'm done, all right?
'Cause he's not God,
he's not Cass, he's not Simba.
He's the friggin' Devil!
Jack?
Uh-oh.
?
I love you, Jack.
I love you so much.
You are gonna be amazing.
Jack?
Hey.
Hey, bud. We, uh,
we've been looking for ya.
I'm sorry. I...
Everyone was so angry.
Yeah, and, um...
I suppose you wanted
to be away from it.
And suddenly, I was.
I'll tell you what.
You got some
special skills, Jack.
That's for sure.
We just need to make sure
we get a grip on 'em, so...
so you don't hurt anybody.
Is that why Dean hates me?
Dean doesn't hate you.
It...
Look, sometimes the wires
in Dean's head get crossed
and -- and he gets frustrated,
and then he mixes
frustration with anger,
and -- and -- and fear.
Why would he be afraid?
Because Dean feels like it's
his job to protect everyone.
And right now,
we need to protect you.
But we may also need
to protect people from you.
Maybe I'm not worth
all this.
Your mom thought you were.
So did Cass.
So do I.
? I'll be working
on the graveyard shift ?
Getcha another?
Yeah. Sure.
What the hell?
You're not drivin', right?
I've just -- I've seen you
around the hotel.
Passin' through with...
what, your buddies?
Uh, that's my brother,
and some messed up kid.
Oh, the kid's messed up?
Yeah, issues with his dad.
The older fella.
No, that's, uh, Donatello.
Uh, he's a...
guy we work with.
I hated my old man.
I ran away myself.
See, my mom would never
stick up for me.
But...
you know kids.
No matter what, they still want
the old man's approval.
Well, that's how it was
with me, just...
You know, that's, uh,
that's how it was
with me, too.
I'm talkin' your ear off I'll --
I'll grab you that drink.
You know what? I'm good.
Uh, I'm gonna take a walk.
There you go. Thank you.
Thanks.
? I'll be working
on the graveyard shift ?
? Until I die ?
?
Come in.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Good morning.
How's Jack?
Uh, by the way,
sorry to stick him with you.
Things got a little tense
here last night,
so I figured it'd be better
to have him stay in your room.
It's not a big deal.
He's an interesting kid.
Yeah. Yeah,
that's an understatement.
Let -- let me ask ya...
Do you have any idea
how powerful he'll get to be?
I-I don't. No.
But the, uh, the lore says,
quote,
“A nephilim becomes
more powerful
than the angel who sired it.”
In this case, the sire is
an archangel.
So...
Does he know about
his father?
Vaguely.
So he's not bonded
to Lucifer.
He seems to have a real
attachment to his mom,
but only kind of
a fuzzy idea about his dad.
And his mom, Kelly,
was a really good person,
so that makes me think Jack can
be molded the right way.
Mm, molded.
I hope you're right.
Yeah.
?
Who the hell are you?
Mary.
Mary Winchester.
I'm a Hunter.
Doubt it.
Come here.
You don't walk like an angel.
They all walk like they got
sticks up their asses.
Not a demon neither.
I told you.
I ain't never met
a female Hunter.
Not many women, period,
since the wars began.
Wars?
What rock you been under?
I'm not from around here.
Oh.
I don't know anything...
I just got attacked by some kind
of fireball or something.
Angels, yeah.
Always takin' shots.
Maybe I can...help you
find your way.
I'm good.
Ah. Let's keep
this friendly, huh?
Bitch!
?
Uhh!
You're welcome.
Uh, Mary, in case
you didn't notice this,
you left without me.
What is wrong with you?
We need each other.
This is a win-win situation.
Okay? We get outta this...
theme park,
we both get our boys back.
You think I want you to win?
Yeah, I'm -- I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to insist.
Hey.
We should probably hit it.
Uh, I was just gonna
call you, actually.
Um, look...
we are gonna be on the road
a long time today. Right?
Yeah. Well, you know, we don't
have to be 'cause your new pal
could just zap us back
to the bunker like that.
Point is...
if you and I are gonna
do this,
keep Jack on
the right side of things,
then -- then we have to be
on the same page.
Okay. Well, that's the problem,
though, Sam,
'cause we're not on
the same page. Like, at all.
All right. You know what?
I know what's going on here.
Oh. Okay. Well, please, tell me,
what's going on here?
You thinking Mom is gone
and Cass is gone,
and that Jack can't be saved.
Dean, after everything
we've gone through...
We just lost people we love,
people who have been
in our lives for a long time.
Everything's upside-down.
I get it.
But we've been down before.
I mean, rock bottom.
And we find a way.
We fix it because that's
what we do.
And Jack wants to do
the right thing.
Jack's scared to death
of who he is,
and he's scared of you.
Come in.
Morning, guys.
Uh, got a minute? I, uh,
wanna talk to you about Jack.
We just talked about Jack.
- What?
- You were just here.
No, I wasn't.
I was grabbing
breakfast burritos. Extra spicy.
?
Jack?
He's gone.
?
Okay, okay, so -- so --
so -soso who's got Jack?
And who was I -- or what was
I talking to? A shifter?
What would a shifter want
with Jack?
?
Where you going, cowboy?
He -- he went this way.
You sure?
I can feel it.
I'll get the gear.
?
Aah! Uhh!
First angels, now demons.
Terrific.
I guess the word's out.
Donatello.
?
Aah!
Uhh!
Uh, housekeeping
is not gonna like this.
Jack.
As a prophet, Jack,
I speak the words of God.
Do you know who God is?
Yes.
Kind of.
Well, son, God has
a message for you.
You must prepare yourself,
Jack.
Train yourself to use
your gifts,
to fulfill your destiny.
How?
Long ago, a troop
of God's bravest soldiers
were trapped in a distant cavern
of a place called Hell.
I've read about Hell.
It doesn't sound nice.
It's not. That's why we have
to rescue the soldiers.
They're called the Shedim,
and God wants you to
set them free,
to be a hero.
I could do that?
And so much more.
Uh...
You see that patch of earth
there?
Imagine the force of your will,
drilling down
into infinite darkness,
the soldiers being drawn
to the surface.
Do it, Jack!
Do it for God!
?
Focus!
I'm trying.
Try harder, boy!
?
Turn!
Th-- this is worrisome.
I'm sensing a power emanation
alongside Jack's.
It gets stronger the closer
we get to it.
Jasper, Wyoming?
Maybe it's an angel.
No. Something dark.
Do you ever have
any good news?
All right, well,
see if there's anything
in Jasper that's demon-y.
Yeah, there is.
According to Dad's journal,
Jasper is home to
its very own Gate to Hell.
It gets better.
Fantastic.
According to legend,
this particular gate
leads to, “A place where
unimaginable evil emanates
from creatures too wicked
for the Pit to hold.”
What the hell does
that mean?
They're really bad.
?
Ah! Turn!
Are you tired? Really?
You know what? Let me tell you
a couple things.
First of all, we gotta blow
this taco stand
before who knows what
happens to my son.
And second of all, you're the reason
that we are even stuck
in this literally godforsaken
place to begin with.
So I'm sorry you're tired.
It's not my fault you were
born a wimpy little human
with your wimpy little lungs
and your weak little legs.
What?
You heard me.
Don't say another word
on this trip, okay?
?
Just what I need.
Angels.
Hey.
I sense a creature that
stinks of Hell.
Oh, yeah. That would be her.
False!
Identify yourself.
I'm Lucifer.
False.
No, I'm pretty sure
I'm -- I'm Lucifer.
- You wanna tell this guy who I am?
- False.
Lucifer was killed
by the archangel Michael.
What?
This place is nuts!
Freeze!
Oh, what are you gonna....
Are you gonna smite me?
- On my command.
- Oh, for the love of...
Now!
Aah!
Was he kidding?
I mean, even in
land of Bizarro,
an Angel isn't gonna
try to...
Oh, come on!
?
You should be dead.
Okay. And who are you,
and what spaghetti western
coughed you up?
Don't you know me, brother?
Michael?
Summon up all your will, Jack!
Do it for God!
?
Ah! Aha! Ah! You're doing it!
He's doing it! Yes!
?
It's working!
Don't lose focus!
Don't lose focus, Jack!
Yes! Yes!
He's doing it! Keep focused!
?
Jack! Hey! Stop.
Don't listen to them, Jack!
Holy crap!
Focus!
That's not Donatello!
No, that's not Donatello!
Ah, screw this.
?
Jack, he's a demon!
Howdy, boys.
No!
?
Jack...they wanna stop you.
Contain you.
I can give you the world.
You're hurting my friends!
?
You are Lucifer.
I can feel it.
But how is that even possible?
Um...
You know, alternate universes,
interdimensional travel,
blah, blah, blah.
It's her fault.
Uh, I'll buy that
you're Michael,
but you sort of seem like
a cheap knockoff
to the one I left behind,
and he's a hot mess.
I killed my Lucifer.
Tore him apart
in the skies over Abilene.
But hey, can't get enough
of a good thing.
Um...Okay. Why not?
?
Hurt?
No.
It's kinda wimpy.
Aah!
What are you
gonna do? Kill me?
Or...maybe not.
Maybe I need you.
These yellow-eyed things
just keep on comin', huh?
Mm-hmm.
And hopefully this
fourth Prince of Hell
is the last Kardashian
in the family.
According to this,
if that was Asmodeus,
it's the end of the line.
Dean, wait a second.
The kid came through
for us today.
Jack saved us.
No.
No, whatever that was,
that was a reflex.
It was a sneeze.
Maybe next time he sneezes,
he kills us.
Good night.
Ah!
Mnh.
Okay, what the hell?
Give me that. You --
W--
Don't be an idiot.
Look, A, this is not gonna
do anything to you, okay?
And B, you...
What the hell?
Exactly. What the hell am I?
I can't control...
whatever this is.
I will hurt someone.
?
You know, my brother thinks
you can be saved.
You don't believe that.
No, I don't.
So...
if you're right?
If I'm right...
...and it comes to
killing you...
...I'll be the one
to do it.
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man