[ Metallica's
“Nothing Else Matters” playing ]
Dr. Hess: Lucifer is back.
? So close, no matter how far ?
Castiel:
A Nephilim is coming to be.
I can feel it inside me.
? Forever trusting ?
? Who we are ?
Dean.
? And nothing else matters ?
? I never opened myself
this way ?
? Life is ours,
we live it our way ?
? All these words
I don't just say ?
? And nothing else matters ?
? Never cared for
what they say ?
No!
? Never cared for games
they play ?
? Never cared for what they do ?
? Never cared
for what they know ?
? And I know ?
? Yeah! ?
[ Groans ]
?
No!
Father?
?
No, no, no. No, I'm not
your father, Jack.
It is Jack, right?
[ Door opens ]
Father.
[ Door closes ]
Dean: Sam?
[ Ascending footsteps ]
Sammy?
I'm in here.
[ Gun cocks, gunshot ]
No!
[ Distorted screaming ]
[ Windows shatter ]
[ Continues screaming ]
?
[ Screaming stops ]
[ Both grunt ]
? Supernatural 13x01 ?
Lost and Found
Original Air Date on October 12,
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Get away from them.
Mary, right?
Look, seriously, I just wanted
to say thank you for everything.
I owe you, kid.
Mom, Mom, Mom.
I love you.
[ Flames crackling ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Screaming ]
Mom?!
?
[ Birds calling ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Inhales sharply, grunts ]
Wait, was that...
Lucifer's son.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Ah!
[ Grunts ]
?
Can he teleport?
What?
The kid. Does he have wings?
I don't know.
?
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Sizzling ]
? Pirate Pete's... ?
First batch is down.
[ Restaurant jingle playing ]
Dude.
? ...save the hemisphere ?
Check it.
? ...and join us
for a good meal ?
Check what?
This. Can I interest you
in a Cheesebutt?
Or maybe a Salty Butt Combo.
Perhaps my favorite --
the buttshake.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Slurps ]
If Dave sees this,
he's gonna fire you.
Oh, come on. He's fired me,
like, seven times.
And I keep coming back.
You know why?
Uh, because Dave's banging
your mom?
Exactly. Let's face it, buddy.
Around here, I'm untouchable.
Cool. Good for you.
[ Static crackles ]
Father?
?
[ Click ]
Yo, uh...
we're not open yet.
[ Static crackles ]
[ Birds calling ]
Father.
[ Click ]
Whoa.
I think you should call
your mom.
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Ring, beep ]
Hi, baby.
How naked?
[ Engine revving ]
We still have holy oil,
right?
For what?
'Cause we're gonna have to hit
him with everything we got.
Hold on a second.
Can we just talk about
what happened back there?
Sure. Which part?
Let's see, Crowley's dead,
Kelly's dead, Cass is...
Mom's gone,
and apparently,
the Devil's kid hit puberty
in 30 seconds flat.
Oh, and almost killed us.
Yeah, because you tried
to shoot him.
I tried to shoot the monster,
Sam. That's kind of what we do.
We don't know
what he is yet, Dean.
And I had it under control.
I'm sorry. Are you defending
the Son of Satan?
I'm not defending anything.
I'm just saying, look, with
everything that's happened,
I'm obviously spun out also,
but we need a plan.
Yeah, kill him! Okay?
That's the plan.
Look, right now, all that
matters is finding him
and ending him before
he hurts anybody else.
And once we do that, we'll
figure everything else out.
What about Cass?
Is he...
is he really dead?
You know he is.
[ Engine revs ]
?
[ Radio chatter ]
[ Car door opens ]
?
Uh, hi.
[ Mouths words ]
?
Easy. easy now. I'm just...
My name's Christine Barker.
I'm a Sheriff.
I'm just here to help, okay?
Okay?
[ Birds chirping ]
?
Is that --
Castiel.
Always knew he'd meet
a bad end.
He deserved better.
No, he really didn't.
The mother's upstairs,
but she's --
I don't care about
the brood mare.
Where's the child?
Gone.
Of course he is.
?
So weird.
Why don't you head out
on patrol, Earl?
And by the way, there's no such
thing as “weird.”
Everyone's normal in
their own way.
Right.
Sorry, Sheriff.
Yeah.
[ Departing footsteps ]
Totally normal.
Hope those are all right.
Just pulled some stuff
from the lost and found.
Everything fit?
Here. Take a seat.
Sit.
Okay. [ Sighs ] Let's start
with the basics.
What's your name?
[ Sets down water bottle ]
Jack.
Okay, Jack.
Jack what?
What's your last name?
Okay, how 'bout, uh,
where are your parents?
Your mother and father?
My mother, she's in Heaven.
Mm.
My father...
he was supposed to be here,
but he's not.
I'm trying to find him.
I have to find him.
Sure. We can do that.
What's his phone number?
What about his address?
Or an e-mail?
Is there anything
you do remember, Jack?
[ Glove snaps ]
[ Dagon screams ]
I remember when
the bad woman burned.
I remember
the universe screamed.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Hums ]
[ Glove snaps ]
Okay. I'm gonna take
your thumbprint,
and we're gonna run it
through the system.
If we get a match,
we get you home, yeah?
Okay, just like that.
And...press it here.
Okay.
You stay here.
I'll be right back.
Mm. Dude...
How high are you?
I don't know
what that means.
Well, it means, um, like,
wasted, lit,
chonged, blitz, blasted,
blazed, baked.
Nothing, no?
Look, I'm not judging you.
I'm -- I'm jealous.
What are you on?
I'm on a chair
on the floor...
on the planet Earth.
You are so stoned, man.
No, I'm not stoned.
I'm...
What?
Hungry.
I'm hungry.
[ Baby approaching ]
Well...
[ Engine turns off ]
You really think that
Lucifer Jr.'s
at Pirate Pete's
Jolly Treats?
That he was, like, what,
“Before I destroy the world,
let me just grab a bag
of a curly fries”?
Look, if he would've kept
to the main road,
he would've walked past it.
And I don't know --
Fine. Just make it quick.
You're not coming?
No.
Look, maybe you're right.
Maybe the Devil's kid is in
there just hanging out. Okay?
Or maybe he's halfway across
the country, torching Chicago.
I'm gonna call Jody, check in,
see if she can't help us
put a nationwide APB out...
[ Cellphone beeps ]
on a creepy Satanic nudist.
Yeah, right. Good.
[ Car door opens ]
“Good” is not
the word I would use.
[ Slurring ]Fries.
Lady, seriously,
we don't have fries.
It's breakfast only
until 11:00.
But like I've said
three times already,
hash browns are basically
the same.
Boo!
Fries!
[ Door bell jingles ]
Welcome to Pirate Pete's
Jolly Treats. Argh.
How can I help you?
He wants fries.
We all want fries.
[ Clenched teeth ]
Shut up!
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Ignore her.
She's drunk off her ass.
Little bit.
Right, uh...
Okay, I'm -- I'm looking for
a guy.
Uh, he -- he's about
your height.
Uh... [ Inhales deeply ]
naked.
[ Chuckles ]
You and me both, sister.
-What did I say?
-Sorry.
And yeah, I saw him.
?
[ Telephone rings ]
[ Ring ]
North Cove Sheriff's Department.
Barker speaking.
This is Agent Berry.
I'm with the FBI.
Uh, I'm -- I'm calling
because, uh,
did you happen to pick up
a-a kid earlier today,
uh, not exactly dressed.
Um, he...
Uh, yeah. He's here
at the station.
He is?
Great. Great, that's great.
U, okay, hold on to him.
Don't release him until
I get there, all right?
Holy...
Sheriff?
Something wrong?
Uh...
that's something we should
talk about in person.
[ Turn horn honking
in distance ]
Whoa. What happened to
your hand?
Nothin'.
Doesn't look like nothin'.
You punch a wall
or somethin'?
I punched a wall once.
Well, a poster on a wall,
but same diff, right?
Freshman year, I had this
roommate, Becky.
She had this giant poster of
Elsa. You know, from “Frozen”?
And, I mean, first, who brings
something like that to college?
A cartoon? Really?
Like, “Hello, homeschool”,
right?
[ Chuckles ]
You done?
Anyway, Becky was -- and I say
this in the most feminist,
screw the patriarchy way --
a giant super bitch.
She'd take things
and break things
and piss people off and just do
whatever she wanted,
no matter who it hurt.
It's like the whole world
was just Becky to her. You know?
Mm. So you punched her poster.
[ Door opens ]
And lit most of her stuff on fire.
I got issues.
Hey, s--
Dude, what'd you do
to your hand?
Don't ask.
He's super sensitive.
You got anything?
Yeah. I-I know where he is.
Good. Great. Let's go.
[ Car door closes,
engine starts ]
[ Tires squeal ]
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Crackling continues ]
Clark?
Jack?
?
Clark?
Clark!
[ Laughter distance ]
?
[ Crackling continues ]
[ Laughter in distance ]
[ Unsnaps buttons ]
[ Laughter ]
?
Mm. Hey, Mom.
Uh...
Are you okay?
Yeah. Jack was, um,
just hungry.
I don't think he's ever had
candy before.
I like it.
Mm.
I like nougat.
Mm. He really does.
[ Chuckles ]
Did you see...
There's something wrong
with the lights.
It's, uh... [ Chuckles ]
it's crazy.
Show her the, mm, thing.
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Clark laughs ]
[ Candy thuds ]
Mm!
Yeah, dude's, uh...
magic.
Jack, how did you do that?
[ Chuckles ] I don't know.
[ High-pitched ringing,
distorted voices ]
[ Groaning ]
Jack?
[ Grunts ]
[ Ringing and voices continue ]
Are you okay?
I-I don't...I... [ Grunts ]
I-I have to... [ Groans ]
Just wait. Wait.
[ Whoosh ]
[ Glass shatters ]
Mom!
[ High-pitched ringing,
distorted voices ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Lightbulbs exploding ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Ringing and voices continue ]
[ Warped voice ] Hey.
?
[ Taser zapping ]
[ Groans ]
Nice shot.
?
[ Gun cocks ]
Don't...
What the hell
is going on here?
?
[ Exhales deeply ]
[ Handcuffs clink ]
[ Weapons thud ]
I'm sorry. Say that again.
My name is Dean Winchester.
That big fella in there is
my brother Sam.
We kill monsters.
Monsters?
Mm.
Like...
Have you ever seen
a horror movie?
Mm-hmm.
Like that.
So what are you?
Some kind of superhero?
I'm just a guy doing a job.
So that kid you got
in there,
he's, uh...
Not...human?
Not exactly.
So, um...
what is he?
So...
Jack is a nephilim.
He's half-human
and half-angel.
Angels are real, too.
[ Exhales, chuckles ]
Right.
[ Grunts ]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
It's okay. You're okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
You already hurt me.
Yes, I did. I-I'm sorry.
I was just trying to
slow you down.
You -- you were, uh...
Are you all right?
I don't, I...
I was scared,
and when I get scared,
things happen.
I...I can't stop them.
Why were you scared?
Because of the voices.
[ Whispers ]
They were so...loud,
so...angry.
Do you hear them right now?
No.
Good. [ Chuckles ]
Good.
[ Exhales sharply ]
I'm sorry.
What?
Will you tell them that
I'm sorry?
Yeah.
Sure. Of course.
Jack...
how are you, um...
How are we...
talking right now?
I mean, you're --
you're not even a day old.
How do you speak English?
My mother taught me.
So you talked to her.
I was her.
Okay. And, um...
your powers.
Did she teach you those, too,
or...
No, I...
I don't know why
these things happen.
It's like I'm me, but...
not me.
Jack, look, um...
before you were born,
you -- you opened up a door
to another world.
Do you remember that?
[ Inhales deeply ]
Yes.
Okay, um, could you
do that again?
I don't...I...
I have to find my father.
He'll protect me.
Jack, you gotta listen to me.
That's not really what
Lucifer does.
Lucifer?
No, that's not his name.
My father is Castiel.
What?
My mother,
she said Castiel,
he would keep me safe.
She said the world was
a dangerous place.
That's -- that's why I couldn't
be a baby or a child.
I...
That's why I had to
grow up fast.
That's why I chose him
to be my father.
?
Where is he?
He's dead.
?
[ Lighter clicks ]
[ Clears throat ]
[ Sighs ]
Hmm. So...
you gonna share or what?
?
All right, we're good to go.
Really?
[ Door opens ]
Yeah, the Sheriff --
I gave her the talk.
She's gonna need a minute,
but she's cool.
So...
let's grab Damien here
and find some place quiet...
[ Tongue clicks ]
No, no, no, Dean.
[ Chuckles ]
Jack is not evil.
He -- he -- he's just a kid.
Are you...
He's Lucifer's son.
We need him.
What?
Like --
Clark: Help!
?
Hey, Dean.
Oh, no, you --
No, no, no! No.
That won't do jack
against her.
He's not wrong.
Let him go.
Okay.
If she shoots you.
I don't know what he's told you.
I mean, I can guess.
Some line about how he
and his brother...
[ Deepens voice ]
save the world. Grr. So macho,
[ Sighs ]
[ Normal voice ]
But really, he's not a hero.
He's Becky.
Becky? The roommate Becky?
You take things and break things
and piss people off
and just do whatever you want,
no matter who it hurts.
Also, you're a giant
super bitch.
Well, it takes one
to know one.
So, yeah, you're Becky,
and Becky needs to die.
You're on, Barney Fife.
Dean?
[ Metal clanks in distance ]
?
[ Glass shatters, metal creaks ]
Dean?
?
[ High-pitched ringing ]
[ Groans ]
Conrad's voice:
He's here. We have the boy.
[ Whoosh ]
Too late.
[ Grunts ]
No!
[ Groans ]
[ Metal creaks ]
Clark. [ Grunts ]
[ Miriam shouts ]
[ Cell door clangs ]
?
[ Groans ]
Earl?
[ Grunting ]
Man: Yes, Sheriff.
It's Barker.
I need an ambulance at
the station now.
Copy that.
?
[ Clark grunting, groaning ]
We're just gonna put
a little pressure on the wound.
Lift it up. Put pressure.
Aah!
?
[ Spits ]
[ Groaning ]
Hey!
[ Whoosh ]
[ Angels scream ]
[ Blade clatters ]
[ Panting ]
[ High-pitched ringing stops ]
[ Groans ]
Jack!
Why are you here?
We want the Golden Ticket.
Lucifeci2:
Electric Boogaloo.
Why?
Because Bieber in there?
He can do almost anything.
Anything?
[ Chuckles ] Oh, sweet.
Almost anything.
Castiel, he's dead.
All the way dead,
because of you.
[ Grunts, wheezes ]
[ Door bangs ]
?
[ Grunts ]
Sam.
Don't.
Or what, other one?
Guess.
Stay away from the kid.
You're right.
But if we can't have him,
[ Squish ] no one can.
[ Screaming ]
?
Jack.
Jack. J--
?
I...I'm fine.
[ Radio chatter ]
[ Clark coughs, wheezes ]
[ Coughs ]
[ Christine
speaks indistinctly ]
You're gonna be okay.
I'm right here.
You're gonna be brave.
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
[ Ambulance door closes ]
How's the kid?
[ Siren wailing ]
He's gonna be all right.
I mean, Angel Radio sets
his brain on fire,
but other than that...
So apparently, he can take
an angel blade to the heart
and keep on tickin'.
Yeah. I guess.
Listen, I-I think we should take
him back to the bunker with us.
- I know what you're gonna say --
- I agree.
W-what?
I agree.
So you...
changed your mind?
No. No, nothin's changed.
He's still the Devil's kid.
He's still evil.
[ Clears throat ]
He still brainwashed Kelly and Cass.
And even if he hasn't gone
Big Bad yet, he will.
You don't know that.
Yeah, I do.
'Cause when have things ever
gone right for us?
So until I figure out
a way to end him,
we'll bring him home.
At least there, the only people
he can hurt are you and me.
?
[ Sighs ]
[ Engine turns off ]
?
Hey...
Hey, you, uh,
you sure about this, Dean?
I mean, it's --
it's Cass, you know?
Maybe we can bring him back,
like you said.
No, we can't.
Chuck did -- Uh, God did.
Remember that?
So maybe, um, I don't know,
maybe if we prayed to him
or -- or...
You don't think
I've tried that?
?
Okay, Chuck...
or God or whatever.
I...
I need your help.
?
See, you -- you left us.
You left us. You went off...
You said...
you said the Earth would be fine
because it had me
and it had Sam,
but it's not,
and we're not.
[ Voice breaks ]
We've lost everything.
And now you're gonna
bring him back.
Okay? You're gonna
bring back Cass,
you're gonna bring back Mom,
you're gonna bring 'em all back.
All of them.
Even Crowley.
'Cause after everything
that you've done,
you owe us, you son of a bitch.
So you get your ass down here
and you make this right.
Right here and right now!
?
[ Clicks tongue ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Signs clatters ]
[ Whispers ] Please.
Please help us.
?
[ Exhales shakily ]
God's not listening.
He doesn't give a damn.
?
[ Fabric rips ]
[ Gasoline sloshing ]
You wanna say anything?
I...
What do you say?
Right.
Thank you.
You say thank you.
And you say you're sorry.
[ Sloshing continues ]
You hope they're somewhere
without, uh,
sadness or pain.
You hope
they're somewhere better.
You say goodbye.
?
Well, goodbye, Cass.
Goodbye, Kelly.
Goodbye, Crowley.
Goodbye, Mom.
Dean, we don't know if Mom --
Yeah, we do.
We do, Sam.
Lucifer killed her the moment
he realized we trapped his ass.
He killed her. You know he did.
?
She's gone.
They're all gone.
[ Click ]
?
[ Flames whoosh ]
[ Electricity crackles ]
[ Panting ]
[ Grunts ]
Hey.
So you thought you could
run away
from me?
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Laughs ] Really?
[ Groans ]
Really?
You do know I can fly,
right?
So what now?
You kill me?
[ Thunderclap ]
Sure.
[ Gasps ]
Or maybe not.
Maybe...
Maybe I need you.
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man