Well, I'll be damned.
Huh?
Donna, what's shakin'?
We have a case to solve.
This is Officer Stover.
He's lead on the case.
Nice to meet ya.
Call me Doug.
Looks like somebody
might have a crush.
Okay, so now you're sure
it's vampires?
What the cuss?! A vampire?
I'm a monster.
We gotta deal with this
before I hurt somebody.
The cure is good.
Trickiest thing on the list --
blood of the fang who turned ya.
All right, give me
the damn cure.
- We don't scare them anymore.
- Says who?
Huh!
Now that's what
I'm talkin' about.
Hey.
- Yeah.
- Mmm!
- There we go.
- You betcha.
?
? Look in my eyes ?
? And tell me you... ?
? Love me ?
? Tell me you love me ?
? Or, darling, I'll be gone ?
? Gone, gone, gone ?
Please!
Please, no, no, no!
No, please! No!
? Ooh ?
No! Aah!
?
Card declined.
Please see cashier.
Of course.
If I regard wickedness
in my heart,
the Lord will not hear me.
Psalms --
It's not just poetry.
Hey. Um, excuse me.
Your card thing is broken.
Tried it a couple times,
but it's not working.
Here.
I.D., too.
Hmm.
Hanscum.
That's kinda funny.
Old English.
Kind of reminds me
of soap scum or --
Can I just get $30 on 2?
Why don't you smile some?
You can get whatever
you want, darlin'.
Hmm.
?
Wash your windows?
No, I -- No. No, thanks.
?
Come on.
Hey. Hey!
You suck!
?
Oh!
No. No, no.
No!
? Supernatural 13x11 ?
Breakdown
Original Air Date on January 25, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
?
Yo, makin' pancakes.
How many do you want?
?
Yeah. All right. Yeah.
Ho, ho, ho. There he is.
Saved you a short stack.
Hey, Donna, I'm here with Dean.
I'm gonna put you on speaker.
Uh, why don't you tell him
what you told me?
Oh.
It's my niece.
She's gone missing.
And the local cops don't...
I know it's not
your normal thing,
but...
Text us the address.
We're on our way.
Thank you.
?
Hey, Donna.
Hey.
How you holding up?
Oh, you know...not great.
Yeah.
I'm sorry for calling you guys,
but Jody's got her hands full
with the girls.
Hey, never apologize
for calling us.
So what do we know?
Uh, staties found her car
side of the road.
Signs of a struggle.
And what was she doing
out here?
She was taking a gap year.
It's, like, this thing where --
Take a year off, run wild
before you go to college?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
I used to tell her about how
much fun I had when I did it.
Well, she thought that
sounded like an adventure.
She thought...
Donna, hey.
Whatever happened,
it's not your fault.
That's what Doug keeps
telling me, but...
I can't help
but think --
Just focus on the case.
Doug here?
Yeah, he's in there,
talking to the locals.
I'll go check in.
?
Excuse me! Hey!
What are you doin'?
Oh, I, um...
I asked you a question, son.
First off, I'm not your son.
Second --
Whoa, whoa, easy.
Agent Clegg,
this is Agent Savage, FBI.
Oh. Company man.
Wow, you should've told me.
Well, I didn't get a chance.
Uh-huh.
And what field office
are you out of?
I'm just curious
who I should call
about you walking through
my crime scene.
Mm.
I think we got off on
the wrong foot.
Uh, I'm not here
on official business.
The victim, she's family.
She's my cousin, so I'm just
here to get some answers.
Oh.
I can respect that.
All right, come on,
I'll fill you in.
Yeah.
Sorry.
You and Donna are related?
Yeah.
So you were in Sioux Falls
a couple of weeks ago
at the family reunion.
I was there.
Yeah.
Donna said it was
a pretty wild time.
It was wild. Absolutely.
Ha.
?
Now this is where
we found it.
This is an older stretch
of highway,
mostly used
by long-haul truckers.
There's no patrols
to stop the speeders.
So who found the car?
Troopers got
an anonymous tip.
Well, that's convenient.
Yeah, fits with
the pattern, though.
Pattern?
They think it's part
of something bigger.
And Wendy's not the only one.
We found evidence that suggests
she was targeted
by a serial abductor.
Now that spike we found
on the tire,
that's classic Butterfly.
Sorry. Butterfly?
That's what we call him --
what I call him.
He's got kind of
a migrating pattern.
Now in the winter,
he makes his way southward,
targeting people that are
traveling alone,
people who won't be missed.
Then in the summer,
he turns around
and he heads back up north.
Now what about the victims?
Go on.
They disappear.
We've never even found
a body.
So maybe they aren't,
you know, gone gone.
Maybe.
Look, having you all here is not
standard operating procedure,
but if you wanna help...
Now, I've been chasing
this psycho
for the last 12 years.
I could use all the help
I can get.
?
We're in.
No one uses
CB radios anymore.
All that smokey saw
was my rubbers.
No one except truckers.
Breaker, breaker 1-9,
this is 67,
the Midnight Rider.
Looking for the 4-1-1
on my Alice in Wonderland.
Whoa, ho, Midnight Rider.
Sound like that piece
ran out on you.
She's redhead,
brown sedan. She's family.
Breaker, breaker. Anyone?
Hot diggity.
I'll find your Alice.
- She'll be my family, too.
Not if I get there first.
You see?
Told you.
This is stupid.
It'll work. Dad used it
all the time.
This isn't even
our kind of case.
And you know, with the real Feds
here, we should back down.
You're joking, right?
- We're still fugitives.
- They think we're dead.
Do you really wanna get on
the FBI's radar again?
Okay, so what do you
wanna do? Hmm?
Wanna call up Donna and say,
“Hey, sorry about your niece.
These kinds of things happen.
Later.”
And head back to the bunker
so you can mope some more?
I'm not moping.
You got up at 10:00 a.m.
this morning.
10:00 a.m.
You, Mr. Rise
and Freakin' Shine.
And then you turned down
pancakes.
I wasn't hungry.
They're pancakes. Y--
Look, I know you're in
a dark place right now, okay?
I mean, we lost Jack.
Mom is...
I think about 'em, too.
All the time.
But you can't
let it eat you up.
Now look, when I was --
when I was broken up,
you were there for me.
Well, I'm here for you now.
And I'm telling you, the only
way out of this is through.
Now when everything goes
to hell, what do we do?
We put our heads down
and we do the work.
We'll find Jack.
We'll save Mom, we will.
But right now,
Donna needs our help.
Breaker, breaker, Midnight Rider.
Okay?
Felix the Cat here.
Breaker, breaker,
Midnight Rider.
Felix the Cat here.
I, uh, think I got
somethin' for ya.
10-4, Felix.
What do you got?
Better we talk live and in
color. You mind meeting up?
There's, uh, there's a place
off Gold Rush Byway,
just past mile marker 980.
I'll roll through around noon.
It's a date. Over.
All right.
I'll go check that out
tomorrow.
Why don't you hang back in case
something else breaks?
Okay. Look...
Obviously, I'm here
for Donna, all right?
I wanna help.
I know you do.
So let's find
this son of a bitch.
?
? I'm in love with you ?
? And I'm crazy 'bout
the things you do ?
? You're more to me
than any pot of gold ?
? You make me feel good
deep in my soul ?
Let me go!
Let me go! Let me...
Please. Please.
Please let me go.
Please. Please let me go.
Please. Why?
Why are yo ]
? Oh, sweetheart,
a girl like you ?
What are you...
? And if you ever
depart from me ?
Please, help me.
? I'll live on in misery ?
? I can't believe
that you're for real ?
? Because,
because you give... ?
Help me.
Help me, someone!
Help me, please!
? Whoa ?
Please, help me!
Now we subpoenaed
your niece's credit cards
so we can retrace
her steps.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Uh, what's this?
That is the last 12 years
of my life.
Right there is
every person
we think got taken
by the Butterfly.
Really?
Like I was telling Donna,
the last place
that we can put Wendy
is at a gas station
in Oshkosh, Nebraska.
Now based on
the Butterfly's pattern,
I have a short list
of suspects that I like,
but there's one guy in
particular I've always liked
more than the others.
You ever bring him in?
No. Could never get
anything concrete to link up.
Until now.
You see, that night...
he was there, too.
?
That's your guy?
Pastor “Diamond” Don Hankey.
Road preacher.
Ministers to truckers,
mostly.
Don't let his squeaky clean
act fool you, though.
He's got a jacket.
Arrests for lewd behavior,
couple drunk and disorderlies.
Thank you
for your service, son.
And when we picked him up...
we found this.
That's Wendy's.
?
So this girl of yours...
Mm, you saw her
that night?
Yeah. Twice.
Usually, I-I try to stay out
of this sort of stuff.
I just run my route
and keep out of trouble.
But...
that night, that girl...
Like I said,
I saw her twice --
uh, once at a station
off Highway 26
and then later, I was
driving off Road 88 and...
Hey. Hey!
I shouldn't have
left her there.
But, um, I was running behind
schedule and I just...
Well, it's the only reason
I even gassed up there.
That place
gives me the creeps.
And what's
this place called?
Manny's Truck Stop Cafe.
The other night --
we can put you there.
I go where my ministry
takes me.
You know her?
Her name is Wendy Hanscum.
Recent high school grad.
Popular.
She had her whole life
ahead of her.
No?
What about him?
Luis Fernando.
He had a family.
They're both missing.
The girl looks
vaguely familiar.
I've never laid eyes
on the immigrant.
Wow. Nice.
Okay, let's focus
on the girl, then.
Lawyer.
Excuse me?
I know my rights.
Do you think I give
a tinker's damn
about your rights?
I don't care what you
or your goon think.
I know my rights,
so get me a lawyer. Now.
Then you can ask me
anything you like
about your illegal
and your whore.
Tough guy, huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, hey, hey! Agent, Agent,
Agent, Agent. Agent, please.
Mind if I talk to him?
?
Thanks for coming.
Got that report
you asked for.
Everything that's gone down at
Manny's Truck Stop Cafe lately.
- And?
- Couple of D&Ds,
four counts of
public urination, but...
Nothing that screams
secret hunting ground
for a kidnapper.
Not exactly.
Can I ask you a question?
About Donna?
Okay.
Is she gonna be okay?
I mean, I love Donna,
but I've only known her for
a couple years, and this...
I've never seen her
like this.
I'm not sure what you mean.
I mean, she's barely talkin'
to me, and we always talk.
About the Vikes,
about the Real Housewives,
about everything.
This is a tough time,
I know, but...
I think she's hiding
something from me.
Anyhoo, forget it.
It's probably nothing.
I'm probably just spinning.
It's nothing.
Doug, you're a good guy.
And you're gonna be there
for Donna.
You betcha.
So, you know, just...
trust her.
Okay?
I said I want my lawyer.
You sure?
I mean, the Bible doesn't have
much good to say about them.
“But the Pharisees
and the lawyers
“rejected God's purpose
for themselves,
not having been baptized
by John.”
You know your scripture.
Even the good book's
got lawyer jokes.
I know what you're doin'.
And I want --
Lawyer. Yeah, yeah.
Okay, but here's the thing.
This is a small town.
And it's Friday night.
You know?
So if you're lucky,
they might be able to get you
a public defender by Monday.
Maybe.
Which means you get to spend
at least two nights
in the big cell.
Just you and a bunch of guys
who...
well, look at you
and all they're gonna see
is Sunday dinner.
So...if you wanna deal
with that? Super.
Or...
You can answer
a few questions,
and I can
get you outta here.
Your call.
She's good.
Yeah, she is.
Windows? Oil?
How about a girl?
Have you seen her?
May have.
Mm-hmm.
Keep talking.
She was in
a couple nights ago.
Marlon liked her.
Marlon?
He's the cashier.
After she left, he closed up
early and drove off after her.
Didn't come back till dawn.
Uh-huh.
How long you been
on the road?
Oh, a long time.
Maybe 12 years, you'd say?
Yeah, could be.
You just travel
all over, huh?
Across God's green Earth.
?
You a family man, Pastor?
Married, two kids.
They know about that girl
you flashed outside Cheyenne?
How 'bout that teenage boy
says you picked him up
hitchhiking?
I'm weak.
I am made of flesh.
Oh.
That's your excuse?
God knows I'm a sinner.
And my wife, she knows, too.
We're working through it.
Yeah?
She know about this?
Belongs to my niece.
What did you do with her?
I don't...
That's not...
We found it in your van.
You hurt her, right?
No. No, no, no, no.
You made her bleed.
No.
Don't lie to me.
No, I'm not.
Don't lie to God!
I'm not.
I've done wrong, but I've
never hurt anybody.
Never.
Please,
you have to believe me. Please.
Please.
I believe him.
Yeah, so do I.
But the shirt...
Yeah, the shirt doesn't
make any sense. I mean, what?
I'm -- I'm a criminal mastermind
that avoids capture for 12 years
and when I'm finally arrested,
there's a blood shirt in my van
that links me
to one of the victims?
It's too easy.
So someone planted it.
Definitely possible.
I mean, maybe back at
the truck stop?
But if it's not
the Pastor, who is it?
Where is she?
Mmm.
I don't know.
Dean, what are you --
It's how we do things
in the FBI.
It is?
Try again.
I said I don't --
Look, I know you saw her
and I know you went after her.
So where is she?
You won't believe it.
Try me.
?
What? What's that?
It's like eBay.
Kinda.
No!
They're selling him off.
Piece by piece.
Somebody!
Somebody help me!
Oh, god, please!
Help me!
So it ended
about 30 minutes ago.
Show 'em how it started.
Somebody help me!
Oh, god, please!
Hey, come on.
Help --
Aw. What's the matter?
You vegan?
Ah.
How they do it in the FBI.
Who'd do this,
buy pieces of people?
For what? Trophies?
No. It's for food.
Look at the comments.
“Yum.” “Tasty.”
“Can't wait to get my delivery”"
It's takeout for --
Monsters.
What?
We'll talk about it later.
What's there to talk about?
Where does this
broadcast from?
I don't know. Got me.
- I mean, I don't run the thing.
- I just...
Look, I see someone I think
nobody's gonna miss,
I send a message,
I get paid.
And you feel good about that?
No, but, you know,
like you don't got bills?
Guys, guys, look at this.
Please. If anybody's
watching this...please.
Please help me.
Oh, God.
?
Okay, can you -- can you --
can you hack into it
and find out where she is?
I don't know, Dean.
This feed's on
an encrypted TOR server.
I mean,
this is dark web stuff.
Even if I could crack it,
it would take days.
Okay, well, you got 58 minutes.
I can't do it.
Then who can?
The FBI.
So you're sayin'...
monsters are real?
Pretty much.
Those guys, they're not
related to you, are they?
They're Hunters.
They kill monsters.
And so do I.
Sometimes.
Hey. We gotta roll.
Clegg's got a 20 on that video
feed, and we got 42 minutes.
?
This is it.
You head around back.
we'll take the front.
?
All clear.
You okay hanging back?
Someone's gotta watch him.
Dougie,
we'll figure this out
when we get back
to Stillwater, okay?
Here.
20 minutes. Let's go.
?
- What are you doing here?
- You called me.
I called you for an address,
not for backup.
So you send me a link to
a website that sells people,
you don't expect me
to show up?
Look, I don't know
what the hell's going on here,
but I've been hunting
the Butterfly a long time.
Now I need
to see this through.
All right, follow me.
Lady sheriff's pretty hot.
You two a thing? 'Cause, man,
she is way out of your league.
Shut up.
?
No.
? Yeah ?
Please, please,
just let me go.
Please, you don't have
to do this.
Please!
Please, just let me go.
? Yeah ?
No!
? There's a flame, a flame ?
? A big flame in my heart ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? And believe me
when I say ?
?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? I do ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah ?
? Yeah, oh, ho ?
Hey.
Remember what they said
about monsters?
Fun fact --
I am one.
Vampire, actually.
?
Let's have some fun.
One...
Doug!
What happened? Where's Marlon?
Hold on.
Just hold on. You're gonna
be okay. Where are you hurt?
I'm not hurt, but...
?
I don't think I'm okay.
Oh, Doug. Oh, god.
I'm hungry.
- Okay.
- I'm so hungry.
Aah! Aah!
Doug!
Is he...
A vamp. Yeah.
Oh, god.
Yeah.
The change -- sometimes it's
fast, sometimes it's slow,
just depends
on the person.
I just shot him up with
some Dead Man's Blood.
He should be knocked out
for a while.
Oh, jeez.
He'll be okay.
You call this okay?
Look,
he just got turned, okay?
Which means that
he hasn't fed,
which means that there is a cure.
Huh?
We just need to mix up some
sage, a little bit of garlic --
And you need the bloodsucker
who turned him.
Well, thanks for making it
easy for me.
You never even
saw it comin'.
He got you.
He who?
Clegg, man.
He's got your brother.
Where?
Oh. Wouldn't you like
to know.
Shouldn't have been
so rough with me.
I hold a grudge.
Well...
Bring it, Twilight.
Aah!
You, get his blood
and mix that cure.
And you...
Where's Clegg?
I tell you,
you'll kill me.
Oh, I'm killing ya
either way.
You just gotta decide
if you want it fast or slow.
No, no, no. Get further
back with that.
He's a big boy. We need him on
a wide lens.
You...
You're the Butterfly.
And you're Sam Winchester.
You and your brother are famous.
Hell, soon as I saw that
fancy car, I knew who you were.
And I knew you'd be trouble.
Tried to give you that preacher,
but you saw right through that.
So now it's on to Plan B.
Why are you doing this?
Well, 'cause somebody has to.
How many monsters do you think
are out there, Sam?
You know, if you --
you had to guess.
Hundreds. Thousands.
Ah. Add a zero.
Actually, add two.
See, those freaks that you
and your brother chase,
those are just the ones
that can't pass,
either because they're too mean
or they're too stupid,
or both.
But most monsters...
hell, they could be
your next door neighbor.
They work a regular job,
mow the lawns on
a Saturday.
And they need to eat,
which is where I come in.
So you sell them people.
I sell them people
other people won't miss.
And because I do that,
I save lives.
If my customers didn't
have me...
then all those
hungry, hungry hippos
would be out there
huntin' and killin'.
And you couldn't stop 'em.
No one could.
You should be thanking me.
Huh.
Yeah. All right.
Go to Hell.
Mm.
I'll see you there.
Now I know you've been
stalling because you think
Dean's gonna show up,
but...
Sorry, kid. It's showtime.
?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we interrupt your regularly
scheduled program
to bring you something
truly special --
a new auction.
Introducing...
Mr. Sam Winchester!
?
This...
it's gonna work, right?
It worked on me.
Okay.
There you go.
?
$5,000 for the liver.
Going once...
going twice...
Sold!
And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
let's begin the auction
for Sam Winchester's heart!
?
Wendy!
Aunt Donna?
?
$50,000. Do I have $60,000?
$60,000? $60,000, yes!
Do I have $65,000?
Look at that jump! $100,000!
Folks, there are many pieces
to Sam Winchester...
but only one heart.
Look at that! $500,000!
$500,000 going once...
going twice...
Sold!
?
Usually, we do this
next part kinda slow,
so you can feel it,
but since
Dean's out there...
quick and dirty.
Say goodbye, Sam.
Show's over.
Oh, jeez.
Dougie Bear?
Are you okay?
I...
You feel like you wanna
bite any of us?
Not really.
All right.
Then I guess it worked.
W-Wendy?
She's safe.
She's at a hospital.
She's gonna be fine,
just like you.
- Fine?
- Yeah.
I was a vampire.
For a couple hours.
Listen, Doug...
I know it's been a day.
But now you know what's
out there.
Be nice to have another
good guy on our side.
I...
No.
?
Maybe you all can live
this life,
but I can't.
?
I just wanna go home.
So we'll go home.
And what?
I'm a cop 'cause I like
helpin' folks,
but...
Vampires? That's...
?
I'm not...
Doug.
I'm sorry I lied to you...
but I can't give this up.
I know.
Donna, you kill monsters.
You're a damn hero.
But that's...
It's not me.
?
I'm sorry.
I love you.
- Doug, wait!
- Let him go.
Donna, when you choose
this life,
anyone who gets too close,
eventually, they get hurt,
or worse.
So let him go.
He'll be safer that way.
?
You were a little tough
on Donna back there.
What?
Just sayin'.
Was I wrong?
I mean, when has knowing us
ever worked out for anyone?
I mean,
we save people, Sam.
Yeah, we also
get people killed, Dean.
Kaia, for instance.
She helped us
and she died for it.
Hey, look, I know you're
in some sort of a --
No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
don't -- don't...
You keep saying
I'm in a dark place,
but I'm not, Dean.
Everything I'm saying is
the truth. It's our lives.
And I tried to pretend
it didn't have to be.
I tried to pretend we could
have Mom back and Cass
and -- and help Jack.
But we can't.
This ends
one way for us, Dean.
It ends bloody.
?
It ends bad.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man