This life --
hunting, monsters...
there's no joy in it.
Uhh!
There's nothing but pain...
horror...
and death.
You and your brother
keep coming back.
You're an affront
to the balance of universe,
and you cause disruption
on a global scale.
So the next time
you or your brother bite it,
we're gonna toss you out
into the Empty.
And nothing
comes back from that.
Listen, man...
I'm sorry for being
a dick lately.
Right now, I don't believe
in a damn thing.
I need you to keep the faith
for both of us.
?
You got a full battery?
Yep.
You ready?
Yeah.
?
We're gonna get so many hits.
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
What?
Are you sure about this?
Come on, man.
It'll be awesome.
?
Told you it'd
be unlocked.
Why would they
leave it open?
Who's “they”? Come on. No one
even pretends to own this place,
not after --
Whatever. Don't start.
What, you don't wanna
hear about the guy
who used to cut open
people's skulls?
Sure. Of course he did,
Evan.
No, seriously.
He got arrested.
So if he cuts
your skull open,
will you shut
your stupid mouth?
Why do we have to go
up there?
Uh-oh. Someone's scared.
I'm not scared. I just...
Mike punked out.
At least I showed up.
Good. If you're so brave,
let's look around.
?
Where he kept
his patients.
?
Evan,
I don't like this, man.
Quit your whining.
?
So...Yeah, I'm not going
in there.
Fine. Be a little baby.
Come on, man.
?
Told ya.
This guy was freaky.
Evan.
Come check this out.
?
Holy crap.
Put it in your bag.
What? No.
Dude, nut up.
Fine, just...hurry.
D-- What was that?
Nothing.
It was just a weird, like,
house noise. Or the wind.
Yeah, I'm out.
Shawn, come on, don't be --
Go! Keep moving!
Come on, let's go!
Where's Dr. Meadows?
No! No!
?
? Supernatural 13x05 ?
Advanced Thanatology
Original Air Date on November 9, 2017
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
- Hey.
PB&J for breakfast? Strong work.
Yep.
You want a beer with that?
I'm cool?
Come on. Live a little.
Here.
What's going on with you?
What do you mean?
Anyway, check this out.
I think I found something.
Three days ago,
kid named Shawn Raider
was found wandering
on the side of the road
near Grand Junction, Colorado,
bleeding from the head.
Best friend was missing.
And get this --
only word he said?
“Monster.”
Okay. Well, that sounds
like something.
Yeah. So I thought we'd
check it out, you and me.
What about Jack?
He's, uh, he's catching up
on all my old fantasy DVDs --
“Red Sonia,” “Beast Master,”
uh, “Beast Master II” --
you know, with
the time traveling ferrets.
Yeah. Wow how you ever
got laid, I'll never know.
Yeah,
tell me about it.
So I was thinking
we'd leave Jack behind.
Really?
Yeah. We'll put up some
extra warding. He'll be fine.
I mean, when's the last time
we worked a case,
just you and me?
It's been a while.
Exactly. So?
Here.
Agent Page? I thought you always
liked to be Agent Page.
Yeah, well, changing it up.
Can I help you?
Yeah, sorry to
bother you, ma'am.
Agents Page and Plant. FBI.
We're here to follow up
on the incident with your son.
Well, the police have already
been here.
Shouldn't you talk to them?
We did, but we'd like to speak
with you as well. And Shawn.
Something wrong?
Shawn, he...
he won't talk.
He can't.
What do you mean?
The doctors say...
he's okay physically,
that it's psychological.
- You know, trauma, like he...
- he...
saw some-- saw something
so...awful.
God, I don't even know
what he was doing out that late.
Shawn?
Hey, I'm Dean.
I heard you had
a rough time.
You wanna tell me about it?
?
And, uh, Evan,
he's still missing.
Uh...
He, Shawn, and their friend
Mike Ramos,
they're inseparable.
So has anybody spoken
with Mike?
Everyone.
He says he doesn't know
what happened, but...
But you don't believe him.
Those boys do everything
together. I just...
I just --
I just don't know.
What is that? A monster?
Is this the one
you told the cops about?
You know...
I know what it's like
to see monsters.
And I know that even when
they're gone,
they never really go away.
You see 'em when
you close your eyes.
You see 'em
in your dreams...
But you know what?
Me and my brother?
We're the guys that stop
the monsters.
We're the guys that
scare them.
But you gotta talk to me.
?
So he didn't say anything?
Not a word.
Whatever that kid saw,
it messed him up.
Well, I say we talk
to the other friend, uh, Mike,
first thing in the morning.
Sounds like a plan.
- So, strip club?
- Wait.
Sorry. What?
Mm, s-strip...club.
There's one
just outside of town,
the, uh...
Clamdiver.
You wanna go
to the Clamdiver?
Yeah.
It -- it got great reviews.
You read reviews
for the Clamdiver?
It -- it -- it got
four and a half --
Dude, what is going on
with you?
What are you talking about?
All day.
You give me a-a beer
for breakfast.
You -- you gave me Agent Page,
which you always like to be.
You -- you didn't whine about me
blaring my music the whole way here.
And when we stopped for lunch,
you ordered me chili fries.
You love chili fries.
Everybody loves chili fries.
That's not the point.
Now you wanna go hang out
at a strip club?
You hate strip clubs.
No, I don't.
Dude, the last lap dance you had
was -- was -- was at Christmas.
It was a gift
paid for by me.
You spent the entire song
trying to convince the girl
that she should go to
nursing school.
So what is it?
It is my birthday?
Did -- did I win a bet that
I don't know about? What?
No, nothing. Nothing. I-I mean,
I'm just trying to be nice.
-Why?
- Because...
You know why.
I'm fine.
No, you're not, Dean.
You said you don't believe
in anything,
and -- and that's...
that's not true. That's not you.
You -- you -- you do
believe in things.
You do believe in people.
That's who you are.
That's what you do.
I know you're in a dark place,
and I-I just wanna help.
Okay.
Look, I-I've been down
this road before.
and fought my way back.
I will fight my way back
again.
How?
Same way I always do --
bullets, bacon, and booze.
A lotta booze.
Shawn!
It's okay.
It's okay, baby.
Just a bad dream.
?
Try to get some sleep,
all right?
Okay.
That's good.
?
Great.
So...you don't know where
Shawn went that night?
No. I already told the cops.
Right. Of course.
But problem is,
when something bad happens,
we have to triple-check.
Anyway,
I wasn't with them.
“Them”
You weren't with them.
So Shawn was with somebody.
Maybe your friend Evan?
I don't know.
You know, I'd like
to believe you, Mike.
but, um...
here's the thing.
You ever see those
detective shows where,
whenever somebody lies, they
dart their eyes to the side?
That's a real thing?
Oh, yeah.
So if there's anything that
you forgot to tell the police,
I need you to tell me.
Mike.
Evan could be
in serious danger.
He's not.
He's just hiding out
somewhere.
Evan is always
pulling crap like this.
It's just a prank.
Okay, so what happened to Shawn,
that's just a prank, too?
They, um, they were going to
the old Meadows place,
out on Night Hawk Drive.
Okay. How come?
Evan dared us to go, and...
it was stupid and creepy,
and I didn't...
I-I got scared.
But Evan, Shawn...
they're gonna be okay, right?
Hangover raid on the
continental breakfast?
Shh.
What?
First of all,
it's complimentary.
Second of all, what happened
to being nice to me?
You are forgiven.
So I talked to
the other friend -- uh, Mike.
And I think I got something.
Look at this.
Meet Dr. Avery Meadows.
He worked here back in
the early '60s.
Uh, people would come to him
for help with mental illness.
But no matter what the had --
depression, anxiety, whatever --
the cure was always the same.
He lobotomized them.
Mm. Fun.
Yeah. Those that lived,
he kept as “patients.”
And he would experiment
on them in his house,
which is exactly where
Evan and Shawn
were heading that night.
That's where Shawn got freaked
out and where Evan went missing?
Worth a shot.
I mean, when people found out
what Meadows was doing,
he was tried and executed.
But who knows? You know,
maybe he made a demon deal.
Or maybe he wasn't even human
to begin with.
This here? That's what Shawn
was drawing over and over.
Really?
Yeah.
What's up with
the creep-ass mask?
It's a plague mask.
Doctors used to use them.
They thought
they filtered out disease.
As a matter of fact,
when they arrested Meadows,
he was wearing one.
They had to hold him down
to rip it off.
Oh, man.
Hello?
Penny. What happened?
I don't know.
Shawn had a bad dream.
I checked on him. I...
It seemed -- seemed like
he was getting better.
I went back to my room,
but it got a little cold,
so I thought
Shawn must have opened a window.
But when I came back in
to close it,
he was just...gone.
?
This is on me, man.
I saw how messed up Shawn was.
I should've pushed him
harder.
We don't know he's dead,
all right.
Penny said it got cold,
so could be a ghost.
Yeah, but what's a ghost doing,
showing up at a kid's place?
It's not like Shawn was
dragging a body around.
According to the reports,
Meadows was cremated.
So maybe his spirit is tied
to something else, an object...
So, what, Shawn took something
from the house?
It's possible.
All right,
where's the kid now?
Well, Meadows “treated”
the victims at his house.
So if this is him,
maybe that's where
he took Shawn.
?
Shawn?
Shawn, you in here?
Oh, dude.
Check this out.
Definitely a ghost.
Sam.
What's up, Doc?
?
Uhh!
Thanks.
Yeah.
?
Shawn?
The mask.
You said they practically had to
tear it off of him, right?
Yeah.
So if he's tied to
something...
I'm gonna take that
as a “yes.”
Door. Salt. Burn 'em!
All of 'em?
Yeah!
?
- No.
- We ain't got much time.
Hurry!
You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Let's go find Shawn.
Yeah.
?
Dean? Wait.
I can still see your breath.
What the hell, dude?
I think it might be
another ghost.
I think there's a lot.
Let's go! Go!
We need
a doctor! We need a doctor!
Where's the doctor?
They're asking for the doc.
These must be
the people he killed.
Well, if they're ghosts,
then why can't we see them?
Maybe they're not strong enough
to pierce the Veil.
Yeah, but they're strong enough
to kill us?!
Great.
You know what?
Those bodies have gotta be buried
in the house somewhere.
Okay, so we check it,
top to bottom.
There's no time.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna find out where
these bodies are buried.
So?
So I'm gonna ask 'em.
What? How?
Easy.
One needle stops the heart,
the other one
starts it up again.
No, no, no.
Look, we can't talk to 'em
on this side of the Veil,
so I'm gonna go
to the other side.
I'm gonna work my way through
all these Caspers
until we find out where
this freak hid the bodies.
Dean, you're talking about
killing yourself.
Yeah? Well, it worked before.
That's an insane risk
to take.
Listen, I need three minutes.
Okay?
D-don't even...Dean!
?
Dean?
Aah!
Hey.
Damn it.
Hey, hey, hey.
Dean? Dean!
?
Hey! Ghost dude!
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, wait up, pal.
Hello,
my name is Jessica
and I'm here to lead you
to your next life.
Yeah, hi. Dean.
Little busy right now. Yo!
Oh, God.
?
Dean Winchester is
in the Veil!
?
Come on, Dean.
Come on.
Hey.
Hey. Wait up.
Hey. Hey, do you, uh...
Oh, come on.
I know you.
Shawn.
You're the FBI man
from my house.
You're dead, too?
I, uh...
Yeah.
What happened to you?
The man with the drill.
He was in my room.
?
The Doc -- he possessed
you and he killed you.
I-I-I couldn't stop him.
He said I'd feel better,
but...
I just...
I miss my mom.
Shawn, I should've...
I'm so sorry.
Evan's here, too.
We can't leave.
We...
Why can't we leave?
Stupid.
I know you're scared, okay?
But I'm gonna help you.
I'm gonna help you
get out of here.
Help me get home?
Help you go
to a better place.
But I need you to tell me...
The doc, where did he put
your body?
Sam? Sam, I got it!
Let's do this.
All right.
Come on, come on,
come on.
Dean.
Dean?
Hey! Dean!
Why is it not working?
No, no. No, no, no, no.
Dean!
Hey. Can you hear me?
Dean.
Dean!
Dean! Hey, wake up.
Hey, Dean.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey! Hey, Dean. Wake up.
Billie.
We need to talk.
Hey. Hey! Wake up, Dean.
And...
Wake up.
That's enough of that.
Hey!
No, I saw Cass kill you.
How's that working out
for him?
It's funny
to hear a Winchester
talk about
the finality of dying.
This reality --
it has rules, Dean.
So many rules.
And one of them?
Kill one incarnation of Death,
like you did,
the next Reaper to die
takes his place.
So...
when Castiel stabbed me
in the back,
turns out...
I got a promotion.
New job. New gear.
So you died
to become Death?
This universe can be
so many things,
and sometimes, it is poetic.
That's why we need to talk.
?
The hell?
Welcome to my reading room.
?
Know not to leave this lying
around near you. Don't we?
So...am I dead?
You killed yourself.
No.
Are you keeping me dead?
Now that depends on you.
Okay. Uh...
Well, congrats
on the promotion.
Uh, but I got a house
full of ghosts waiting on me
and my brother to get back to,
so if it's up to me --
I didn't say it was
up to you.
I said it depends on you.
Word on
the interdimensional street
is you've been slipping
between worlds, Dean.
I wanna know how you did it.
Now.
Well, I thought Death
knew everything.
Then you can imagine how
this one little blind spot
is really bothering me.
What's in it for me?
What do you want?
Free the ghosts.
Excuse me?
Free the ghosts
at the Meadows house.
Let them move on, I'll tell you
whatever you wanna know.
Deal.
?
Come with me.
You don't have to stay here.
It's going to be okay.
?
It's done.
How do I know I can
trust you?
You don't.
But then again, I'm not the one
breaking cosmic bargains
left and right, now, am I?
Yeah, it's not
like you hold a grudge.
Don't I?
So...spill.
Lucifer's son. Jack.
When he was born,
it created a little rip.
“A little rip”?
Mm.
Into another world?
And you went there?
Mm.
Yeah, I'll just say it's, uh,
it's not Candy Land.
I'll bet.
Why do you care?
Because I do.
Because...
this whole multi-versal
quantum construct we live in,
it's like a house of cards.
And the last thing I need
is some big, dumb Winchester
knocking it all down.
Hmm.
That does sound like us.
You've changed.
When you bargained with me
just now,
you could've asked
to go back, to live.
Well, I figure
with you in charge,
there's no getting back
for me.
That doesn't sound like
the Dean Winchester I know and love.
The man who's been dead
so many times
but it never seemed
to stick.
Maybe you're not that guy
anymore,
the guy
who saves the world,
the guy who always thinks
he'll win
no matter what.
You have changed.
And you tell people
it's not a big deal.
You tell people
you'll work through it,
but you know you won't,
you can't,
and that scares the hell
out of you.
Or...am I wrong?
What do you want me to say?
Doesn't matter.
I don't matter.
Don't you?
I couldn't save Mom.
I couldn't save Cass.
I can't even save
a scared little kid.
Sam keeps trying to fix it,
but I just keep
dragging him down.
So I'm not gonna beg.
Okay, if it's my time,
it's my time.
You really believe that.
You wanna die.
Dean...
every notebook
on this particular shelf
tells a version of
how you die.
You specifically --
heart attack,
burned by
a red-haired witch,
stabbed by a ghoul
in a graveyard,
and on and on.
?
But which one's right?
That depends on you,
on the choices you make.
Well, I guess I made
my choice.
But...
unfortunately,
none of these books say
you die today.
Come again?
Since I got this...
new job,
I stand witness to
a much larger picture.
Do you know what I see?
You.
And your brother.
You're important.
Why?
You have work to do.
That's all you need to know.
And trust me,
having my eyes opened to
the necessity of any humans,
especially Winchesters,
is not a thrill.
So...you wanna die,
but I say...
keep living.
Hmm.
?
I need to know. My mom --
Hey. You're okay.
Yeah.
You're okay.
How'd it go?
About how you'd figure.
Hey, what happened
back there?
I mean,
the shot didn't work
and all of a sudden,
you're back.
I don't know. I guess it took a minute
for the drug to kick in.
I guess I got lucky.
Lucky?
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
Hold -- Dean. Hold on a second.
What about the ghosts?
'Cause I checked the EMF.
They're all gone.
Was that lucky, too?
We can talk about it later.
We won't talk about it later.
You know that.
I saw Death.
The Death.
He's dead.
No, she's not.
It's Billie.
I guess she got a new gig.
She's the one that
took care of the ghosts.
W-why would she help us?
She wanted Intel.
She said that we're important,
that we have work to do.
What the hell
does that mean?
I have no friggin' clue.
?
You okay?
No.
Sam, I'm not okay.
I'm pretty far from okay.
You know, my whole life,
I always believed that
what we do was important.
No matter what the cost,
no matter who we lost,
whether it was Dad or --
or Bobby or...
And I would take the hit.
But I kept on fighting
because I believed
that we were making the world
a better place.
And now Mom and Cass...
And I-I don't know.
I don't know.
So now you don't
believe anymore.
I just need a win.
I just need a damn win.
?
? Your eyes are moist,
you scream and shout ?
? As though you were
a man possessed ?
? From deep inside
comes rushing forth ?
? All the anguish
you suppressed ?
? Upon your wall
hangs your degree ?
? Your parents craved
so much for you ?
? And though you're trained
to make your mark ?
? You still don't quite know
what to do ?
? It's never too late
to start all over again ?
? To love the people
you caused the pain ?
? And help them
learn your name ?
? Oh, no, not too late ?
? It's never too late
to start all over again ?
? You say you've only got
one life to live ?
? And when you're dead
you're gone ?
Yeah.
? “You left us alone” ?
What?
?
? Tell me who's to say
after all is done ?
? And you're finally gone,
you won't be back again ?
? You can find a way
to change today ?
? You don't have to wait
till then ?
? It's never too late
to start all over again ?
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man