I'm gonna devote myself
to finding Jack.
We combine our powers,
remake the world in my image.
Before he crushed my skull,
Lucifer showed me
his true face.
I've seen it, too.
[ Screams ]
[ Whispers ]
I'm scared, Sam.
I don't suppose you guys have
any more of my grace.
The tank's a little low.
It'll recharge, eventually.
Whatever we didn't use on you,
we used to open up a rift.
Mom and the kid, they're not
with Michael anymore.
[ Gasps, grunts ]
We must assemble
our most powerful allies
- But before you answer, Lucifer is back.
- Mm.
- Wait, you're actually gonna help us?
- Yeah, no tricks?
Mmm!
Tricks are for kids.
Dean, we're going to
that place
and we're gonna save
Jack and Mom, together.
And if we die?
We'll do that together, too.
? ?
Dean, you can't possibly
eat another.
That's your seventh piece.
No, it's not.
Castiel's right. I counted.
Okay, first,
don't be a narc.
And secondly, seven pieces
is perfectly normal.
Uh, it's really not.
It's not even a whole pie.
[ Laughs ]
Was he always like this?
Even as a baby.
John and me, we used to call him
our little piglet.
[ Mouth full ]
All right, I'm done.
With love.
Mm.
Thanks, Mom.
You know what? Let me help you.
[ Clears throat ]
Hey, Mom, um,
how you holding up?
You haven't really said much
since you got back, you know --
h-how you're doing,
how it was over there and...
It was hard.
But somehow,
I always knew that you...
you and Dean --
would come and save us.
And you did.
Mom?
Yes, Sam?
Sam? Sam?
Mom?
Sam?
[ Beep ]
Sam? Sam?
[ Gasps, exhales sharply ]
[ Alarm beeping ]
[ Turns off alarm ]
[ Groans ]
[ Sighs ]
Rowena: Fruit from
the Tree of Life.
Blood of a most holy man.
Dean.
Rowena: And, uh...
Ow.
“Something from the other side”"
Hey. How's Gabriel?
He said he needed
a minute alone.
He wanted to extract his grace
by himself.
“In private.”
So I left him alone
in Dean's room.
What? No.
I hate to interrupt,
but I can't be the only one
who's noticed
the rather glaring hole
in this plan.
We open up the rift,
it gives us a day
to find and save
your mom and the boy.
And it's a very big world
over there,
and you're not even sure
where they are, so...
She's right. The clock
may run out on us.
Yeah. It might.
[ Gun cocks ]
Yeah, well, we don't have
any better ideas.
Mm, that's inspirational.
Here it is!
The final ingredient --
a fresh serving
of archangel grace.
[ Vial clatters ]
This is what you call
a serving?
That is the jet fuel
of divine emissions.
It'll be more than enough
to get the job done.
? ?
[ High-pitched ringing ]
Koth Munto Nuntox!
? ?
Okay, everyone ready?
Yeah, all right.
Let's do this.
? ?
[ Music warping,
electricity fizzling ]
[ Crackling ]
Okay.
Well, that was...fast.
Very, very fast.
One could even say
premature.
Um...
I thought it would be enough.
Sam: All right, great.
What do we do now?
Hell if I know.
You do know.
We all do.
We need archangel grace.
Gabriel's obviously
running a little low,
and we don't know how long
it'll take him to recover.
So that leaves exactly
one source on Earth.
No.
I don't like it either,
but there is no other way.
? ?
We need Lucifer.
? Supernatural 13x21 ?
Beat the Devil
Original Air Date on May 3, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
It's all I want.
It's all I can think about.
But we've been down
this road before.
Teaming up
with Lucifer --
We're not teaming up
with him.
We just need his grace.
Oh, “just”.
We've trapped his ass
before.
Yes, and every time,
it ends up the same way,
with the Devil being
on the loose again.
Look, Sam,
I was used by Lucifer, too.
It was the worst possible
violation.
So I-I'm not taking
your reluctance lightly,
but he is already out there,
and we've been ignoring it
and avoiding dealing with him
because we're afraid.
We let Lucifer out of the Cage,
and he has never stopped being
our responsibility.
It's not always like that.
Gabriel, please.
? ?
Just 'cause I take
a little extra time to recover.
I don't need to hear
your excuses.
It doesn't make me any less
of an archangel.
Mm, right.
You know,
it could've been you...
Uh?
...who screwed up that spell.
Just sayin'.
I heard your, uh,
magical unbinding didn't take,
that you got
knocked back down a peg.
Maybe it's you who are
off your game.
A drunk 6-year-old
could execute that magic.
It wasn't the spellcaster
or the spell.
It was the ingredient.
? ?
Think they'll be
much longer?
The Three Amigos?
With their bro hugs,
pep talks, and melodrama?
Count on it.
[ Romantic music playing ]
[ Thinking ]
Quite a tidy, wee tush
he's got going on there.
Sort of...cute.
Mm.
? ?
[ Thinking ] Oh, she's so...
so tiny, so angry.
That milky white skin,
dancer's body.
God, I bet she's flexib--
? ?
So...we've a little time.
How would you like
to fill it?
? ?
To fill what?
I know a thing or two about
wounded masculine pride.
? ?
So?
No, you're right.
You're right. I don't like it,
but it's our only choice.
Another fun, great choice.
Well, hey, bright side is,
even if we do pull it off,
we still only get 24 hours
in the Apocalypse World.
And Rowena's right.
We'll be lucky to even
hear a word of Mom and Jack,
much less save 'em, so...
[ Tongue clicks ]
Wait a second.
What?
Guys?
Rowena: Whoo! Ooh!
[ Gasps ] Oh!
Uh...
We were just...
Reading. Books.
Here in the, uh, library.
Which is the room we're in
right now.
Did you boys arrive
at a...
decision?
Sam has a plan.
? ?
Harry Chapin: ? My child
arrived just the other day ?
? He came to the world
in the usual way ?
? But there were planes
to catch ?
Keep 'em comin', pal.
Keep 'em comin'.
That's some tolerance
you got there.
? And he was talking
'fore I knew it ? [ Sighs ]
Yeah, it's more like
a curse.
Believe it or not,
I'm barely even buzzed.
Still, that can't be good
for you.
[ Mutters, laughs ]
Who cares?
You know, I had Heaven and Hell
in the palm of my hand.
And you know what I learned?
They don't matter.
Nothing matters.
Okay.
You know what? All this time,
there was one thing
that mattered.
? My son turned 10
just the other day ?
? He said,
“Thanks for the ball, Dad” ?
?  “Come on, let's play” ?
I had a son.
? “Not today,
I got a lot to do” ? [ Sighs ]
You know, I used to
be able to sense him.
You know,
feel him in the world.
Ever since I've been down here,
I can't -- I can't feel him.
It's like he dropped off
the face of the Earth.
Not that finding him
would change anything.
His bitch of a mother
poisoned him against me,
probably forever.
Sorry to hear that.
But I'm sure things
will work out in the end.
Jack will come around.
? But we'll get together then ?
? You know we'll have
a good time then ?
? ?
Jack?
I never told you his name.
You didn't?
Nah. Didn't.
Ah, I swear that you did.
[ High-pitched voice ]
Ah, I swear that I didn't.
? “I'm so proud of you” ?
Who are you, pal?
[ Barstool clatters ]
? “What I'd really like, Dad,
is to borrow the car keys” ?
What's the matter, buddy?
You did something to me.
Yeah.
Kinda spiked your drink.
Think of it
as a magical roofie --
powerful enough to
bring down any archangel,
even me.
? You know we'll have
a good time then ?
? ?
Hey, brother.
Aah!
? ?
[ Grunts ]
I killed you.
Surprise.
Ugh.
? I've long since retired,
and my son's moved aw-- ?
? ?
? I said, “I'd like to see you
if you don't mind” ?
? He said, “I'd love to, Dad,
if I could find the time” ?
Welcome back.
Whoa.
? “But it's sure nice
talking to you, Dad” ?
? “It's been sure nice
talking to you” ?
Okay.
What in the hell did you
put in that drink, man?
White sage,
a little burdock,
a pinch of salt.
? My boy was just like me ?
Very simple ingredients
for a very potent spell.
[ Laughing ] I...
I killed you, too.
? I don't know when ?
Bye.
Adligetur fera!
Ah!
? ?
[ Groans ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Okay. [ Inhales deeply ]
[ Song ends ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Crying ]
Well, okay, do it.
[ Sniffles ]
Put me out my misery. Go ahead.
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
? ?
He's awake.
Oh, hey, Sam.
? ?
Oh, look at this.
All the people I love to torture
in the same room.
What's the occasion, guys?
? ?
Ah. Okay, I think I see
what's going on.
You're planning a trip
to save Mother Mary,
and you need my grace.
Is that about it?
Good guess.
[ Groans ]
[ High-pitched ringing ]
? ?
Okay, you could've done this
back at the bar.
Could've drained me,
killed me.
What's this really about?
Humiliation? Revenge?
Ah, those are just bonuses.
See, we got a lot of work to do
back in Apocalypse World,
but not a whole lot of time
to do it.
So I realized something.
I realized we could use you.
Koth Munto Nuntox!
? ?
Use you not to just
crack the door open,
but to keep it open.
So we're gonna drain you.
We're gonna keep on
draining you.
Like a stuck pig.
Grace on tap.
Sorry, bro.
And then,
when we get back,
then we'll kill you.
Cool.
You gonna be okay
back here?
Aye. Someone needs to keep
an eye on the Devil.
Go. Save your mum.
You ready?
? ?
Ready.
[ Sam and Castiel grunt ]
Gabriel: Ow!
[ Dean grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Panting ]
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Oh, boy. [ Grunts ]
Yeah.
Well, that was...fun.
I could've used a heads up
about this landing site.
Yeah.
Thought we'd get spit out
in the same spot,
but this isn't it.
All right, well, Charlie --
the other Charlie --
said that Mary and Jack
have an outpost in Dayton.
Okay. Let's get our bearings
and head that way.
Cass, where are we?
Uh, Kentucky.
Northeast Kentucky.
Or what used to be Kentucky.
Which means that's north.
Okay, so Dayton's that way.
Roughly.
Two days by foot, but...
that way.
After you.
- Dean: Let's go.
- Sam: All right.
? ?
I don't know, Red.
I think I'd be a tad insulted
if I were you.
It's not like you have
the posh job here
of babysitting me.
I mean, there is a sort of
old-fashioned rightness to it,
if you think about it.
The men going off
to face the trials
and glories of war.
Woman staying home
in the kitchen,
where she belongs.
I know you're trying
to bait me
with your seeming
Neanderthal misogyny.
Anything to distract yourself
from your profound,
deeply emasculating
humiliation.
Mm. Sorry, Lucille,
I'm not biting.
Okay.
? Oh... ?
? The Camptown ladies
sing this song ?
? Doo-dah, Doo-dah ?
? The Camptown racetrack's
five miles long ?
? Oh, doo-dah day ?
? Goin' to run all night! ?
? Goin' to run all day! ?
? I bet my money
on the bob-tailed nag! ?
? Somebody bet on the gray! ?
[ Thunder rumbling,
rain falling ]
? ?
Have you, uh, have you thought
about what's next,
after we get back to Earth?
Uh, yeah, not so much,
seeing as we still gotta
find Jack and Mary.
Ah, not to mention
survive Michael
and his super angel army.
Right.
Although, I did tick off
some, uh,
bucket list items recently.
Got some revenge.
Had sex with
a 300-year-old redhead.
But what's next for me?
I don't really know.
This world is, um,
is obviously glutted
with angels,
But back home in our world,
you know,
it's -- it's just Naomi
and a handful of others.
They're trying to keep
the lights on,
but Heaven's dying,
Gabriel.
Are you serious?
Very.
And you think I could
fix it?
Gosh. I skipped out
on Heaven, Castiel.
They wouldn't want me back.
As far as they're concerned,
I'm a screwup.
Hell, as far as I'm concerned,
Well, Heaven's been run into
the ground by upstanding angels.
Perhaps a screwup is just
the change we need.
? ?
[ Thunderclap ]
Dean: You seem different
since we got here.
Sam: Really?
Yeah, like you're...
lighter,
happier, more energetic.
I don't know.
Maybe it's just, you know,
Mom and Jack and... [ Sighs ]
You know, I mean, we've been
working at it so hard
for this for so long,
and now we're finally here.
We're close.
Can't you feel it?
? ?
[ Woman screams ]
[ Man screams ]
? ?
Not our world,
not our problem.
Right?
? ?
[ Hisses, growls ]
Maggie, run!
[ Screeches ]
[ Screams ]
[ Growls ]
Aah!
[ Screeches ]
[ Slices ]
[ Thud ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Thunder rumbling ]
What the hell was
that thing?
What do you mean?
A vampire.
It's not like any vamp
we've ever seen.
Who are you?
I'm Sam. Uh, Dean,
Gabriel, and Cass.
We, uh --
We're not from around here.
Tell me, what makes
a bloodsucker look like that?
Starvation.
When Michael's armies started
to wipe out the humans,
they didn't think about monsters
or what happened to 'em
when their food source
dried up.
Turns out, not eating
makes them wild.
Nothing but pure,
stupid appetite.
Which way you headed?
North.
To Dayton?
[ Exhales ] We were going
that way, too.
We'd heard the rebels,
Jack and Mary,
set up a satellite colony there,
an outpost.
Wait. What do you mean
you were?
Me, Floyd,
the rest of our group,
we were crossing north
through the Morehead Tunnel...
? ?
stumbled into a whole nest
of those things.
? ?
Nine of us went in.
Only me and Maggie
came out.
? ?
This tunnel,
is it the only way north?
There's a mountain pass,
but it's a long way around.
Tunnel's the quickest route.
If the long way
is the safe way...
No. We're already two days out
from Dayton as it is.
We don't have time
for a detour.
Listen, we've faced worse
than a nest of vamps before.
Much worse.
So if you still wanna
get to Dayton,
we'll keep you safe.
As far as we're concerned,
we're going through
that tunnel.
? ?
?  ...dah day! I bet my money
on the bob-tailed nag! ?
? Somebody bet on the gray! ?
One more time! [ Laughing ]
Hey, come on, Red.
I'm just trying to have
a good time with you.
Like last time.
You remember that?
When I surprised you
at your hotel room?
? ?
Oh. I mean, I even wanted you
to put up a fight.
I wanted a little bit
of a tussle,
but... [ Sighs ]
you froze.
You choked.
So I choked ya.
What was that like,
burning to death?
? ?
You know, I can't get
that smell out of my nose,
that...
ashy reek of burnt up ginger!
[ Laughs ]
- Shut your mouth!
- Oh!
You want to get inside my head,
twist the knife?
Two can play that game.
Do you know what your grace
is making possible right now?
The heartfelt family reunion
of Sam, Dean, Cass, Mary,
and your very own son Jack.
That's right.
Your wee boy's over there,
and he'll be so glad to see
his three fathers.
Of course, as far as he's
concerned, they are his father.
And you?
You're nothing to him.
Or me.
? ?
Or anyone now.
Nothing.
? ?
[ Gasping loudly ] Aw, Red, you shouldn't
have made me mad.
Step into my office.
[ Choking ]
[ Thud ]
[ Sniffs ] You know...
[ Whoosh ]
you and Gabe, you kicked me
when I was down.
I didn't have any fight.
I didn't have anything to live for.
[ Gasping ]
But you, you,
you gave me something
to fight for again.
My boy.
So for that,
that I'm gonna be quick.
[ Grunts ] Defendatur!
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ High-pitched ringing
continues ]
? ?
Bollocks.
Fine.
This isn't how you wanted
things to work out,
but yes, Rowena, thanks to you,
Sam and Dean'll be trapped in
some sort of nightmare universe
with the Devil himself.
And you're the only person
who might be able
to devise a way to keep the door
back home open for them.
But... [ Sighs ]
Sorry, boys.
Au revoir, bon voyage,
not my problem.
? ?
Bollocks!
Bums bollocks.
[ Thunderclap ]
You good?
What do you think?
Second time's a charm,
right?
Sam:
All right, here's the plan.
Stay close, keep walking.
Anything moves, kill it.
Let's do this.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
[ Metal door clanks ]
? ?
[ Metal rattles ]
[ Thunder rumbling ]
? ?
[ Thud ]
Floyd: Aah!
[ Screams, pants ]
Sorry.
Tripped.
Ugh!
? ?
[ Low snarling ]
[ Chewing sounds ]
Sam: Wait, wait, wait.
Here. Let me.
[ Chewing continues ]
? ?
[ Growls, snarls ]
[ Hisses ]
[ Slices, thud ]
? ?
[ Water dripping in distance ]
[ Screeches ]
[ Screaming ]
Maggie! Maggie!
[ Vampire growling ]
[ Blade clanks ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Maggie panting ]
[ Snarling ]
You all right?
Mm-hmm.
Let's keep moving.
[ Rustling in distance ]
[ Dripping continues ]
[ Wind whistling ]
Hey. We got a blocked passage
over here.
Need to move some rocks.
[ Rustling ]
[ Rocks clinking, thudding ]
Guys?
[ Low growling ]
Sam: Dean?
[ Growls, screeches ]
- Aah! Aah!
- Floyd?
[ Growling ]
Aah! Maggie, help!
Aah!
[ Screeches ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Thud ]
I got it. I got it.
- [ Growling ]
- [ Floyd shouting ]
[ Maggie screaming ]
? ?
[ Grunting ]
[ Continues screaming ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Snarling ]
? ?
Oh!
[ Snarling ]
[ Groans ]
Sammy!
[ Snarls ]
Dean!
[ Grunts ] Sam!
[ Gasps, groans ]
[ Growls ]
[ Gasping ] Dean.
? ?
Castiel: Sam!
[ Grunting ]
[ Slices ]
[ Growls ]
Aah!
[ Gunshot ]
[ Thud ]
Castiel: Sam!
Sammy!
[ Growling in distance ]
? ?
Dean. Dean.
What?
He's gone.
No!
Dean!
[ Shouts ]
We don't have time.
[ Breathes shakily ]
? ?
Dean, we can't save him.
Aah! [ Groans ]
[ Grunts ] Dean!
Dean?
Um, about your friend,
I'm so s--
? ?
[ Metal squeaking ]
Maggie: We must be
getting close to Dayton.
[ Castiel grunts ]
On the outskirts at least. [ Groans ]
I-I-I can't.
This...this warding is
too strong.
[ Grunts ]
? ?
[ Thunder rumbling ]
[ Grunts, exhales deeply ]
[ Gun cocks ]
Whoa.
[ Cocks gun ]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. We're --
we're not here to fight.
[ Gun cocks ]
We're just looking for...
Mary.
Castiel.
? ?
How did you even find us?
[ Gasps ]
? ?
Dean...
where's Sam?
? ?
[ Metal continues squeaking ]
[ Gasps, grunts ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Boo!
[ Gasps ]
[ Laughs ] Hey, Sammy.
No.
Yeah. [ Sighs ]
I mean, you could do
the whole pinch yourself,
rub your eyes thing,
or you could put on
your big boy pants
and just, you know,
cut right
to the realization
that yep, it's me.
Y-you -- you...
? ?
You brought me back.
I did.
You're welcome.
Why?
Oh, well,
I'm getting to that.
[ Gasps ] The rift.
The rift. Rowena.
Oh, she's okay.
I mean,
I-I was gonna kill her,
but she blasted me here before
I had a chance to, so...
It's great, self-defense.
But, uh, I was
coming here anyway.
But we drained you.
So how did I have the juice
to pull off
my little Lazarus trick?
Uh, that's a long story,
but I was basically
tracking you here,
and then I came across
a handful of Michael's angels
and I...
ate 'em.
I guess it's not really
a long story, is it?
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want what everyone wants.
I want a personal apology
from Pop.
I want rerun-free, year-round
episodes of “Drag Race”.
Yeah, got it. Okay, right.
We're done here.
Are you going?
Here.
It's dark out there.
[ Button clicks ]
[ Growling ]
Yeah, they're sorta...
sorta all over there,
and I'm holding them back.
They're just waiting for
a little snap of the fingers,
but I didn't want 'em flooding
in here and eatin' ya again,
not until after
we finished our convo.
[ Growling continues ]
What do you want?!
? ?
I want
what you already have --
a relationship with my son.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Okay, there was a time
that I would,
you know,
just grab him, but...
I've grown.
Yeah, sure you have.
I have, Samuel.
I want my son,
and you're gonna help me.
How?
Well, I don't feel like
he'll give me a chance
unless I come bearing gifts.
Yep. Boop!
That's you.
Look, Sammy,
I'm -- I'm not asking you
to -- to like it
or to like me.
All I'm asking is that
you acknowledge the truth,
that I was the one who
brought you back to life,
that I was the one who lifted
you from the darkness
and into the light.
Okay?
? ?
Apocalypse World,
Michael's armies --
you really think
you and your family
can handle that stuff alone?
You need me.
? ?
And what if I say no?
[ Clears throat ] All right,
let me just make this
really,
really, really easy --
easy enough for even you
to understand, Sammy.
I'm gettin' to Jack
one way or the other.
The only question is,
you coming with?
Or that?
[ Growling continues ]
? ?
Your move, champ.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
? ?
No, he can't be dead.
He can't be dead.
Jack, I --
Couldn't you bring him back?
[ Stammers ]
Why didn't you bring him back?
I'm not strong enough.
Jack...
If we could've, we would've.
I'm so sorry.
? ?
We have to go back,
get his body.
? ?
[ Bell dinging ]
Sam.
? ?
[ Sinister music playing ]
Hello, son.
? ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man