Allow me to make
an introduction.
Mr. Ketch, meet
the archangel Gabriel.
Mom's trapped
in another reality.
We need it, the spell,
to open the rift.
We stealth in,
we get Mom, we get Jack.
Boom. Family reunion.
I understand you may need
an archangel for a spell.
Let's do this.
- Ah.
- Whew.
Well...here we are.
Yeah.
You do know where we are,
don't you?
Because, not to be a nag,
but we've only got 24 hours before...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just give me --
give me a minute.
...the rift closes.
Look, we just got spin-cycled
through space and time, okay?
And yes, this is...
different than
my last drop-by.
And what's
this “we” crap, hmm?
You came here
to save yourself, so...
go save yourself
somewhere else.
Well, actually,
I thought I could help.
What?
Find the boy.
And your...mother.
She's in danger.
I owe her that.
You know, she sees you, she'll
probably kill you. Again.
Perhaps, but you don't know
where you are
or what's out there
or even...
You get the picture.
Would having a little bit
of backup really be so bad?
Well, this is quite
the vacation spot, isn't it?
Yeah. If you had your heart
set on Mai tais,
well...sorry.
Hmm.
Down. Down.
Down. Down. Down.
Is this everyone?
Yes, Commander.
For high crimes
of fomenting rebellion
against the archangel Michael,
these humans shall be executed.
Freakin' angels.
Not smart.
No.
Wait.
Charlie?
? Supernatural 13x18 ?
Bring 'em Back Alive
Original Air Date on April
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I know you.
You're not the usual
human scum.
Not the slickest hook-up line,
Captain Charm.
You're with the Resistance.
Inner circle.
She's met with the nephilim
and the other-worlder, Mary.
Michael will want her
at the Northern Camp,
for interrogation.
Champ, when the Resistance
crushes you,
I'm gonna be there
to shred your feathers
and grind them into dust.
Dean...
Looking forward to it.
Dean is in Apocalypse World,
alone?
No, he's with Ketch,
so he's not alone.
Because that makes it better.
Cass,
wanted to go solo.
- And you let him?
- I...
He didn't give me much of
a choice. Anyways, Dean's right.
As long as he's over there,
and we're here,
we need to be
taking care of Gabriel,
getting him right again.
Gabriel? Yeah.
You didn't tell me
it was this bad.
Yeah, well, years
of isolation and torture
and Asmodeus
draining his grace.
Come here. Help me out.
Hey, Gabriel.
Hey, pal.
- Mm!
- Okay. Oh -- Just...
Gonna get ya to bed,
all right?
- Let me, uh, help you up.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Gabriel, it's Sam Winchester.
Do you remember me?
I don't think he does.
Remember the video you sent
to my brother Dean Winchester
and me
after you...supposedly died?
You told us how to stuff Lucifer
back in the Cage.
Sam, he doesn't...
I know he doesn't.
I'm just...
trying to see if anything's
going on in his head.
All right, well...
Gabriel's grace.
Ketch brought it.
Maybe if he's juiced up,
it'll help.
All right.
Mnh.
Sam, I don't think
he's gonna open up
and let the choo-choo in.
A technique for feeding
recalcitrant children. And...
I think a little coercion
may be necessary.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Hey! Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa whoa!
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Where've you been?
Out.
Right. Out.
Look, Jo, uh, you got
a pretty sweet deal going here,
so you might wanna...
I don't know, pitch in,
drop the attitude,
stay by my side.
Play strip poker?
Shouldn't you be out
doing...kingly things?
Commanding the angels,
inspiring mankind?
Stuff?
I'm here, aren't I?
On the throne,
available to be worshipped.
We came here to change things,
make Heaven better,
help the angels...
Dumah.
Perfect timing. Okay,
I have a question for you,
and I want you to be straight
with me. Okay?
Don't you think Jo
should show a little bit
more enthusiasm for being...
for want of a better word,
First Lady?
Pull her weight?
Little bit?
Keep me happy?
Couples issues aren't my area.
So that's a “yes.” Okay?
So you're here with
breaking news about my son. Go.
The few angels that we could
spare are scanning the planet,
but so far, nothing.
Yeah, well, he's a priority,
so...
We don't have the manpower.
He's a priority.
Of course.
Wow.
They would never treat
my old man that way.
Ever.
If he said, “Scour the Earth,”
they'd say, “S.O.S. or Brillo?”
Yeah, well, you're not him.
Your father created.
You inherited.
Yeah? Well, I'm the one
on the throne right now,
and y'all are gonna treat me
that way, okay?
Uh-huh.
Well, before all of us
start treating you like God,
you might try acting
like God.
Just a thought.
This is unacceptable.
Ketch, who's wily, possible
he could fly under the radar.
But the archangel?
The archangel.
I should at least
detect a blip.
We're connected.
You might say
we're blood brothers.
Get.
What's the hold-up?
Oh, just practicing stealth.
You know, the art
of infiltrating
a hostile
and unfamiliar environment
whilst remaining
undetected.
Hence, “free.”
Hence, “effective”"
You, I see, prefer the bull in
a china shop technique.
No, I prefer
the “let's find Charlie
before the angels turn her
inside-out” technique.
Remind me again why
we're risking everything
to find this girl?
Because she's seen my mom.
She's seen Jack. We need her.
And you're sure that's
what this is about?
You're sure it's not...
personal?
We're running out of time.
Let's pick up the pace.
Ketch?
Come on.
Aah!
Oh, you're a strong one!
Angels'll pay double for you.
Most of the slaves
is a might scrawny.
Aah!
Where were you going to take him?
You do want to live, yes?
You heard him.
Where were you gonna take me?
You think I'm gonna tell you?
Aah!
Let try that again.
The silo.
What silo?!
P.O.W. camp.
Four, five hours from here.
Follow the road.
Okay. Thanks.
Sam!
What is this? Is --
Did he do this?
Enochian?
It's his story.
Starts with his death.
Or...what appeared
to be his death.
“Per usual, my brother had
double my brawn
“and half my brains.
“He assumed the counterfeit me
“was what vanished that night,
and he thought that
he'd stabbed the real thing.”
“The truth is,
“the thing Luci skewered
was a fake.
There are plenty of fakes
to go around.”
“Everyone believed
Gabriel was gone.
“And suddenly, I was free.
“No obligation
to God or Heaven,
“or mankind.
“And so I did
what anyone would do --
“I moved to Monte Carlo
and shacked up with
porn stars.”
Well, y--
He goes on and on for quite
a while about porn stars
and, uh...
Cass, please.
Okay, so Gabriel was captured,
delivered to Asmodeus.
“For years, I knew nothing
but endless torture.”
“Asmodeus, once the weakest
of Hell's princes, grew strong
by feeding on my grace.”
Well, obviously,
his intellect is intact.
Yeah. So why isn't he
talking to us?
I don't know.
Maybe he can't.
Or maybe
he's choosing not to.
Maybe he thinks it's safer
that way.
Ready or not, world,
New God is open for bidness.
All right, children...
I shall hear your prayers.
- Dear God...
- God, if you're listening...
Please, God...
Unbelievable. Losers.
Whining.
I can't believe Pop put up
with it as long as he did.
...if you could give me
a sign? I could really use...
Let's begin the exorcism.
Vade retro Satana!
Nunquam suade nobis vana!
Sunt mala quae libas.
Ipse venena bibas!
Cessa decipere humanas creaturas...
eisque aeternae
perditionis venenum propinare!
Most glorious
Prince of the Heavenly armies,
Saint Michael the Archangel,
defend us!
Don't get
holier-than-thou with me, Father Davis.
You and your camgirl
addiction.
Begone, Satan!
You shall no more dare
to deceive the human race!
Okay, fellas.
Fellas?
Oh, crap.
Okay, first of all, chill.
Couple things, guys.
Not Satan.
Minor player.
Total nobody,
gettin' a day rate.
Anthony...
what are you doing, man?
Just having a little fun.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Beat it.
Get outta here!
Don't come back!
You're welcome.
Who are you?
I'm Lucifer.
No.
Yeah.
Lucifer is the beast!
The scourge of mankind!
Whoa. Ho.
Ouch.
Yeah, gotta hand it to
the old man. Perfect marketing.
Okay, little known factoid --
Pop made me into the fall guy.
He made me into
the all-purpose villain.
It's sort of worked out okay
because I'm...
sort of running Heaven
right now.
Blasphemy!
- In the holy authority...
- It's a new suit, thank you very much.
...they driven
before the fire...
Whoa!
...so the wicked perish --
Relax.
...and deceits of the Devil!
Aah!
Damn it.
That Hunter
may've been a bumpkin,
but his weaponry is
cutting-edge.
These I don't even recognize.
Yeah, that's...
Angel-killing bullets.
Might wanna hang on
to those.
Mm.
Ah.
You don't look good.
Yeah, well, you're not
my type, either. I'm fine.
We'll take a break.
Your wound may be more serious
than we thought.
Aw, he barely hit me. Come on,
we don't have time for this.
Eh, by all means.
What was it with you and this
Earthly “Charlie,” anyway?
Old girlfriend?
Let me guess --
she broke your heart.
Dean.
Oh, God, you're burning up.
Let's take a look at that wound.
- No, no, I'm fine. We gotta keep moving.
- Do shut up. Huh?
How's it look, Mom?
I must reiterate --
it's not possible
for an angel to heal
an archangel.
I'm just trying to jolt his mind
into thinking straight.
Even then, Sam...
Gabriel...it's --
it's possible that he's lost.
Taro root,
trace of arsenic...
basidiomycota...
and...
Why don't you just skip
the birdseed,
give me the flask?
Your shortness of breath
and delirium
are symptoms of a poison
the Men of Letters use
to disable monsters
in the field.
- Of course it is.
- My guess is that the bounty hunter
used a similar toxin
to coat his bullets
to hobble his prey...
at first.
What do you mean,
“at first”?
Well, if -- if the antidote
isn't administered,
then the victim dies
a particularly gruesome death.
You guys are such dicks.
Yes. Well...
guilty.
Now then...
this will smart.
There we are.
Good lad.
Here we go,
just a little more.
Right?
There we are.
Gabriel, you have to dig
yourself out of this hole.
Look, I know you think
it's safer inside.
No more torture. No more pain.
No more expectations.
I've been there. You were
nothing like your family.
You sure as hell weren't
like your dad. Me either.
And just like you,
I got out.
Or I-I thought I got out.
But then...
then my family needed me.
And this is my life.
No matter how many times
I tried to fight it,
this is what
I was put here to do.
This is where I make the world
a better place.
And sure, yeah, hookers
in Monte Carlo sounds great,
but your family needs you.
Jack, your nephew,
needs you.
The world needs you.
We need you.
Gabriel, I need you.
So, please, help us.
Porn stars.
They were porn stars, Sam.
There you are.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay. okay.
This is absurd.
You must rest.
Okay, look...
I-I'll give you that...
anti-poison
merit badge award, okay?
I do appreciate it, but...
we're running out of time.
So...
How about you rest?
I'm gonna keep going.
In five minutes.
Good plan.
Perhaps we can use this moment
to revisit the Charlie issue.
Not gonna happen.
To your point, we are
running out of time.
We don't know where
your mother and Jack are.
We don't even know
if we'll find this Charlie.
And if we do, a rescue
may be impossible
and stupid.
I propose we return home,
regroup, reinforce ourselves,
and we may have a shot
at saving everyone.
All right, look,
I'm gonna...
repeat myself.
Charlie's not gonna give
the angels what they want.
Your Charlie wouldn't.
They're gonna kill her,
100%,
and I'm not...
What?
What's the story
you're not telling me?
Charlie was like family.
She was a sister to me.
She did more for me and Sam
than I can even say.
And she was...
she was butchered.
And we couldn't
get there in time,
and I...
You feel you failed her.
I know I did.
That, I understand.
Uh, hello?
What about your story
you're not telling me?
Oh, I've had
many failures...
friends and colleagues
who have died on my watch.
Only difference is,
I didn't...
try to save them.
“Duty” and all that...
rubbish.
Well, you do suck.
What the hell?
Perhaps rescuing this Charlie
will wash some of the stain
off my hands.
“Impossible and stupid,” huh?
You say that
like it's a bad thing.
Come on.
One more time.
The location and number of
bases the Resistance holds.
One more time --
bite me.
You're trying my patience.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'll try harder.
Bite me!
Aah!
This is pointless.
She dies.
Is it helping?
I...I don't know.
Hello.
Samuel.
I hope you're having
a pleasant day.
It's come to my attention
you boys have something
belongs to me,
and I'd like it back.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh, I believe you do.
And I'm-a give you one chance
to return him to me.
No harm, no foul.
I'm hanging up.
Do not hang up on me.
Gabriel is of no use to you
in his current condition.
Should you choose to resist me,
I will have no choice
but to take him by force.
I will reduce you
and that sad little bunker
of yours to ashes.
You got 10 minutes to decide.
Now you can hang up.
Nothing in this universe
is worth my time or talent.
Nothing.
Humans, angels...
all flawed beyond redemption.
Lucifer...
It's all because
of Pop's little...
propaganda machine, spewing
poison about me for centuries.
Done.
So you're just giving up?
No.
No, I'm gonna refocus.
I've come to realize the key
to finding my bliss
is fatherhood.
You.
Yeah.
It's obvious, right?
I just...I devote myself
to finding Jack.
We're gonna combine
our powers.
I'll remake the world
in my image,
with pathetic little people
who worship me.
Me. Me.
Love that good plan.
Awesome plan.
Finding your bliss?
Yeah?
So humans don't like you.
Oh, wow. I'm sorry.
Instead of bellyaching about it,
why don't you make Heaven right?
Make good on your promises.
Make angels.
Give the existing ones
their wings back.
Yeah, I-I can't really
do that.
What?
I lied, so, uh,
just keep that to yourself,
though, okay?
So you know --
It's not the humans.
It's not the angels.
It's not your father's
propaganda that's killing you.
It's your complete failure.
You say you want to find
your son, but you don't.
Not really.
So you sit there
because you're afraid.
You're afraid of him, afraid
of looking into in his eyes
and seeing nothing
but contempt.
You can't replace your father.
You can't create anything.
You have nothing.
You might as well go back
to the Cage.
And now you don't have me.
“Silo.” No, he wasn't kidding.
Gratifying.
Now what?
The Resistance
will be broken.
It is being broken.
One by one, your leaders are
being rooted out and destroyed.
Soon, there'll be
none of you left.
No! No!
No!
“For high crimes,
“the prisoner
Charlie Bradbury,
“like all traitors
before her,
will be executed”"
All hail Michael.
We gotta
get you outta here.
Who the Hell are you?
No time!
We gotta go now! Go!
All right, I did what I could
to help the bunker's warding,
but who knows if
it's enough.
How's he?
I don't know.
Thanks.
Your warding wasn't designed
for the likes of me, Samuel.
I've come to claim
what's mine.
Oh, I missed you, boy.
I'm-a have to punish you
rather severely, I'm afraid.
And as for you two...
Aah!
Gabriel!
What are you doin', son?
You know too well
what I can do to you.
I broke you!
You're too weak!
Not anymore.
Oh, by the way,
I always hated
that dumbass suit.
So to recap,
there's another world,
a “better” world,
with no Michael,
and it has another me?
Well, had.
And you were friends
with her. Me? Her?
Yes. Very.
How very?
Well, she was into chicks.
Oh.
I like her.
Look, I know this is
a lot of information,
everything I'm telling you,
okay, but...
we're running out
of time here.
I need to know where
the nephilim is -- Jack.
And -- and my mom's
with him, right?
Your mom?
Yes. She's from our world, too.
Uh...Last I heard,
they were fighting somewhere
in what remains of
Dayton, Ohio, but I don't...
Wait. Your mom?
Yeah.
Why would I believe
any of this?
Because of that.
Wow.
Whoa.
Too much information.
Okay, slow down.
I'm not...processing.
And there's more.
Michael wants to come to
this Earth and destroy it,
and we may need your help
to fight him.
What?
Yeah.
Welcome to the team.
Uh...yeah.
Not so much.
I mean, thank you for the rescue
and for the redemption arc.
But, uh, I'm not really
a team guy,
so...I'm gonna bounce, okay?
Um, but, you know,
it's been, um...
What's the opposite of fun?
That.
No, Gabriel, don't -- you --
you can't just walk away.
If Michael comes here,
he will end this world.
And the last time the world was
ending, I put my money on you.
I think you can
pull it off again.
No.
You cannot turn your back
on your father's creation.
Castiel...
my father turned
his back on his creation.
Guess it just runs
in the family.
No, Gabriel, please.
Okay. The thing's gonna
be closed any minute.
We gotta get a go.
Dean, you need to go through.
Bring back Sam
and your angel and Gabriel
and the bloody Navy SEALs,
whatever help you can get.
But I should stay.
Wait. What?
If we're going up against
Michael, we need to be ready.
We need to know what he's up to,
where your mother and Jack are.
I'm staying, too.
Are you kidding?
You got Michael and a billion
angels on your ass.
Dude, this is my home.
My friends are here
and they're in trouble.
If you really do have a way
to take down Michael,
get back here and do it.
Until then,
this is my fight.
I don't wanna lose you
again.
That's not your call.
Dean, it's closing.
Go!
Dean!
Dean! Hey! Hey.
Hey.
You're hurt.
No, no. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Hey, the -- the --
the rift, it's...
Where's Mom? Where's Jack?
Long story --
so Mom and the kid,
they're not
with Michael anymore.
Ketch and Charlie are staying
back to try to find them.
There's a Charlie over there.
She kicks ass.
T-- Uh, Charlie...Bradbury?
Yeah.
What's this?
What -- what...
What'd I miss?
There was a demon incursion,
led by Asmodeus.
Sorry,
Asmodeus got in here?
Yeah, and -- and --
and Gabriel killed him.
Gabriel? That's great.
So he's back.
Where is he?
He just left.
What do you mean, he left?
Um...
We asked Gabriel
to help us, and then...
then he said “no”"
He doesn't get to
say “no.”
We still have his grace,
though, right?
Sam?
Uh, we -- we used his grace
to -- to heal him.
So it -- it's gone.
It's all gone.
So if it's gone,
then that means
that we can't open
that door again.
If we can't open the door, then
I should've never come back!
Son of a bitch!
Every time!
Every time we get close,
it always falls apart.
Every freakin' time.
Dean...
we will find Gabriel.
We will.
We better.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man