We must assemble
our most powerful allies
to rescue our family and
confront the archangel Michael.
Mom and the kid, they're
not with Michael anymore.
Dean, we're going to
that place.
We're gonna save
Jack and Mom, together.
And if we die,
we'll do that together, too.
- We need archangel grace.
- No.
I don't like it either,
but there is no other way.
We need Lucifer.
- Hey, brother.
- Aah!
Bye!
Adligetur fera!
We got a lot of work to do
back in Apocalypse World,
and not a whole lot of time
to do it.
We could use you, not to
just crack the door open,
but to keep it open.
So we're gonna drain you,
and we're gonna
keep on draining you.
When we get back,
then we'll kill you.
Cool.
Ow!
Aw, Red, you shouldn't have
made me mad.
Step into my office.
Defendatur!
Bollocks.
Which way you headed?
North.
To Dayton? We'd heard
the rebels, Jack and Mary,
set up a satellite colony there,
an outpost.
We were crossing north
through the Morehead Tunnel.
This tunnel,
is it the only way north?
Tunnel's the quickest route.
- No!
- Sammy!
Dean!
Sam!
Dean. Dean.
What?
He's gone.
Dean, we can't save him.
Boo! Hey, Sammy.
You brought me back.
I did.
- Why?
- I want what you already have --
a relationship with my son.
And you're gonna help me.
And what if I say no?
You coming with? Or that?
Your move, champ.
Sam?
What happened?
He, uh...
he brought me back.
It's what I do.
It is not what you...
How did you get in here?
VIP pass.
I'm with the band.
Come on, shouldn't you
be thanking me?
I-I give Sammy an extra life.
Besides, what with my...
little bro here being
a hot mess,
I figured you'd need me.
So I'm here to join the team.
Your name is Jack.
And yours is Lucifer.
No. No, no. No.
You don't talk to him.
And you, don't listen to him.
Um, don't you think that's
his choice?
No.
Are you trying to keep me
from my son?
Well, this is
Kelly Kline's son.
He's nothing like you.
Don't say
he's nothing like me.
I'm the only one
who understands him.
This power he has?
I'm powerful,
dangerous, ruthless.
In the...best sense, though.
No. Kill him.
He can't.
He's not strong enough.
Dean...
- You've got the blade!
- Stop it.
He's the Devil! Kill him!
Stop it!
? Supernatural 13x22 ?
Exodus
Original Air Date on May 10, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Well, great.
Does that when he's scared.
Way to go, “Dad”!
I'll go look for him.
I don't know understand
all the hostility.
You...need...me.
I am a walking weapon.
I know this Michael.
Heck, I beat him.
So how 'bout
a little R-E-S-P-E-C-T?
Hmm.
In case your innate evil
overwhelms
this newfound team spirit,
you won't mind
wearing these then, will you?
You're not at full power.
They should hold you.
Slap 'em on.
So if you're here,
is the rift closed?
No, it's open.
I left Rowena some grace.
So you have...
I'm thinkin'...
31 hours, give or take?
Hey. Listen, I'm sorry
about all this.
Are you good?
I'm alive. Yeah.
Well, then you got nothing
to apologize for.
I thought I'd lost you, man.
What are we gonna do
about Lucifer?
I'll handle him.
I will, Dean. Let me handle him.
Okay.
Hi, Jack. I'm your mom.
I daydream about...my baby,
you.
I wish I could see you grow up.
No one would blame you
if one day,
you look for your dad.”
Jack, don't let anyone tell you
who you're supposed to be.
You are who you choose to be.
Maybe not worth all this.
Your mom thought you were.
So did Cass.
So do I.
Aah! Uhh!
Why are you being
so nice to me?
Because I know what
it feels like
to feel like
you don't belong.
No!
I'm sorry.
Don't!
Hey, mama.
Miss me?
Uhh!
- That's a yes?
- Let's go!
Nice shot.
Yeah. No kidding.
Hey, um, we really should
go look for Jack
and get back home
before it's too late.
I, uh...Boys, um...
About that...
I'm not going back.
I'm sorry. What?
I fought beside these people.
I respect them.
I respect their cause.
You can't expect me
to just abandon them.
No, Mom, that's not --
You heard what Lucifer said.
We have 31 hours --
I -- Sam...
Dean...
I know what you went through
to come find me.
But these people
are being slaughtered.
They need me here.
No, we need you, Mom.
We do.
Come on, Cass, old sport.
I am not your sport,
and I will not broker
a relationship
between you and your --
Speak of the Not Devil.
Son.
It's Jack.
Jack, talking with Lucifer,
it's -- it's not a good idea.
I'm not gonna talk.
I'm gonna listen.
He's gonna listen.
We have been mopping up
the world for years. Years.
We have been knocked down.
We've been possessed.
We've lost friends. We've lost
family. We've lost each other.
And we never walk away,
ever.
And sometimes, we should've,
because not every fight
everywhere can be won.
It just can't.
Right? Tell her.
I think Mom made up her mind.
See?
Wait. What?
Mom doesn't want to leave
these people.
So let's take 'em with us.
They'll never leave their home.
They'll never leave their cause.
I'm not saying
abandon the fight.
I'm saying we get them
somewhere safe,
then we all figure out a way
to take down Michael.
Then once we do, they can
come back and save their world.
You'd do that for them?
Well, we got...What, nine
busting out? What's a few more?
How many are we talking?
25.
Jack...
Wow.
I have been waiting for
this moment for so long,
I almost don't know
what to say.
This...this dad thing is
sort of new to me.
So, um...
Do -- do you have any questions
that you wanna ask?
Don't let my status
as a legend hold you back.
Now just...fire away.
Why does everyone hate you?
Huh.
Wow, he just got right to
the -- right to the point.
That's good. That's good.
Good question.
Um...
So you've, uh, probably
heard the stories. Right?
Anything ugly happens,
any evil befalls the world,
it's my fault.
Fake news.
And that's not entirely tr--
Well, I mean,
yes, I have done things
that I am not
entirely proud of.
I have led the occasional soul
to ruin. This is true.
But, Jack, it's because
humans are so messed up.
They're -- they're
so willing to be led.
My mother was human.
Awesome lady. Incorruptible.
Not like that.
You know, great kisser.
And, uh, lost
my virginity to her.
No? Too soon?
I mean, the point is...
humans are not perfect.
They are hardwired to fall.
And when they do,
they need a fall guy.
That's a vast
oversimplification.
Okay, true or false,
Cass --
Um, for almost,
like, ever,
I've been locked away
in a Cage?
Yes.
True! It's true.
So how did I do
all this evil
for all these centuries,
I wonder?
Who locked you up?
My dad,
'cause I told the truth.
See, he loved humans so much,
he couldn't see their flaws.
And I told him about it,
and he got mad.
He got --
He felt like I was...
personally dumping on
his masterpiece,
and so he kicked me out.
No time-out,
no “go in the corner”,
you know,
anything like that.
Just...gone, banished.
And yes, as Cass says,
I have done some bad things.
I had my reasons,
and I just want
the opportunity to
get better.
Doesn't everybody?
Don't you?
Okay, well, getting
an extra 25 through that rift,
that may not be possible.
Cass, hey.
Any update on Jack?
- He's back.
- Great. Where is he?
He's with Lucifer.
So I want you to
think about this.
Your Grandfather is God.
Think about that --
Of all the powerful families
in history...
Forget the Tudors, Trumps,
Jackson Five.
We're numero uno.
What's he like? God?
Hey! Hey!
Well --
I told you no talking!
And I told you no listening.
Dean, he's in chains.
His mouth isn't.
Shoulda gagged him.
No, I need to know about
my powers, my family.
Jack, we are your family.
We've been protecting you.
We've been honoring
your mother's wishes.
We're your family.
Jack, you have no idea
who Lucifer really is.
And I never will
unless I talk to him.
Jack...
Dean!
He's my father.
We should reach base camp
in a couple of hours.
Sam, go back there
and check out
what Helter Skelter's sayin'
to the damn kid.
Yep.
Take it easy on Jack.
He's been fighting a war.
He's trying so hard
to prove himself, but...
he's lost people, friends.
He'll take a minute to
get through it.
I was just telling my dad that
now that he's here,
we have enough power
to kill Michael.
Jack, that's not really
the plan.
But...
this is our chance.
Dean, like it or not,
Lucifer is Jack's father.
He's going to take
an interest in him.
So what, we're supposed
to just let Lucifer
drag him over
to the dark side?
Jack isn't going to
the dark side.
He'll see
Lucifer's true nature.
And he'll see it
through his own eyes,
not yours.
Hey. Find him?
No.
Gabriel went ahead to scout,
but he should be back by now.
- Angels!
- Hey, right there!
Ho! Guns up!
Kill them, on my command.
Oh, yeah, about the cuffs --
I knew they wouldn't hold me
in this world.
Long story short, I didn't want
your impotence to get awkward,
so I just went along.
You're welcome. Welcome.
Right?
Don't...thank me at once.
See? Team player.
Creeps me out. You know?
Yeah, but it's no Sioux Falls.
Why should it look like
Sioux falls?
Uh, just our, uh, our Bobby
back in our world, he, um...
He liked to freeze his ass off
every winter?
Yeah, well, this Bobby's
gonna pass on that.
Anyhow, it's good
to see you boys again.
I knew you couldn't
stay away.
Yeah.
You know where we can
find Charlie? Or Ketch?
Oh, they ain't back yet.
They got a tip
on an angel kill squad
lookin' to execute
some, uh, resistance.
They went to head 'em off
at the pass.
You let Charlie go with Ketch?
She let Ketch come with her.
It's her operation.
Bobby, we're gonna
have to hit the road soon.
We're running out of time.
Now about that.
Mary said you wanna take
a bunch of our people
back to this “Other Earth?”
Yeah. Yeah, that's the idea.
Well, no offense,
but that may be
the dumbest friggin' idea
in a landfill of dumb ideas.
So there's Michael,
your other uncle.
Sort of a studly type.
You know, warrior guy.
I met Michael here.
He tortured me.
Same.
We owe him one, right?
High five.
Right here. Yeah.
That's your Uncle Gabe.
We sort of met.
Let's go say hi.
So...
thing about Gabe --
class clown.
And you're an assclown.
Ha! You hear that?
He's such cut-up.
I mean, I can't...
Yeah, uh, I guess your time
with Asmodeus
didn't do you any favors,
did it, bud?
Well, my time with you
was worse.
- You recall --
- I recall, uh, nothing.
I don't recall anything at all.
Happy endings.
All good, happy ending.
Uh, meet Gabriel, your uncle.
Hello.
So I was just shaking up
the old family tree
for, uh, young Jack here.
You know, talking about
the good old days.
How tough Pop was.
Right, G?
I mean, we -- we butted heads
a lot, you know.
But, uh...
you know, I think -- I think,
in hindsight,
I should've given him
some slack 'cause, he's, uh...
You know,
being a dad is tough.
Okay, you think dad was
a “bad guy,”
and you were a victim?
You were not a victim.
That was just your excuse.
My excuse for what?
For it all, Lucifer.
For it all.
For high crimes
against the realm
and its exalted ruler, Michael,
the prisoner is
condemned to death.
That will do.
Easy.
We're gonna take you outta here.
No, you aren't.
Drop the gun.
You're coming with us.
So let me get this straight.
You want us to follow you
through a magic door
that's gonna blast us
the hell outta here
and into some kind of
Fairy Tale World
where everything's pretty?
Okay, that -- that's not exactly
what I -- what I was
t-trying to say, but...
Andy, look, I get that
you don't know my sons,
but you do know me.
That world does exist.
Hear them out.
No one here is runnin' out
on our buddies,
runnin' out on the fight.
Nobody's saying “run out”"
Guys, don't know if you've
noticed, but you're losing.
Okay? You're outmanned.
You're outgunned.
My brother and I...
back home, we're sitting on
the biggest collection
of lore and -- and weapons
in our world.
Now something in there,
it -- it might be enough
to even the odds.
So we find that, then you
come back here with a plan,
a plan to beat Michael
and his armies.
And then you win.
Exactly.
You may think you don't know us,
but you do.
We've been where you are.
Hell, we are you.
We'll talk to our people,
take a vote.
That's all we ask you.
Thank you.
Just got news about
Charlie and Ketch.
Goin' after the execution squad
went sideways.
They're the ones who got
ambushed.
Where did they hear about
this execution?
Aah!
Let's try this again,
shall we?
Aah!
How many fighters
do you have?
Where's your battalion
based?
Are you familiar with
a place called Boardwalk?
No.
Well, it's very near
Park Place.
Go to Oriental Avenue
and take the B&O Railroad
straight to Hell.
Mmm. Mmm.
Is that all you've got
to make me talk?
I've sent for an expert
in these matters.
No talking will be required.
Good evening, Castiel!
Welcome.
What do you want from me?
I didn't do nothing.
We're thinking you did.
Did you tell Charlie and Ketch
about the angel kill squad?
I...
Yeah.
So you set 'em up.
I don't know what
you're talkin' about.
Aah!
You wanna try that again?
This is stupid.
Dean said to stay behind.
Any angels show up,
we gotta defend this place.
It is really killing you,
you're not out there
impressing your kid, huh?
Lucifer, do you really see
a version here
where he sticks by you?
I think the kid
is pretty blown away
by the old man, so...
Yeah. I do.
He's a kid.
He likes shiny objects
and magic tricks.
But he's not like you.
I can see it in his eyes.
His mother's bloodline,
the Winchesters' influence...
I can be an influence.
Ugh.
He's not gonna want that.
He'll see who...
what you are.
I've changed.
Dude, it's me.
I've known you since
the stars were made.
You can't change.
You're incapable of empathy
or love.
You live to be worshipped
or feared. Or both.
Okay. I-I see that you've --
you've drunk the Kool-Aid.
Fine.
Oh, is this the part
where you tell me
that, uh, Dad made up all those
so-called lies about you?
Got it.
Yeah!
Yeah, Pop locked me up, okay?
Don't you get it?
Humans were innocent
and beautiful.
But you...
you couldn't stand
that the old man loved them
more than he loved you.
So you tempted them
and you corrupted them
just to prove
how flawed they were.
You better be careful, man.
Dad saw that your evil
was like the first few
cells of cancer...
that it would spread like
the disease
unless He cut it out.
That is why
he locked you up,
to stop the cancer.
But it was too late then.
And guess what?
It's too late for you now.
We've been studying you.
Pure steel.
I haven't seen many
like you.
But...
But you have to understand
that everyone
has a breaking point.
A...point of pain.
Particular
primitive fear, maybe.
But it's a nerve
so...raw
that your will doesn't
exist to be factors.
And then
all your little secrets,
they flow from your mind
to mine...
until your mind
no longer exists.
Secure the area!
Aah!
More than one of us.
Fascinating.
I've gotten used to it.
I gotcha. Yeah.
Sorry.
Well, hello.
You actually saving me?
It's about bloody time.
You align yourself with
the h-humans.
I vastly prefer them
to angels.
Don't think that you are
better than me.
Well, we are the same.
Yes.
We are.
- Bobby.
- Good work.
Good work.
Got a win. Don't get many
these days.
Real proud of you boys.
And got some news.
We took a vote,
see who was idjit enough
to go off to
this “Other Earth” with you.
Yeah? Any takers?
Everyone.
I...
Me included.
Whatever reason, I got
a good feeling about you two.
Great.
Hey.
All right, Dean, that's great.
How in the hell we gonna
do this?
I mean, we only have
a few hours left, and --
Yeah. No, I know.
I-I have no...
Bobby? Tell me about the bus.
You're gonna
let Lucifer drive?
This way,
we know what he's doing,
and Cass
can keep an eye on him.
We're running out of time.
Hey, guys, we're down
to 1 hour, 57 minutes.
Yeah.
All right.
Jack? Jack.
Hey. Where you headed?
Hold up.
Before I go, there's
something I have to do,
something I promised myself
I'd do.
Kill Michael.
Jack, you -- you can't --
Look, we have to...
We have to get
these people to the rift.
We'll -- we'll seal Michael up
and leave him here.
No.
Look, I've seen what he's done,
the people he's killed.
He deserves to be punished.
Yeah, I got this.
See, I think what --
what Sam is trying to say
in his own...
super simplistic and silly way,
is maybe you should
give this a-a rethink.
I mean, I know
I've been encouraging you
to take Michael out,
but it ain't easy.
I tried it.
And if he catches you,
then we're all gonna
have to waste a lot of time
trying to rescue you, and...
that puts pretty much everyone
in danger.
Look, I know you feel like
you're doing the right thing,
but sometimes, doing
the right thing can go wrong.
My father makes a valid point.
Father.
Good boy. Wanna come?
Let's do this.
Come on.
Kids.
I mean, you just gotta --
you gotta know how to talk
to 'em. You know what I mean?
It's closing.
We're running out of time!
Come on!
Oh.
Koth Munto Nuntox.
Oh, hell, yeah.
How's that possible?
Lucifer! Let's go!
Let's go. Come on.
Hey, come on!
Cass, Ketch,
show 'em how its done.
Follow me!
Mom, Bobby.
Charlie, you're with them.
See you on the other side,
bitches.
- Huh.
- Hmm.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold up.
What? I-I wanna be
with my son.
We need you and Gabriel here
in case something goes wrong.
Wasn't that the whole point
of you being on the team?
Rowena.
About bloody time!
Koth Munto Nuntox!
- All right, let's go.
- Come on. Come on.
Let's go. Single file.
Gentlemen.
Lu.
You don't really wanna
try this again, do ya?
Um...
Yeah.
Can it be?
Gabriel?
Go. I can buy some time.
Gabriel, don't.
All I did on Earth was run.
I'm not running anymore.
Go!
- Gabe! No!
- No!
Go. Go!
Sam, what are you doing, man?
I'm hurt.
Please.
How did you think
this was gonna end?
No. No!
No!
It kept closing. I couldn't keep
it open another five seconds.
Well, you did it, Rowena.
You got us all here.
We owe you one.
Don't think I won't collect.
Gabe -- he'd been
on the run for so long...
He sacrificed himself.
He's the reason
Sam and me got out.
We owe him everything.
What about Lucifer?
Sam handled it.
All right, listen up.
We made it.
Don't know much about
this place,
but it's a place
without Michael,
so that's a turn for the better.
I don't want none of you
going' soft on me
because we are gonna
get ourselves ready
and go back home
and set our people free.
Yeah!
He's been here for five minutes.
Look who's taken over the joint.
While we celebrating, let's not
forget our brothers and sisters
who didn't make it.
They will never be forgotten,
and we will do right by them.
- Hear, hear!
- Yeah!
And now a toast
to our new brothers --
Sam and Dean Winchester.
Thanks, boys.
Welcome to the family.
- Sam and Dean!
- Welcome!
Why should I trust you?
I saw how they do
the spell.
I know what it takes.
It's some blood,
some fruit,
a glow-y rock, and then...
Bam. We step through,
both of us.
And then?
And then I get my son,
and you get...
Everything else.
Are we agreed?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man