It's a powerful spellbook,
a tome of Druidic magic
called the Black Grimoire.
A powerful spellbook
shows up,
and all of a sudden,
you're here to help?
Do you want to break the curse
on your brother?
We need to find that book.
Abi!
The book.
You're no fun.
Oh, if you're looking
for Rowena,
she is presently indisposed,
which is a delicate way
of saying
I stomped on her face
till the white meat showed
and then set her on fire
just in case.
I don't need to waste my grace,
and there's plenty
in the cupboard.
Oh, touch me and I'll --
Don't worry.
I won't take it all.
Save some for a rainy day.
You would seem to be
the weak link on this team.
Yes, my grace is a little bit
depleted, but give me time, man.
Now you know better than
to screw with me, Asmodeus.
Oh, I knew better than to screw
with the old you.
I'm a collector.
Lucifer could be useful.
Castiel is a card to play if
the Winchesters get out of line.
Hey, Marty.
How's your night?
?
Hi.
Hey.
Excuse me.
Aegrota amore.
?
Oh, my God. Hi.
I was totally hoping
we could talk.
You want to talk with me?
Mm-hmm.
I mean, you're so handsome.
Really?
What's your name?
Dale.
I'm Jamie, and that's
my sister Jennie.
Y'all from around here?
Nah, my sister and I
are on our way
to this little town
called Lebanon.
Heard of it?
I can't say that I have.
You are so beautiful.
Oh. Thank you.
Anyway, we're out of gas
and we're out of money.
Tragic, right?
That is terrible.
Well, what can I do for ya?
I'll do anything.
I knew you were our hero.
The easiest thing
would be to take all the money
from the register,
grab a couple bottles
of good vodka,
and bring it outside.
What about Marty?
What about him?
?
Finally.
Got it for you, baby.
What's with the hammer?
Oh, my God, sexy,
it's just for in case.
Like, for protection.
This is a dangerous place
at night.
I mean, that guy in there
totally just got killed.
Oh, don't worry. I won't let
anything bad happen to you.
I love you.
Oh, I love you, too.
Uh, what was
your name again?
- Dale.
- Right. Yes.
But don't worry, Dale.
Our mom taught us
three really important steps
to looking out for ourselves.
Always look your best.
never get attached to a man.
And always make the death
look non-magical,
so you don't
attract Hunters.
The death?
Now be a good boy and hold
really still for me.
How'd we do?
So good.
? Supernatural 13x12 ?
Various & Sundry Villains
Original Air Date on F
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
All right.
We've got
“Principia Phantasmagoia”.
We have...
“Archive of
the Unnatural Occurrences”.
[ Thud .
And we've got “Jower et Nuet”.
Kind of a weird name.
“Jour et Nuit.”
It's, uh, it's French.
It means
“The Book of Day and Night.”
Fancy.
So this is everything
that even mentions
some alternate realities.
So there's bound to be
something in here
that talks about
the Apocalypse World, right?
Yeah, maybe.
Dude.
I'm just saying, Dean,
Jack was our way over there,
obviously, so with him gone --
Okay, well,
Jack's been gone before.
We found him once.
We can find him again.
No, no, he didn't run away.
He is literally in
an alternate reality.
Okay, so we'll just come up
with a plan B, okay?
You said it yourself. We just keep
our heads down and we'll do the work.
You said that.
And I was right.
Yeah.
So you read, do your Sam thing.
I'm gonna go for a beer run.
Yeah.
We should probably
loop Cass in at some point.
We'll fill him in when he calls.
He checks in every day.
Yeah, with a bunch
of questions and no leads.
I'm sure he is doing
the best he can.
Just go get beer or...
?
Huh. Always thought
you'd have a...
bigger stick.
What's your name again?
They call me Dipper.
And you let them.
Listen, Dipper,
it's not the size of the stick,
it's how you use it.
Funniest thing --
I'm always hearing that
from guys with...
little sticks.
Smooth.
We gave the warding
a little kick.
Just for you.
Thanks. So considerate.
Appreciate that a lot.
You're not nice,
and I don't like you.
You're treating me like
an every day angel!
And if I had
just a little more power,
I could tear
this place apart!
Just sayin'.
Ah!
You don't have that power,
and they know it.
Okay, well, if somebody
would be a pal
and let me eat
a little of his grace,
I would have enough strength
to get out of here
and butcher that
son of a bitch!
Well, that's a nice,
horrifying plan.
Little cannibalism.
Really? I seem to remember
a somebody
snacking on angel grace
once upon a time.
There is no “I” in “team”"
Castiel.
I want you to remember that.
Fine, whatever. I can wait.
Asmodeus was
my weakest creation.
Oh, he was, was he?
Doesn't seem that weak
to me.
Yeah, yeah, that -- that whole
shape-shifty thing he does?
I-I didn't give him that.
But so what? The old dog's
learned some new tricks.
Eventually, he's gonna mess up.
Then he's mine. Okay?
Excuses aside,
you're saying that
you're too weak
to overcome even
your weakest creation.
Shut up.
Somebody! Help!
Please, there's something
wrong with my sister!
Please, please. Please.
Okay. Watch out,
watch out, watch out.
- What happened?
- I don't know. Please.
She just --
she just collapsed.
I -- We were walking
and...
Aegrota amore.
Doesn't a kiss, like,
usually wake up
your true love?
?
Thank you.
You saved me.
Are you Dean Winchester?
I-I...
Yeah.
How are you feeling?
Good.
Real good.
?
Hey, uh...
I think
you might be right.
I think maybe it's time
we go ahead and call Cass,
because, I mean, if -- if...
You all right?
Am I all right?
I'm in love.
You...Oh, are you?
I mean, I am, like,
full-on twitterpated here.
Seriously, I can't wait for you
to meet her, either.
She -- I mean, she's...
She's sweet
and she's beautiful
and she's just
kinda sorta perfect.
Anyway, I'm thinking of asking
her to move in with me here...
if that's cool,
'cause this is big-time.
Ahh.
Uh, Dean, w-what are you doing
with the Black Grimoire?
It's a gift. For Jamie.
For...Jamie?
My soul mate.
Sure. Right.
And she happen to ask
for that book by, uh, name?
Yeah! I mean, isn't that
kind of cosmic fate,
- that we actually have it?
- Like...
“Cosmic fate.”
Right, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay.
I think I know
what's going on here.
Do you remember, uh,
uh, Becky in Vegas?
The love spell and...
No.
M--
Okay, I think Jamie must be
a-a witch or a demon --
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa.
- What?
- Be nice.
'Cause she's got a sister.
And if you play your cards
right, you know,
you guys might fall
for each other.
You know, the less attractive
siblings, they fall in love.
That's kind of cute,
right? Huh?
Just hold on a second.
I can't wait
'cause she's waiting for me at
the market, so I'm just gonna...
Okay. All right.
That's fine.
You know why?
I'll walk 'cause it is...
? gorgeous outside ?
Wait a second.
Dean, listen, honestly --
Ooh.
Right on the button.
Listen, when I get back
from my date,
I'm gonna help you
ice that, okay?
All right, thanks.
Good talk, pal! Good talk!
You gonna make the call
after we get the book?
No. We're fully, like,
making an audible.
?
Where's the car?
I wanted the car.
There you go.
Good boys get a kiss.
Close your eyes.
?
Get away from him.
You heard me.
Don't point a gun at her!
- Hey!
- Uhh! No, Dean!
Don't you point a gun at her!
What are you doing?!
Where is it?
- You're jealous!
- There's gotta be a hex bag.
Where is it?
Please, just --
We should get out of here,
in case the one with the hair
actually wins.
- No, no, no, don't -- don't leave.
- Bye, boys.
Where is it? Huh?
?
Look, Dean!
Look, I got it!
Hex bag! Wait, Dean --
Aah! No!
I'm sorry, Sam. I just --
I love her so much.
Hello, boys.
Rise. Rise.
Mm.
Don't think we forgot
about you.
When the boss gets back,
big plans for you.
Oh, does he have big plans?
Hey, what's that gonna be worth
when Michael gets here
and, oh, yeah,
murders us all?
Right, if he gets here.
There's no “if” here
in this equation, okay?
Let me -- let me just --
let me just tell you something
about my dick brother --
about every version
of my dick brother, okay?
When he decides to do
something, he does it.
Doesn't matter what the cost
or who has to die.
It is gonna happen, 'cause
that's just the way he rolls.
If you're right, how much
time do we have?
How much time? Oh.
I guess that depends
on how much time he spends
torturing Mary Winchester.
He liked her, right?
Oh, Cass,
you should've seen it.
I mean,
the things he did to her.
In all my time in hell,
I have never seen anything
that horrible.
Just...Oh!
Stop. I don't wanna hear
any more of your lies.
Oh, this coming from the angel
who almost has me beat
in that department,
and that's saying a lot, pal.
Well, you always say a lot.
Okay, let's face it,
Cassandra,
the truths I say hurt
'cause they're hard to swallow,
so people call 'em lies.
Go figure.
You want truth?
How 'bout I tell you
a few truths about your son?
Did you just have
an angel stroke?
Did you know that
he loves movies?
Fantasy movies,
movies with heroes
who crush villains.
Well, that's --
that's -- that's nurture.
That's not nature.
And he's thoughtful.
He's emotional.
Remarkably intuitive.
You -- you know, he, uh,
he resurrected me
just out of instinct.
Isn't that
a beautiful gesture?
?
Yeah, that's, uh,
that's beautiful.
Jack would rather kill you
than hug you.
Seems relevant.
Did you know he doesn't --
he doesn't even really
look like you.
And he reminds me so much
of his mother.
?
Wow.
Ask me.
How are you alive?
Lucifer told us
he killed you
pretty, uh...
pretty graphically.
And he did.
But I take precautions to ensure
that if I die...
it is temporary.
You're talking about
a, uh, resurrection spell,
like last time?
Mm, mm.
That said,
it took a very long time
to heal.
And I'm not interested in it
ever happening again,
which is why I need
the Black Grimoire.
What a coincidence.
You happen to show up
right when it's stolen.
Oh, no coincidence.
I felt the book moving.
In a moment of weakness, I may
have put a tracking spell
on the Grimoire
behind your backs.
Moment of weakness, huh?
Right.
Why do you want it so bad?
Why now?
Oh, years ago, the Grand Coven
cast a binding spell
limiting aspects of my magic.
There's a page in the Grimoire
that may help.
Help you become more powerful?
Yeah, that's what we want.
- Help me protect myself.
- Let me get this straight.
You, uh, felt the book moving
and you decided, what?
You'd -- you'd -- you'd
show up and just take it?
Well, I thought about asking you
nicely for it, but...
Yeah, but you knew we'd
tell you to go to Hell.
Exactly.
Now I'm -- I'm worried the girls
will damage the book,
and you're worried about
the awful things
they'll do with it, so...
Let's...help each other,
shall we?
We don't need your help.
We've handled witches before.
You're familiar with
our work, right?
Ah. Oh, you Winchesters.
I've changed.
Honestly.
Having your skull crushed
and being burned alive
can do that to a girl.
And it's my tracking spell,
so if you want to find
those girls...
Well, lover?
Okay.
You'll need me.
Sl?inte.
Oh.
One more thing.
Where's my son?
There are
whole parts of this
I can't really read.
Because it's
too complicated?
No. Because it's ultra...
old.
I mean, some
of these symbols
are things
Mom never even mentioned.
Um, so we wing it.
We're really good
at improvising.
And you've totally got
the skills.
Aw. Thanks.
Now you girls are gonna
pay for that stuff, right?
Wow. Thanks for the reminder
of how shopping works.
- Well, because last time you just --
- Oh, my God!
Shut up, Brenda.
Like, please, shut up.
She's so rude.
Huh.
What?
I-I'm pretty sure this says
we need a soul to sacrifice.
Okay.
?
Fergus is dead?
Yep.
Killed himself for us.
That doesn't sound like him.
Right, well,
Fergus, uh, uh...
Crowley, um,
he had changed a lot.
You'd have
been proud of him.
Is that so?
Fergus was my only child.
And I promise you, I'd much
rather have a living son,
even one that hated me,
than a dead hero.
Because of him...
Lucifer is trapped
in another reality. So...
Yeah, the Devil's gone.
Oh, don't be stupid.
He's never gone!
Okay, listen, I know what
Lucifer's cap--
Oh, c-can we not?
It's like reminiscing about
an abusive relationship.
Why do that?
Let's get back to the book.
What kind of hurt can -
these chicks do with it?
Oh, I'm sure they have
big plans.
Sounds like you know 'em.
Just remember being
a young, overly ambitious,
wee witch.
And I have to give them
some credit.
Outfoxed you, didn't they?
Tell me...
did they get to fifth base?
There's no such thing
as fifth base.
Oh, you poor, sheltered boy.
Anyway...
What's by is by. And who knows?
If I help you,
maybe you'll change your minds
about helping me.
- No.
- Not happening.
So we were maybe
too optimistic.
Don't bail out now, Jennie.
I'm not.
But if this goes wrong,
who knows what could happen?
Ugh. If you, like, really don't
think we can do this,
then it's time to make
a phone call.
No.
I'm not asking for help.
We're doing this for Mom.
She taught us everything,
sacrificed so much for us.
She sacrifice
so many people for us.
She was an amazing witch,
and she deserves to be alive
and gorgeous and with us.
And with this book, we can
absolutely bring her back.
I know. Just...
just don't yell at me.
?
Listen.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm the big sister
and I'm supposed
to be the strong one
or whatever, but...
?
Yeah?
I just...really miss her.
I do, too.
I know.
And...
I, like,
really believe in us.
Jamie, I...
I just want her back so bad.
And we're going to
get her back,
even if we have to cast
every spell in this book
and crush the skulls
of, like, a million people
to make it happen.
Okay.
- Yes?
- Yeah.
I believe in you, too, Jennie,
because I love you.
Aw.
That's so great.
?
Still need that soul, right?
For sure.
Cool.
?
Welcome to
Stillwater, Oklahoma.
How depressingly Midwestern.
All right, Red. Where to?
The tracking spell
isn't like GPS.
The book's not moving
and it's in this general area.
We'll need to speak
to the yokels.
Okay, well, small-town folks
usually like to look out
for themselves.
I can make them talk.
Uh, your spells tend
to boil people's brains,
So maybe let us handle it.
Fine, fine, we can do
your very time-consuming
investi...
Okay, see, “we” aren't
doing anything.
I'll keep an eye on her.
Great.
Leave me with the babysitter
if you must,
but do start with the women.
Something tells me
those girls
aren't popular
with other ladies.
Face it.
You are useless and impotent
and unnecessary,
and you will die alone,
unmourned.
You talking to me,
pretty boy?
No, he's talking to me.
Yeah.
Yeah. Well,
he does have a point.
Aw, did you lose
your little stick?
I did.
How did you...
- Turns out rage is a good motivator.
-Ah!
And I think you forgot something.
I'm Lucifer.
Told you size didn't matter.
You...
Whoops.
Someone got mad
and broke his warding.
?
Good times.
Well, this is boring.
Is there...
I don't know, music?
Yeah, yeah, uh, you know,
Dean has a tape of
Led Zeppelin's “Moby Dick”
with an 8-minute drum solo.
Let me see.
It's around here somewhere.
Are you very sure
I can't just enslave
some townsfolk
and make them take us
to the girls?
I'm very sure you can,
but I'm also very sure
you shouldn't.
Bless your precious heart,
you just described
my entire life.
Rowena...
even if you pull off whatever
plan you're trying to pull off,
and even if you manage
to get the book back --
I've been on
my best behavior.
Okay, sure.
Let's say
you get the book.
It's not gonna change
anything.
You're still gonna feel
helpless.
What Lucifer did to you --
Told you, I don't...
?
Before he crushed my skull,
Lucifer showed me his face.
His true face.
I'm scared, Sam.
All the time.
I've seen it, too,
what he really
looks like behind --
behind whatever vessel.
It...
Yeah, still keeps me up
at night.
How do you deal with it?
I guess I don't deal with it.
Not really. I mean, I...
I pushed it down and, um...
the -- the world kept
almost ending,
so I-I keep
pushing it down, and...
I don't know. I...
I don't really talk about it,
not even with Dean.
I mean, I-I-I could. You know,
he'd -- he'd listen, but...
?
That's not something
I really know how to share.
?
Hi there.
Been to a few other places,
haven't had much luck.
Was hoping you could
help me out.
Oh, happy to try.
What do you need?
I'm looking for these
two girls, uh, in town --
Jennie and Jamie.
Oh. The Plum sisters.
Right. Yeah, I'm looking
to track them down.
Hmm. You and every other man
west of the Ozarks.
Popular, huh?
That's one word for it.
And a whole mess of trouble.
Well, they took something,
and I need to get it back.
Heard it before --
they stole your heart,
you can't live without them.
They stole a book.
A book?
Mm.
Honey,
now I know you're lying.
I doubt they can even read.
Well, that has been
up for debate.
If it helps, I don't plan on
being nice about it
when I do find them.
Mm.
?
You gonna be really mean?
Yeah.
'Cause it's about damn time
someone was.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mmm.
Even if you do get
the book,
and even if you
get your power back,
it won't matter.
You won't ever be able
to change what happened.
You won't be able to change
how helpless you felt,
or how helpless you feel.
You're still gonna
get scared.
And that feeling...
that feeling never
goes away.
Never?
Never.
?
Hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
I just need a minute.
I'm not fleeing.
Don't release the hounds.
- Hey.
What's going on?
Uh, she, uh, she's just needs
a minute. She's all right.
All right, well, I got
the address. Rowena was right.
These girls are not
fan favorites.
Right.
Time to get that book.
Oh, no, no.
You've done yo bit, okay?
We'll take it from here.
I was afraid
you might say that.
Manete!
Rowena!
Rowena, stop!
Rowena, damn it!
Oh, come on.
All right.
I don't think it said
anything about tin foil.
Okay, so you don't
think it said anything?
I told you, there's all kinds
of weird writing.
I was totally honest
about that.
Maybe there was something
wrong with his soul.
Maybe he was, like, a really
bad guy or something.
Come on. He as obviously
a total Boy Scout.
I don't think
that even matters.
We need to do something.
I'm looking!
I'm looking.
You were supposed to get
the book and wait for me.
I...Uh...
Okay, like, the Winchesters
were all over us and --
And we didn't wanna
call you.
Because we can
take care of ourselves.
I told you about the book,
where to look for the boys.
We had a deal.
Now I've had to use them
to find you.
You brought them here?
When you nincompoops ran,
I did what I had to do.
But I can still cast the spell.
We can still complete our deal.
You'd still help us?
As long as you give me the book
when we're done.
You don't need it anyway.
Witches of your level
would --
- “Witches of our level”?
- Yes.
Are you saying what our Mom
taught us wasn't good enough?
Jennie, I think she's saying
we're not good enough.
You think
you're so smart, huh?
Well, we already did
the spell.
Mostly.
Mostly?
What have you done?
It's, like, step one of
bringing her back.
We'll figure out the rest
after she kills you.
Unfortunate, but not
my first zombie, luv.
Abi!
Oh, side effect of
the spell --
she's, like, magic-proof.
Ooh!
And she's totally gonna
eat your brain.
Needed a minute, huh?
You don't have to say it, Dean.
Oh, I'm gonna say it.
She played you.
She played us.
And she's scared.
Yeah, well, she better be.
Come on.
You're, like, 8 feet tall.
You can't reach that?
I almost got it.
Okay, got it, got it.
Ahh.
All right.
All right, let's go kill
some witches. You want that?
They'll be
more of them coming.
You know...
this would be so much easier
if I was stronger.
Hint, hint, hint.
Oh, come on, Castiel.
We just fought side by side,
mano e mano.
You gotta trust me now, man.
Come on.
Oh, I trusted you,
when we fought the Darkness,
and then you betrayed us.
And I trusted you --
Ah!
?
Fool me once...
I promise to leave you
a little. Come on.
?
Uhh!
This is me,
learning from my mistakes.
It's just a magical zombie.
You've deal with worse than
magical zombies before, Rowena.
Oh!
Clearly you wanted your mom back
in better shape!
I can still do that.
Nah, you missed
your chance to play nice.
And you're kind of
all bark, no bite,
so she's gonna bite you.
You're terrible.
- Rowena!
- Boys! Wonderful!
I've been stalling them
until you arrived.
Hey, lovebug. Can't introduce
you to Mom right now.
She's busy. How 'bout
that kiss I owe you?
Sure.
Guns. Okay, super scary.
Witch-killing bullets.
Moveantur!
Aah!
?
Sammy!
They're really weirdly strong.
I think
it's probably a spell.
You think?
Aah! Uhh!
?
Jennie!
Uhh!
Aah! Son of a...
?
Magic won't work on
this abomination!
Got any suggestions?!
Quickly!
Try shooting her in the head!
No!
?
Mom!
Impetus Bestiarum!
Rowena.
End it.
?
You really thought
afterall that,
I was going to try
to kill you?
Yeah, you double-crossed us.
Triple-cross, actually.
So I ended up on your side,
and we defeated the villains,
just as I planned.
Yeah, not buying that.
And that book?
You're gonna either
give it to us
or we can take it,
either way.
You know what
I've seen, what it's like.
Lucifer may be locked away,
but he'll be back.
He always comes back.
And when he does...
I can't be helpless again.
I need the spell.
?
Can't believe I fell
for a love spell.
And got clocked by
a witch with a hammer.
And zombie mom.
Those are the details
that sell the story.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Getting beat up by a girl --
that's a story
I wanna tell someone.
Girls beat us up
all the time.
Mm. True.
Hey, you know that Rowena
is not our friend, right?
Yeah, I know that.
Hmm.
Then what's that?
You gave her the page.
She got in your head, man.
She didn't get in my head.
Look, what happened to Rowena
was messed up, okay?
But you just let the deadliest witch
in the world
walk away with a page
from this book.
Yeah, and if Rowena
breaks bad,
I will hunt her down myself
and put a bullet in her.
I will, Dean.
But if she's right, and if
she does see Lucifer again,
then...
I hope she makes him suffer.
You gotta get out of
this dark place.
You know, whatever's
going on in your head...
Dean.
What?
You know what? Honestly?
Yeah, how 'bout honestly.
I know what Rowena is
dealing with.
And she's not
the only one who...
feels helpless.
What do you mean?
?
I mean, I had a plan,
you know. I, uh...
Help Jack, um,
bring Mom back.
It wasn't much,
but it was something.
It -- it kept me from
spinning off the rails.
A-and now...Jack is gone,
Mom is still in hell,
basically,
a-and I-I-I just...
We'll figure it out.
Dean, we don't have a plan.
We don't know what to do.
So -- so...how?
I don't know.
?
But we will, you and me.
Yeah.
Night.
?
Ego sum filia naturae.
Cum osculatione lunae.
Da mihi vocem liberatam.
Remitte vim meam.
Fiam invincta.
Ego sum filia naturae.
Cum osculatione lunae.
Da mihi vocem liberatam.
Remitte vim meam.
Fiam invincta!
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man