Whatever you want from me,
I'll give it.
If you want, I'm here.
Claire: What?
This is some sort of
halfway house for wayward girls?
If you ever need someplace
to go, my door's always open.
[ Voice breaks ] Mom!
Jody: Losing everything
you've ever known or loved,
no one can understand that.
Alex: You can.
Halestorm:
? Am I brave enough? ?
? Am I strong enough? ?
? To push away my fear ?
? To stand where I'm afraid ?
? I am through with this ?
[ Sighs heavily ]
? I am the fire ?
? Roaring like a storm ?
Move!
? And I am the one ?
? I am the fire ?
Claire: I've been hunting.
Alone.
And I know it's not what
you wanna hear,
but this is something
I have to do on my own.
I'm Sheriff Donna Hanscum.
Oof-ta.
Jody: You know,
if you want any pointers
on how to fight this crazy crap,
I'm willing to fill ya in.
I'd like that.
? Won't let the past
decide my fate ?
Your mother, she's alive.
What?
But she's in danger.
What? What kind of danger?
It's easier if I show you.
I experimented, opening doors
to other worlds.
Help!
Jack: I saw her.
Somebody help me!
But I needed --
A dreamwalker.
Sam: Kaia Nieves.
? I've been sacrificed ?
We need you
to dream walk for us.
I only go to one place --
the Bad Place.
It's just
blood and monsters.
? I am the fire ?
? I am burning brighter ?
? Roaring like a storm ?
[ Whoosh ]
? And I am the one ?
? I've been waiting for ?
? Screaming like a siren ?
? Alive and burning brighter ?
? I am the fire ?
?
Patience?
Jody, I had a vision.
Something bad's coming.
[ Truck engine purring ]
?
[ Blade scrapes ]
[ Breathing shakily ]
?
[ Blade continues scraping ]
Wanna hear a joke?
Man: Ed.
Don't play
with your damn food.
Knock, knock.
Come on, girly.
I said, “Knock, knock.”
[ Inhales sharply ]
Who's there?
[ Growls ]
[ Screams ]
- Ed!
- [ Laughs ]
[ Truck approaching ]
?
[ Engine stops,
truck door opens ]
[ Truck door closes ]
[ Gravel crunching ]
[ Footsteps approach ]
[ Knock on door ]
Who's there?
Woman: Delivery.
[ Door creaks ]
I think you got
the wrong house.
Huh?
Your name's
right on the box.
?
You Hunter bi--
[ Gunshot ]
[ Thud ]
[ Rifle cocks ]
Amanda Fitzmartin?
I'll be right there.
[ Door creaking ]
?
[ Growls ]
- [ Claire grunts ]
- Aah!
Aah!
Who the hell
do you think you are?
[ Grunts ]
[ Squish ]
[ Gasps ]
I kill monsters.
[ Squish ]
That's who the hell I am.
?
Your mother's
been looking for you.
Uh-huh.
It's gonna be okay.
[ Gasping ]
[ Growls lowly ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Grunts ] Aah!
[ Thud ]
?
Like I said,
totally okay.
[ Mrs. Fitzmartin
speaking indistinctly ]
Oh! Amanda!
?
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Ring ]
[ Beep ]
Hi, Jody.
Hi, Claire. It's...
it's Sam and Dean.
They're missing.
Where the hell are we?
Jody:
They were on a hunting trip,
and I haven't heard from them
for a few days.
It's time to come home.
? Supernatural 13x10 ?
Wayward Sisters
Original Air Date on January 18,
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
?
Tried Donna, Walt.
Nobody's heard anything.
[ Front door opens, closes ]
Surprise.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
Hi, Jody.
Alex. You miss me?
Not really.
?
Uh, it's just a werewolf.
No big deal.
?
[ Chuckles ] Whoa.
When did we become huggers?
I'm just glad you're home safe.
There's somebody
I want you to meet.
This is, uh, this is Patience.
- Hi.
Patience drove up from Atlanta.
She's been staying with us
for a few days.
- You a Hunter?
- Psychic.
Cool.
You're wearing
my sweatshirt.
Uh...Jody --
She sleeping
in my room, too?
Actually, the guest room
is storage now. So --
It's fine.
I'm the one who left.
[ Sighs ]
So...Sam and Dean --
What do we know?
Sam: Hey, Jody. Uh, thanks
for your help earlier.
So listen, we're looking for
someone -- Kaia Nieves.
She might be the key
to saving Mom.
So if you hear anything --
Dean: Gotta go. Call you later.
Ow.
Baby.
That was three days ago.
Haven't heard anything since.
What about the girl? Kaia.
Jody: Yeah, I ran her name
through the system.
She was picked up
for possession in Minnesota,
and then she escaped from
court-ordered drug rehab
three days ago.
Warrant out for her arrest.
Check the rehab center
and the local hospitals.
Already did.
?
[ Line rings ] Man: 911. What's the nature
of your emergency?
You gonna be okay?
Yeah.
All right.
Where you going?
Night shift.
So Sam and Dean are missing,
and you're bailing?
I have a job, Claire.
Mm. Well, so do I.
It's called hunting.
Good luck.
[ Train whistle blowing
in distance ]
[ Door opens, closes ]
What is she talking about?
Hmm?
Claire...
If this is about
me hunting alone,
I know I should've
called more...
No, hold on. Hold on.
...but I'm fine. I'm good.
I'm safe.
[ Voice breaks ] No, you're not.
Patience had a vision.
That's why she's here.
?
I...
I saw you die.
[ Chuckles ]
?
Claire, she's the real deal.
So every vision you have,
it always comes true?
I don't know.
I'm still figuring all this out.
So you might be wrong.
Claire, this is serious!
I'm trying to protect you!
Jody, that's always
your excuse.
Every time we'd go out on
a hunt together, you'd end up
taking care of the monster
while I just wait in the car.
That happened one time!
It happened every time, Jody!
You -- you've never
even seen what I can do.
Claire,
if I put the brakes on you,
it's because you can't go
dive-bombing into every fight.
Yes, I can!
That is how you save people.
Sitting back
and making the perfect plan,
losing time...
that's how people
end up dead.
And if you end up dead?!
I won't.
Claire, you can't just
run away from this.
Watch me.
[ Front door opens, closes ]
?
[ Emergency radio chatter ]
[ Low snarling ]
?
[ Siren wailing ]
The patient in Room 11's
been released.
Her room needs to be
sanitized.
Already done, and I processed
her discharge paperwork.
[ Tone sounds ]
Well done.
[ Woman speaking indistinctly
over P.A. ]
Nice outfit.
[ Sighs ] It's a uniform.
What's your excuse?
I look great.
You look like
Biker Barbie.
Thank you.
[ Tone sounds ]
You knew?
[ Pen scratching ]
About the whole
vision thing?
Yep. And I knew how
you'd react.
So...you have a job?
But you still help Jody
with cases?
I thought you wanted out of
the whole monster thing.
If she needs my help
with anything --
the dishes, monsters --
I'm there, for her.
Unlike me.
?
Alex, the way things
were going,
if I'd stuck around,
she just would've worried
all the time.
Claire, she never stopped.
Anyway... [ Sighs ]
I'm guessing you didn't crash
my job for a heart-to-heart.
What do you want?
?
[ Lowered voice ]
Two minutes in your system?
[ Lowered voice
I told you. Already checked.
Well, did you run
rock star aliases?
From metal gods to
obscure hair bands. Nothing.
Okay, what about the girl, Kaia?
[ Typing ]
Yes.
You try Jane Does?
I did. [ Sighs ]
But...
[ Beep ]
An unidentified woman
was just brought in.
- Where?
- Here.
[ Telephone ringing
in distance ]
Woman: So your vital signs
are stable
and your concussion's minor,
but we're gonna need to keep you
here under observation.
Mm.
[ Device beeping ]
?
Where you going?
Hey, I get it.
If I had the cops on my ass,
I'd be racing outta Dodge, too.
Who are you?
I'm a friend of
Sam and Dean Winchester.
And I think
you know them, too.
Leave me alone.
Hey.
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Growls ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Screeches, snarls ]
?
[ Clicks ]
Uhh!
[ Snarls ]
[ Growls ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Screeching ]
?
[ Screeching, gagging ]
Ugh. [ Panting ]
[ Grunts ]
So let's talk.
[ Garage door whirring ]
[ Hatch closes ]
[ Whirring stops ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
Ohh.
Dude.
Jody:
What's under the mask?
[ Glove snaps ]
Let's find out.
You've seen one of
those things before, huh?
In my dreams.
And not just one of them.
Those things, they --
they travel in packs.
They pick up your scent
and they don't stop.
So you fight them.
Fight? No.
I run.
But...
sometimes, they catch me.
Is that how you got that?
I've got others, all over.
?
Me, too.
Look.
Ghoul bite.
Bar fight with a vampire.
He threw me through
a window.
?
And this one?
Hmm?
Um...
heroic battle
with a doorknob.
[ Laughs ]
I tripped.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
?
Kaia?
What happened?
[ Squishing ]
Oh, God.
Don't scream.
Mnh. Might puke.
?
What is that?
- I don't know.
- She does.
It's okay.
You can tell.
Uh, I'm a dreamwalker.
It means when I sleep,
I see another world... [ Squishing ]
...this other dimension.
Seriously?
The Bad Place.
It's where that came from.
Your friends Sam and Dean,
they wanted me to help them
open a door to another world.
And we did,
but something went wrong.
Okay, so then how did
this thing end up here?
?
The door's still open.
If we find it,
we find Sam and Dean.
No.
If they're there,
they're already dead.
[ Crackling ]
No, don't -- don't tell me
it tastes like chicken.
[ Mouth full ] No, Sam,
it's a lizard.
It tastes like a lizard.
[ Groans ]
And we really gotta
get moving,
keep looking for
that door.
[ Spits ]
Yeah, if there is
a door.
Well, last time we opened one,
it stayed open.
Yeah, for a few hours.
We've been here for what?
Two days and change?
I mean, look, man, I hope
you're right. I really do.
But if you're not,
and we're stuck here
in this freaking
MonsterLand?
I mean, nobody back home
even knows
where to start looking
for us.
So what are you saying?
I'm sayin'...
eat up.
[ Roaring, heavy thudding steps
in distance ]
That sound closer to you?
Yeah.
What do you think it is?
Let's not find out.
[ Roaring continues ]
[ Thudding steps continue ]
?
So...you're leaving?
If I go now, maybe my dad
will take me back.
Is that what you want?
To go back home,
pretend you're
Little Miss Perfect
and not
a powerful psychic?
[ Sighs heavily ]
This is just...
all way too freaky.
I mean, your mom's out burying
a monster in the backyard.
Well, you gotta bury him
somewhere.
Um...
I came here to tell Jody
about my vision,
and Claire just
blew it off.
And I am not a fighter.
I couldn't even imagine
going up against
one of those...things.
You don't have to be a fighter.
I'm not. Not really.
You know,
we help in other ways.
[ Sighs ] I'm sorry.
[ Zips bag ]
I can't do this.
[ Departing footsteps ]
[ Car alarm beeps ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Growls ]
[ Gasps, breathes heavily ]
We have to go. Now.
- What?
- Those monsters, they're coming.
Lots of them.
They're after me.
Then we should stay
and fight.
There's too many.
They'll kill us.
Maybe. Maybe not.
Look, I gave up a lot
to come here,
to do what was right,
to save you.
You wanna brush that off? You
wanna think I'm a fake? Fine.
But I'm telling you, right now,
we're all in danger.
Claire...
?
[ Glass shattering ]
[ Growling ]
?
[ Screeching ]
Believe me now?
?
[ Engines stop ]
[ Car doors open, close ]
Why are we stoppin'?
Taking a breather.
I called in some backup.
Like what?
The National Guard?
Ohh. Better.
[ Horn honks ]
?
Hiya, ladies.
Hey, Donna.
Oh!
Okay, you, too,
Rainbow Brite.
Come on, bring it in.
Patience, Kaia, this is
Sheriff Donna Hanscum.
She's, uh, she's killed
a lot of vampires.
Ah, ya know. I do what I do.
[ Chuckles ]
Anyhoo, brought the basics.
?
Why do you have all this?
I'm from Minnesota.
Kaia, where were you
when this went down
with Sam and Dean?
I don't know.
We were heading west
out of Mankato,
towards Sioux Falls.
So...Route 14.
We got run off the road.
[ Tires screeching ]
We pulled into
an abandoned boatyard.
I didn't see a sign.
The Larsen Brothers Shipyard,
just off Route 14.
Shut down in '08.
We'll check it out.
Yeah.
Jody: Claire.
Come here.
So...who knows how to use
a flamethrower?
Claire, I know you're not
gonna like this,
but I need you to stay here to
keep Kaia and the girls safe.
Just until we've checked
things out, okay?
?
Okay, Jody.
Go.
?
Look, Dean, I don't think this
is just a different world.
I think it's
a different universe.
Yeah, well,
this universe sucks.
Yeah.
[ Rustling ]
What was that?
?
[ Both grunting ]
Uhh!
?
[ Birds chirping ]
Jody: You think this is
the place?
Oh, yeah.
You betcha.
?
Kaia: Room over there?
[ Bird chirping ]
You're scared.
Yeah.
Jody always said
I'd get myself killed.
Hunting. And I'd be like,
“Good.” Yeah.
I'm gonna go out,
then that's
how I wanna do it,
doing something great.
But Patience's vision...
It's one thing thinking
that you're gonna die.
But actually knowing it?
For once, a part of me kinda
just wants to sit back
and let Jody handle it,
you know?
Stay safe.
But Sam and Dean saved
my life, and...
I can't sit this one out.
Then don't.
If you go,
I'll go with you.
Maybe together,
we can save them.
?
Oof-ta.
There it is.
?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
We're gonna go back,
right?
You know, tell the girls?
?
- I'm going in.
- What now?
If I don't, she will.
Donna, I cannot lose
another child.
?
[ Low growling ]
Jody...
?
[ Thumping ]
[ Object shatters ]
[ Gasps ] Jeez.
- Is that a...
- Mm. Yep.
[ Clattering ]
[ Canids roar ]
?
[ Low growling ]
[ Canids roar ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Roars ]
Come on.
?
Sam.
Sammy!
[ Grunts ]
Hey.
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Grunts ]
What happened? [ Grunts ]
?
Hey, yo!
[ Grunts ]
Darth Dickwad.
[ Clang ]
What the hell?
What was that all about?
[ Roar in distance ]
[ Low growls ]
?
I think it just rang
the dinner bell.
?
Patience, give me your keys.
Jody's not picking up
her phone.
Something's wrong.
?
[ Low growling ]
[ Thud ]
?
[ Loud thud ]
We make a run for
the truck, we're dead.
We stay here, we're dead.
All righty, then.
[ Thudding ]
[ Growling, screeching ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Thud ]
[ Roars ]
[ Whoosh ]
I called. You didn't answer.
We worried.
Where's the other one?
There's another one?
Probably bolted.
[ Metal clanks ]
Is that the door?
Claire.
Claire!
?
[ Gasps ] Look.
Claire, please, wait!
Oh, hell.
?
- What?
- It's getting smaller. It's closing.
No, Claire. Wait!
Jody, I know you're trying
to protect me,
but I need to save
Sam and Dean,
and you have to let me.
I know.
?
You ever shot a gun before?
No.
[ Racks shotgun ]
Okeydoke, here ya go.
Aim in
their general direction,
relax, and squeeze.
Squeeze. Don't pull.
[ Growling ]
Oh, there he is.
[ Racks shotgun ]
Hiya, buddy.
[ Continues growling ]
?
Upstairs! Move!
[ Gunshot ]
Donna: Jody. Little help!
Patience: Help!
?
[ Gunshots ]
Donna: Jody!
Alex: Jody!
[ Gunshots continue ]
Go.
I'll protect you.
?
[ Gunshots continue ]
[ Zaps ]
[ Gasps ]
- You okay?
- Yeah.
[ Growling ]
This way.
[ Thudding steps approaching ]
[ Gunshots continue ]
Aah!
Come on.
[ Growls ]
?
[ Grunting ]
[ Clanking ]
They're gone?
[ Gunshots ]
[ Loud thud ]
?
[ Groans ] Damn it.
[ Growling ]
Dean, you hearing that?
[ Grunts ]
[ Bindings snap ]
[ Roars ]
Claire?
Hey, boys.
[ Bindings snap ]
My hero.
Hey. How did you get here?
The door, it's still open.
For now.
Where's Jack?
I think he's in
the other place with your mom.
[ Loud roar, growling ]
- It's time go.
- Yeah, we gotta go. Gotta go.
?
Okay.
Anything gets in here,
take it down.
[ Clip clicks ]
Hey.
You got this.
[ Sliding, thudding sounds ]
[ Low growling ]
All right, girls.
Let's go to work.
[ Loud growl ]
[ Gunshots ]
?
Kaia: There!
[ Branch snaps ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Squish ]
Uhh! [ Gasps ]
?
[ Whispers ] Kaia.
[ Grunts ]
?
[ Thudding steps approaching ]
[ Foliage rustling ]
[ Roars, snarling ]
?
[ Gunshots ]
[ Growls ]
[ Gunshots, glass shatters ]
[ Screeching ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Growling ]
[ Gunshots ]
[ Canid screeches ]
?
- No, no, no, no, no! Claire!
- Aah!
- Come on. We gotta go.
- Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
[ Roaring ]
[ Zaps ]
[ Screeching ]
Aah!
[ Gasping ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Zaps ]
[ Claire panting ]
No!
[ Grunts ]
Claire: [ Grunts ] No.
[ Crying ]
?
[ Sobbing ]
[ Sobs ]
Sam: Bye, guys.
You know, I tried
talking to her.
Yeah, she's, uh, she seems
pretty shut down.
Claire's gonna need
a lot of time.
Well...um...
when she is ready
to hear it...
You tell her “thank you”
from us.
Jody, that rift
was open for a while.
More of those things
may have come through.
Now we've seen some freaks,
but over there,
it's a whole new world of bad.
We will handle it.
Come on. You guys
take care of the world.
We got Sioux Falls covered.
Damn right you do.
?
[ Car door opens, closes ]
[ Engine starts, revs ]
?
Bye.
[ Knock on door ]
Hey.
Claire...
You were right.
Now this isn't on you,
not all of it.
No.
I told you to go.
I didn't even think.
I just raced in. No plan.
I said I'd protect her.
I get it now...
why you are
the way you are with me.
?
Because of the...
this feeling.
?
You don't have
to do this alone.
When you're ready,
if you want...
we're all here for you.
?
I killed a monster.
[ Donna and Alex chuckle ]
What?
Welcome to the family.
?
[ Inhales deeply,
exhales sharply ]
[ Sniffles ]
?
Claire: [ thinking ]
I came back to Sioux Falls
to save
Sam and Dean Winchester.
And...I did.
No...
[ Jody speaks indistinctly ]
We did.
Oh, here. Here.
We saved Sam and Dean.
All of these amazing women.
My family.
They don't know it yet.
They think I'm staying
because I'm broken.
But I'm staying
because I need them.
My family.
My army.
[ Indistinct conversation ]
The thing that killed Kaia
is still out there.
?
And I don't care if
I have to tear another hole
in the universe.
?
We're going to find it.
[ Zaps ]
?
And I'm going to kill it.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man