Your Men of Letters,
chroniclers of all that which
man does not understand.
Most are dead or defunct,
but others, I'm not so sure.
- What is this?
- Our crest.
The Aquarian Star.
This is actually
their lair. We're legacies.
- Ketch.
- Who are you working for?
Mr. Ketch...
meet the Archangel Gabriel.
Insanidox Koth Munto.
No, please! No!
Please.
Insanidox Koth Munto...
Yokoth.
Insanidox Koth Munto,
Yokoth! Yokoth!
Yokoth!
? Supernatural 13x17 ?
The Thing
Original Air Date on April 5, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Dean?
Yeah?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Uh...
Whatcha readin'?
Well...um...
I finally found something
on the Seal of Solomon,
but it -- it's really weird.
- Yeah. Hit me!
- All right.
“Then Mighty Solomon
commanded unto his priests,
“'Bind my seal.'
But the jewel was of
the cosmos.”
“Jewel of the cosmos”?
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Maybe a-a meteorite?
Mm. Yeah, maybe.
Well, forget what it is.
Where the hell would that be?
It doesn't say.
Okay, so, we've got
blood of a holy man,
we've got fruit from
the Tree of Life,
but this piece of Kryptonite,
we've been through every book
in this place
and we got squat.
Yeah.
All right. I guess we should
check the archives again.
Great.
All right.
I go left, you go right.
I love books.
What?
Nothing.
Pfft.
Oh, come on.
Are you kidding me? Dean!
S-- Hey.
Are you serious?
What?
Oh. It's hilarious.
Forget that. Look.
The Men of Letters found it.
Solomon's treasure.
Where?
1917, in what is
modern day Israel.
According to this,
they dug it up.
And, uh, here, look at
the, uh, right there.
Uh, “among the items found --
a crystal that glowed
with an unearthly light.”
That's gotta be the seal, right?
It's gotta be. Where is it?
Uh, uh, it says that
they took it to, uh,
Cap-- “Capitalum” Seven
in Portsmouth, Rhode Island.
Capitulum Seven.
Yeah.
Capitulum means, uh,
“chapterhouse.”
Yeah.
So the Men of Letters has --
has only one bunker,
but they have smaller outposts
all over the place.
Capitulum One is in Jamestown.
Capitulum Seven, I guess,
is in Portsmouth, Rhode Islandla
There it is.
Jinkies.
You're gonna stop saying that
eventually, right?
I don't know. Probably not.
Look...
Let's go!
You sure this is it?
That's what the map says.
So where's the door?
Dean.
Huh.
No way.
Ask questions, get answers.
This way.
Looks familiar, huh?
Yeah.
Except for that.
Mm.
Great.
More books.
You love books.
All right, look for anything
on King Solomon.
Don't know where to start, Dean.
Hmm.
No way.
Dean?
Hmm?
Check this out.
Who's there?
Help me!
Is someone there?!
Hurry!
Please! Please!
Who are you?
We're help to help you.
But...
How long have you
been down here?
I don't know.
You have to get me out of here.
Wait. Are you...
are you Sandy Porter?
Born in 1903?
Yes.
Thank God you found me.
No, no, no, no.
Asmodeus is busy.
Then why did he call
for me?
Don't know. Ask him yourself
when he's ready,
which he isn't,
because he's busy, so...
Might you have something
to read?
That's...not possible.
It's true.
Sandy, it's 2018.
You were down there
for almost 100 years.
No. You're lying.
Sandy, I know it's a lot
to take in, okay? But...
Well, look, this is --
this what a car looks like now.
Well, they should.
This...this is a phone
and a camera
and...everything else.
Welcome to the future.
Please.
Yeah, no way.
This thing's amazing.
Look, you just click on
the kitty video.
It loads just like that.
Look! Napping in a sunbeam!
Look at him!
Look at this little guy.
His little hat!
Oh, yeah. I love cats.
There we go.
Oh, just a little more.
Bad time?
My lord, I...
I tried to stop him.
Did you now?
Look, you called for me.
I came.
If you don't need me,
I have --
Ketch, Ketch, Ketch.
My boy.
I called you
'cause you work for me.
And I need you
when I need you.
That's not our arrangement,
and I'm not the help.
This is a freelance contract.
So be a good lad...
and wait.
Amy.
Hey, Buck. Have you decided
what you want?
Yeah. I'd like to try
something different.
Poor Buck.
He comes in here
bird-dogging after Amy,
and she won't give him
a simple yes or no.
Well, whatever you think, Amy.
I mean, you know better than me.
So many.
Still, if Amy don't want any,
I'll go a few rounds
with that boy.
Yeah, bring it on.
Ohh. I like talking
with you, Marco.
You make me laugh.
Sit anywhere you like, hon.
Everything's so...
Thanks.
electric.
Yeah.
Folks, what'll it be?
Uh, well, what's good?
Well, people love
the Clam Cakes,
but if you ask me,
gotta try the Stuffies.
I don't know what Stuffies are.
I'll take two.
And the Clam Cakes.
Anything to drink?
- Uh, water will be great.
- Oh, that's exciting.
It comes with a lemon.
You sure you can handle that?
How 'bout you, sweetie?
Oh, my goodness.
You're all skin and bones.
When's the last time
you ate somethin'?
You know, let's get her
the, uh, the -- the meat loaf.
? But if you'd only
look at me ?
? I'd show you how true
love can be ?
Marco?
We got a problem.
Yes, we do.
A very big problem.
I don't...
how...
How am I still alive?
Um...
we don't really know yet.
And...and how are you so calm
about the fact that...
I'm still alive?
This kind of weird.
It's sort of our thing.
I-I don't know what that means.
It means we can help you.
We just have to, um...
You know what? Let's start
with the basics.
How did you get down there
in the first place?
I met this man.
He said that he was...
a part of a secret club.
I thought he was talking about
a speakeasy or something.
But he called it
Men of...Words?
Men of Letters?
Yes.
How -- how did you know that?
Like I said,
it's sort of our thing.
Wait a second.
So these Men of Letters,
they were the ones who --
who chained you down there?
I think.
I-I...
Sandy, whatever happened
down there,
you're safe now, okay?
We'll protect you.
I promise.
There was chanting...
Insanidox Koth Munto.
Please. Please.
And then there was this...
light.
Yokoth! Yokoth!
Like a...
rip in the air.
And it happened...
They were using me to...
to feed it.
To feed what?
The monster.
Sure I can't get you
any coffee?
Excuse me.
Sweetie, you okay?
Mr. Ketch.
Sorry to keep you waitin'.
Why am I here?
The pieces to a spell.
A real big magic
sort of affair.
I've heard.
Their pet angel was just
in the Holy Land.
You knew and didn't tell me?
You didn't ask.
I shouldn't have to ask.
I was merely gathering
intelligence.
In the future, you let me
fill in the blanks.
The last prophet that
checked out of here
said they was trying to
open up a portal
to another, even more
epically messed up world.
To do that, they need
ingredients.
We need to stop 'em.
Ingredients? Such as?
Well, if they got the spell
from the Demon Tablet,
which they did --
some blood, few other things,
and a whole mess
of archangel grace.
Ah.
And here you are,
pumping it into your veins.
Everyone needs a little
pick me up from time to time.
But enough about my juice box.
It's time we talk about us.
You see...
I don't believe you understand
the nature of this relationship.
You pay me, I do what
needs to be done.
End of transaction.
Yeah. See, no.
It's more like, I own you.
You don't o--
And it's time
you get in line, boy.
If that's how you feel,
I believe I'm done here.
Good day.
Hmm.
You're done when I say
you're done.
Ooh.
You're gonna learn, son.
You do what I say...
when I say!
And if you ever even think
about sassing me again...
Ah. Look what you did
to my suit.
- Okay, what the hell, man?
- I mean...
we tested her
for everything --
holy water, silver,
she passed it all, so...
Yeah, and she's been
down in a basement for 90 years.
How does she look
the way she does?
And this doesn't sound like
the Men of Letters either.
I mean, they're boring. They wear tweed.
They smoke from pipes.
They -- they...
they don't kidnap people.
Except apparently, they did.
Oh, and this, uh, the --
the -- the flash of light
Sandy talks about seeing,
the “rip in the air,”
sounds like --
Like a rift.
So what now? They're opening
doors to different worlds
and -- and Buffalo Billing
chicks?
And feeding a monster.
So...not boring after all.
But all the Men of Letters
died 60 years ago.
Longer than that.
So then, who's been
keeping her down there?
You know what? How 'bout this?
You stay here with Sandy.
I'll go back --
No, no, no, no. What?
What?
I'm not gonna let you
go back there by yourself.
- Dean --
- No, this is what we're gonna do.
We're gonna find Sandy
a motel room.
We're gonna teach her
how to use the TV.
Well, we're gonna have
to tell her what a TV is.
- And then we're gonna go back together.
- Here we go.
Lobster roll, no bun, and kale
salad for you, String Bean.
Kale's a garnish.
It's healthy.
I'm watching my cholesterol,
like you should be.
Yeah, I'm watching
my cholesterol.
Watching it go up.
Well, I guess
I will see you...
later.
All right.
What the hell?
- Clam Cakes.
- Mmm.
Two orders of Stuffies.
See? Garnish.
And meat loaf
for our young lady.
Hey. Something weird's
going on.
Sam.
Go get Sandy.
Sam? Sam?
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Wait -- wait...
Sandy!
What's going on?
Hey. Wait. Wait. What's...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Aah!
Sandy! Come here. Sit down.
Buck!
Ah!
- Dean?
- Sammy!
Dean.
Hey! What are you doing?
Sammy!
They're still out there.
We gotta call the police.
My phone's not working.
They're all dead. Landline, too.
Who's that?
The police.
What are you doing?
They took my brother.
I'm gonna get him back.
Who are you?
What do you want?
What you stole from us.
The monster.
The what?
Less a monster, more a god.
A...
Wait, what are you
talkin' about?
How'd you find our chapterhouse?
My -- my brother and I,
we -- we're, uh...
our family was Men of Letters.
So was ours.
Kinda.
Kinda?
Our great-grandfather,
Diego Avila, was a member.
Well, until he --
He went psycho.
Jim Jones style.
Pretty much.
Diego fought in World War I,
and after that,
all he could see was blood
and violence in this world,
so he decided to fix it.
How?
Summon a god from another
dimension and start over.
“Upon us we shall call forth
new gods,
“Yokoth
and her mate Glythur.
“And they will cleanse
this world of hate
and bring a new paradise.”
They summoned Yokoth, but...
didn't exactly bring paradise.
It ate Diego and most
everyone else.
Then it tried to summon its mate
before they bound it.
Men of Letters
disavowed the whole deal.
It banned all the survivors,
closed down
the chapterhouse tight.
Our grandparents,
our parents,
us,
we've been watching over it
ever since.
You mean...
Sandy?
You think you're
so high and mighty,
better than the rest of us.
But you, Mr. Ketch,
you are more wicked
than any demon I know.
I know 'em all.
At least I still have
a soul.
What you think
that buys you, huh?
Souls are messy,
all conflict and confusion.
Well, I know who I am.
Do you?
Because you say you have
this code,
this Men of Letters code,
handed down for centuries.
But wait. Wait a minute.
You work for me.
You act like you're this
cold-blooded killer.
But you know what I see
when I look in your eyes?
Fear.
And regret.
And pain.
I see
your chewy middle, boy.
You want redemption,
but you ain't never gonna
get it.
Your kind -- our kind --
we can't be redeemed.
All we can do is
spread our pain around.
So no, you don't know
who you are.
But I do.
Which is why
no matter where you go,
no matter what you do,
you're mine.
Are they gone?
Someone -- someone should see
if they're gone.
No. No, not happening.
You're trying to tell me
Sandy is a god
from another dimension?
All she wants to do is eat.
And breed.
Then why didn't you kill it?
You don't think we've tried?
As far as we know,
she can't die.
So we have been
keeping her locked up.
Well, that is,
until you came along.
So, you know,
nice work on that one.
When we saw what you did,
we knew that we had
to get her back.
So Marco slipped something
into your food.
Oh, you don't say.
We have been starving Yokoth
for decades, keeping her weak.
But if she gets food
in her belly...
We're all dead.
Hey.
Sandy?
Ohh!
Oh.
What are you looking at?
If I had half your power,
I'd...
In fact...
I believe it's time to go.
Consider this a rescue.
Come on, you. Come on!
Come on.
This would all go
so much faster
if you just flapped
your bloody wings.
What the hell?
Where were we?
Aah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
String Bean.
I-I thought you were dead.
No, not yet.
Where's my brother?
He came out
to check on Buck.
It's them.
No, take it easy.
They're with us.
What?
It's a long story.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
She got food in her belly.
Dean.
If she fed on him,
he would be here.
So what, then?
It's like we said --
if she's not feeding,
she's breeding.
Sandy, what the hell?
Sandy's dead.
She's been dead
for a long time.
Okay. I'll play.
What's your name?
Yokoth.
Star of Madness.
Ravager of Galaxies.
Mother of Faceless Hordes.
Cool.
Let me guess.
You're not from around here.
I'm really not.
When the foolish humans
open the door,
they had no idea
what was waiting for them
on the other side.
You mean you?
I mean us.
It was supposed to be us.
Glythur and I, together.
But my love...They shut the riff
before he could make it through.
Oh, my god. That's tragic.
It's like a Hallmark movie.
But with tentacles.
I like you, Dean.
You're strong.
And I enjoy looking at
your face.
Whew.
You're making me blush.
That's why I'm going
to allow you
to be Glythur's host.
Sorry, what?
The host?
We've consumed
most of our universe,
but this one is so full
of...
light.
And of life.
Y...
And it looks...
It looks delicious.
Okay, look, I don't know
what kind of
kinky Gatekeeper-Keymaster thing
you got going on here, but...
I think I'll pass.
Shh.
Insanidox Koth Munto, Glythur!
She has
the Seal of Solomon!
You can't kill me!
Panto Koth Munto!
No!
Aah!
Dean.
Glad you could make it.
So...
that's why we came.
I mean, we -- we -- we need
the seal to get our family back.
If it could take us somewhere
other than, uh,
tentacle porn land --
not that there's
anything wrong with that.
When you cast a spell,
you need a guide,
something that's been
where you need to go.
Got it?
Got it.
Careful.
When you open the door, it only
stays open for 24 hours.
And you never know
what's on the other side.
Well, whatever it is,
we'll be ready.
I hope you're right.
You sure
you're all right?
Considering I was
about three seconds away
from being
an interdimensional booty call,
yeah,
I'd say I'm all right.
Well...
we have the Seal. Right?
So all we need now is
an archangel, and we're set.
Sure, that sounds easy.
Yeah.
- Wait.
- Son of a bitch.
I come in peace.
Yeah, right.
And I brought you a gift.
Wait a second. Is that...
That Gabriel?
No, no, that's impossible.
He...
He's dead.
We...we saw him die.
Or did you?
What did you do to him?
Not me. Asmodeus.
The Prince was
holding him prisoner
until I liberated
the poor man.
And I understand
you may need
an archangel for a spell,
perhaps.
Well, what luck.
We need his grace.
No, no, no, no, no.
Calm down. Calm down.
Nervy.
Here.
Take that. And, uh...
Mm.
The archangel blade.
Why would you...
What's the catch?
What do you want?
Protection.
From Asmodeus.
The one you're working for?
Was working for.
But when he finds out that
I stole his prize milk cow,
well, I imagine that he'll hunt
me to the ends of the Earth.
So...
this is the only
safe place I know.
What? Do you think
you're just gonna move in?
Dibs on the top bunk?
- No.
- Deal.
What?
I don't know what the hell's
going on here.
But if this helps us get Mom
back, helps us get Jack back,
then...sure.
Whatever you want.
Gabriel...Man,
what happened to you?
All right, let's do this.
Well,
shouldn't we wait?
Wait? Why?
We got everything we need.
Everything else is just
burning daylight.
Come on.
Let's open this door.
All right.
I'll gather my gear.
Uh...hold on.
I'm heading in alone.
What?
Look, we got
a busted up archangel here.
And who the hell knows
what else? Okay?
Somebody's gotta stay here
just in case.
And I'm coming with you.
As I said,
Asmodeus will be hunting me
to the ends of the Earth,
so it's better if
I'm not on this Earth.
It's not that much better
over there.
You know it's
a war zone, right?
Won't be my first,
shan't be my last. Hmm?
Fine.
Fine?
So you want Ketch to go
and not me?
I don't care if he dies.
Hell, I'm kind of
rootin' for it.
Still, you can't --
No, I have to.
It takes something
that's been over there before
to open up the right door,
so that's either you or me.
So I'm gonna go.
And if something happens to me,
if -- if -- if time runs out,
then I need you
to come and save me
and save Mom and save
whoever else, okay?
It's safer
if we go together.
Oh, there's no such thing as
safer over there. You know that.
I know you don't like this,
okay? I don't expect you to.
This is the way it's gonna be.
Something that's been there,
right?
All right.
Remember, it's only 24 hours.
Koth Munto Notox.
Okay.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man