Resync: Xenzai[NEF]
I think he wants us to pick up
where he left off.
Saving people, hunting things.
Family business.
I don't understand the blind faith
you have in the man.
It's called being a good son.
You're just pissed off
you couldn't control me anymore.
lf only your boys knew
how much their daddy loved them.
Dad?
-Did he say anything to you?
-No.
I'm dealing with Dad's death.
Are you?
Listen to her purr.
You ever heard anything so sweet?
lf you two wanna get a room,
just let me know.
Oh, don't listen to him, baby.
He doesn't understand us.
-You're in a good mood.
-Why shouldn't I be?
-No reason.
-I got my car.
Got a case. Things are looking up.
Give you a couple of severed heads
and a pile of dead cows...
...and you're Mr. Sunshine.
How far to Red Lodge?
About another 300 miles.
Good.
The murder investigation is ongoing.
That's all I can share with the press.
Sure, we understand that.
But just for the record.
You found the first head last week,
correct?
Okay, and the other,
a Christina Flanagan.
-It was two days ago. Then--
-Excuse me, sir.
Oh, thank you.
-Sorry, time's up. We're done here.
-One last question.
-About the cattle.
-Excuse me?
The cows found dead...
...split open, drained,
over a dozen cases?
What about them?
So you don't think there's a connection?
Connection with...?
First, cattle mutilations.
Now, two murders.
Kind of sounds like ritual stuff.
You know, like satanic-cult ritual stuff.
You... .
-You're not kidding.
-No.
Those cows aren't being mutilated.
-You wanna know how I know?
-How?
Because there's no such thing
as cattle mutilation.
Cow drops, leave it in the sun...
...within 48 hours
the bloat will split it open so clean...
...it's just about surgical.
The bodily fluids fall down
into the ground, get soaked up...
...because that's what gravity does.
But, hey, it could be Satan.
What newspaper
did you say you work for?
-World Weekly News.
-Weekly World News.
-World--
-Weekly World.
World-- I'm new.
Get out of my office.
-John.
-Jeff.
Jeff, I know that.
Dr. Dworkin needs to see you
in his office.
But Dr. Dworkin's on vacation.
He's back and he's pissed.
He's screaming for you.
-So if I were you, I would:
-Okay.
Okay.
Those Satanists in Florida,
they marked their victims?
-Yeah. Reverse pentacle on the forehead.
-Yeah.
So much F'd up crap happens in Florida.
All right, open it.
You open it.
You wuss.
Well, no pentagram.
-Poor girl.
-Maybe we should look in her mouth.
See if those wackos
stuffed anything down her throat.
You know, kind of like the moth
in Silence of the Lambs.
-Yeah, yeah, go ahead.
-No, you go ahead.
-What?
-Put the lotion in the basket.
Right, yeah, I'm the wuss, huh?
Whatever.
-Dean, get me a bucket.
-Find something?
No, I'm gonna puke.
-Wait, lift her lip up again.
-What?
-You want me to throw up.
-No, no, no. I think I saw something.
What is that, a hole?
-It's a tooth.
-Sam, that's a fang.
A retractable set of vampire fangs.
You gotta be kidding me.
Well, this changes things.
You think?
-How's it going?
-Living the dream.
-What can I get for you?
-Two beers, please.
So we're looking for some people.
Sure. It's hard to be lonely.
Yeah, but that's not what I meant.
Great, so these people, they would've
moved here about six months ago.
-Probably pretty rowdy, like to drink.
-Yeah, real night owls, you know?
Sleep all day, party all night.
Barker Farm got leased out
a couple months ago. Real winners.
They've been in here a lot.
Drinkers. Noisy.
I've had to eighty-six them
once or twice.
Thanks.
-Smile.
-What?
-Show us those pearly whites.
-For the love of--
You wanna stick that thing
someplace else? I'm not a vampire.
Yeah, that's right. I heard you guys.
-What do you know about vampires?
-How to kill them.
Now, seriously, bro,
that knife's making me itch.
-Hey.
-Whoa, easy there, Chachi.
See? Fangless. Happy?
Now, who the hell are you?
Sam and Dean Winchester.
I can't believe it.
I met your old man once.
Hell of a guy. Great hunter.
I heard he passed. I'm sorry.
That's big shoes.
But from what I hear, you guys fill them.
Great trackers. Good in a tight spot.
-Seem to know a lot about our family.
-Word travels fast.
-You know how hunters talk.
-No, we don't, actually.
I guess there's a lot
your dad never told you, huh?
So... .
So those two vampires,
they were yours.
Yup. Been here two weeks.
-Check out that farm?
-A bust. A bunch of hippie freaks.
They could kill you
with that patchouli smell.
Where's the nest, then?
I got this one covered.
Don't get me wrong,
it's a real pleasure meeting you.
But I've been on this thing
for over a year.
I killed a fang back in Austin,
tracked the nest here.
I'll finish it.
-We could help.
-Thanks.
But I'm a go-it-alone type of guy.
Come on, I've been itching for a hunt.
Sorry. But, hey, I hear there's
a chupacabra two states over.
Go ahead and knock yourselves out.
It was real good meeting you, though.
I'll buy you a drink on the flip side.
So I guess I gotta buy you that drink.
Here you go.
-No, no, I got it.
-Come on.
I insist.
-Thank you, sweetie.
-You're welcome. Thanks.
-Another one bites the dust.
-That's right.
Dean...
...you gave that big-ass fang
one hell of a haircut, my friend.
-Thank you.
-That was beautiful, absolutely beautiful.
-Well. You all right, Sammy?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-Well, lighten up a little, Sammy.
-He's the one who gets to call me that.
Okay. No offense meant.
Just celebrating a little. Job well done.
Right, well, decapitations
aren't my idea of a good time, I guess.
Oh, come on, man.
It's not like it was human.
-You gotta have fun with your job.
-That's what I've been trying to tell him.
You could learn a thing or two
from this guy.
Yeah, I bet I could.
Look, I'm not gonna
bring you guys down.
I'm just gonna go back to the motel.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
Sammy.
Remind me to beat that buzz kill
out of you later, all right?
-Something I said?
-No, he just gets that way sometimes.
Tell you what...
...match quarters for the next round.
So I pick up this crossbow,
and I hit that ugly sucker...
...with a silver-tipped arrow
right in his heart.
Sammy's waiting in the car...
...and me and my dad
take the thing into the woods...
...and burn it to a crisp.
I'm sitting there and I'm looking
into the fire and I'm thinking to myself:
"I'm 1 6 years old.
Kids my age are worried about pimples,
prom dates.
I'm seeing things
that they'll never even know.
Never even dream of. "
-So right then, I just sort of--
-Embraced the life?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
How'd you get started?
First time I saw a vampire,
I was barely 18.
Home alone with my sister.
I hear the window break in her room.
I grab my dad's gun, run in.
Try to get it off her.
It was too late.
So I shoot the damn thing...
...which is about as useful
as snapping it with a rubber band.
It rushes me, picks me up,
flings me across the room...
...knocks me out cold.
When I wake up...
...the vampire's gone...
...my sister is gone.
And then?
Then... .
Try explaining that one
to your family.
So I left home.
And then bummed around,
looking for information.
How you track them,
how you kill them.
And I found that fang.
It was my first kill.
Sorry about your sister.
Yeah.
She was beautiful.
I can still see her, you know?
The way she was.
But, hey, that was a long time ago.
I mean, your dad.
It's gotta be rough.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know,
he was just one of those guys.
Took some terrible beatings...
...and just kept coming.
So you're always saying to yourself,
you know:
"He's indestructible.
He'll be always around.
Nothing can kill my dad. "
And just like that:
He's gone.
I can't talk about this to Sammy.
You know, I gotta keep
my game face on.
But the truth is,
I'm not handling it very well.
-Feel like I have this--
-Hole inside you?
And it just gets bigger and bigger
and darker and darker?
Good. You can use it.
Keeps you hungry.
Trust me, there's plenty out there
needs killing and this'll help you do it.
Dean, It's not a crime to need your job.
-Harvelle's Roadhouse.
-Hey, Ellen, Sam Winchester.
Sam, it's good to hear from you.
-You boys are okay, aren't you?
-Yeah. Yeah, everything's fine.
-Got a question.
-Yeah, shoot.
You ever run across a guy
named Gordon Walker?
-Yeah, I know Gordon.
-And?
He's a real good hunter.
Why you asking?
We ran into him on a job
and we're kind of working with him.
Don't do that, Sam.
I thought you said
he was a good hunter.
And Hannibal Lecter's
a good psychiatrist.
Look, he is dangerous to everyone
and everything around him.
lf he's working on a job,
let him handle it, move on.
-Ellen--
-No, Sam.
You just listen to what I'm telling you,
okay?
Right, okay.
Know why I love this life?
It's all black and white.
There's no maybe.
You find the bad thing, kill it.
See most people spend their lives
in shades of gray.
ls this right, is that wrong? Not us.
I'm not sure Sammy would agree
with you, but... .
Doesn't seem like your brother's
much like us.
I'm not saying he's wrong,
just different.
You and me, we were born to do this.
It's in our blood.
Wait.
Step back, Eli.
My name's Lenore. I'm not gonna
hurt you. We just need to talk.
Talk? Yeah, okay.
But I might have a tough time...
...paying attention
to much besides Eli's teeth.
He won't hurt you.
You have my word.
Your word? Oh, yeah, great. Thanks.
No offense, but you're not
the first vampire I've met.
We're not like the others.
We don't kill humans.
We don't drink their blood.
We haven't for a long time.
-What is this, some kind of joke?
-Notice you're still alive.
Okay, correct me if I'm wrong here,
but shouldn't you be starving to death?
We've found other ways: cattle blood.
-You're responsible for all the--?
-It's not ideal. ln fact, it's disgusting.
But allows us to get by.
-Okay, why?
-Survival.
No deaths, no missing locals...
...no reason for people like you
to come looking for people like us.
We blend in.
Our kind is practically extinct.
Turns out we weren't as high up
the food chain as we imagined.
Why are we explaining ourselves
to this killer?
-Eli.
-We choke on cow's blood...
...so that none of them suffer?
Tonight, they murdered Conrad
and celebrated.
-Eli, That's enough.
-Yeah, Eli, that's enough.
What's done is done.
-We're leaving this town.
-Why did you bring me here?
-Why are you even talking to me?
-Believe me, l'd rather not.
I know your kind. Once you have
the scent, you'll keep tracking us.
It doesn't matter where we go.
Hunters will find us.
-You're asking us not to follow?
-We have a right to live.
-We're not hurting anyone.
-Right, you keep saying.
But give me one good reason
why I should believe you.
Fine.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to let you go.
Take him back. Not a mark on him.
This is the best pattern I can establish.
It's sketchy at best.
It's all coming from this side of town.
The nest would be around here, right?
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
Problem is there's 35, 40 farms
out there.
I've searched about half of them already,
but nothing yet.
Covering their tracks real good.
Well, I guess we'll just
have to search the other half.
What time is it? Where is Sam?
Car's parked outside.
Probably went for a walk.
-Seems like the take-a-walk type.
-Yeah, he is, but--
-Where you been?
-Can I talk to you alone?
You mind chilling out
for a couple minutes?
Maybe we gotta rethink this hunt.
What are you talking about?
Where were you?
-ln the nest.
-You found it?
They found me, man.
How'd you get out?
How many did you kill?
None.
-They didn't just let you go.
-That's what they did.
-All right, well, where is it?
-I was blindfolded. I don't know.
-Gotta know something.
-We went over that bridge.
-But maybe we shouldn't go after them.
-Why not?
I don't think they're killing people.
You're joking.
Then how do they stay alive or undead,
whatever the hell they are?
The cattle mutilations.
They live off of animal blood.
-And you believed them?
-Look at me, Dean.
They let me go without a scratch.
Wait, so you're saying--?
No, man. No way.
I don't know why they let you go.
I don't really care.
We find them and we waste them.
Why?
What part of "vampires"
don't you understand?
If it's supernatural, we kill it.
That's our job.
No, Dean, that is not our job.
Our job is hunting evil.
lf these things aren't killing,
they're not evil.
Of course they're killing people.
They're all the same, Sam.
They're not human, okay?
We have to exterminate them.
No, Dean. I don't think so, all right?
Not this time.
Gordon's been on those vamps
for a year.
-Gordon? You're taking his word for it?
-That's right.
Ellen says he's bad news.
You called Ellen?
And I'm supposed to listen to her?
We barely know her.
-No, thanks. I'll go with Gordon.
-Because Gordon's such an old friend.
-You think I can't see what this is?
-What?
-He's a substitute for Dad. A poor one.
-Shut up, Sam.
He's not even close, Dean.
Not on his best day.
-I'm not gonna talk--
-You slap on this fake smile...
...but I can see through it.
I know how you feel.
Dad's dead, and he left a hole
and it hurts so bad you can't take it.
But you can't just fill that hole
with whoever you want to.
It's an insult to his memory.
Okay.
You hit me all you want.
It won't change anything.
I'm going to that nest.
You don't wanna tell me where it is,
fine. I'll find it myself.
Dean.
Gordon?
-You think he went after them?
-Probably.
-We have to stop him.
-Really? Because I say we lend a hand.
Just give me the benefit of the doubt,
would you? You owe me that.
Yeah, we'll see.
I'll drive. Give me the keys.
He snaked the keys.
I can't believe this.
I just fixed her up too.
The bridge, is that all you got?
The bridge was four and a half minutes
from their farm.
-How do you know?
-I counted.
They took a left out of the farm,
then turned right onto a dirt road.
Followed that for two minutes,
slightly uphill.
Then took another quick right
and we hit the bridge.
You're good.
A monster pain in the ass...
...but you're good.
-ln the truck, thank you.
-We can't leave like this.
Lenore, listen to me.
We need to stay and fight.
They were my friends, too, Eli.
My family.
That's not what I'm talking about.
This is self-defense. Kill or be killed.
They can't hunt us if they're dead.
Killing those three
wouldn't solve anything.
There's more where they came from.
We're outnumbered.
This is all we can do.
-Try and reason with--
-You can't reason with these people.
They're gonna kill us all anyway.
We should at least
take a few of them with us.
I'm not giving up hope.
lf we can change they can change.
Now, go into town
and gather the others.
We leave before sunrise.
Dead man's blood, bitch.
-Sam, Dean, come on in.
-Hey, Gordon, what's going on?
Just poisoning Lenore here
with some dead man's blood.
She's gonna tell us
where all her friends are.
-Wanna help?
-Look, man--
Grab a knife.
I was just about to start in
on the fingers.
Whoa, hey, let's all just chill out, huh?
-I'm completely chill.
-Gordon, put the knife down.
Sounds like it's Sammy
that needs to chill.
Just step away from her, all right?
You're right.
I'm wasting my time here.
This bitch'll never talk.
Might as well put her
out of her misery.
I just sharpened it
so it's completely humane.
-Gordon, I'm letting her go.
-You're not doing a damn thing.
Hey, hey, hey.
Gordon, let's talk about this.
What's there to talk about?
It's like I said, Dean, no shades of gray.
Yeah, I hear you.
-And I know how you feel.
-Do you?
The vampire that killed your sister
deserved to die. But this--
Killed my sister?
That filthy fang didn't kill my sister.
It turned her.
Made her one of them.
So I hunted her down
and I killed her myself.
-You did what?
-Wasn't my sister anymore.
It wasn't human. I didn't blink.
-Neither would you.
-So you knew all along then?
You knew about the vampires.
They weren't killing anyone.
You knew about the cattle
and just didn't care.
Care about what?
A nest of vampires
suddenly acting nice?
Taking a little time-out
from sucking people...
...and we're supposed to buy that?
Trust me.
Doesn't change what they are.
And I can prove it.
Let him go.
-Now!
-Relax.
lf I wanted to kill him,
he'd already be on the floor.
Just making a little point.
Hey.
You think she's so different?
Still wanna save her? Look at her.
They're all the same.
Evil, bloodthirsty.
No. No.
You hear her, Gordon?
We're done here.
-Sam, get her out of here.
-Yeah.
I've got you.
Gordon...
...I think you and I got some things
to talk about.
Get out of my way.
-Sorry.
-You're not serious.
Having a hard time believing it,
but I know what I saw.
lf you want those vampires,
you gotta go through me.
Fine.
What are you doing, man?
You're doing this for a fang?
Come on, Dean.
We're on the same side here.
I don't think so, you sadistic bastard.
You're not like your brother.
You're a killer. Like me.
Oh, sorry.
You know...
...I might be like you...
...and I might not.
But you're the one tied up right now.
I miss anything?
Not much.
-Lenore get out okay?
-Yeah.
All of them did.
Then I guess our work here is done.
How you doing, Gordy?
You gotta tinkle yet?
All right.
Well, get comfy.
We'll call someone in two or three days,
have them come out, untie you.
Ready to go, Dean?
Not yet.
I guess this is goodbye.
Well, it's been real.
Okay. I'm good now.
We can go.
-Sam.
-Yeah?
Clock me one.
-What?
-Come on. Come on.
I won't even hit you back. Let's go.
No.
Let's go. You get a freebie.
Hit me. Come on.
You look like you just went 1 2 rounds
with a block of cement, Dean.
I'll take a rain check.
I wish we never took this job.
It's jacked everything up.
What do you mean?
Think about the hunts we went on,
our whole lives.
-Okay.
-What if we killed things...
...that didn't deserve killing?
I mean, the way Dad raised us--
Dean, after what happened to Mom...
-...Dad did the best he could.
-I know he did.
But the man wasn't perfect.
And the way he raised us
to hate those things?
And, man, I hate them. I do.
When I killed that vampire at the mill...
...I didn't even think about it.
Hell, I even enjoyed it.
You didn't kill Lenore.
Well, but every instinct told me to.
I was gonna kill her, kill them all.
Yeah, Dean, but you didn't.
And that's what matters.
Yeah.
And because you're a pain in my ass.
I guess I might have to stick around
and be a pain in the ass, then.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Resync: Xenzai[NEF]
Subtitles by
RETAIL