Dad wants us to pick up
where he left off.
Saving people, hunting things.
The family business.
You know the truth about Sammy?
I've known for a while.
You get premonitions of people
about to die?
- Death visions?
- Yeah.
The demon said he had plans for me.
- Do you have any idea what he meant?
- No.
I want you to watch out
for Sammy, okay?
Did he say anything to you?
No.
Can't talk about this to Sammy.
Gotta keep my game face on.
You're on edge. You're erratic.
Except for when you're hunting,
then you're downright scary.
The truth is
I'm not handling it very well.
You're tailspinning, man.
And you won't let me help you.
No, no, no. You're not gonna...
No, I swear, it's not in me.
Oh, God. We're all gonna die.
- Maybe he's telling the truth.
- He's not him, not anymore.
No, stop. Stop it!
Ask her! Ask the doctor!
- It's not in me!
- I just...
I can't tell.
No, please. Don't, don't.
- I swear, I swear.
- I got no choice.
It's not in me. It's not in me.
Don't. Don't.
Please.
Sam?
Continue on OR-224 west.
There are two towns in the U.S.
named Rivergrove.
How come you're so sure
it's the one in Oregon?
There was a picture of Crater Lake.
Okay, what else?
I saw a dark room, some people,
and a guy tied to a chair.
And I ventilated him?
Yeah.
You thought
there was something inside him.
- A demon? Was he possessed?
- I don't know.
All your visions are tied
to the yellow-eyed demon.
Was there any black smoke?
Did we try to exorcise him?
No, nothing.
You just plugged him. That's it.
I'm sure I had a good reason.
I sure hope so.
What does that mean?
I mean, I'm not gonna waste
an innocent man.
- I wouldn't.
- Never said you would.
- Fine.
We don't know what it is,
but whatever it is...
...that guy in the chair is part of it.
Let's find him, see what's what.
- Fine.
He was there.
- Morning.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah.
Billy Gibbons, Frank Beard.
U.S. Marshals.
- What's this about?
- We're looking for someone.
A young man, early 20s.
He'd have a thin scar
right below his hairline.
- What'd he do?
- Well, nothing.
We're looking for someone else.
We think this young man can help.
He's not in any trouble or anything.
Well, not yet.
I think maybe you know
who he is, master sergeant.
My dad was in the Corps.
A corporal.
- What company?
- Echo 21.
So can you help us?
Duane Tanner's got a scar like that.
But I know him.
Good kid, keeps his nose clean.
Oh, I'm sure he does.
Do you know where he lives?
With his family, up Aspen Way.
Thank you.
Hey.
"Croatoan"?
- Yeah.
Roanoke? Lost colony? Ring a bell?
Dean, did you pay
any attention in history class?
Yeah. The shot heard around the world,
how bills become laws.
That's not school.
That's Schoolhouse Rock!
Whatever.
Roanoke was one of the first
English colonies in America, late 1500s.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I do remember that.
The only thing they left behind
was a single word carved in a tree.
- Croatoan.
- Yeah.
And, I mean, there were theories,
Indian raid, disease.
Nobody knows what really happened.
They were all just gone.
I mean, wiped out overnight.
You don't think that's what's
going on here? I mean...
Whatever I saw in my head,
it sure wasn't good.
But what do you think could do that?
Well, I mean, like I said,
all your weirdo visions...
...are always tied to
the yellow-eyed demon somehow, so...
We should get help.
Bobby, Ellen, maybe.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
I don't have a signal.
I don't either.
Line's dead.
I'll tell you one thing.
If I was gonna massacre a town,
that'd be my first step.
- Yeah?
- Hi.
Looking for Duane Tanner.
He lives here, right?
- He's my brother.
Can we talk to him?
- He's not here right now.
- You know where he is?
Yeah. He went on a fishing trip
up by Roslyn Lake.
- Your parents home?
- Yeah, they're inside.
Jake, who is it?
U.S. Marshals, sir.
We're looking for your son Duane.
Why? He's not in trouble, is he?
No. We just need to ask him
a couple routine questions.
When's he due back from his trip?
- I'm not sure.
- Well, maybe your wife knows.
You know, I don't know.
She's not here right now.
Well, your son said she was.
- Did I?
- She's getting groceries.
When Duane gets back,
there's a number where he can get you?
Oh, no,
we'll just check in with you later.
That was kind of creepy, right?
- Little too Stepford?
- Bigtime.
It's okay, Mom. It's not gonna hurt.
- No!
- Put it down.
Hello?
Hello, we need a doctor here.
Mrs. Tanner, what happened?
- She's been attacked.
- Dr. Lee?
It's okay.
- Bring her in.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Hey.
Is that...?
Mr. Tanner?
Was he attacked too?
No, actually, he did the attacking
and then he got himself shot.
- Shot?
- Yeah.
- And who are you?
- U.S. Marshal.
I'd show you my badge, but...
Oh, sorry. Bring him back here.
Wait, you said Jake helped him?
Your son Jake?
They beat me.
Tied me up.
- I don't believe it.
Pam.
Beverly, you have any idea
why they would act this way?
- Any history of chemical dependency?
No, of course not.
I don't know why.
One minute,
they were my husband and my son...
...and the next,
they had the devil in them.
We gotta talk.
Those guys were whacked out
of their gourds.
What do you think?
Multiple demons, mass possession?
If it's a possession, there could be more.
God knows how many.
It could be like a frigging
Shriner convention.
- Great.
- That's one way to wipe out a town.
- Take it from the inside.
- I don't know.
We didn't see any demon smoke
or any of the other usual signs.
Well, whatever.
Something turned him into a monster.
If you'd taken out the other one,
there'd be one less to worry about.
I'm sorry, all right?
I hesitated, Dean. It was a kid.
No, it was an it.
Not the best time
for a bleeding heart, Sam.
- How's the patient?
- Terrible.
- What the hell happened?
- We don't know.
- You just killed my neighbor.
- Didn't have a choice.
Maybe, but we need
the county sheriff. I need the coroner.
- Phones are down.
- I know, I tried.
- Tell me you got a police radio.
- We do.
But it crapped out,
like everything else.
I don't understand.
- How far to the next town?
- About 40 miles down to Sidewinder.
I'll go there
and see if I can find some help.
My partner will stick around,
keep you guys safe.
Safe from what?
We'll get back to you on that.
Huh.
What?
His lymphocyte percentage
is pretty high.
His body was fighting off
a viral infection.
- Really? What kind of virus?
- Can't say for sure.
Think an infection could've
made him act like that?
None that I've ever heard of.
Some can cause dementia,
but not that kind of violence.
Besides, I've never heard of one
that did this to the blood.
- Did what?
- There's this weird residue.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say it was sulfur.
Sulfur.
- Oh. Hey.
- Sorry, road's closed.
Yeah, I can see that. What's up?
- Quarantine.
- Quarantine?
- What is it?
- Don't know.
Something going around out there.
- Who told you that?
- County sheriff.
- Is he here?
- No. He called.
Say, why don't you get out of the car
and we'll talk a little?
Oh, you're a handsome devil,
but I don't swing that way, sorry.
I'd sure appreciate it if you got out
of the car, just for a quick minute.
Yeah, I bet you would.
I don't understand.
Are you saying my husband
and Jake had a disease?
That's what we're trying
to find out.
Now, during the attack,
do you remember...
...did you have any direct contact
with their blood?
Oh, my God.
You don't think
I've got this virus, do you?
Beverly, I don't know what to think.
But with your permission,
we'll take a blood sample.
- Hands where I can see them!
- Son of a--
Get out of the car!
Out of the car!
All right, easy there, big guy.
- Put it down! Down!
- Lower it now! You one of them?
- No, you? Could be lying.
- No.
- So could you.
- All right. All right.
We could do this all day, all right? Let's
take it easy before we kill each other.
- What's going on with everybody?
- I don't know.
My neighbor, Mr. Rogers...
- You got a neighbor named Mr. Rogers?
- Not anymore.
He came at me with a hatchet.
I put him down.
He's not the only one.
It's happening to everyone.
I'm heading to doc's place.
There's some people left.
- I'm getting out.
- There's no way out.
They got the bridge.
- I don't believe you.
- Fine, stay here. Be my guest.
Well, this ought to be a relaxing drive.
What if we all have it?
- What if we all go crazy?
- You've gotta stay calm.
All we can do is wait.
The marshal's bringing help.
I can't, I...
No, I've gotta go.
Pam.
No, you don't understand.
My boyfriend's out there.
I gotta make sure he's okay.
Hey, hey, wait. Wait, please.
I know you're upset, all right?
But it's safer if you stay here for now.
Help is coming.
There they are.
Sammy! Open up!
Did you guys get to a phone?
Roadblock.
- I'm gonna have a word. Doc's inside.
- All right.
What's going on out there?
I don't know. I feel like
Chuck Heston in The Omega Man.
The sarge is the only sane person.
- What are we dealing with? You know?
- Yeah, doc thinks it's a virus.
- Okay, great. What do you think?
- I think she's right.
- Really?
- Yeah.
The infected are trying to infect others
with blood-to-blood contact.
It gets better. The virus leaves
traces of sulfur in the blood.
- A demonic virus?
- Yeah, more like demonic germ warfare.
At least it explains
why I've been having visions.
- It's like a Biblical plague.
- Yeah.
You don't know
how right you are, Dean.
I've been poring
through Dad's journal.
Found something
about the Roanoke colony.
- And?
- Dad had a theory about Croatoan.
He thought it was a demon's name,
known as Dever or Reshef.
A demon of plague and pestilence.
Well, that's terrific.
Why here? Why now?
I have no idea.
But, Dean, I mean, who knows
how far this thing can spread.
We gotta get out of here.
We gotta warn people.
They've got one. In here.
What do you mean?
The wife. She's infected.
We gotta take care of this.
We can't leave her in there.
My neighbors, they were strong.
The longer we wait,
the stronger she'll get.
You're gonna kill Beverly Tanner.
Doctor, could there be any treatment?
Some kind of cure for this?
- Can you cure it?
- I don't even know what it is.
I told you, it's a matter of time.
Just leave her there.
You can't shoot her like an animal.
Sam.
Mark. What are you doing?
Mark, it's them.
They locked me in here.
They tried to kill me.
They're infected, not me.
Please, Mark.
You've known me all your life. Please.
You're sure she's one of them?
Yeah.
Ah! Oh, God. Is there any on me?
- Am I okay?
- You're clean. You're okay.
Why are we staying here?
Please, let's just go.
No, we can't,
those things are everywhere.
Oh, God.
Shh, shh, shh.
She's right about one thing.
We can't stay here.
We gotta get out,
to the roadhouse or somewhere.
- Let people know what's coming.
- That's a good point.
Night of the Living Dead
didn't end pretty.
I'm not sure we got a choice.
Folks up here are good with rifles.
Even with all your hardware,
we're easy targets.
So unless you got some explosives...
We could make some.
Hey! Let me in! Let me in, please!
It's Duane Tanner.
Oh, thank God.
Duane, you okay?
- That's the guy that I:
- Yeah.
Who else is in here?
Hey, whoa, whoa, easy there, chief.
Hey, doc, give Duane
a good once-over, would you?
Pam?
- Who are you?
- Never mind who I am.
- Doc?
- Yeah, okay.
Duane, where you been?
I was on a fishing trip up by Roslyn.
I came back this afternoon.
I saw Roger McGill being dragged out
of his house by people we know.
They started cutting him with knives.
I ran. I've been hiding in the woods
ever since.
Has anybody seen my mom and dad?
Awkward.
You're bleeding.
- Where'd you get that?
- I was running. I must've tripped.
Tie him up. There's rope there.
- Wait--
- Sit down!
Sorry, Duane. He's right.
We gotta be careful.
Careful? About what?
- Did they bleed on you?
- No. What the hell--? No!
Doc? Any way to know for sure?
Any test?
- I've studied Beverly's blood work.
- My mom?
It took three hours
for the virus to incubate.
The sulfur didn't appear
in the blood until then.
No, there'd be no way of knowing.
Not until after Duane turns.
Dean, I gotta talk to you. Now.
Sit in that chair over there.
This is my vision, Dean.
- It's happening.
- Yeah, I figured.
You can't kill him. Not yet.
We don't know if he's infected or not.
I think we're damn sure.
Guy shows up out of nowhere.
Got a cut, his whole family's infected.
We should keep him tied up
and wait and see.
For what? For him to hulk out?
Infect somebody else?
No, thanks, can't take that chance.
I'm not happy about this.
It's a tough job. You know that.
It's supposed to be tough.
We're supposed to struggle.
- That's the point.
- What does it buy us?
- A clear conscience, for one.
- Well, it's too late for that.
- What's happened to you?
- What?
You might kill an innocent man
and you don't even care.
You don't act
like yourself anymore.
You know what? You're acting like
one of those things out there.
Hey.
Open the damn door. Dean.
Don't do it, Dean! Don't.
No, no, no. You're not gonna...
No, no, I swear, it's not in me.
Oh, God. We're all gonna die.
Maybe he's telling the truth.
- No, he's not him, not anymore.
Stop, stop it!
Ask her. Ask the doctor.
It's not in me!
I can't tell.
Please, don't.
Don't, please. I swear, it's not in me.
It's not in me, I swear.
I swear, it's not in me. Don't. Don't.
I got no choice.
No.
Damn it.
It's been over four hours.
Duane's blood is still clean.
I don't think he's infected.
I'd like to untie him,
if that's all right.
Sure, yeah.
You know I'm gonna ask you why.
Yeah, I know.
So, why? Why didn't you do it?
We need more alcohol.
How you holding up, Pam?
Good.
It'll all be over soon.
In fact...
...I've been waiting
for this the whole time.
- For what?
- To get you alone.
She bled on him.
He's got the virus.
Doctor, check his wound again,
would you?
Doctor.
What does she need to examine him for?
You saw what happened.
Did her blood actually
enter your wound?
- Of course it did.
- We don't know for sure.
Can't take a chance.
You know what to do.
Nobody shoots my brother.
He won't be your brother
much longer. You said it.
- Nobody's shooting.
- You were gonna shoot me!
- You don't shut your pie hole, I might.
- Dean, they're right.
I'm infected.
Give me the gun and I'll do it.
- Forget it.
- I won't become one of those things.
- We've still got some time--
- For what?
I understand he's your brother,
I'm sorry. I gotta take care of this.
I'll say this once.
Make a move on him, you'll be dead.
You understand me?
I mean, do I make myself clear?
Dean.
- Then what are we supposed to do?
Get the hell out of here, that's what.
Take my car. You got the explosives.
There's an arsenal in there.
You two go with him. You got enough
firepower to handle anything now.
What about you?
Dean, no, no.
Go with them.
This is your only chance.
- Not gonna get rid of me that easy.
- No, he's right, man. Come with us.
Okay, it's your funeral.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for everything, marshals.
Oh, actually,
we're not really marshals.
Um... Oh.
Wish we had a deck of cards
or a foosball table or something.
Dean, don't do this.
Just get the hell out of here.
No way.
Give me my gun and leave.
For the last time, Sam, no.
This is the dumbest thing
you've ever done.
I don't know about that.
Remember that waitress in Tampa?
Dean, I'm sick.
It's over for me.
It doesn't have to be for you.
- No?
- No, you could keep going.
Who says I want to?
What?
I'm tired, Sam.
I'm tired of this job.
This life.
This weight on my shoulders.
Man, I'm tired of it.
So, what?
So you're just gonna give up?
I mean, you're just gonna
lay down and die?
- Dean, I know the stuff with Dad had--
- You're wrong.
It's not about Dad.
- I mean, part of it is, sure--
- Then what is it about?
You better come see this.
There's no one. Not anywhere.
They've all just vanished.
Well, it's been five hours
and your blood's still clean.
I don't understand it,
but you dodged a bullet.
But I was exposed.
- How could I not be infected?
- I don't know, but you're just not.
I mean, when you compare it
with the Tanners' samples...
What the hell?
What?
Their blood.
There's no trace of the virus.
No sulfur, nothing.
Doc, the sarge and I are getting
the hell out of here, heading south.
- You should come.
- I'd better get over to Sidewinder.
Get the authorities up here,
if they'll believe me.
Take care.
What about him?
He's gonna be fine.
No signs of infection.
Hey, man, don't look at me.
I got no clue.
I swear,
I'm gonna lose sleep over this one.
I mean, why here? Why now?
Where the hell did everybody go?
It's not like they just frigging melted.
And why was I immune?
Yeah. You know what?
That's a good question.
You know, I'm already starting to feel
like this is the one that got away.
Do you mind pulling over
up ahead there?
All right.
- I gotta make a call.
- No phone out here.
I got it covered.
What the hell is that?
It's over. You'll be pleased.
I don't think any more tests
are necessary.
The Winchester boy,
definitely immune, as expected.
Yes, of course.
Nothing left behind.
So... Last night.
You wanna tell me what the hell
you were talking about?
- What do you mean?
- What do I mean?
I mean, you said
you were tired of the job.
And that it wasn't because of Dad.
- Forget it.
- No, I can't. No way.
I thought we were gonna die.
You can't hold that over me.
No, you can't pull that crap
with me, man.
- You're talking.
- And what if I don't?
Then I guess I'll just
have to keep asking until you do.
I don't know, man.
I just think maybe we ought to...
...go to the Grand Canyon.
- What?
- Yeah, you know...
...all this driving back and forth
across country.
I've never been to the Grand Canyon.
Or we could go to TJ.
Or Hollywood,
see if we could bang Lindsay Lohan.
You're not making any sense.
I just think we should
take a break from all this.
Why do we gotta get stuck
with the responsibility?
Why can't we live life a little bit?
Why are you saying all this?
No, no, no, Dean.
You're my brother, all right?
So whatever weight you're carrying,
let me help a little bit.
I can't. I promised.
- Who?
- Dad.
What are you talking about?
Right before Dad died...
...he told me something.
He told me something about you.
What?
Dean, what did he tell you?