Dad wants us to pick up
where he left off:
Saving people, hunting things.
The family business.
You were the bank robber
on the 11:00 news, not me.
- Yeah?
- This is Agent Victor Henricksen.
My job's to bring you in.
Alive's a bonus, but not necessary.
I've been looking for you for weeks.
And I know about Sam.
I know about the murder in St. Louis,
the Houdini act in Baltimore.
I know about the desecrations
and the thefts.
I know about your dad.
You don't know crap about my dad.
We are so screwed.
Well, this makes a lot of sense.
First, they close down the cellblock
and now they open it back up again.
There's your tax dollars at work, huh?
Here.
You got that ready?
Yikes.
Would hate to have gotten
thrown in here.
- Hey, you feel that, man?
- What?
Whoa. What was that?
Uh...
Hey.
Hey, guard. Hey.
Come on, man.
Hey. Guard.
Come here. Come on. Help me.
Going down to B block. Randall again.
Copy that.
Come on, man.
- Hey. Guard, hey.
Shut up, old man.
Come on. I'm trying to sleep.
You telling me you didn't see that?
What are you, blind?
Hey!
Randall, cool it.
Cool it, my ass.
There's somebody there.
Turn out your light and go to sleep.
I'm not gonna say it again.
Yeah, Randall, shut up.
Lights out, B block.
Copy that. Lights out.
Good night, ladies.
- Aah! God!
What's going on, man?
What's going on?
No. No. No.
No! No! No!
Aah, no!
This way.
I hate this plan, Dean.
Yeah, I got that
the first 10 times I heard it.
Freeze.
Don't move.
I said freeze!
Hold it right there.
Put your hands behind your heads.
Sit down on your knees. Now.
I got them.
- Hands behind your back.
The other hand.
Front. To the right.
I call this one the "Blue Steel."
Yeah, that's great. To the right.
Okay, back to the lineup.
- Who looks better, me or Nick Nolte?
- Shut up.
Well, it's about time.
I'll have a cheeseburger.
Extra onions.
You think you're funny.
- I think I'm adorable.
It is a pleasure to finally meet you
in person, Dean.
I'm Special Agent Victor Henricksen.
This is my partner, Special Agent Reidy.
Henricksen.
Not the Milwaukee Agent Henricksen.
Live and in person.
Ha.
Oh, nice shot.
You can hang that up in your cell
at Supermax.
All right, maybe we can just forget
the cheeseburgers, huh?
Oh, yeah. Keep that game face on.
Try and cover up how cornered you are.
Read him the charges.
Well, we got mail fraud, credit card fraud,
grave desecration.
Skip to the good ones.
Armed robbery, kidnapping,
and, oh, three counts of first-degree murder.
And after Milwaukee, your brother is now
a suspect in a murder case himself.
I'd say for you two, "screwed to hell"
is a major understatement.
Well, where there's life,
there's hope, huh?
Ah, see, that's what I kept thinking...
...as I was searching for your assess
all over hell and gone.
Your dad taught you well.
The way you cover your tracks.
And after Milwaukee, the way you...
...vanished.
Near went nuts trying to find you.
- Ask him.
- He near went nuts.
And after all of that, you get tripped up
on a motion detector.
Pretty rookie move.
Gotta say, I was...
...surprised.
- Dean Winchester?
- In the flesh.
- And you are?
- Mara Daniels, Public Defender's Office.
I've been assigned you
and your brother's case.
Oh.
- Are you Henricksen?
- Yeah, and we're not quite done here.
Uh, yeah, you are.
And if you don't mind...
...I would like
to meet with my clients, privately.
Unfortunately, your arraignment
on the breaking and entering charge...
...won't be until Tuesday.
- And they'll keep us in the county jail?
- That's right.
- Green River County Detention Center?
- Yes.
And considering the charges
you're facing...
...no judge is going to grant bail.
Yeah, we figured that.
Extradition papers have already been filed
from five separate states.
Missouri and Wisconsin
being the biggest...
...the robbery and the murder raps.
How long can we stall extradition?
A week. Maybe less.
All right, let's go. Watch your step.
Come on. Keep moving.
- You're mine, baby.
Looking good, move it along.
Don't worry, Sam,
I promise I won't trade you for smokes.
I call top bunk.
Okay.
My roommate
doesn't say much, how's yours?
He just keeps staring at me...
...in a way that makes me really uneasy.
- It sounds like you're making new friends.
- Dean.
This is, without a doubt, the dumbest,
craziest thing we've ever done.
And that's in a long, storied career
of dumb and crazy.
Calm down. It's all part of the plan.
Oh, really? So Henricksen
showing up was part of the plan?
Yeah, that guy moves
a little faster than I thought.
Look, all we gotta do is find this ghost,
put the sucker down...
...then grab ourselves
a couple of teardrop tattoos.
That's not funny.
Dean, what about this escape plan? It-?
It's 100-percent sure.
I wouldn't have gone in if it wasn't.
I mean, come on, man,
this place has all the signs of a haunting.
- Innocent people are dead. Four so far.
- Yeah, innocent.
You from Texas all of the sudden?
Just because people are in jail...
...doesn't mean they deserve to die.
If we don't stop this...
...people are gonna continue to.
We do the job wherever it takes us.
Look, Dean,
just be straight with me, all right?
- You're doing this for Deacon.
- Damn right.
Well, you barely even know the guy.
We know he was in the corps with dad.
He saved Dad's life. We owe him.
But don't you think
he's asking a little much?
It doesn't matter.
We may not be saints,
but we're loyal and we pay our debts.
Now, that means something to me
and it ought to you.
I'm not thrilled about this either,
but Deacon asked us to hunt this...
...and that's what we're gonna do.
- You know, this chicken isn't half bad.
- Great. Finish mine.
All right, so let's go back over this.
Spirit suspect number one
is Mark Moody, right?
Yeah. Psycho-killer extraordinaire.
Satanism. Ritual murder. Died in jail.
- Are you sure it's him?
- Pretty sure.
Dean, considering our circumstances,
I'm gonna need a bit better than pretty sure.
Really pretty sure.
Moody died of a heart attack, which is
what the victims in here are dying of.
He died in the old cellblock, which they
closed after he croaked, 30 years ago.
They opened that back up,
the killings started.
You think his spirit
was released somehow?
Mm-hm.
What if he was already cremated?
I'm guessing there's something
that belongs to him keeping him around.
Whatever it is, we gotta find it,
and you know the rest. I'm done.
- Sorry, I-
- Watch where you're going.
- Yeah, sure, I just-
- He said he was sorry.
Dean.
- You talking to me?
Are you talking to me?
Great, another guy who's seen Taxi Driver.
Yeah, I'm talking to you.
Trust me. Let it go.
Dean, come on.
See, that's how you gotta talk
to these guys.
Instant respect.
You were saying?
Oh, great.
We can end this right now.
No harm, no foul.
That's enough!
On your feet, Lucas.
Yes, sir, boss.
- What's your name?
- Winchester.
Well, Winchester, not a good start.
Solitary.
You too, Lucas.
Yes, sir.
- Are we having fun yet, huh?
I wish I had a baseball.
What?
- What did you say?
- I said I wish I had a baseball.
You know, like Steve McQueen.
Yeah. Well, I wish I had a bat,
so I could bash your fricking head in.
Okay.
Well, so much
for the bonding-in-solitary moment.
Oh, crap.
Lucas, listen to me. Stay very still.
Aaarggh!
Henricksen?
Hey, Daniels.
Can I have a word?
Have a seat. What's on your mind?
I've been going through the Winchester
charges, and I gotta say...
...there are some weird inconsistencies.
Welcome to my world.
I talked to a cop in Baltimore
who swears up and down...
...these boys saved her life,
and helped her catch a killer.
There's a witness
to your robbery in Milwaukee...
- ...she swears Sam and Dean saved her life.
- From what?
- She was a little unclear on that.
- That's because she's nuts.
I was in Milwaukee.
I spoke to her, to all the witnesses.
- And?
- And, all I know is...
...wherever these guys go, people die.
It's that simple.
I don't know that it is.
They just don't seem cut-and-dry
guilty to me.
- I think there's more to this.
- Like what?
I don't know.
I can't put my finger on it.
It's just...
...strange.
Strange?
Yeah, okay.
Grownups are trying to get some
work done here, so if you don't mind...
How you doing?
I'm 54 years old, mopping the floor
of a crapper with bars on the windows.
How you think I'm doing?
All right.
Bad ice-breaker.
I'm Sam.
- Randall.
- Nice to meet you.
Randall? Hey, weren't you there
the night that guard died?
- Yeah.
- Well, what happened?
They say the stress of the job got him.
Yeah? What do you say?
Why are you inside, kid?
Because I got an idiot for a brother.
- That'll do it.
- Yeah.
Well, this place ain't so bad.
Compared to the old cellblock,
this is the Hilton.
You spent time in the old block?
Oh, yeah, I was a regular customer.
- Didn't they have Mark Moody for a while?
- He was there.
I was there too,
the night that lunatic bought it.
Yeah. It was a heart attack, right?
His heart stopped after the guards
stopped using his head for batting practice.
Next morning, I was in his cell
mopping up the blood. What a mess.
Wait, so he was beaten
and nobody reported it?
You kept your mouth shut unless you
wanted to die from the same heart attack.
Randall...
...exactly how much blood was there?
Call.
Three aces.
That's a bad beat.
That's bad beat, but see, I'm full.
Threes over aces.
Ha-ha. I'm sorry.
Hey, it's a cruel game, my friend.
Sorry, guys.
- It's like picking low-hanging fruit.
- You don't even smoke.
You kidding?
This is the currency of the realm.
Look, I got a good lead on Moody.
- Yeah, me too.
- His spirit paid a visit last night.
- What?
Clock-stop, flickering lights, cold spot.
I mean, he did everything but yell, "Boo."
- What happened?
- He walked right by me.
Lucas wasn't so lucky.
I mean, the way he was screaming...
The guy was a jerk,
but he didn't deserve to go like that.
What did you find out?
Yeah, so I think I know
where we might find his remains.
- Blood in his old cell.
- I thought it was a heart attack.
After the guards worked him over.
Apparently there was so much blood,
they had trouble mopping it out.
How we gonna get in?
I got a plan.
That's the Sammy I know.
You're like Clint Eastwood
from Escape From Alcatraz.
Problem is, if we find something,
how are we gonna burn it?
We don't have any accelerant.
Good thing I'm like James Garner
from The Great Escape.
Hey, fellas, who's ready to deal?
- You sure about this?
- Pretty sure.
Yeah, well, considering the circumstances,
I'd like a little better than pretty sure.
Okay, really pretty sure.
I'd like mine al dente.
Perfect.
Save room for dessert, Tiny.
Ha-ha-ha.
Hey, I wanted to ask you...
...because I couldn't help but notice
you are two tons of fun.
Just curious, is that a thyroid problem or is
that some deep-seated self-esteem issue?
Because, you know,
they're, uh, just doughnuts.
They're not love.
Guys, give me a hand.
Get him off.
- If we waited any longer, you'd be dead.
- You waited long enough.
Do yourself a favor. Don't talk.
Take them both up to the infirmary.
- Hey, Tiny.
- Yeah?
Hey, sorry about the things
I was saying earlier.
I can't really tell you why,
but I had to get you angry.
So...
- Anyway, sorry.
- It's okay.
The truth is,
I have low self-esteem issues.
My old man treated me
and my brother like crap.
Right up until the day he died.
How'd he die?
My brother shot him.
Okay.
- Oh, crap.
- What is it?
What's going on?
Oh, God.
What is it?
No!
Tiny.
Tiny!
Guard!
Wait, you're telling me it wasn't Moody?
Unless he liked going around
dressed like a nurse.
Poor Tiny, man. Poor, giant Tiny.
So this is like the ghost of some
nurse who worked here or something?
- I don't know, I guess.
- "I don't know, I guess"...
...isn't really working for me.
See, I thought we were done.
I called Deacon, it's happening.
We're getting out tonight.
I guess we gotta do
some quick research, then.
How? I mean, maybe you haven't noticed,
we're in jail.
So you wanna know about some nurse?
- Why do you wanna know?
We got our reasons.
But we'll make it worth your while.
So this nurse, she would have had
white hair, one screwed-up eye.
- Is that ringing a bell?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I remember her.
- You remember her name?
- No, that's still kind of fuzzy.
Give it to him.
- I earned these.
- Dean.
Glockner. Nurse Glockner.
- Nasty old bitch worked here in the '70s.
- You know her?
I met her once.
I had to get a tetanus shot.
She damn near jabbed the needle
through my arm.
- At least I got out of there alive.
- What do you mean?
There were stories,
I don't know if they were true.
- Cons love to talk, but we're all liars.
- What kind of stories?
Guys would go up with a cold,
next thing, they're in a body bag.
A whole rash of heart attacks.
Young guys. Old guys.
- Heart attacks?
- Yeah. The story was...
...Glockner had it out for cons...
...and she did this Charles Bronson thing
with a hypodermic.
That was the rumor.
Nobody proved anything.
- So whatever happened to Glockner?
- I don't know.
I finished my bit and left.
Next time I landed back in here,
she was gone.
Let's say those stories
on Glockner were true.
It's a thought. In life she's a vigilante.
In death, same thing.
But how's she tied in
with the old cellblock?
If she's going after cons,
why kill that guard?
I did hear in the yard
that guard wasn't exactly squeaky clean.
So, well, maybe she's going after anybody
that breaks the law, like me.
- You heard in the yard?
- Yeah.
Dean, does it bother you at all
how easily you seem to fit in here?
- No, not really.
- All right, well, listen.
Either way, we need more info on Glockner.
If she's buried.
If so, where?
And we got five hours to get it.
Don't give me that
we-gotta-see-this-thing-through look.
We are leaving tonight, no matter what.
I just don't wanna let Deacon down.
We owe him.
But we don't owe him our lives, Dean.
- Where you going?
- I'm gonna go talk with our lawyer.
You want me to what?
Her name was Glockner, okay?
She worked here as a nurse in the '70s.
Now, I need you to find out everything
about her, most importantly how she died.
- And where she's buried.
- Are you nuts?
You have any idea
the kind of the trouble you're in?
I have a vague notion.
Good, so let's forget about some
random nurse and talk about your case.
- Mara. It's Mara, right?
- Yeah.
I get that you're trying to help me, okay?
I do.
But believe me when I say
that this is the best way that you can help.
Really, how? Explain that to me.
I wish I could, but I can't. I'm just gonna
have to ask you to trust me on this.
Why should I?
- Henricksen says you're a monster.
- I'm a monster?
Well, he's wrong, okay?
I'm not what they say I am.
- Everybody says that.
- Yeah.
If you're as smart a PD as I think,
then you can tell with just one look...
...whether or not your clients are guilty,
okay? Just like that.
So I want you to look at me. Really look.
And you tell me, am I guilty?
We're not the bad guys.
- She go for it?
- No. No, not so much.
- Maybe she'll still come around.
- We can't wait around to find out.
- We could give it another day.
- No, we're leaving tonight, and that's it.
Not gonna finish?
We're gonna let people die?
Don't give me that.
This was your stupid plan.
I went along,
but we're sticking to the plan.
Okay, you leave, I'm gonna stay.
- Hey, don't turn away from me.
- Screw you.
What? Screw you.
Hey, hey.
All right, hard case.
I see the usual methods ain't gonna work.
You too, sweetheart.
Come on.
Take off.
I wanna handle this alone.
Deacon, you are beating the holy hell
out of me, man.
Sorry, Dean.
I thought I was going easy on you.
Just trying to make it look real.
Yeah, well, mission accomplished.
So is it over?
- No. It turns out it wasn't Moody.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Then who?
It's some nurse
who used to work here.
But we're shy on all the intel.
Which is why
we should stick around.
Oh, hey, guys.
- You wanna fight for real?
- We gotta go now.
Guys.
We're leaving. Otherwise we'll be leaving
for Milwaukee with Henricksen.
- Oh, come on.
- Guys.
What?
Your lawyer left this for you.
Would you look at that?
Man, I am frigging velvety smooth.
You wanna open it after you're done
patting yourself on the back?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Wow.
- What?
Well, you wanna share
with the class, Dean?
Glockner died in the old cellblock
after Moody bit it.
It seems they had a little inmate uprising,
she got caught in the middle.
They dragged her to a solitary cell,
gave her severe cerebral edema.
- Someone bashed her head in.
- Yeah.
- Say where she's buried?
- Yep.
Then let's get you the hell out of here.
Don't worry, we'll get rid of this thing.
Good, because I want it
out of my prison.
Boys, uh...
...I can't thank you enough for this.
I know it was asking a lot,
but you still came through.
Your daddy raised you right.
Well, we owed you.
I hope to see you again, huh?
Just not in here, okay?
- Yeah. We'll do our best.
Right. Yeah.
Oh.
- Where do you want it?
- What?
Yeah, um...
Uh...
Make it look real, son.
Oh, man, are you a sight for sore eyes.
You know, I almost wish
I could see Henricksen's face.
Really? I'd be happy
if I never saw him again.
- We're not really out of the woods yet.
- Yeah.
Good point.
I told you, one of them
came up behind me.
- You let them get the drop on you?
- Yeah.
I screwed up, all right?
- What do you want me to say?
- I wanna know where they're headed.
- How the hell would I know?
- Let's start over again.
For God's sake.
Again. I wanna know everything they did
today from the minute they woke up.
Got up.
Breakfast. Visiting hours. Rec time.
- Any visitors?
- Just their lawyer.
It's an easy question.
What did you and Dean talk about?
I have already told you...
...it was a private conversation
between me and my client.
Right. And just three hours later,
he just happened to bust out.
Now, tell me what he said.
We gotta move it.
If Henricksen gets to the lawyer...
I thought she couldn't say anything.
That lawyer-client privilege thing.
The privilege doesn't apply, Dean.
- So she'll talk?
- She has to.
Oh, that's frigging super.
Let me make this simple.
You don't come clean,
I will put you on the hook for abetting.
That's ridiculous.
Don't think that I can?
You think this is some game?
I am the last person on planet Earth
you wanna screw with.
Now, tell me what he said.
He wanted me to do some research.
On a prison nurse that died in 1976.
What? Why?
- I don't know.
- What else?
They wanted to know
where she was buried.
Did you find out where?
- Yeah.
- Did you tell them?
Yeah.
Tell me.
Got her.
Aah!
You let those two go.
You sure this is the right cemetery?
She said Mountainside.
Mountainside Cemetery.
- You thought we were screwed before.
- Yeah. Yeah, I know.
We gotta go deep this time.
Deep, Dean?
We should go to Yemen.
Oh, I'm not sure
I'm ready to go that deep.