San Francisco California
Hey, Maddie.
Listen,I,uh,hate to pull you away,
but I'm gonna need you to come back to the office with me.
Really?
Yeah,it turns out I got to file those docs by midnight.
I'm gonna need you to,um...
This isn't working at all,is it?
No,it's not,Nate.
Listen,I've had a couple.
I shouldn't really drive.
- Could you just give me a lift --
-  I already called you a cab.
I'll see you in the morning.
Does that happen a lot?
Only on the days that end with a "Y.
" You okay?
Yeah.
I've got to go.
www.opensubtitles.org/en
Supernatural 2x17 - HEART
here is the detective
That's a pretty nasty bite.
You know what bit him?
I haven't quite determined that just yet.
Come on,doc.
Off the record.
Okay,way,way off the record.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say the guy was attacked by a wolf.
But unless I know that the zoo is missing one of their lobos,
I'm going with pit bull.
I like my job.
Yeah,I hear you.
One more thing.
This guy -- was his heart missing?
Yeah,how did you know that?
I haven't even finished my report.
Lucky guess.
This lawyer guy first heart-free corpse in town?
First man.
Over the past year,several women have gone missing.
Dead bodies all washed up later in the bay,
too deteriorated to draw firm conclusions.
- But no hearts.
- No hearts
They were all hookers working at hunter's point.
Cops are trying to keep things under wrap,
- but they're looking for a serial killer.
- And the lunar cycle?
Yeah,month after month,all the murders happened
in the week leading up to the full moon.
- Which is this week.
- There is the lawer
Awesome.
Dean,could you be a bigger geek about this?
I'm sorry,man,but what about a human by day,
a freak animal killing machine by
moonlight don't you understand?
We haven't seen one since we were kids.
Okay,sparky.
Then you know what?
- After we kill it,we can go to disneyland.
- Know what the best part about it is?
We already know how to bring these suckers down.
So what's our next move?
Talk to the girl who found the body.
Madison: I don't understand.
I already gave my statement to you.
Well,we just need to verify a few things.
This is my neighbor glenn. Glenn,this is detective...
landis.
And detective dante.
Well,guess I'll leave you to it.
Okay.
Thanks for the casserole.
Oh,how thoughtful.
Just call if you need anything.
He's sweet.
He came over to check on me.
Have- have a seat.
You must be pretty shaken up.
You were nate mulligan's assistant,right?
For two years,yeah.
So you knew all about him.
Probably knew more about him than he did.
Nate was...
he was nice.
But...
You get a few scotches in him,and he started hitting
on anyone in a 5-miles radius.
You know the type.
Yeah. I do,actually.
- Did,uh,did he have any enemies?
- What do you mean?
Sure looked like an animal attack.
We're just covering all the bases.
Anyone that might have had a beef with him
- former client,an ex.
- What?
Well,this is embarrassing,
but my ex-boyfriend,kurt.
- Kurt have a last name?
- Mueller
After we broke up,he went kind of nuts.
He's...
well,he's kind of been stalking me.
He got it in his head that something was going on between Nate and I.
He showed up at my office.
- And what happened?
- Kurt got into it with nate.
Threw a punch before security grabbed him.
I was lucky to keep my job.
When was the last time you saw kurt?
A few nights ago.
Actually,the night Nate died.
We were all grabbing drinks at this bar,and Kurt showed up.
And?
Nothing.
It was...
like he was watching me.
Then he was gone.
Tell you the truth...
he scares me.
So,what do you think?
Stalker ex-boyfriend.
He hates the boss.
And he was there that night.
Think he's our dog-faced boy?
Well,it's a theory.
We've had worse.
What do you say we pay kurt a visit?
Nothing but leftovers and a six-pack.
Check the freezer.
Maybe there's some human hearts behind the
haagen-dazs or something.
Sam,come here.
Check it out.
Somebody there?
I'll call 911.
I'd say Kurt's looking more and more like our cujo.
If he's out here,we better check on Madison.
What's going on?
Police business,glenn.
What is it?
Well,maybe we should talk privately?
Has kurt been here?
Not exactly.
What exactly does "not exactly" mean?
Well,he was outside last night -- just looking.
Just looking at me.
Has he done something?
- We're not really sure.
- It's probably nothing.
But...
we just don't want to take any chances.
In fact,one of us should probably stay here with you,
just in case he stops by.
- Where does he work?
- He owns a body shop.
You mind grabbing that address for us? Thanks.
- All right,you go.I'll stay.
- You go after the creepy ex.
I'm gonna hang here with the hot chick.
Why do you always get to hang out with the girls?
Because I'm older.
No,screw that. We settle this the old-fashioned way.
Dean,always with the scissors.
Shut up. Shut up. Two out of three.
God!
Bundle up out there,all right?
- Um,do you want to sit on the couch?
- No. No,no,I'm okay.
- It's more comfortable.
- Uh,I'm fine.
You know,I think I will sit on the couch.
Let me guess.
You're sitting on her couch trying to think of something to say.
- Did you find kurt?
- He hasn't been at work all week,
but because I'm good,
and I mean really,really good,
I got a line on where he might be.
- What's she wearing?
- Bye,dean.
Oh,sammy.
- Who died and made you sheriff?
- I will call who I want.
Whatever you want. Look what time it is.
- You're gonna wake her up and start talking about -
- I saw that.
What? Saw what?
Okay,this is the deal --
my house,my tv.
I never get to watch my show,
so suck it up.
wait,so
so kindall married ethan's father just to get back at him?
And now she's set to inherit all the casinos that were supposed to go to ethan.
What a bitch!
- Admit it -- you're hooked.
- No,no,no,no,no,no.
I wouldn't say I'm hooked.
Can I ask you a question?
It's ... it's a little personal.
You've seen my entire underwear collection.
Go ahead.
Okay,um...
well,you're -- you're clearly smart.
I mean,your house is full of great books,you know?
- And you're independent.
- Uh-huh.
What were you doing with kurt?
I don't know.
I mean,it's not like he introduced himself,like,
"hi,I'm possessive and controlling,and I like to punch people.
Want to be my girlfriend?
" Yeah,well,
I guess we all make mistakes.
Yeah,well,mine's wanted by the police.
You want to know why I stayed with him? Really?
I was too insecure to leave.
Well,I find that hard to believe. You don't really seem like the type.
Yeah,well some stuff happened.
My life changed,I changed,for the better,I think.
- What happened?
- Well,for one thing,I got mugged.
And that's supposed to be a good thing?
I know,it sounds strange,
and don't get me wrong -- it rattled me --
but then it hit me.
I could keep feeling sorry for myself
or I could take control of my life.
I chose the latter.
First thing I did was tell kurt he had to go.
- Smart move.
- Apparently.
Everything else just opened up,blossomed.
It's all been wonderful,really.
What?
Doesn't everybody think that being a victim of random violence is
the best thing that ever happened to them?
Yeah,not so much.
You're...
unusual.
Unusual like...
- "unusual"?
- No,no,no.
Unusual like...
impressive.
You think so?
Sorry.
- Hey.
- I found him.
Good. Don't take your eyes off him.
Oh,yeah,my eyes are glued.
Look,sammy,I got to let you go.
I,uh,I don't want to miss anything.
So,um...
I'm gonna turn in.
Okay,yeah.
- Well,I'll be here.
- Okay.
If you hear anything,if you wake up,just -- just call out.
- Dean,you okay?
- Yeah,now that I'm conscious.
The werewolf knocked me out.
Sam,it's madison.
What? !
Yeah,awesome job of keeping an eye on her.
Dean,I've been here the whole time.
She's in bed asleep.
Well,she wasn't an hour ago.
Check her right arm. I nicked her with a silver knife.
Morning.
Um,wherare my pajamas?
Sam?
What's going on?
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
And neither are you.
you're psychotic.
The whole "I'm a cop" trick.
God,I am so stupid.
Well,I guess neither of us are who we said we were,huh?
Sam,you're sick,okay?
You're imagining things.
Monsters don't exist. Not really.
You know what? Save the act.
It's not an act!
I am not a werewolf! There is no such thing!
It's made up,all right?
They're not real! You know they're not real!
No? Then where did that come from?
I don't know!
Sam,god,you need help.
Please,don't do something that you're gonna regret.
I'm not what you think I am.
I'm not.
How you doing?
My head feels great,thanks.
We got to talk.
She says she has no idea what I'm talking about.
She's lying.
Maybe. Or maybe she really doesn't know she's changing.
Maybe when the creature takes over,she blacks out.
Like a really hot incredible hulk?
Dude,she ganked her boss and her ex-boyfriend.
That doesn't sound ration unconscious.
But what if it was,dean?
What if some animal part of her brain saw
both those guys as threats?
- Hell,the cop,too.
- Are you the dog whisperer now?
Look,man,I just...
I don't know. There was something in her eyes.
Yeah,she's killing people.
- But if she has no control --
- xxxxxx
even if she's telling the truth,
it's not gonna change anything.
I'm not putting a bullet through some girl who
has no idea what's happening.
sam she is master
You're feeling sorry for her?
Maybe I understand her.
Look,there might be another way we can get the job
done without having to waste her.
Are you thinking what I think you're thinking?
Dad's theory.
Lycanthropy might have a cure if you kill the werewolf
who bit you,severing the bloodline.
Might have a cure. Meaning "who knows?
- " It's worth a shot.
-  We don't even know where to look.
The puppy that bit her --
it could be anyone,anywhere. Could have been years ago.
No,I don't think so.
Madison...
when were you mugged?
Please,it's important,all right?
Just answer the question.
About a month ago.
- Did you see the guy?
- No.
He grabbed me from behind.
Did he bite you?
How did you know that?
Where?
O-on the back of my neck.
Oh,that's just a love bite.
Believe me,that could have been a lot worse.
- Where were you at the time?
- Walking home from a friend's loft.
Let me guess.
Not too far from hunter's point?
Same place where those other murders happened.
I'm telling you,it's the werewolf's hunting grounds.
But that doesn't mean it's gonna be out there tonight.
It's the right time of the lunar cycle.
I know it's a long shot.
You're forgetting something.
Maddie's probably gonna turn soon.
We can't let her take off to an all-you-can-eat buffet.
I'll stay with her.
And if she busts loose?
- Sam?
- I'll do it.
- Sam.
- I'll shoot her,all right?
But,dean,I need you to go out there.
At least go look for the thing.
Dean,please.
We can save this girl.
Fine.
Please.
Just let me go.
Look...
I know you're scared.
I also know that there's no way in hell you're gonna believe me.
But I'm doing this...
because I'm trying to help you.
I'm not gonna lie,all right?
The odds aren't exactly in our favor.
But if this goes the way I pray it does...
I'll untie you,
and I'll walk out that door,
and I'll never come back.
You'll live the rest of your life...
and I'll just be a bad memory.
Hey!
It happened...
again.
Where am I?
H-help me.
God. Oh,my god.
easy gelen
just take it easy
It should be over now.
You'll never see me again.
It was sort of sad,actually.
Glenn had no clue what was going on.
Why do you think he turned Madison
instead of just killing her?
I don't know.
He kind of seemed to have a thing for her.
Maybe his primal instinct did,too.
Maybe he was looking for a little hot breeding action.
Yeah. Something like that.
So?
So what?
- Speaking of madison...
- oh,whatever.
- You liked her. Maybe,uh -
- dean.
She thought I was a stark-raving lunatic.
You saved her life.
But she doesn't know that.
You know,for a stakeout, your car's a bit conspicous.
What are you still doing here?
Honestly? Uh...
we're pretty sure you're not gonna turn tonight,
but we got to be 100%,
so,you know,we're... lurking.
- Look,I know this sounds crazy -
- it sure does.
Well,if we're gonna wait it out...
we might as well do it together.
You were telling the truth,weren't you?
About everything.
What you did -- it was to help me.
Yeah.
I did all those horrible things...
when I turned.
You didn't know.
So when will we know for sure?
- Moonrise?
-  No,I don't think so.
You turned middle of the night last night.
I think we got to hang in until sunup.
Well,looks like we got ourselves a few hours to kill.
Poker,anyone?
Oh,no,you guys talk.
Does -- does this mean it worked?
Yeah,I think so.
Oh,god,thank you.
Thank you so much.
You too,Dean.
Thank you.
Ah,don't mention it.
So,I'm just gonna head back to the hotel and
watch some pay-per-view or something.
That was smooth.
He means well.
He means he thinks you're gonna get laid.
- Look,I --
- it's okay.
No.
I know I scared the crap out of you,all right?
I -- I mean,I tied you to a chair.
That's right up there with me scratching up your face.
There's just no way...
we could go back,you know?
To before it happened.
You're right.
There's just no way.
she -- she turned.
What?
I couldn't grab her in time.
We'll find her,sammy.
I already called bobby.
He doesn't know anything,except he
knew severing the bloodline wouldn't work.
They all say it's impossible to reverse it.
How come she didn't turn when we were with her?
You put her to bed and then she wolfed out.
Maybe she's got to be asleep to turn.
What the hell does it matter?
We got to find some way to help her,some legend we missed.
Don't you think someone we know would have known?
Then we have to look harder until we find something.
Sammy,I don't think we got a choice here anymore.
What?
- She's a sweet girl,but part of her is -
- evil?
Yeah.
That's what they say about me,dean.
So me you won't kill,but her you're just gonna blow away?
Sam?
Madison,where are you?
I don't -- I don't -- I don't know where I am.
Do you see any street signs?
Um... yeah,yeah.
Middle point.
Hold on,maddie.
We're coming to get you.
Just stay where you are.
I don't remember anything.
I probably killed someone last night.
Didn't I?
There's no way to know yet.
Is there something else we can try to make it go away?
We'll find something.
There's got to be some answer -- somewhere.
That's not entirely true.
Madison,you deserve to know.
We've scoured every source.
There's just no cure.
Is -- is he right?
Well,we could lock you up at night,but...
you bust out,and some night you will...
someone else dies.
I'm sorry. I am.
So I guess that's all there is to it,then.
Stop it. Don't talk like that.
Sam,I don't want to hurt anyone else.
I don't want to hurt you.
Put that down.
I can't do it myself.
- I need you to help me.
-  Madison,no.
Sam.
- I'm a monster.
- You don't have to be.
We could find a way,all right?
I can. I'm gonna save you.
You tried.
I know you tried.
This is all there is left.
Help me,sam.
I want you to do it.
- I want it to be you.
- I can't.
I don't want to die.
I don't.
But I can't live like this.
This is the way you can save me.
Please.
I'm asking you to save me.
sam
I'm sorry.
No,you're right.
She's right.
- Sammy,I got this one.
- I'll do it.
She asked me to.
- You don't have to.
- Yes,I do.
Please.
Just wait here.
www.opensubtitles.org/en
SUPERNATURAL - SEASON2 EPISODE 17 - HEART