Dad wants us to pick up
where he left off, saving people...
...hunting things, the family business.
Today's your lucky day, kid.
- You watch out for Sammy, okay?
- Dad, you know I will.
Dad?
Time of death, 10:41 a.m.
I miss him, man. And I'm not all right.
- Neither are you.
- I'm dealing with Dad's death.
Dad's dead.
It hurts so bad you can't take it.
I'm okay.
The next person who asks me if I'm okay...
...I'm gonna start throwing punches.
Okay, we've got booze.
We've got chocolate.
And-- Wait for it.
-- tortured emo rock, a guaranteed cure
for any broken heart.
You didn't have to do all this.
- I'm fine.
- Yeah, I can see that.
Thanks, Neil.
You're a good friend.
Yeah.
Oh, God, it's probably him.
I'll take care of it.
- Where is she?
- Chill out. Think about this for a second.
- I need to talk to her.
- Some other time.
You get out of my face, Neil.
Angela?
Leave me alone.
Angela, I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
- You're sorry. Oh, that's great.
- Angela, listen to me.
I don't wanna listen to you.
I'm done listening.
- Listen to me.
- No...
I loved you.
Angela?
Come on, Sam, I'm begging you.
This is stupid.
- Why?
- Going to visit Mom's grave?
She doesn't have a grave.
There was no body left after the fire.
- She has a headstone.
- Yeah, put up by a man we've never met.
So you wanna go pay your respects
to a slab of granite put up by a stranger?
- That's not the point.
- Well, then, enlighten me.
It's not about a body or a casket.
It's about her memory, okay?
And after Dad,
it just feels like the right thing to do.
- It's irrational, is what it is.
- Look, man, no one asked you to come.
Why don't we swing by the Roadhouse?
We haven't heard anything on the demon.
We should be hunting that son of a bitch.
That's a good idea. You should.
Just drop me off. I'll hitch a ride...
- ...and I'll meet you there tomorrow.
- Right.
I'd be stuck with those people, making
awkward small talk until you show up.
No, thanks.
I think, um...
I think Dad would have wanted you
to have these.
I love you, Mom.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Angela Mason.
She was a student at the local college.
Funeral was three days ago.
And?
You saw her grave. Everything dead
around it in a perfect circle.
- You don't think that's a little weird?
- Maybe the groundskeeper went aggro...
- ...with the pesticide.
- No, I asked him.
No pesticide, no chemicals.
Nobody can explain it.
Okay. So, what are you thinking?
I don't know. Unholy ground, maybe.
Un--?
What?
If something evil happened,
it could easily poison the ground.
Remember the farm
outside of Cedar Rapids?
- Yeah.
- Could be the sign of a demonic presence.
Or the Angela girl's spirit,
if it's powerful enough.
Don't get too excited,
you might pull something.
It's just, stumbling onto a hunt?
- Here, of all places?
- So?
Are you sure this is about a hunt?
Not about something else?
What else would it be about?
- You know, just forget it.
- You can believe what you want, Sam.
But I let you drag my ass out here.
Least we can do is check this out.
Yep. Fine.
Girl's dad works in town.
He's a professor at the school.
Hey.
Hi. Good to see you.
- Dr. Mason?
- Yes.
I'm Sam. This is Dean.
We were friends of Angela's. We...
We wanted to offer our condolences.
Please, come in.
- She was beautiful.
- Yes, she was.
This is an unusual book.
Oh, it's Ancient Greek. I teach a course.
So a car accident, that's...
That's horrible.
Angie was only a mile away
from home when, uh...
It's gotta be hard...
...losing someone like that.
Sometimes it's like
they're still around...
...almost like
you can still sense their presence.
- You ever feel anything like that?
- I do, as a matter of fact.
That's perfectly normal, Dr. Mason.
Especially with what
you're going through.
You know, I still phone her.
And the phone's ringing
before I remember that, uh...
Family's everything, you know?
Angie was the most important thing
in my life.
And now, well, I'm just lost without her.
We're very sorry.
There's something going on.
We just haven't found it yet.
Dean, so far you got a patch
of dead grass and nothing.
Something turned that grave
into unholy ground.
There's no reason
for it to be unholy ground.
Angela Mason was a nice girl
who died in a car crash.
That's not exactly vengeful-spirit material.
You heard her father.
Maybe Daddy doesn't know everything
there is to know about his little angel.
You know what? We never
should've bothered that poor man.
- We shouldn't even be here anymore.
- So, what, Sam? We just bail?
Without even figuring out
what's going on?
I think I know what's going on here.
It's the only reason
I went along with you this far.
- What are you talking about?
- This is about Mom's grave.
- It's got nothing to do with it.
- You wouldn't step within 100 yards of it.
Look, maybe you're imagining a hunt
where there isn't one...
...so you don't have to think
about Mom or Dad.
You wanna take another swing?
Go ahead, if it'll make you feel better.
I don't need this crap.
- Dean, where are you going?
- I'm gonna go get a drink. Alone.
Seriously, get that camera out of my face.
What, you shy?
I am, as a matter of fact.
Then maybe this'll help you overcome it.
I hate you.
Oh, liar. You're crazy about me
and you know it.
Shut up.
You know, I just had an idea. We can
make a whole different kind of video.
You jerk.
Yeah, but I'm your jerk.
- Please turn the camera off.
You're beautiful, you know that?
You know that, right?
- Who the hell are you?
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Hold on.
- I'm calling 911!
- I'm Angela's cousin.
- What?
Yeah, her dad sent me over
to, uh, pick up her stuff.
My name's Allan. Allan Stanwick.
Her dad didn't say
that you were coming.
Well, I mean...
...how else would I have the key
to your place?
So I'm sure you got a view of Angela
that none of the family got to see.
Tell me, what was she like?
- What was she really like?
- She was great.
Just great.
I mean, she was so...
- Great.
- Yeah.
There you go.
You two must've been
really close, huh?
We were.
But it's not just her. It's Matt.
- Who?
- Angela's boyfriend.
Right, Matt.
- Um, what about him?
- He killed himself last night.
He cut his own throat.
Who does that?
That's terrible.
He was taking Angela's death
pretty hard, and I guess...
- He'd been messed up about it for days.
- Messed up how?
He kept saying
that he saw her everywhere.
Well, I'm sure that that's normal. I mean,
with everything that he was going through.
He said that he saw her.
As in an acid trip or something.
Were Angela and Matt a happy couple?
Was there any reason
Angela would be angry with him?
What?
No, of course not. Why do you ask?
Just asking.
Where did Matt live?
Next on the Skin Channel:
Casa Erotica 4:
A Tale of Two Latin Beauties.
Hey.
What?
Awkward.
- Where the hell were you?
- Just working my imaginary case.
Yeah, and...?
Oh, well, you were right.
I didn't find much.
Yeah. Except Angela's boyfriend
died last night, slit his own throat.
But, you know, that's normal.
Uh, let's see. What else?
Oh, he was seeing Angela everywhere
before he died.
But, you know, I'm sure that's just me
transferring my own feelings.
Okay, I get it. I'm sorry.
Maybe there is something going on here.
Maybe? Sam, I know how to do my job,
despite what you might think.
We should check out
the guy's apartment.
I just came from there.
A pile of dead plants,
just like the cemetery.
Hell, dead goldfish too.
- So unholy ground?
- Maybe.
I'm still not getting that powerful
angry-spirit vibe from Angela.
I have been reading this, though.
You stole the girl's diary?
Yeah, Sam.
- If anything, the girl's a little too nice.
- So, what do you wanna do?
- Keep digging, talk to her friends.
- You get any names?
You kidding me?
I have her bestest friend
in the whole wide world.
I didn't realize the college employed
grief counselors.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you talk, we listen.
Maybe throw in a therapeutic collage.
Whatever helps jump-start the healing.
Well, I think I'm okay. Thanks.
Well, you heard what happened
to Matt Harrison, right?
Yeah, I did.
We just wanted to make sure
you were okay.
Grief can make people do crazy things.
Look, I'm sorry
about what happened to him. I am.
But if Matt killed himself,
it wasn't because of grief.
- No? Then why?
- It was guilt.
- Angie's death was Matt's fault.
- How was Matt responsible?
She really loved that guy.
But the night of the accident,
she walked in on him with another girl.
Hmm.
She was really torn up.
That's why she crashed the car.
Um, look, I gotta get ready for work.
So thanks for the concern,
but seriously, I'll be okay.
Well, that vengeful-spirit theory
is starting to make sense.
I mean, hell hath no fury.
So if Angela got her revenge on Matt,
you think it's over?
Well, there's one way to be sure.
Yeah?
- What's that?
- Burn the bones.
Burn the bones?
Are you high?
- Angela died last week.
- So?
There's not gonna be bones.
There's gonna be a ripe, rotting body
in the coffin.
Since when are you afraid
to get dirty, huh?
Ladies first.
Hold that.
I missed you.
They buried the body four days ago.
I don't get it.
Look.
What is that?
I'm not sure.
I've seen
these kinds of symbols before.
Dean, take it easy. Okay?
You're Angie's friends, right?
- Dr. Mason--
- We need to talk.
Well, then, come in.
Thanks.
You teach Ancient Greek. Tell me...
...what are these?
I don't understand.
You said this had something to do
with Angela.
It does. Please, just humor me.
They're part of an Ancient Greek
divination ritual.
- Used for necromancy, right?
- That's right.
Before we came here, we stopped by
the library and did a little homework.
Apparently, they use rituals like this one
for communicating with the dead.
Even bringing corpses back to life,
full-on zombie action.
Yeah.
I mean, according to the legends.
- Now, what's all this about?
- I think you know.
- Dean.
- Look, I get it.
Okay? There are people
that I would give anything to see.
- But what gives you the right?
- Dean.
- What?
- What's dead should stay dead.
- What you brought back...
...isn't even your daughter.
These things are vicious. They're violent.
They're so nasty, they rot the ground.
I mean, come on,
haven't you seen Pet Sematary?
You're insane.
- Where is she?
- Get out of my house.
I know you're hiding her somewhere.
Where is she?
Dean, stop. That's enough.
Dean, look.
Beautiful, living plants.
- We're leaving.
- I'm calling the police.
Sir, we're sorry.
We won't bother you again.
- What is the matter with you?
- Back off.
That man is innocent.
He didn't deserve that.
Maybe he's keeping her
somewhere else.
Stop it. That's enough, okay? Enough.
- Sam, I know what I'm doing.
- No, you don't. At all.
Dean, I don't scare easy,
but you're scaring the crap out of me.
- Don't be dramatic.
- You're lucky this turned out to be a case.
Because if it wasn't,
you would've found something else to kill.
You're on edge. You're erratic.
Except for when you're hunting...
...because then you're downright scary.
You're tailspinning, man.
And you refuse to talk about it,
and you won't let me help you.
- I can take care of myself, thanks.
- No, you can't.
You know what? You're the only one
who thinks you should have to.
You don't have to handle this on your own.
No one can.
- If you bring up Dad's death one more time--
- Stop. Please. Dean, it's killing you. Please.
We've already lost Dad.
We've lost Mom.
I've lost Jessica.
And now I'm gonna lose you too?
We better get out of here
before the cops come.
I hear you. Okay?
Yeah, I'm being an ass. And I'm sorry.
But we got a zombie running around.
We need to figure out how to kill it.
Right?
Our lives are weird, man.
You're telling me.
Come on.
Honey, is something bothering you?
It's about Matt.
- Haven't we talked about that?
- I know, but--
Haven't we wasted
enough time on him already?
Come sit down.
You always said
that he didn't deserve me.
- You were right.
- Angela...
...you didn't get out
and go see Matt, or...?
I've been here the whole time.
Neil, you really think
I could do something like that?
No.
I don't know. I can't help it.
- You just-- You seem--
- Different?
You're right. I am.
I've realized...
...you're the only one
who ever really loved me.
You proved that.
You brought me back.
I'm with you now.
Isn't that what you always wanted?
We can't just waste it
with a headshot?
Dude, you've been watching
way too many Romero flicks.
- So there's no lore on how to smoke them?
- No, Dean, I'm telling you there's too much.
There's a hundred legends
on the walking dead...
...but they all have different methods for
killing them. Some say setting them on fire.
One said-- Where is it?
Right here.
-- feeding their hearts to wild dogs.
That's my personal favorite.
Who knows what's real
and what's myth?
- Is there anything they have in common?
- No. A few said silver might work.
- Silver's a start.
- Yeah. But how are we gonna find Angela?
- We gotta figure out who brought her back.
- Any ideas?
I think if it's not her dad,
it might be that guy Neil.
- Neil?
- Yep.
- How'd you come up with that?
- Well, you got your journal, I got mine.
"Neil's a real shoulder to cry on.
He so understands
what I'm going through with Matt."
There's more in here where that came from.
It's got unrequited Duckie love all over it.
But that doesn't mean
he brought her back from the dead.
Mm. Did I mention that
he's Professor Mason's TA?
Has access to all the same books?
Hello?
Neil.
It's your grief counselors.
We've come to hug.
Silver bullets?
Yeah, enough to make her rattle
like a change purse.
Unless this is where
he keeps his porn.
- Sure looks like a zombie pen to me.
- Yeah.
An empty one.
You think Angela's
going after somebody?
No, I think she went out
to rent Beaches.
Look, smart-ass,
she might kill someone.
We gotta find her, Dean.
Yeah.
All right, she clipped Matt
because he was cheating, right?
- Yeah.
- Well, it takes two to, you know...
...have hardcore sex.
I don't know, it just seemed that
Angela's roommate...
...was broken up over Matt's death.
I mean, like, really broken up.
Hello?
Hi, Lindsey. I'm home.
You know what you did.
I'm sorry. I am so sorry.
You're not sorry enough!
Oh, God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Hey, I got you. I got you.
Damn, that dead chick can run.
What now?
I say we go have
a little chat with Neil.
So the silver bullets,
they did something, right?
Yeah, something. But not enough.
What else you got?
Um...
Okay, besides silver, we have nailing
the undead back into their grave beds.
It's mentioned a few times. It's probably
where the vampire-staking lore came from.
- Their grave beds? You serious?
- Yeah.
How the hell are we gonna get
Angela back to the cemetery?
What are you guys doing here?
I've heard of some people doing some
desperate things to get laid, but you...
You take the cake.
Okay, who are you guys?
You might wanna ask Angela
that question.
- What?
- We know what you did.
The ritual.
Everything.
Crazy.
Your girlfriend's past her expiration date
and we're crazy?
When someone's gone,
they should stay gone.
You don't mess
with that kind of stuff.
Angela killed Matt.
She tried to kill Lindsey.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Hey.
No more crap, Neil.
His blood is on your hands.
Now, me and him can make this right,
but you gotta tell us where she is.
Tell us!
My house. She's at my house.
Are you sure about that?
Listen, it doesn't really matter
where she is.
There's only one way to stop her.
We've gotta perform another ritual
over her grave.
To reverse the one that you did.
We're gonna need some black root,
some scar weed, some candles.
It's complicated, but it'll get the job done.
She'll be dead again in a couple hours.
I think you should come with us.
I'm serious, Neil.
Leave with us, right now.
No.
Listen to me.
Get out of here as soon as you can.
But most of all, be cool.
No sudden movements.
Don't make her mad.
Let's go.
- You said you'd stay in the house.
I'm sorry.
I just needed to see you.
Neil, please.
You have to help me.
Oh, God.
Come with me to the cemetery.
Neil, they're trying to kill me.
We have to stop them.
You mean kill them.
It's true.
- Matt and Lindsey.
- They hurt me.
If you love me,
you'll make sure nobody hurts me again.
Take me to the cemetery,
and then all this will be over.
We can start new lives together.
Okay.
God help me, but okay.
I'll go get the car.
Just... Just wait here.
Neil, you look nervous.
No, I'm fine.
Were you going to leave me?
- No, of course not. I--
- You were, weren't you?
How could you?
- Neil, I loved you.
- Angela--
You really think this is gonna work?
No, not really.
But it was the only thing
I could come up with.
Wait. It's not what you think.
I didn't ask to be brought back.
But it's still me.
I'm still a person. Please.
Wait, don't!
What's dead should stay dead.
- Rest in peace.
- Yeah. For good this time, okay?
You know, the whole fake-ritual thing,
luring Angela into the cemetery...
...pretty sharp.
Thanks.
But did we have to use me as bait?
I figured you were more her type.
She had pretty crappy taste in guys.
I think she broke my hand.
You're just too fragile.
We'll get it looked at later.
You wanna stay for a while?
No.
Dean, what is it?
- I'm sorry.
- You--?
For what?
The way I've been acting.
And for Dad.
I mean, he was your dad too.
- And it's my fault that he's gone.
- What are you talking about?
I know you've been thinking it.
So have I.
Doesn't take a genius to figure it out.
Back at the hospital,
you know, full recovery.
It was a miracle.
And five minutes later,
Dad's dead and the Colt's gone.
You can't tell me
there's not a connection there.
I don't know how
the demon was involved.
the whole thing went down, exactly.
But Dad's dead because of me.
- And that much I do know.
- We don't know that. Not for sure.
Sam...
...you and Dad...
...you're the most important people
in my life.
And now...
I never should've come back, Sam.
It wasn't natural.
And now look what's come of it.
I was dead.
And I should have stayed dead.
You wanted to know
how I was feeling.
Well, that's it.
So tell me...
...what could you possibly say
to make that all right?