Dad wants us to pick
up where he left off.
Saving people, hunting things.
The family business.
You're planning on bringing
the demon here, aren't you?
Having some stupid, macho showdown?!
I have a plan, Sam.
Dean is dying, and you have a plan!
I won't hunt this demon,
Not until we know Dean's okay.
Did you really think you could trap me?
Oh, I don't want to trap
you. I want to make a deal.
I will give you the colt and the bullet,
But you got to help Dean.
You got to bring him back.
You still need to sweeten the pot.
Giving to Salomon, these protective
circles, they really work.
You get a demon in one,
they're trapped, powerless.
What's going on? Oh, my god.
Get a doctor.
Run!
What happened?
Talk to me. Dogs.
Stay with us, baby! Dogs... Black dogs.
Robert?
Robert, don't you die on me!
So much for our low profile.
You got a warrant in St. Louis, and now
you're officially in the feds' database.
Dude, I'm like Dillinger or
something. Dean, it's not funny.
It makes the job harder. We
got to be more careful now.
What do they got on you?
I'm sure they just
Haven't posted it yet.
Well, you're no accessory,
Nothing? Shut up.
You're jealous. No, I'm not!
Uh-Huh.
All right,
What do you got on the case there,
you innocent, harmless young man, you?
"Architect Sean Boyden plummeted to
his death from the roof of his home,
A condominium he designed"
Build a high rise and
jump off. That's classy.
When did he call animal control?
Two days earlier.
Did he actually say "black dog"? Yeah.
"Vicious, wild, black dog"
The authorities couldn't find
it, and no one else saw it.
In fact, the authorities are a
little confused as to how a wild dog
Could get past the doorman,
Take the elevator up, and start roaming
the halls of the cushiest joint in town.
After that, no more calls.
He doesn't show up for work.
Two days later, he takes a swan dive.
You think we're dealing
with an actual black dog?
Well, maybe. What's the lore on it?
It's all pretty vague.
There are spectral black
dogs all over the world, but
Some say they're animal
spirits, others say death omens.
But anyways, whatever they are, they're
Big, nasty...
Yeah, bet they could hump
the crap out of your leg.
Look at that one. Huh?
What? They could.
So,
You and Sean Boyden were
business partners for
Almost 10 years, right?
That's right.
Now, one more time, this is
for... A tribute for Mr. Boyden,
"Architectural Digest".
Funny to you? No,
It's just uh
"Tribute".
Yeah.
See, Sean always got the tributes.
He kills himself,
Leaves me and his family behind,
But he gets another tribute.
Right.
Any idea why he'd do such a thing?
I have no clue. I mean,
he lived a charmed life.
How so?
He was a flat-Out genius.
I mean, I'm capable,
but, next to him, uh...
It wasn't always that way either.
No?
You  want to know the truth?
There was a time where he
couldn't even design a pup tent.
Hell, 10 years ago, he was working
as a bartender at this place called
Lloyd's,
A complete dive.
So, what changed? You got me.
But overnight
He gets this huge commission,
And he starts designing...
He starts designing the most
Ingenious buildings
Anyone has ever seen. It was like
The level of Van Gogh and Mozart.
What?
It's funny.
True geniuses, they...
Seem to die young, don't they?
To have
That kind of talent...
Why...
Why just throw it away?
So?
The secretary's name is Carly.
She's 23. She kayaks...
And they're real.
You didn't happen to ask her if she's
seen any black dogs lately, did you?
Every complain called in this week
About anything big, black, or
dog like. There's 19 calls in all,
And, uh,
I don't know what this is.
You mean, Carly's my space address?
Yeah, my space. What the hell is that?
Seriously, is that like
some sort of porn site?
I swear, if this is
another freakin' pomeranian
Barking in the neighbor's yard...
Afternoon, ma'am.
Animal control.
Oh, someone already came yesterday.
Oh, we're just following up.
We're looking for Dr. Sylvia Perlman.
The  doctor,
Well, she...
I don't know exactly when she'll
be back. She left two days ago.
Okay.
And you are?
I'm Miss Perlman's maid.
So, where did the doctor go?
I'm not sure.
She just packed and went.
She didn't say where.
That stray dog, did you find it finally?
Uh, not yet.
You know,
You didn't ever happen to
see the dog yourself, did you?
Well, no. I never even heard it.
I was almost starting to think the
doctor was imagining things, but
She's not like that, so...
You know, I read she was
The chief surgeon at the hospital.
So she's got to be, what, 42, 43?
That's pretty young for that job.
Youngest in the history of the place.
She got the position 10 years ago.
An overnight success, 10 years ago.
Yeah, we know a guy like that.
Oh, look at this.
Lloyd's bar.
Miss Perlman?
I've been calling for hours!
You need to vacate the room,
or you got to pay for the night!
Okay,
No problem.
H ey.
Yeah?
That's weird.
What? Think someone planted these?
In the middle of all these weeds?
These are, uh, what do you call them?
Yarrow flowers? Yeah.
Used for certain rituals, aren't they?
Yeah, actually, summoning rituals.
So,
Two people become sudden
successes about 10 years ago,
Right around the time they were
hanging out here at Lloyd's.
Where there just happens
to be a crossroads.
You think? Let's find out.
Seem about the dead center to you?
Yahtzee.
I'd be willing to bet
that's graveyard dirt.
And a black cat bone.
That's serious spellwork.
I mean, that's deep south hoodoo stuff.
Used to summon a demon.
Not just summon one.
Crossroad's where pacts are made.
These people are actually making
deals with the damned thing.
You know, 'cause that always ends good.
They're seeing dogs, all right...
But not black dogs.
They're seeing hellhounds,
Demonic pit bulls.
Whoever this demon is, it's
back and it's collecting.
And that doctor lady,
wherever she's running,
She ain't running fast enough.
Holy...
Holy?
Guess again.
Now save poor bob, if you please
I want to play guitar.
I want you to make me the
best blues man ever lived.
If that's what you want...
So...
How...
Do we shake on it?
So, it's just like the
Robert Johnson legend, right?
I mean, "selling your soul at the
crossroads", that kind of deal?
Except that wasn't a legend.
You know his music.
You don't know Robert Johnson songs?
Sam, there's occult
references all over his lyrics.
I mean, "Crossroad blues,"
"Me and the Devil blues,"
"Hellhound on my Trail"?
Story  goes that he died
choking on his own blood.
He was hallucinating and
muttering about big, evil dogs.
And now it's happening all over again.
Yeah.
We got to find out if anyone else
struck any bargains around here.
Right,
So, we got to clean up
these people's mess for them?
They're not exactly squeaky-Clean.
Nobody put a gun to their head and
forced them to play "let's make a deal".
So, what, we should
just leave them to die?
Somebody goes over Niagara in a barrel,
you gonna jump in to try to save them?
Dean...
All right...
Fine.
Rituals like this, you got to put
your own photo into the mix, right?
So this guy probably summoned the thing.
Let's see if anyone inside knows him...
If he's still alive.
What's this guy's name,
again? George Darrow.
Apparent quite the regular at Lloyd's.
This house probably ain't up
next on "mtv cribs", is it?
Yeah.
So, whatever kind of deal he made...
Wasn't for cash.
Ah, who knows? Maybe his place is
full of babes in princess Leia bikinis.
I'm just saying,
This guy's got one epic bill come due.
Hope at least he asked
for something fun.
Look at that.
What is that, pepper?
Who the hell are you? George Darrow?
I'm not buying anything.
Whoa, looks like
You  went for the wrong shaker, there.
Usually, when you want to keep
something evil out, you go for the salt.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Talking about this.
Tell me...
You seen that hellhound yet?
Look,
We want to help.
Please,
Just 5 minutes.
So, what is that stuff out front?
Goofer dust.
What, you boys think you know something
about something, but not goofer dust?
Well, we know a little
about a lot of things,
Just enough to make us dangerous.
What is it?
Hoodoo.
My grandma taught me.
Keeps out demons.
Demons, we know.
Well, then,
Keep it.
Maybe it'll do you some good.
4 minutes left.
Mr. Darrow...
We know you're in trouble.
Yeah, that you got yourself into.
But it's not hopeless, all right?
There's got to be something we can do.
Listen,
I get that you boys want to help,
But sometimes a person makes their bed
and they just got to lie down in it.
I'm the one called that
demon in the first place.
What'd you do it for? I was weak.
I mean, who don't want to be great?
Who don't want their
life to mean something?
I just...
I just never thought about the price.
Was it worth it?
Hell, no
Course, I asked for talent.
Should have gone for fame.
I'm still broke...
And lonely.
Just now I got this pile of
paintings don't nobody want.
That wasn't the worst.
Go on.
Demon didn't leave.
I never counted on that.
After our deal was done, the damn
thing stayed at Lloyd's for a week,
Just chatting,
Making more deals.
I tried to warn folks, but
Who gonna listen to an old drunk?
How many others are there?
This architect,
A doctor lady. I kept up with
them. They've been in the papers.
At least they got famous.
Who else, George? Come on, think.
Oh, one more.
Uh, nice guy, too.
Hudson,
Evan I think.
I don't know what he asked for.
Don't matter now.
We're done for.
No.
No, there's got to be
a way. You don't get it.
I don't want a way.
Look, you don't... I called that thing!
I brought it on myself!
I brought it on them.
I'm going to hell,
One way or another.
All I want is to
finish my last painting.
Day or two, I'm done.
I'm just trying to
hold him off till then,
Buy a little time.
Okay, boys, time you went. Go
help somebody that wants help.
We can't just... Get out!
I got work to do.
You don't really want to die.
I don't?
I'm tired.
Evan?
Are you spying on the neighbors?
No, I, uh,
I thought I heard something
in the yard, but it's nothing.
You all ready to go?
You know, if I didn't know better, I'd
say that you want me out of the house.
Of course not. It's just, you've...
You've barely seen your
sister since she had the baby.
Well, what are you
going to do all weekend?
Um, not much. I got some bills to pay.
Come here.
I'll miss you.
You better.
You know I love you, right?
Forever.
Of course. Evan, are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Now, get going.
Okay, I'll call you when I get there.
Hey, sweetie?
I love you, too.
Yes? Evan Hudson?
Yeah.
You ever been to a bar called Lloyd's?
Would have been about 10 years ago.
Come on, we're not demons.
Any other bright ideas?
Evan?
Please!
Don't hurt me.
We're not gonna hurt you, all
right? We're here to help you.
We know all about the
genius deal you made.
What?
How? Doesn't matter.
All that matters is
we're trying to stop it.
How do I know you're not
lying? Well, you don't.
But you're kind of running low
on options, there, buddy boy.
Can you stop it?
Don't know.
We'll try.
I don't wanna die.
Of course you don't. Not now. Dean...
Stop. What'd you ask for, anyway, Ev?
Huh?
Never need viagra, bowl
a perfect game, what?
My wife.
Right, getting the girl.
That's worth a trip to hell for.
Dean, stop. No.
He's right. I made the deal.
Nobody twisted my arm. That, uh,
Woman,
Or whatever she was, at the bar, she
said I could have anything I wanted.
I thought she was nuts, at first, but...
I don't know. I was...
I was desperate.
Desperate?
Julie  was dying.
You did it to save her?
She had cancer. They
had stopped treatment.
They were moving her into
hospice. They kept saying,
"Matter of days".
So, yeah, I made the deal...
And I'd do it again.
I'd have died for her on the spot.
Did you ever think
about her in all this?
I did this for her.
You sure about that?
I think you did it for yourself...
So you wouldn't have
to live without her.
But, guess what, she's gonna
have to live without you now.
What if she knew how much it cost?
What if she knew it cost your soul?
How do you think she'd feel?
Okay, that's enough. Evan,
Sit tight, all right?
We're gonna figure this out.
You all right? Why wouldn't I be?
Hey, I got an idea.
You throw George's
hoodoo at that hellhound,
Keep it away from Evan
as long as you can.
I'm gonna go to the crossroads
and summon the demon.
Summon...
Are you nuts?
Maybe a little.
But I can trap it.
I can exorcise it and I can buy us time
to figure out something more permanent.
Yeah, but how much time?
I don't know. A while.
It's not easy for those suckers to claw their
way back from hell and into the sunshine.
No.
No way. Not allowed to say no, Sammy,
Unless you got a better idea.
Dean, you can forget it, all right?
I'm not letting you
summon that demon. Why not?
Because I don't like where your
head is at right now. That's why not.
What are you talking about?
You've been on edge ever since
We found that crossroads,
Dean, and I think I know why.
We don't have time for this. Dad.
You think maybe dad made
one of these deals, huh?
Hell,
I've been thinking it.
I'm sure you've been thinking it, too.
It fits, doesn't it?
I'm alive, dad's dead.
Yellow-Eyed demon was involved.
What if he did?
What if he struck a deal?
My life for his soul.
Hey, guys, I think I
hear it! It's outside!
Just keep him alive, okay?
Dean? Go!
So,
What brings a guy like
you to a place like this?
You called me?
I'm just glad it worked.
First time?
You could say that.
Oh, come on, now.
Don't sell yourself short.
I know all about you, Dean Winchester.
So you know who I am.
I get the newsletter.
Well, don't keep me in suspense.
What have you heard?
Well,
I heard you were handsome.
You're just edible.
What can I do for you, Dean?
Maybe we should do this in my car.
Nice and private.
Sounds good to me.
What is that stuff? Goofer dust.
Are you serious?
Yeah. Afraid so.
Look, believe me, don't
believe me... Whatever you want.
Just whatever you do,
Stay inside this circle, all right?
So, I was hoping we could strike a deal.
That's what I do.
I want Evan Hudson
released from his contract.
So sorry, darling.
That's not negotiable.
I'll make it worth your while.
Oh, really?
What are you offering? Me.
Well, well, well.
You'd sacrifice your
life for someone else's.
Like father, like son.
That's the last of it.
You did know about
your dad's deal, right?
His life for yours.
Oh, I didn't make the deal myself, but,
Boy, I wish I had.
After you.
Such a gentleman.
A devil's trap?
You've got to be kidding me.
What?
You hear that?
No. Where?
Right outside the door.
Just don't move, all right?
Stay where you are.
You stupid, stupid...
I should rip you limb from limb.
Take your best shot.
No,
I don't think so.
I'm not gonna put you
out of your misery.
Yeah? Why not?
'Cause your misery is the whole point.
It's too much fun to watch.
Knowing how your daddy died for you,
How he sold his soul.
I mean,
That's got to hurt.
He's all you ever think about.
You wake up, and your first thought is
"I can't do this anymore".
You're all lit up with pain.
I mean, you loved him so
much. And it's all your fault.
You blew it, Dean.
I could have given you what you need.
What do I need?
Your father.
I could have brought him back.
Your loss.
See ya, Dean.
I wish you a nice, long life.
Hold on.
Do you still hear it?
No.
Is it over?
It's here!
You're lucky I've got a soft spot
for lost puppies and long faces.
I just can't leave you like this.
Besides,
You didn't call me here
to bargain for Evan.
Not really.
Can you bring him back?
My dad?
Of course I can,
Just as he was.
Your dad would live
a long, natural life,
Like he was meant to.
That's a promise. What about me?
I could give you 10 years,
10 long, good years with him.
That's a lifetime.
The family could be together again.
John, Dean, Sammy...
The Winchester boys all reunited.
Look,
Your dad is supposed to be alive.
You're supposed to be dead.
So, we'll just set things straight,
Put things back in their natural order,
And you get 10 extra years on top.
That's a bonus.
You think you could...
Throw in a set of steak knives?
You know, this smartass
self-Sefense mechanism of yours...
Dean...
Now you're really trapped.
That's got to hurt.
Let me out now.
Sure.
We just got to make a
little deal here first.
You call off your hellhound
And let Evan go.
Then I'll let you go.
I can't break a binding contract.
And by "can't," you
mean "don't want to"?
Last chance.
Evan and his wife get to
live to a ripe old age.
Going...
Going... Let's talk about this.
Okay, gone.
Stay inside the circle!
Come on, Dean...
What are you doing?
Oh, you're just gonna
go on a little trip.
Way down south.
Look, forget Evan. Think of your dad.
Regna terrae,
Cantate deo, psallite domino.
Qui fertur super caelum caeli
Ad orientem,
Ecce dabit vocem suam, vocem virtutis.
Tribuite virtutem deo.
Qui fertur super caelum
caeli ad orientem,
Circle's broken! Come on!
Omnis fallaciae,
Libera nos domine.
Hostis humanae salutis.
Wait!
What the hell was that for?
Sealing the deal.
I usually like to be warned
Before I'm violated with demon tongue.
Evan Hudson is free.
He and his wife will live long
lives. How do I know you're not lying?
My word is my bond. Oh, really?
It is when I make a deal.
It's the rules.
You got what you wanted.
Now let me go.
You're gonna double-Cross me?
Funny how I'm the trustworthy one.
You know,
You renege, send me to hell,
Sooner or later I'm gonna climb out, and
Skinning Evan Hudson will
be the first thing that I do.
I got to tell you,
You would have never pulled
that stunt if you knew.
Knew what?
Where your dad is.
You should have made that deal.
See, people talk about hell,
But it's just a word.
Doesn't even come close
to describing the real...
Shut your mouth, bitch! If
you could see your poor daddy,
Hear the sounds he makes
'cause he can't even scream.
How about I send you back there?
What?
How did I get here?
"Key to the Highway" by Big Bill Broonzy
Demons lie all the time, right?
Maybe she was lying.
Come on, is that really what you think?
How could he do it?
He did it for you. Exactly.
How am I supposed to live with that?
You know, the thought of him,
Wherever he is right now...
I mean, he spent his
whole life chasing that
Yellow-Eyed son of a bitch.
He should have gone out fighting.
That was supposed to be his legacy,
You know?
Not bargaining with the damn thing.
Not this.
How many people do you
think dad saved total?
That's not the point,
Sam. Evan Hudson is safe
Because of what dad taught us.
That's his legacy, Dean.
Now, we're still here, man,
So we got to keep going.
For him.
Dean? Yeah?
When you were trapping
that demon, you weren't...
I mean, it was all a trick, right?
You never considered actually
making that deal, right?