DEAN: Dad wants us to pick up
where he left off.
Saving people, hunting things,
the family business.
Before Dad died,
he told me something.
Something about you.
-What?
-That I might have to kill you.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-I don't know.
Did he know the demon's plans
for me?
Am I supposed to go dark side?
Who are you?
-Please. You're in danger.
-What's your name?
-Ava Wilson.
-You must be one of us.
-One of who?
-One of the psychics, like me.
There are others like us out there.
And we're all a part of something.
I'm not part of anything. Okay?
You see this?
I am getting married
in eight weeks.
You can't run from this.
And you can't protect me.
I can try.
-Maybe I can help.
-You've done all you can.
Go back to your fianc?.
You'll be safe there.
AVA: Promise me you'll call then.
SAM: I promise.
Ava.
[SQUEAKING]
Most of the stuff is up here.
I can't believe you're closing,
Ms. Thompson.
You know, my parents
got engaged here.
My grandparents too.
Yeah, a lot of people did.
Boxes are at the end of the hall.
-Need any help?
-Oh, no, ma'am, I got it.
He's gonna take our toys?
Only the ones you
don't play with anymore.
It's not like you don't
have enough already.
-Son of a bitch.
-Watch your mouth.
-Maggie said it first.
Watch your mouth too, Maggie.
TYLER:
Good night, Tabitha.
SUSAN:
Ah!
Oh, God!
Yes, yes, are you there?
You have to send someone,
right now!
An ambulance.
There's been an accident.
He fell on the stairs.
I don't know. I think he's....
Tyler. Don't look!
Don't look!
Yes.
Susan Thompson.
Just-- Just hurry! Hurry. I--
No, I don't know.
I didn't see it happen.
SAM:
Yeah.
Okay.
Thanks, Ellen.
DEAN: What'd she say?
-She got nothing.
Me, I've been checking every
database: federal, state and local.
No one's heard anything about Ava.
She just-- Into thin air, you know.
What about you?
No. Same as before.
-Sorry, man.
-Yeah.
Ellen did have one thing.
A hotel in Cornwall, Connecticut.
Two freak accidents
in the past three weeks.
Yeah, what's that have to do
with Ava?
It's a job. I mean, a lady drowned
in the bathtub.
A few days ago, a guy falls down
the stairs, head turns a complete 180.
Which isn't exactly normal,
you know?
I don't know, Dean, it might be
nothing, but I told Ellen...
-...we'd think about it.
-You did?
Yeah.
-You seem surprised.
-Well, yeah, it's just, you know...
...not the patented
Sam Winchester way, is it?
-What way is that?
-Just figured after Ava...
...there'd be, you know, more angst
and droopy music...
...and staring out the rainy windows.
Yeah, I'll shut up now.
Look, I'm the one who told her
to go back home.
Now her fianc?'s dead...
...and some demon's taken her off
to God knows where. You know?
We've been looking
for a month now...
...and we got nothing.
So I'm not giving up on her but I'm
not gonna let other people die either.
We gotta save as many people
as we can.
Wow, that attitude is just way
too healthy for me.
I'm officially uncomfortable now,
thank you.
All right, call Ellen,
tell her we'll take it.
DEAN:
Dude, this is sweet.
We never get to work jobs like this.
Like what?
DEAN:
Old school haunted houses, you know?
Fog, secret passageways,
sissy British accents.
Might even run into Fred
and Daphne while we're inside.
[DEAN CHUCKLES]
Daphne, love her!
Hey, wait a sec.
I'm not so sure "haunted"
is the problem.
What do you mean?
You see this pattern here?
That's a quincunx. It's a five-spot.
-Five-spot?
-Yeah.
-That's used for Hoodoo spell work?
-Right.
You fill this thing with blood weed,
you got a powerful charm.
Yeah, I don't see any blood weed.
Don't you think this place
is a little too...
...white meat for Hoodoo?
Maybe.
SUSAN: May I help you?
-Hi.
Yeah, I'd like a room
for a couple of nights.
SUSAN:
Hey!
-Sorry about that.
-No problem.
Well, congratulations. You could be
some of our final guests.
Sounds vaguely ominous.
No. I'm sorry. I mean, we're
closing at the end of the month.
Let me guess.
You guys are here antiquing?
-How'd you know?
-You just look the type.
So a king-sized bed?
SAM:
What? No.
No. No. We're two singles.
-We're just brothers.
-Yeah.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
What did you mean
that we looked the type?
You know, speaking of antiques...
...you have a really interesting
urn on the front porch.
Where'd you get that?
I have no idea.
It's been there forever.
Here you go, Mr. Mahoggoff.
[PING]
-You'll be staying in Room 237.
-Okay.
Sherwin, could you show
these gentlemen to their rooms?
Let me guess.
Antiquers?
DEAN:
I could give you a hand with that bag.
-I got it.
-Okay.
-So the hotel is closing up?
-Yep.
Miss Susan tried to make a go of it.
But the guests don't come
like they used to.
-Still, it's a damn shame.
-Oh, yeah?
It may not look it anymore,
but this place was a palace.
Two different vice-presidents
laid their heads on our pillows.
My parents worked here.
I practically grew up here.
Gonna miss it.
Here's your room.
Thanks.
You're not gonna cheap out on me,
are you, boy?
[DEAN CHUCKLES]
DEAN:
What the--?
What?
That's normal. Why the hell
would anyone stay here?
I'm amazed they kept
in business this long.
All right. Victim number one.
Joan Edison, 43 years old, a realtor.
Handling the sale of the hotel.
And victim number two
was Larry Williams.
-Moving some stuff out to Goodwill.
-There's a connection.
-They're shutting the place down.
-Maybe someone doesn't wanna leave.
-They're using Hoodoo.
-Who is our witch doctor?
-That Susan lady?
-No, it doesn't seem likely.
-I mean, she's the one selling.
-So, what then? Sherwin?
I don't know.
The most troubling question is,
why do they assume we're gay?
Well, you are kind of butch.
I think you're overcompensating.
Right.
Hey.
Look at that. More Hoodoo.
DEAN: Hi there.
-Hi.
-Everything okay with your room?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, everything's great.
-Good.
Well, I was just in the middle
of packing, so....
Hey, are those antique dolls?
Because this one. This one, he's--
He's got a major doll collection
back home. Don't you?
-Big time.
Yeah. You think he could--
We could come in and take a look?
-I don't know.
-Please?
He loves them.
He won't tell you.
He always dressing them up
in tiny outfits...
...and you'd make his day.
She would. Huh? Huh?
It's true.
-Okay, come on in.
-All right. All right.
Wow.
This is a lot of dolls.
And they're nice, you know,
they're not super creepy at all.
I suppose they are a little creepy.
But they've been
in the family forever.
Lot of sentimental value.
What is this?
-The hotel?
-That's right. Exact replica, custom-built.
His head got twisted around.
What happened to it?
Tyler, probably.
TYLER:
Mommy! Maggie's being mean.
Tyler, tell her I said to be nice, okay?
Hey, Tyler. I see you broke your doll.
You want me to fix it?
I didn't break it.
I found it like that.
-Oh. Maybe Maggie did it?
-No. Neither of us did it.
Grandma would get mad
if we broke them.
SUSAN: Tyler, she wouldn't get mad.
-Grandma?
Grandma Rose.
These were all her toys.
Really? Where is Grandma Rose now?
TYLER:
Up in her room.
SAM: You know, I'd really love to talk
to Rose about her incredible dolls.
No.
I mean...
...I'm afraid that's impossible.
My mother's been very sick...
...and she's not taking any visitors.
What do you think? Dolls? Hoodoo?
Mysterious shut-in Grandma?
Well, dolls are used in all kind
of Voodoo and Hoodoo...
...like curses and binding spells and--
Maybe we found our witch doctor.
I'll go see what I can dig up
on Booming Granny.
You get on-line, check old obits,
freak accidents.
-See if she's whacked anybody.
-Right.
Don't go surfing porn, that's not
the kind of whacking I mean.
I've been meaning to ask.
What sort of renovations
are you planning?
They never told you?
Told me what?
Ms. Thompson, we plan
on demolishing the hotel.
Oh. I see.
Excuse me.
[HUMMING]
[DOOR CREAKING]
[GAGGING & GRUNTING]
Thank you again.
What happened?
The maid went in to turn down
the sheets, and he was just...
-...hanging there.
-That's awful. He was a guest?
He worked for the company
that bought the place.
Hm.
-I don't understand.
-What?
Had a lot of bad luck around here.
If you'd like to check out,
I'll give you a full refund.
No, thanks. I don't scare that easy.
There's been another one.
Some guy hung himself in his room.
Yeah. I saw.
We gotta figure this out and fast.
What'd you find out about Granny?
You're bossy.
What?
And short.
Are you drunk?
Yeah. So? Stupid.
Dude, what are you thinking?
We're working a case.
That guy who hung himself.
-I couldn't save him.
-What are you saying?
-You couldn't have done anything.
-That's an excuse, Dean.
I should've found a way to save him.
I should've saved Ava too.
You can't save everyone,
even you said that.
No, Dean!
You don't understand.
The more people I save,
the more I can change.
-Change what?
-My destiny, Dean!
All right, time for bed.
Come on, Sasquatch.
Come on.
-I need you to watch out for me.
-I always do.
No, no, no!
You have to watch out for me.
All right?
And if I ever turn
into something that I'm not...
-...you have to kill me.
-Sam.
Dean, Dad told you to do it.
You have to.
Yeah? Well, Dad's an ass.
He never should've said anything.
You don't do that.
-You don't lay that crap on your kids.
-No, he was right to say it.
Who knows what I might become?
Even now, everyone around me dies.
Yeah, well, I'm not dying, okay?
And neither are you.
Come on, sit down.
No, please, Dean, you're the only one
who can do it.
-Promise. Dean, please.
-Don't ask that of me.
You have to promise me.
I promise.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Find any good antiques?
No. No. Got distracted.
Have a drink.
Yeah. Thanks.
So poor guy.
Killing himself.
That kind of thing seems
to be going around lately.
Yeah, yeah.
I heard about the other ones.
It's almost like this hotel
is cursed or something.
Every hotel has its spilled blood.
If people only knew what's gone on
in some of those rooms...
...they've checked into....
You know a lot about the place?
Down to the last nail.
I'd love to hear some stories.
Boy, you should never say
that to an old man.
This is little Miss Susan
and her mother, Rose.
Happier days.
DEAN:
They're not happy now?
Well, would you be, leaving
the only home you ever knew?
I don't know. I never really knew one.
Well, this is Rose's home.
It's been in the family over a century.
Used to be the family estate.
And now she gets to live in
some senior living graveyard...
...and they tear this place down.
That's too bad.
-I hear Rose isn't feeling well either.
-No, she isn't.
What's wrong with her?
It's not my business to say.
DEAN:
Who's this?
That's Rose.
When she was a little girl.
Who's that with her?
That's her nanny, Marie.
She looked after Rose
more than her own mother.
[GROANING]
How are you feeling, Sammy?
I guess mixing whiskey and Jager...
...wasn't such a gangbuster idea,
was it?
I'll bet you don't remember
a thing from last night, do you?
I can still taste the tequila.
You know there's a really good
hangover remedy.
It's a greasy pork sandwich
served in a dirty ashtray.
-Oh, I hate you.
-I know you do.
Hey, turns out when
Grandma Rose was a tyke...
...she had a Creole nanny
who wore a Hoodoo necklace. Ugh.
-So you think she taught Rose Hoodoo?
-Yes, I do.
All right.
I think it's time we talk to Rose.
You need to brush your teeth first.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hello?
Susan?
-Clear?
-Mm-hm.
SAM:
Mrs. Thompson?
Rose?
Hi, Mrs. Thompson, we're not here
to hurt you, it's okay.
Rose?
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
This woman's had a stroke.
Yeah, but Hoodoo's hands-on.
You gotta mix herbs and chant,
build an altar.
So it can't be Rose.
Heck, maybe it's not even Hoodoo.
You know, she could be faking.
Yeah, what do you wanna do,
poke her with a stick?
Dude, you're not gonna
poke her with a stick.
What the hell?
What are you doing in here?
-The door was--
-We wanted to ask Rose--
She's scared out of her wits.
I want you out of my hotel in two
minutes or I'm calling the cops.
Your turn. Eightsies.
Have you started packing yet?
-No.
-Why not?
-I don't wanna move.
-Yes, I know. But we have to.
-Maggie says we're not allowed to.
-Yeah.
Tyler, enough.
Maggie is imaginary.
You're too old to have an imaginary
friend and I'm done pretending.
I don't like her.
-I could lug those boxes for you.
-I got it, Sherwin, thanks.
Okay then.
See you later.
[SQUEAKING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
-You okay?
-I think so.
DEAN: Come on, come on,
let's get inside. Let's go. Come on.
-Whiskey.
-Sure.
I know the feeling.
What the hell happened out there?
-You want the truth?
-Of course.
First we thought it was
some sort of a Hoodoo curse.
But that out there?
That was definitely a spirit.
SAM:
Here.
You're insane.
It's been said.
I'm sorry, we don't exactly
have time to ease you into this.
But we need to know
when your mother had the stroke.
-What's that have to do with--?
-Answer the question.
About a month ago.
Right before the killings began.
See?
What if Rose was working Hoodoo...
...but not to hurt anyone,
to protect them?
She was using the urns
to ward off the spirit.
-Till her stroke. She couldn't anymore.
-I don't believe this.
Listen, that car didn't try
to run you down by itself, okay?
I mean it did, technically,
but the spirit can-- Forget it.
Believe what you want.
You and your family are in danger.
All right? You need to clear
everybody out:
Your employees, your mother,
your daughters, everyone.
I only have one daughter.
-One?
-Tyler had a sister named Maggie.
Maggie's imaginary.
Where's Tyler?
[GRUNTING]
She's going to stay here with me.
And you can't stop me.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Maggie, don't. You're not supposed
to bother Grandma.
I know.
Come on. Let's play.
-Can we have a tea party?
-We can have lots of tea parties.
Forever and ever and ever.
SUSAN:
Tyler?
Oh, my God. Tyler.
She's not here.
Susan. Tell us what you know
about Maggie.
Tyler's been talking
about her since Mom got sick.
Okay. Did you ever know
anyone by that name?
-No.
DEAN: Think.
Could be someone that lived here.
Passed away.
My God, my Mom
had a sister named Margaret.
Barely spoke about her.
Did she die here when she was a kid?
She drowned in the pool.
Come on.
I don't like it up here.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
All you have to do is jump.
TYLER: I can't swim.
-I know.
But it won't hurt, I promise.
And then we can be together.
Forever.
And no one will bother us.
Why don't you just come
with me and Mommy?
Because I can't leave here.
And you can't leave me.
Please? I don't want to be alone.
Tyler.
-Tyler.
DEAN: Come on.
Mommy.
Ah!
-Is there another entrance?
-Around back.
DEAN:
All right. Let's go.
Keep working.
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
It'll all be over soon.
Stand back.
Son of a bitch.
WOMAN:
Margaret.
[COUGHING]
Oh, my God, thank God.
TYLER: Mommy.
SUSAN: Yeah, baby. I'm here.
Tyler, do you see Maggie anywhere?
No, she's gone.
Mommy.
You'd really do that for me?
Yes?
If you did, I'd let them go.
But I don't understand.
You kept me away for so long.
I thought you didn't love me anymore.
Okay...
...little sister.
SUSAN:
Don't worry, honey.
We're leaving in two minutes,
we just gotta get Grandma.
I don't get it. Did Maggie just stop?
-Seems like it.
-Where the hell did she go?
[SUSAN SCREAMING]
The paramedics said
it was another stroke.
You think...
...Margaret could've had
something to do with it?
-We don't know.
-But it's possible.
Yeah.
Susan, I'm sorry.
My God, you have nothing
to apologize for.
You've given me everything.
-Ready to go, kiddo?
-Yeah.
You're sure Maggie's
not around anymore?
I'm sure. I'd see her.
Well, I guess whatever's going on
must be over.
You two take care
of yourselves, all right?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Both of you.
I think you could've hooked up
some MILF action there, bud.
-I'm serious, I think she liked you.
-Yeah, that's all she needs.
Well, you saved the mom,
you saved the girl, not a bad day.
I could have saved them myself but
I didn't want you to feel useless.
All right. I appreciate it.
Feels good getting back
in the saddle, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, it does.
But it doesn't change what we
talked about last night, Dean.
We talked about
a lot of things last night.
-You know what I mean.
-You were wasted.
But you weren't.
And you promised.
MAGGIE:
Two, three, four, five, six, seven...
...eight, nine, 10, 11, 12...
... 13, 14, 15, 16...
... 17, 18....
Thirty-four, 35, 36, 37....
[ENGLISH - US - SDH]