dad wants us to pick up where he left off
saving people, hunting things, the family business.
"THEN"
Her attacker,a white male...
that's not even a good picture.
Shapeshifter?
Every culture has a shapeshifter lore.
Something that can look like anyone?
Freeze.
Stay on your knees.
He's being held on suspicion of murder.
Murder?
"BREAKING NEWS"
We are still here live.**************
And though a short exchange of weapons fire occurred just a few minutes ago,
police and S.W.A.T.Teamsmaintain position as we enter the third hour of this intense stand-off.
Authorities estimate as many as 10 hostages are being held inside the bank.
No word as yet on the identity of the suspects
Something's happening.
I think they're opening a door.
Roger, you getting this?
Over there.
Turn the camera over there.
No, no, no, no, no!
Don't even think about it!
Get the hell back!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-??
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Supernatural
Season 2 Episode 12
"Milwaukee,Wisconsin"
"One Day Ago"
So, what's it like -- being an fbi guy?
Well...
it's dangerous.
You know.
And the secrets we got to keep -- oh, countless secrets.
But mostly it's -- it's lonely.
I so know what you mean.
Yeah.
Helena was our head buyer.
"NIGHTSHIFTER"
She -- she was family, you know?
She said it herself every year at the christmas party.
She said we were the only family she had.
So there were never any signs that she'd do something like this.
No...
still can't believe it, even now.
That night, helena came back to the store after closing, cleaned out all the display cases and the safe.
Edgar, our night watchman -- he caught her in the act.
He didn't know what to do.
He'd known her for years.
He called me at home.
And that's when she took his gun?
She shot him in the face.
I heard him die over the phone.
Any idea what her motive could have been?
What motive?
It makes no sense.
Why steal all those diamonds, all that jewelry and then, what, just dump it somewhere?
Just hide it and then go home.
She killed herself?
The cop said she dropped the hair dryer in the bath and fried herself.
They should know, right?
Yeah.
Well, thanks, frannie.
I think that's all I need.
Really?
I mean, 'cause i've got more, you know, if you wanted to interview me...
sometime in private?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
You're a true patriot.
You really are.
Why don't you write your number down there for me?
So you never saw the security-camera footage yourself, then.
The police -- they took all the tapes first thing.
Of course they did.
This is it.
Freaking cops.
They were just doing their job.
No, they're doing our job, only they don't know it, so they suck at it.
Talk to me about this bank.
Milwaukee national trust -- it was hit about a month ago.
Same M.O.As the jewelry store?
Yep, inside job, longtime employee, the "never in a million years" type.
Dude robs the bank, then goes home and supposedly commits suicide.
Resnick was the security guard on duty?
Yeah, he was actually beaten unconscious by the teller who heisted the place.
Oh, god.
Yeah.
Mr.Resnick!
Ronald resnick.
Fbi, mr.Resnick.
Let me see the badge.
I already gave my statement to the police.
Listen, ronald, just some things about your statement we wanted to get some clarification on.
You read it?
Sure did.
Come to listen to what I got to say?
That's why we're here.
Well...
come on in.
See, none of the cops ever called me back, not after I told them what was really going on.
They all thought I was crazy.
First off, juan morales never robbed the milwaukee national trust.
That I guarantee.
See, me and juan were friends.
He used to come back to the bank on my night shifts, and we'd play cards.
So you let him into the bank that night, after hours.
The thing I let into the bank...
wasn't juan.
I mean, it had his face, but it wasn't his face.
Every detail was perfect, but too perfect, you know, like if a doll maker made it,
like I was talking to a big juan doll.
A juan doll?
Look, this wasn't the only time this happened.
There was this jewelry store, too, and the cops and you guys, you just won't see it.
Both crimes were pulled by the same thing.
And what's that, mr.Resnick?
Chinese been working on them for years, and the russians before that
part man, part machine, like the terminator, but the kind that can change itself, make itself look like other people.
Like the one from "t2."
Exactly!
So not just a robot, more of a -- a man-droid.
A man-droid?
What makes you so sure about this, ronald?
I made copies of all the security tapes.
I knew once the cops got them, they'd be buried.
Here.
Now watch.
WatcH.
Watch him.
Watch.Watch.
See, look, there it is!
You see?
He's got the laser eyes.
Cops said it was some kind of reflected light, some kind of "camera flare."
Okay?
Ain't no damn camera flare.
They say I'm a post-trauma case.
So what?
Bank goes and fires me.
It don't matter.
The man-droid is still out there.
If the law won't hunt this thing down, I'll do it myself.
You see, this thing, I-it kills the real person, makes it look like a suicide,
then it sort of like morphs into that person, cases the job for a while till it knows the take is fat,
and then it finds its opening.
Now, these robberies, they're grouped together,
so I figure the man-droid is holed up somewhere in the middle -- underground maybe -- I don't know.
M-maybe that's where it recharges its m-man-droid batteries.
Okay.
I want you to listen very carefully.
'Cause I'm about to tell you the god's honest truth about all of this.
There's no such thing as man-droids.
There's nothing evil or inhuman going on out there.
It's just people.
Nothing else.
You understand?
- The laser eyes  - just a camera flare, mr.Resnick.
I know you don't want to believe this, but your friend juan robbed the bank, and that's it.
Get out of my house!
Now!
Sure.
First things first.
Man, that has got to be the kicker, straight up.
When you told that poor son of a bitch to -- what did you say, "remand" the tapes that he copied?
"Classified evidence of an ongoing investigation"?
That's messed up.
What are you, pissed at me?
No, I just think it's a little creepy how good of a fed you are.
We could have thrown the guy a bone.
He did some good legwork here.
"Man-droid"?
Except for the man-droid part.
I liked him.
He's not that different from you and me.
People think we're crazy.
Except he's not a hunter.
He's just a guy who stumbled onto something real.
If he were to go up against this thing, he'd get torn apart.
Better to stay in the dark and stay alive.
Yeah, I guess.
Shapeshifter.
Just like back in st.Louis.
Same retinal reaction to video.
Eyes flare at the camera.
I hate those freaking things.
You think I don't?
One didn't turn into you and frame you for murder.
- Well, look, if this shifter's anything like the one we killed in missouri - then ronald's right.
All right, they like to lair up underground, preferably the sewer.
All the robberies have been connected so far, right?
Through the, uh, sewer main layout.
There's one more bank lined up on that same sewer main.
Well, we haven't had any flags go up on our system yet.
No, no, this is a glitch in the overall grid.
Just want to make sure the branch monitors are kosher.
Better to be safe than sorry, I guess.
That's the plan.
All righty.
You guys need anything else?
Oh, no, no, no.
We'll be in and out.
Just a routine check.
Okeydokey.
I like him.
He says "okeydokey."
What if he's the shifter?
Well, then we follow him home, put a silver bullet through his chest plate.
Okay.
You got any popcorn?
Looks like mr.Okeydokey'S...
okeydokey.
Maybe we jumped the gun on this, dean.
We don't even know it's here.
Maybe we should just go to the sewers and...
and...
dean, we're supposed to be looking for eyes.
I'm getting there.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Hello, freak.
Got him.
Sam.
What?
Hello, ronald.
This is not a robbery!
Everybody on the floor now!
Get down, damn it!
Come on!
On the floor, on the floor.
In the middle!
On the floor in the middle.
In middle, on the floor, come on!
Hurry up!
Come on!
And you said we shouldn't bring guns.
I didn't know this was gonna happen, dean.
Let me do the talking.
I don't think he likes you, agent johnson.
There's only one way in or out of here, and I chained it up, so nobody's leaving, you understand?
Hey, buddy.
Why don't you calm down?
Just calm down.
What?
You!
Get on the floor now!
Okay, we're doing that.
Just don't shoot anybody, especially us.
I knew it -- as soon as you two left.
You ain't fbi.
Who are you?
Who are you working for, huh?
The men in black?
You working for the man-droid?
We're not!
You shut up!
I ain't talking to you!
I don't like you!
Fair enough.
Get over there.
Frisk them down, make sure they got no weapons.
Go!
And what have we here?
I'm not just gonna walk in here naked.
Give that there.
No, no, no, no.
We know you don't want to hurt anybody.
But that's what's gonna happen if you keep waving that cannon.
Why don't you let these people go?
No!
I already told you.
If nobody's gonna stop this thing, then I've got to do it myself!
We believe you!
That's why we're here.
You don't believe me!
Nobody believes me!
How could they?
Come here.
What?
No.
You're holding the gun, boss.
You're calling the shots.
I just want to tell you something.Come here.
It's the bank manager.
What?
Why do you think we got these getups, huh?
We've been monitoring the cameras in the back.
We saw the bank manager.
We saw his eyes.
His laser eyes?
Yes.
No.
No!
We're running out of time.
We got to find him before he changes into someone else.
Like I'm gonna listen to you.
You're a damn liar.
I'll shoot you!
Get down!
Take me.
Take me as a hostage.
But we got to act fast because the longer we just sit here, the more time he has to change.
Look at me, man.
I believe you.
You're not crazy.
There really is something inside this bank.
All right.
Y-you come with me.
But everyone else gets in the vault!
Come on, move!
Move, move!
Then you lock it up.
It's okay, everyone.
Just stay cool.
Now spin that.
Spin that there.
Who is that man?
He's my brother.
He is so brave.
Check behind the desk.
What the hell is that?
Oh, great.
When it changes form, it sheds its old skin.
So now it could be anybody.
So...
so weird.
Its robot skin is so lifelike.
Okay, let's get something straight.
It's not a man-droid.
It's a shapeshifter.
Shapeshifter?
Yeah.
It's human, more or less.
It has human drive.
And in this case, it's money.
But it generates its own skin.
It can shape it to match someone else's features
so I-it kills someone and then takes their place.
Kills them -- I don't think it matters.
What are you doing?
Nice.
You remember the old werewolf stories?
Pretty much came from these guys.
Silver's the only thing I've seen that hurts them.
Come on, ronald.
How we doing?
Another day in paradise.
No one's come out yet?
This guy locked himself in.
First thing he did.
All right.
Cut the power.
What are you, nuts?
That's just it.
I'm not nuts.
I mean, I was so scared that I was losing my marbles, but this is real.
I mean, I-I was right.
Except for the man-droid thing.
Thank you.
Yeah, don't mention it.
Damn it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What is it?
They cut the power.
It's probably their way of saying hi.
Who?
Cops.
The cops?
You weren't exactly a smooth criminal about this, ron.
You didn't even secure the security guard.
He probably called them.
- Well, I didn't think to - hang on.
Let's just take a breath for a second.
They probably got us surrounded.
They cut the power to the cameras, so there's no way of telling who the shapeshifter is.
It's not looking good, ron.
Did you hear that?
Has your brother always been so...
wonderful?
I mean, staring down that gun.
And the way he played right into that psycho's crazy head, telling him what he wanted to hear?
Hero or something.
Yeah.
Oh, my g-- you saved us!
You saved us!
Actually I just found a few more.
Come on, everybody, let's go.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Sam, look, ronald and i need to talk to you.
It shed its skin again.
We don't know when.
Could be in the halls, the vault.
Great.
You know, dean, you are wanted by the police.
Yeah.
So even if we do find this damn thing, how the hell are we gonna get out of here?
One problem at a time.
I'm gonna do a sweep of the whole place, see if I can find any stragglers.
Once we get everyone together, we got to play "find the freak."
So here.
I found another one of these for you.
Now, stay here.
Make sure ronald doesn't hurt anybody.
- Help him manage the - help him manage?
Are you insane?
Look, I know this isn't going the way we wanted.
Understatement.
But if we invite the cops in right now, ronald gets arrested, we get arrested, the shifter gets away.
Probably never find it again, okay -- ron!
Out of the light!
Seriously?
Ron's plan was a bad plan.
It was a bit of a crazy plan, but right now, crazy's the only game in town, okay?
Hi, ronald.
I'm gonna keep this open, get you folks some fresh air in there, all right?
But no one leaves this vault.
I don't understand.
Why are you helping him?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
H-hello?
I think I got to get out of here.
Sir, I'm very sorry, but you're just gonna have to stay put.
What do you mean, demands?
Ronald...
hang up.
I-I'm not a bank robber.
I got to really get out of here.
Sir, you can't leave.
Kind of a crime fighter, I guess.
Ronald!
Look...
No, I'm acting alone.
Ronald...
the less the cops know, the better.
I think this dude's having a heart attack!
Great.
Could be our guy, could be a trick.
Are you just gonna let the man die?
No one's dying in here!
Cover the door.
Can you tell me how many hostages this guy's taken?
One of the people in here could be having heart trouble.
You need to send in a paramedic.
Just stay calm, sir.
Just send in a paramedic, okay?!
Don't try anything else!
Please.
Paramedic?
Guy don't have time for that, man.
Listen, I-I'm sorry, okay?
But nobody's getting out.
He's dying right in front of you.
Help.
Come on, man.
You got to unlock the front door.
We got to get him out of here.
Both of you stay where you are!
You know what, ronald?
He's right.
We got to get this man outside.
Come on.
I got you.
I'll help you.
Oh, I got him.
It's cool.
Thanks.
Watch your step.
Thank you.
Sure.
Let's go up these steps.
Hey, can I talk to you for a second?
You have the gun, man.
Whatever.
Stop!
Come back here!
Here.
Take care of the guard.
I'm going after the shifter.
Sorry, ron.
You did a real good job tracking this thing.
You really did.
Oh, god, please don't hurt us.
You shouldn't be back here right now!
You're in danger!
Now go back to the vault, now.
*********
**************
***********************
No, no, no, no!
Back up!
Don't even think about it!
*****************
I said get back now!
One of the hostages seems to have taken over the situation.
Excuse me?
Go, go, go.
We are so screwed.
Yeah?
Slipped his skin.
What?
Yeah, bastard shifts fast, a lot faster than the one in st.Louis.
It's like playing a shell game.
It could be anybody again.
I think most of the employees are in the vault.
You search every inch of this place.
I'm gonna go round everybody up.
Crap.
What?
The feds are here.
Oh, crap.
Lieutenant robards.
Yeah.
Special agent hendrickson.
Let me guess.
You're lead dog now, but you would just love my full cooperation.
I don't give a rat's ass what you do.
You can go get a doughnut and bang your wife for all I care.
What I do need is your S.W.A.T.Team locked and loaded.
Listen, agent, something's not right about this.
It's, uh...
it's not going down like a usual heist.
That's because it isn't one.
You have no idea what you're dealing with, do you?
There is a monster in that bank, robards.
And I thought you were one of the good guys.
What's your name?
Why would you care?
My name's dean.
I'm sheri.
Hi, sheri.
Everything's gonna be all right.
This will all be over soon, okay?
Yeah.
This is special agent victor hendrickson.
I'm not really in a negotiating mood.
Good.Me neither.
It's my job to bring you in -- alive's a bonus, but not necessary.
That's harsh for a federal agent, don't you think?
Well, you're not the typical suspect, are you, dean?
I want you and sam out here unarmed, or we come in.
And, yes, I know about sam -- bonnie to your clyde.
Yeah, well, that part's true, but how'd you even know we were here?
Go screw yourself.
That's how I knew.
It's become my job to know about you, dean.
I've been looking for you for weeks now.
I know about the murder in st.Louis, the houdini act you pulled in baltimore.
I know about the desecrations and the thefts.
I know about your dad.
You don't know crap about my dad.
Ex-marine, raised his kids on the road, cheap motels, backwood cabins -- real paramilitary survivalist type.
I just can't get a handle on what type of wacko he was -- white supremist, timmy mcveigh, tomato, tomahto.
You got no right talking about my dad like that.
He was a hero.
Yeah, right.
Sure sounds like it.
You have one hour to make a decision, or we come through those doors full automatic.
Scramble your men.
Five minutes, then we go in.
What?
Hendrickson, they've let out one hostage so far.
They've hurt no one as far as we can tell.
You don't know these winchesters.
They're dangerous and expertly trained.
We can't risk the lives of all those people.
Dean's a greater risk to them than we are.
This is crazy.
Crazy's in there, and I just hung up on it.
amn it.
We got a bit of a problem outside.
We got a problem in here.
Sheri?
We're gonna let you go.
What?
Why me?
As a show of good faith to the feds.Come on.
I think I'd rather stay here with the others.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to insist.
I thought you were letting me go.
Oh, god!
Was that community theater, or are you just naturally that good?
This is the last time you become anybody, ever.
god
Dean, wait, wait, wait.
What's the advantage of this plan?
I mean, fainting now wouldn't help it survive.
No!
Get her out of here now!
Don't shoot!
I work here.
***********
************
Gross.
Move!
Clear!
Clear.
Move.
Male, african-american, goner.
Telling you, man, I just walked her out of the bank.
She must have a twin sister or something.
Sir, my team said it's secure.
They're gone.
You tell your team to tear it apart -- the ducts, the ceilings, everything.
I don't think that's necessary.
Why not?
*Oh, mama, I'm in fear for my life from the long arm of the law*
*lawman has put an end to my running and I'm so far from my home*
*oh, mama, I can hear you a-cryin' you're so scared and all alone*
*hangman is comin' down from the gallows and I don't have very long*
we are so screwed.
*The jig is up, the news is out they finally found me*
*the renegade who had it made retrieved for a bounty*
*never more to go astray the judge will have revenge today on the wanted man*
*oh, mama, I'm in fear for my life from the long arm of the law*
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-??
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Supernatural
Season 2 Episode 12
Warning:  Unknown(): open(/mnt/136/sdb/1/b/gerdiffuse/sessions/sess_ceb1d74816fac2803f973d7ba8919ceb, O_RDWR) failed: No such file or directory (2) in Unknown on line 0
Warning:  Unknown(): Failed to write session data (files). Please verify that the current setting of session.save_path is correct (/mnt/136/sdb/1/b/gerdiffuse/sessions) in Unknown on line 0