Dad wants us to pick up
where he left off...
...saving people, hunting things,
the family business.
Still running credit-card scams?
- Think credit card fraud's easy?
Okay, Mr. Burkowitz.
- Federal marshals.
- Environmental majors.
Father Simmons.
U.S. Wildlife Service.
- Nigel Toughnell.
- Dr. Jerry Kaplan.
- Reporters.
- Art dealers.
- Students.
Homeland Security.
Pretty illegal, even for us.
SWAT team discovered
a local woman bound and gagged.
Her attacker, a white male,
approximately 24 to 30 years of age...
...was discovered hiding
in the home.
- Shapeshifter?
- Every culture has a shapeshifter lore.
Legends of creatures who can transform
themselves into animals or other men.
Hey.
Cops are blaming
this Dean Winchester guy...
...for Emily's murder.
- Sorry I'm gonna miss it.
- What?
How many chances will I have
to see my own funeral?
Under what name?
Oh, yeah, that's my favorite so far.
Possible IDs in three states
that we know of.
I gotta call you back.
Well...
...first I thought you were
just stepping up your game.
Credit card fraud...
...breaking and entering.
Now, this one puzzled me.
Grave desecration.
But still, these are
a long way from murder.
Then we get a fax from St. Louis.
Where you're suspected of torturing
and murdering a young woman.
However, no one could prove
anything, of course...
...because, supposedly, you died there.
Hands where I can see them.
- But I gotta tell you something.
You look pretty healthy to me.
So now we know Karen Giles
wasn't the first person you murdered.
Going somewhere, Sam?
But I guarantee you, she's the last.
Thought you might be thirsty.
Okay, so you're the good cop.
- Where's the bad cop?
- He's with your brother.
Okay. And you're holding us why?
He's being held
on suspicion of murder.
- And you? We'll see.
- Murder?
You sound genuinely surprised.
Or are you that good of an actor?
- Who's he supposed to have murdered?
- We'll get to that.
You can't just hold us here
without charges.
Well, actually, we can for 48 hours.
But you, being a pre-law student,
would know that.
I know all about you, Sam.
You're 23 years old, no job,
no home address.
Your mother died
when you were a baby.
Your father's whereabouts
are unknown.
And then there's the case
of your brother, Dean.
Whose demise was, well,
just a little bit exaggerated.
Feel free to jump in
whenever you like.
Shy? No problem, I'll keep going.
Your family moved around a lot
when you were a kid.
Despite that, you were
a straight-A student.
Got into Stanford with a full ride.
Then, about a year ago,
there was a fire in your apartment.
One fatality, Jessica Moore,
your girlfriend.
After she died, you fell off the grid.
Left behind everything.
I needed some time off.
To deal.
So I'm taking a road trip
with my brother.
How's that going for you?
Great.
I mean...
...we saw the second largest
ball of twine in the continental U.S.
Awesome.
We ran Dean's fingerprints
through AFIS.
- Okay.
- Got over a dozen possible hits.
Possible hits.
Which makes them worthless.
But makes you wonder. What are we
gonna find when we run your prints?
Yeah. Well, you be sure
to let me know, all right?
May I?
- Please.
- Great.
Sam, you seem like a good kid.
It's not your fault
Dean's your brother.
We can't pick our family.
Right now, detectives in St. Louis
are exhuming a corpse.
They're trying to figure out
how your brother faked his own death...
...after torturing
all those young women.
Dean's a bad guy.
His life is over.
Yours doesn't have to be.
You want me to turn against
my own brother?
No. We already caught him cold.
Red-handed at the Karen Giles
murder scene.
We just need you to fill in
some missing pieces.
Why would I do that?
Because I can talk to the DA.
Make a deal for you.
You can get on with your life.
Dean's as good as gone.
My dad and Tony Giles
were old friends.
They were in the service together.
We've known him
since we were kids, you know.
We came when we heard
about his death.
There you go.
- Anthony Giles.
- Who's Anthony Giles?
A Baltimore lawyer.
Working late at his office.
Check it out.
Ah...
His throat was slit,
but the room was clean.
- No DNA, no prints.
- Keep reading. It gets better.
"Security cameras failed to capture
footage of the assailant."
- Somebody tampered with the tapes--
- Or it's an invisible killer.
My favorite kind.
- What you think, Scully? Check it out?
- I'm not Scully. You're Scully.
No, I'm Mulder.
You're a redheaded woman.
So...
...would've been hard for Dean
to kill Tony...
- ...considering we weren't in town.
- Tell me what happened next.
Okay, that's when we went
to see Karen.
She was barely holding it together.
We just wanted to be there for her,
you know.
Insurance.
I totally forgot about the insurance.
We're very sorry to bother you
right now...
...but the company is required
to conduct its own investigation.
- You understand?
- Sure.
Okay. If you could just
tell us anything...
...you remember about the night
your husband died.
Tony and I were supposed
to have dinner.
He called and said that
he was having computer troubles...
...and he had to work late.
That was it.
You have any idea
who could have done this?
No. No. It's like I told the police,
I have no idea.
Did Tony mention anything unusual...
...to you in the days
before his death?
Unusual?
Yeah, like strange.
- Strange?
- You know, Karen, weird.
Weird noises...
...visions, anything like that?
- Ahem.
- What?
He had a nightmare
the day before he died, but--
What kind of a nightmare?
He said that he woke up
in the middle of the night.
There was a woman
standing at the foot of the bed.
He blinked, she was gone.
I mean, it was just a nightmare.
Did he say what she looked like?
What the hell difference does it
make what she looked like?
It's just our company's
very thorough.
He said she was pale
and she had dark red eyes.
So I gave Karen a hug.
Told her to call me if she needed
anything, and that was it.
End of story.
Sam, I am trying to help you here.
But you have got to be honest
with me.
Now, we have an eyewitness.
Someone who saw two men...
...fitting your and your brother's
description breaking into Giles' office.
Look, Karen called us later,
said there was stuff she wanted...
...from Tony's office,
but the police weren't letting her in.
Like a picture of the two of them
in Paris, and some other stuff.
Look, it was wrong to enter
a crime scene, but she gave us the key.
Hey.
Anthony Giles' body was found
right about here.
"Throat slit so deep,
part of his spinal cord was visible."
What do you think?
Vengeful spirit, underline vengeful?
Yeah, maybe.
I mean, he did see that woman
at the foot of his bed.
Hey, look at this.
Dana Shulps?
What's that? A name?
I don't know, but it's everywhere.
All work and no play
makes Jack a dull boy.
Wow.
I'd say we've officially
crossed over into weird.
Maybe Giles knew her.
Maybe it's the name of our pale,
red-eyed mystery girl.
Well, let's see what we can see.
There's not a single mention
of a Dana Shulps anywhere.
There's not a D. Shulps...
- ...or any other kind of frigging Shulps.
- Great.
- What do you got?
- Nothing.
No Dana Shulps has ever lived
or died in Baltimore...
- ...in the last 50 years, at least.
- So, what now?
Well, I think I'm pretty close
to cracking Giles' password.
- Maybe something in his personal files.
- By close you mean...?
Thirty minutes maybe.
Awesome.
So I guess I just get to hang out.
So awesome.
- Dude, seriously.
- All right.
I'm gonna talk to Karen, see if she
knows anything about this Dana Shulps.
Great.
Keep going, sparky.
Dean went back to Karen's place
to check up on her.
I mean, you know,
she'd been pretty upset earlier.
So why didn't you go with him?
I just went back to the motel.
How'd you know I was there,
by the way?
We found the motel matchbook
on your brother when we arrested him.
Let's quit fooling around. You were
with your brother the whole time...
...you were in Baltimore.
Why separate now?
- Your brother left to go murder Karen.
- He didn't kill anyone.
I heard the 911 call.
Karen was terrified.
She said someone was in the house.
Emergency services.
- Hello.
- I think I saw somebody in my house.
- What is your address?
It's 421 Clinton Avenue.
Please, can you--? Hello?
Karen, you in there?
Oh, God.
Seriously, what the hell?
Freeze. Stay on your knees.
Hands where I can see them.
Now.
Cuff him.
- You getting anywhere with him?
- No.
Just a lot of wise-ass remarks.
You?
Sam's story matches Dean's
to the last detail.
Yeah? Well, these guys are good,
I'll give them that.
If we don't get Sam to flip,
we have nothing...
- ...but a lot of circumstantial evidence.
- We got Dean at the crime scene...
...with blood on his hands.
Juries have convicted for less.
Yeah, but, I mean,
where's the murder weapon?
What's the motive?
You talk about reasonable doubt--
Diana...
...do you have reasonable doubt?
We keep leaning on these guys,
one of them will tumble.
And don't forget about St. Louis.
I'm telling you,
this Dean guy is our guy.
I know Tony Giles
was a friend of yours.
Yeah, he was. He was a good friend.
Look, and I know you wanna
clean this mess up quick.
But come on, Tony knew a lot
of criminal types, maybe we just--
Criminal types?
He was a defense lawyer
for God's sakes.
Of course he knew criminal types.
Okay. All right, let's get back at them.
No. You know what?
Let them stew in their juices for a bit.
Come here.
Dana Shulps, Dana Shulps,
Dana Shulps.
Dana-- Dana Shulps.
Maybe it's not a name.
Anagram maybe?
- Mr. Winchester?
- Yeah.
I'm Jeff Krause.
I'm with the public defender's office.
I'm your lawyer.
Oh, thank God, I'm saved.
Hey, can I steal a pen from you,
some paper?
Sure.
Well, the police haven't found
a weapon yet, so that's good.
But they got your prints...
...and, literally, blood on your hands.
And with your police record...
Mr. Winchester, what are you doing?
- I think it's an anagram.
- A what?
An anagram.
Same letters, different words.
Could you do me a favor?
See if you recognize
any of these words.
Local names, places,
anything like that?
Do you understand how serious
these charges are?
I'm handcuffed to a table.
Yeah, I get it.
Humor me. Take a quick look.
Well...
S- U-P, I don't know about that...
...but Ashland is a street name.
- It's not far from here.
- Street?
Let's start with where you were
the night that Anthony Giles died.
- Can you get in to see my brother?
- Mr. Winchester...
...you could be facing
a death penalty here.
Hey, thanks
for the law review, Matlock.
But if you wanna help me...
...I need you to see my brother.
I hope that was meaningful.
But I'd like to discuss your case now.
Sure thing, Matlock.
You two really are brothers,
aren't you?
Now, as you know...
...the DA might be interested in--
We need you. With the other one.
Counselor...
...your boy decided to confess.
Mr. Winchester,
I'd advise against that strongly.
Talk directly into the camera.
Start by stating your name
for the record.
My name is Dean Winchester.
I'm an Aquarius. I enjoy sunsets...
...long walks on the beach,
and frisky women.
And I did not kill anyone.
But I know who did.
Or rather, what did.
Of course, it can't be for sure, because
our investigation was interrupted.
Our working theory
is that we're looking for a kind of...
...vengeful spirit.
Excuse me?
You know,
Casper the bloodthirsty ghost?
Tony Giles saw it.
I'll bet you cash money
Karen did too.
The interesting thing
is the word it leaves behind.
For some reason, it's trying
to tell us something.
But communicating
across the veil ain't easy.
Sometimes the spirits,
they get things jumbled.
You remember redrum?
Same concept.
You know, it's...
Could be word fragments.
Other times...
...it's anagrams.
See, at first we thought
this was a name, Dana Shulps.
But now, we think it's a street.
Ashland.
Whatever's going on...
- ...I'm betting it started there.
- You arrogant bastard.
Tony and Karen were good people.
You're making jokes.
I'm not joking, Ponch.
You murdered them in cold blood
just like that girl in St. Louis.
Oh, yeah, that wasn't me either.
That was a shapeshifter creature
that only looked like me.
Get up.
Hey, hey.
Pete, that is enough.
You asked for the truth.
Lock his ass up.
What the hell?
Where is he?
What'd he do?
The fire escape's way over--
- What?
- These two guys.
Hilts and McQueen?
What is that?
Hilts is Steve McQueen's character
in The Great Escape.
Can we make this quick?
I'm a little tired.
It's been a long day,
with your partner assaulting me and all.
I wanna know more about that stuff
you were talking about earlier.
Time Life, Mysteries of the Unknown.
Look it up.
Let's pretend for the moment
you're not entirely insane.
What would one of these things
be doing here?
A vengeful spirit?
Well, they're created
by violent deaths.
And then they come back
for a reason, usually a nasty one.
Like revenge on the people
that hurt them.
And these spirits...
...they're capable of killing people?
Where did you get that?
I don't know.
It wasn't there before.
You've seen it, haven't you?
- The spirit.
- How did you know?
Because Karen had the same bruises
on her wrists.
I bet that if you look at Giles'
autopsy photos, he's got them too.
It's got something to do
with this spirit. I don't know what.
I know.
You think you're going crazy.
Well, let's skip that part, shall we?
Because the last two people
who saw this thing...
...died pretty soon after.
You hear me?
You think I'm gonna die?
You need to go to Sam. He'll help.
You're giving your brother up?
Go to the first motel in the yellow pages.
Look for Jim Rockford.
It's how we find each other
when we separate.
You can arrest him if you want.
Or you can let him save your life.
These showed up after you saw it?
Yeah, I guess.
All right.
You're gonna have to tell me
exactly what you saw.
You know, I must be losing my mind.
You're a fugitive.
I should be arresting you.
All right, well, you know what?
You can arrest me later.
After you live through this.
But right now,
you gotta talk to me. Okay?
Okay, great. Now, the spirit,
what did it look like?
She was...
...really pale.
And her throat was cut.
And her eyes, they were like
this deep dark red.
It appeared like she was trying
to talk to me, but she couldn't.
It was just a lot of blood.
You know what? Here. I've been
researching every girl who's died...
...or gone missing
from Ashland Street.
How'd you get those?
Those are from crime scenes
and booking photos.
You have your job, I have mine.
Here, I need you to look through these,
tell me if you recognize anyone.
This is her.
I'm sure of it.
"Claire Becker, 28 years old. Disappeared
about eight or nine months ago."
But I don't even know her.
Why would she come after me?
Well, before her death, she was
arrested twice for dealing heroin.
- You ever work Narcotics?
- Yeah.
Pete and I did. Before Homicide.
- You ever bust her?
- Not that I remember.
It says she was last seen
entering 2911 Ashland Street.
Police searched the place,
didn't find anything.
Guess we gotta check it out ourselves.
See if we can find her body.
What?
Well, we gotta salt and burn her bones.
It's the only way to put her spirit to rest.
Of course it is.
So, what exactly
are we looking for?
I'll let you know when we find it.
Sam.
Sam!
Hey. Hey, I'm here. What is it?
- What happened?
- Claire.
- Where?
- She was here.
Did she attack you?
No. No, she was just, like,
reaching out to me.
She was over there by the window.
Hey, wait. Help me move this.
Our little mystery word.
Now the extra letters make sense.
What is that?
Well, spirits and certain remains
give off electro-magnetic frequencies.
So if Claire's body was here,
that would indicate that?
Yeah. Well, that's the theory.
Yeah, yeah. There's definitely
something in there.
You know, this is bothering me.
Well, you are digging up a corpse.
No, not that. That's pretty
par for the course, actually.
Then what?
It's just... I mean, no vengeful spirit
I've ever tussled with...
...wanted to be wasted. So why
would Claire lead us to her remains?
It doesn't make any sense.
All right, here. Give me a hand.
Her wrists.
Yeah, they'd be bruised
just like yours.
That necklace
mean something to you?
I've seen it before.
It's rare. It was custom-made
over on Carson Street.
I have one just like it.
Pete gave it to me.
- Now this all makes perfect sense.
- I'm sorry?
Yeah, you see,
Claire is not a vengeful spirit.
She's a death omen.
Excuse me?
Claire's not killing anyone.
She's trying to warn them.
See, sometimes spirits don't
want vengeance, they want justice.
Which is why she led us here.
She wants us to know
who her killer is.
How much do you know
about your partner?
- Oh, my God.
- What?
About a year ago, some heroin
went missing from lockup.
Obviously it was a cop.
We never found out who did it.
But whoever did it would need
someone to fence their product.
Somebody like a heroin dealer.
Somebody like Claire.
So I'm being extradited
to St. Louis, huh?
And you just decided to transfer me
yourself, 800 miles at 2 in the morning?
This can't be good.
All right, thanks.
- What is it?
- Pete just left the precinct.
- With Dean.
- What?
He said the prisoner had to be
transferred, and he just took him.
Dispatch has been calling.
He won't answer the radio.
- Radio? He took a county vehicle?
- Yeah.
It should have a LoJack.
You just gotta get it turned on.
Pee break? So soon?
You know, you might wanna
get your prostate checked.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, I'm cool in the van.
You go do what you gotta do.
You're a cocky son of a bitch.
You think those people in St. Louis
are gonna buy that crap?
Here's the thing.
You're not gonna make it to St. Louis.
You're gonna die trying to escape.
Wait. Wait.
Let's talk about this. You don't wanna
do something you're gonna regret.
- Or maybe you do.
Pete.
- Put the gun down.
- Diana?
How'd you find me?
I know about Claire.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Put the gun down.
Oh, I don't think so.
You're fast. Pretty sure I'm faster.
- Why are you doing this?
- I didn't do anything, Diana.
It's a little late for that.
It wasn't my fault.
Claire was gonna turn me in.
I had no choice.
And Tony? Karen?
Same thing.
Tony scrubbed the money.
Then he got skittish...
...and then he wanted to come clean.
I'm sure he told Karen everything.
It was a mess, I had to clean it up.
I just panicked.
How many more people
are gonna die over this?
There's a way out.
This Dean kid's a frigging gift.
We can pin the whole thing on him.
Okay? No trial, nothing,
just one more dead scumbag.
Hey.
No one will question it.
Diana, please...
...I still love you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah, why don't you buy me
another necklace, you ass.
Don't do it. Don't do it.
You doing all right?
Not really.
The death omen, Claire.
- What happens to her now?
- It should be over.
She should be at rest.
So, what now, officer?
Pete did confess to me,
he screwed up both your cases royally.
I'd say there's a good chance
that we can get your cases dismissed.
- You could take care of that for us?
- I hope so.
But the St. Louis murder charges?
That's another story.
I can't help you.
Unless...
...I just happened to turn my back,
and you walked away.
I could tell them
the suspects escaped.
- Wait, are you sure?
- Yeah, she's sure, Sam.
No, it's just you could lose
your job over something like that.
I want you guys out there
doing what you do best.
Trust me. I'll sleep better at night.
Listen, you need to watch your back.
They're gonna be looking
for both of you now.
Get out of here. I gotta radio this in.
Hey, wouldn't happen to know
where my car is by chance?
It's at the impound yard on Robertson.
Don't even think about it.
It's okay, it's all right.
Don't worry. We'll...
We'll just improvise.
We're good at that.
Yeah, I've noticed.
- Nice lady.
- Yeah, for a cop.
- Does she look familiar to you?
No, why?
I don't know.
Anyway, are you hungry?
No.
For some reason...
...I could really go for some pea soup.