Kids, never underestimate
the power of destiny.
Because when you least expect it,
the littlest thing
can cause a ripple effect
that changes your life.
Take for instance
my trip to Chicago.
That security guard was
a little bit handsy.
That's funny.
She barely touched me.
Uh, Gate 23. Come on.
If we miss this flight,
I will never forgive myself.
Why was this flight
so important?
Let's back up a few months
to the fall of 2006.
I had just sold my first
building design and become
the youngest project manager
in my firm's history.
Suddenly I was
being headhunted.
One firm was even considering me to
run their entire New York office.
They were flying me in
for a final interview
at their corporate
headquarters in Chicago.
It was the opportunity
of a lifetime.
It was my destiny.
There was just one problem.
Hi, wait, two more.
Sorry, you're too late,
I already shut the doors.
Well, I'm sure if we pull
real hard we can open them.
Hmm, I wish it worked like that, but
see, once I close those doors,
that's it.
Nobody else is allowed
down that jet-way.
Except for that guy.
Please, if-if I miss this flight, I'll miss
the chance to interview for my dream job.
I'm sorry, sir.
His dream job!
Didn't you ever have a dream job?
Something from when you were a little
girl, that was all you wanted to do?
I mean, for God's sakes,
I'm sure you didn't go to bed at night
dreaming about being a...
I mean, uh...
This is a cool job.
Please, I have to
be on this flight.
I'll see what I can do.
But it doesn't look good.
Thanks.
Your uniforms are pretty.
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com
Okay.
They haven't armed the doors yet,
so you still have a chance.
It's up to the captain now
and they're calling us back.
Great, please let us know
soon as you hear anything.
Sure, and for the future,
we recommend you arrive
at the airport an hour and
a half before your flight,
not, you know,
one minute after.
Normally, I'm
incredibly responsible.
I just had to go to court this
morning and get sentenced.
Not that I'm a
criminal or anything.
Yeah, he just jumped
a subway turnstile.
You seem to have a lot of problems
with the rules of travel.
Hello?
Oh, that is great news.
It's my mom--
she found her missing earring.
Have a seat.
I'll call you when I hear something.
Where was it?
That thing better
have call waiting.
Could you just call the firm
and explain what happened?
It's down to three people
and I know they need to
make their decision today.
I sort of feel my not showing up
might put me at a disadvantage.
I'm so stupid.
Why did I have to
jump that turnstile?
Hey, don't be so
hard on yourself.
And isn't this whole thing
really Barney's fault?
She had a point.
It was kind of Barney's fault.
Let's back up a few months.
Oh, Marshall,
how's the broken toe?
Oh, man, it kills.
You want some aspirin, baby?
You know I don't
believe in pain killers.
Wow, your first broken bone.
Kind of kills your whole
"Unbreakable" theory.
Marshall used to think
he was indestructible.
Well, it added up.
I've never broken anything.
I've never been sick,
and when I need to,
I can summon
incredible strength.
Ted, tell her the story
of the really heavy door.
There was a really heavy door.
He opened it.
On one pull.
Well, you must be really bummed, you're
not gonna be able to run tomorrow.
Yeah. It sucks,
all that work I put in training
for the marathon was a total waste.
Training for a marathon.
What?
You don't need to train for a marathon.
You just run it.
You're kidding, right?
Not at all. I could run a
marathon anytime I wanted to.
So like tomorrow, you think you
could wake up, roll out of bed,
and just run the New
York City Marathon?
Absolutely.
Barney, we're talking
about 42 kilometers.
Thanks, Canada.
I'll take it from here.
Barney, it's like 26 miles.
Here's how you run a marathon.
Step one, you start running.
There is no step two.
Okay, you know what? Prove it.
Take my number and
run in my place.
I will bet you 50 bucks you
don't even finish the race.
50 bucks?
Gee,  Grandpa, if I win,
maybe I can buy myself
an ice-cream cone.
Make it $10,000.
You have a gambling problem.
You'll bet me 50.
Fine, then no bet.
Okay, $50.
The next morning,
as the marathon began,
we were focused on
Marshall's computer.
Each runner gets a tracking chip
so you can follow them online,
see when they pass certain checkpoints.
Barney's got mine in his shoe.
Ooh, he's starting!
This ought to be good.
Wow.
He's already passing
the second checkpoint.
This tracking thing is amazing.
When we get married,
you're getting one of these.
Wow. Look at his time.
It's pretty impressive.
He's gotta be cheating, okay.
He knew we'd check.
Yeah, he'll do
anything to win a bet.
Remember that time he bet me that Men
at Work sang "Hungry Like the Wolf,"
and when he found out that they didn't,
he tried to hire them to?
Well, it looks like, "Barney" should
be coming over the Queensboro Bridge
and up First Avenue within
the next hour or so. But...
there is no way that
that's really him.
It's really him.
Hey! That's mine.
Yeah, you'd better run!
- What up, non-finishers?
- Wow.
- Very impressive, Barney.
- Right?
Yeah, my time would have been
like a half an hour better,
but I met this total hottie on
Mile Seven. We took a quick detour
and had our own mini
marathon behind a Nathan's.
I won.
I'm not sure anyone in
that story is a winner.
So where's my 50 bucks?
All right.
I got to admit,
you earned this.
Huh? Can't believe they haven't
made a coin for this yet.
Anyway, I'm heading home.
Might go hit the gym.
Oh, hey, just so you know,
uh, all marathon runners get
to use the subway
for free today.
Wow. You know I really should
check out this "subway."
Heard so much about it.
Wow. Look at me. Slumming it.
Maybe I'll make a
weekend out of it
and I'll call my bridge
and tunnel girl tonight.
You're dating a girl
from New Jersey?
No.
So Barney did it.
He actually finished
the marathon.
But a little while later...
I got an interesting phone call.
- Hello?
- Ted, it's Barney.
Listen to me, I need you to come
and pick me up on the subway.
What, what are
you talking about?
I was sitting here,
totally minding my own business.
Finisher.
Yeah, you know what I mean.
86th street.
My legs don't work.
I've already ridden the
subway twice end to end.
I've seen where
it turns around.
Ted, you don't ever want to see
where the subway turns around.
Barney's legs won't work.
He's riding the subway
from end to end
because he physically
can't get off the train.
Best 50 bucks I ever spent.
Listen to me, Ted.
I'm going to lose you any second.
I'm on the fourth car of the six train
heading south from Pelham
Bay Park in the Bronx.
Meet me at the 86th Street station in,
like, half an hour?
All right. I'll be right there.
Stay where you are.
Ted, Ted.
Oh, come on. You're not even going
to give up your seat for him?
I'm sorry. I can't.
Douche.
- Barney?!
- Ted!
H ey!
No...!
See? If Barney never
tried to run the marathon,
you never would have
jumped that turnstile,
you wouldn't have had
that court date today,
and we would have
made this flight.
You're right.
Everything can be
traced back to him.
Like that rash we
all got at Christmas.
All right,
I have to see what's going on.
- So I was able to get you two seats.
- Really? That's great!
No, no, not you. I'm talking to
my mom about Blue Man Group.
Ma, can I call you back?
Okay, what about our flight?
Can we get on?
I'm still waiting for... Huh.
Looks like your
flight left already.
What? No, n-n-n-no, n-no.
I have to be in Chicago today.
Well, he never even
called you back?
Well, it's typical pilot.
They don't call you back at work
and they don't call you back after
you spend two nights with them
at a Radisson in Orlando.
It turned out there was one other
flight that would just barely get me
to Chicago on time
for my job interview,
but it was all the way on the
other side of the airport.
What was the name of
the airline again?
I think it was something
like Flights R' Us.
Was  the "R" backwards?
God, I hope not.
- Geez.
- Stupid smart carts.
More like dumb carts.
If we miss this flight,
it's all Barney's fault.
You know, Barney never would have
run the marathon in the first place
-  if Marshall hadn't broken his toe.
- Yeah, so?
What, you think
this is my fault?
For Marshall, the initial idea to run
the marathon came way back in April.
My pants are starting
to feel a little tight.
Oh, that's okay.
I love that cute little belly.
I cannot allow this.
What?
I am going to run the
New York City Marathon.
"It is important to load
up on carbohydrates
two to four hours
before a big run.
Try a breakfast of a bagel,
a banana,
oatmeal, strawberries
and some orange juice."
Here you go, Marshmallow.
Just like the book said.
Yeah, but from now on, I'm eating
all of my breakfast runner-style.
Liquids are digested faster.
That way, no energy is wasted,
and it's all about the run.
"Don't forget to give yourself
plenty of positive reinforcement."
This is gonna be
your best run yet.
You're going to accomplish
all of your goals.
You are a robot sent
from the future
to win the marathon!
You are... Marshall.
You are Marshall! Yeah!
"Chafing or blisters can
occur in a number of areas,
including the feet, armpits,
or even the nipples.
Try using some petroleum
jelly on the affected areas."
Oh, gosh!
Dude, you are a
terrific runner.
Tomorrow you're gonna run and
finish the New York City Marathon!
You're the best.
You look good.
Nobody does it better than you.
Marshall? Oh, my God!
So, yes, it was your fault.
I mean, if you don't show up at the
apartment in the middle of the day,
Marshall doesn't break his toe,
Barney doesn't run in his place,
I don't jump the turnstile
and get a court date,
and we make our flight
in plenty of time!
And I don't fall down and bite
my tongue at the airport.
That really wasn't my fault.
I wouldn't have walked in on
Marshall if it weren't for Lily.
Hey, think about it.
Hey, what's going on here?
Oh, looks like they're
camping out for something.
Yeah, but for what?
I don't know. Usually there's a
Stormtrooper or Klingon in line
to give you some indication.
"Annual wedding dress blowout.
Designer sample
dresses up to 90% off.
Doors open tomorrow, 8:00 a.m."
Oh, my God. Can you believe what some
nut bags will do to save a few bucks?
We have to camp out.
- Are you serious?
- You don't understand.
This is an amazing sale.
I've heard about it before,
but I never knew where it was.
We'll have a wedding dress campout.
It'll be fun.
I can't go.
I've got this thing.
- What thing?
- A penis.
- This is the place.
- Oh, wow.
Badgley Mischka! Melissa Sweet!
Vera Wang!
Oh, Robin, do you have any idea
what you guys stumbled onto here?
You said wang.
Oh, this reminds me of the ticket
line to Lilith Fair, 1998.
Only fewer mullets.
You should feel good. You're only, like,
the tenth craziest bride in New York.
Ooh, this is comfy.
We might actually
be able to sleep.
That's kind of annoying.
Well, I'm sure somebody will be
out here to turn it off any minute.
I don't think I can take this.
Every time it turns off,
I think,
oh, maybe it won't
turn on again,
but then it does.
Why does it, Robin?
Why does it keep turning on?
It's gonna be okay,
sweetie. Why...
Why don't we make a
game out of it, okay?
Why don't we sing along?
If we get through this,
I swear I'm gonna live
my life differently.
I just want to tell my parents
I love them one more time.
Morning, ladies.
- It's him. It's the car guy!
- Get out of here!
The next morning, Robin was too tired
to go all the way back to Brooklyn,
so while I was at work,
she went to crash at my
apartment for a couple hours,
and that's when...
Nobody does it better than you.
Marshall?! Oh, my God!
So if Lily hadn't dragged me
down to the wedding dress store,
we would have made
the first flight.
Oh, thank God.
The doors are still open. We made it.
Hi. Please.
We really need to get on this flight.
Oh, my God!
You're that reporter
from Metro News 1.
Yes, yes, I am.
I can't believe
you recognized me.
- You did that story on the giant pizzas?
- Would you check to see
- if you have any more seats?
- One moment, sir.
Were those pizzas real?
Come on, were they?
- Robin...
- One second, Ted.
Um, you know,
a lot of people ask me that.
The truth is,
the pizzas were real.
- Calzones. Trick photography.
- I knew it!
God, it is so nice
to meet a fan!
And I would be a fan of your
work if you could get us
two seats on that next flight.
Well, the, uh, flight attendants are
just finishing up their final
seat count.
Let me see what I can find out.
Would it help if I got on and gave an
impassioned speech about my destiny?
I think it might hurt.
This is such a nightmare.
Okay, so we agree? This goes
back to Lily wanting to camp out
for a wedding dress?
No.
Wait. It goes back further.
Remember why we were eating
hot dogs on the East Side?
1939?!
This penny's from 1939!
A 67-year-old penny.
Do you realize this penny was
minted during World War II?
Oh, so was my grandfather,
but that doesn't make him interesting.
Look, I know a little
something about coins,
and this baby is worth
something to a collector.
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is!
You know what?
I'm gonna take you out to dinner
with the money I get
for this little guy.
And that's exactly what I did.
You're lucky there's still a place that
serves anything for a dollar fifty.
Hey, that's 150 times
its original value.
Actually, the meal
was only $1.49.
1984.
Hey, in 50 years,
we can get dinner again.
How dare you.
Hey, what's going on?
I don't know. Looks like they're
camping out for something.
Yeah, but for what?
It was me.
I started this.
If I hadn't picked
up that penny,
we wouldn't have gone to get hot
dogs all the way across town.
And we wouldn't have seen
that wedding dress store,
Lily wouldn't have wanted
to camp out there,
and I wouldn't have needed a nap
at your apartment the next day.
Marshall wouldn't
have broken his toe.
Barney wouldn't have
run the marathon.
I wouldn't have jumped
that turnstile,
gotten arrested,
had that court date...
And we would have
made our flight.
I don't think we can go
back any further than that
unless you know who
dropped the penny.
I wish I did.
Though that person's already
been punished enough,
losing a sweet penny like that.
Uh, sir?
Oh, please tell me you
have some good news.
Uh, I'm afraid not.
There are no extra
seats on the plane.
I'm sorry.
All, right, well,
thanks for trying.
I can't believe this.
That's it, it's over.
Ted, come on.
Your destiny just wasn't to
make it to Chicago today.
Anyway, if that firm really wants you,
they'll reschedule.
But that's not what happened.
They didn't reschedule.
They hired someone else.
And as it turned out,
three months later,
that guy ended up having
to relocate to Chicago.
Kids, funny thing
about destiny--
I  thought I was destined
to get that job.
But I was wrong.
My destiny was to
stay in New York.
Because if I hadn't,
I never would have
met your mother.
Transcript : Raceman
Subtitles : Willow's Team
www.forom.com