[Quirky music]
Sync by n17t01
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Sync by n17t01
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
Emily Birch?
Is that her...
the one whose blood
Jordan wears around his neck?
Yeah.
It was almost 20 years ago.
He was Eugene Greer.
That's Jordan Chase?
No one could ever take
your place.
You know that.
You know, I'm glad
you didn't touch any of them.
Really?
Why is that?
Because this DNA test
will clear you
and leave you all to me...
And to her.
The men who hurt you,
they made DVDs
of everything they did.
Did everyone watch it?
I managed to get it
out of evidence in time.
You think
you can just pay me off
like I'm the corner whore?
Stay the fuck away from Deb!
I trusted you.
And while you were fucking me,
you were spreading shit
about my brother behind my back.
Fuck you.
- Who'd you say you were?
- A friend of Joey's.
I got to pick up
a few things for a stakeout.
It's for Detective Quinn.
You see his name there.
A strange call
came into my office
from an Alex Tilden.
Alex Tilden, 3040.
Here it is.
Look at this.
Looks like a partial footprint.
What if the vigilante
is one of their victims?
This all becomes so...
Natural.
- Uhh!
- You okay?
Yes.
But with Lumen,
I'm someone different.
In her eyes,
I'm not a monster at all.
Detectives.
We appreciate you
fitting us in.
We wanted to thank you
for your phone call
regarding Alex Tilden...
It was really helpful.
- That's good to hear.
- We followed up immediately.
We went to his house, but...
It looked like
we had just missed him.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Yeah, it is, because...
He seems to have disappeared
off the face of the earth.
I see.
Yeah, like Cole Harmon.
And Boyd Fowler.
Yeah, him too.
Now, I keep asking myself,
what's the connection?
What do these three people
have in common?
You.
You're what
they have in common... you.
Oh, here it comes.
Why don't you just...
save us a lot of time
and tell us
what that connection is?
[Sighs]
[Scoffs]
It's ridiculous
that you think I have anything
to do with this.
I gave you my DNA!
What were the results?
Go on, remind me.
Your DNA wasn't found
on any of the barrel girls.
That's correct,
so all this right here
is a colossal waste
of my time and yours.
Well, I've got
nothing but time.
So you can keep
fooling everybody
in your little seminars,
but I'm onto you.
You're obsessed with me.
That's what this is about.
It happens... you achieve
a bit of fame,
and people latch onto you
in various twisted ways.
I'd be careful if you were you.
It's typically seen
in someone
who's trying to avoid
facing the dismal nature
of her own small life.
- I think you slipped up.
- It's not at all healthy.
And I think a barrel girl
got away.
It's something
I can help you with.
And now she's hunting down
the people that took her.
And people all around you
are dropping like flies.
You could be next.
Seriously, I'll be fine.
It's you I'm concerned about.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Jordan Chase...
We know exactly where he is.
Yeah, but...
There's no way to get to him.
The entire top floor
is guarded.
Elevators?
Monitored.
Stairs?
Locked from the inside.
Yeah.
But you know how to pick locks.
[Sighs]
Not without setting off
the fire alarm.
[Chuckles softly]
Okay.
So we have to figure out a way
to get him to come out.
How?
He has everything
he needs up there.
Not everything.
Me.
He wants me.
No.
There's got to be a way
to use me as bait.
It worked with Cole.
I'm not gonna use you as bait.
It's too dangerous.
You know I can do this.
Yeah, I do.
I saw you kill Alex Tilden.
But we have to be
extra careful.
Jordan has more than
just our eyes on him.
The police.
My sister.
I'm so sorry that
I put you in this position...
having to lie to her like that.
I don't like it,
but it's not the first time.
She's never suspected anything?
[Chuckles]
I don't know.
Maybe Deb has a blind spot
when it comes to me.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm taking advantage of her,
but it's for the best.
She's not like us.
"Us."
Oh, uh...
There's a camera in the room.
The baby monitor
is picking up the signal.
Somebody's watching us.
Jordan has to be behind this...
And close by.
Wireless cameras
have a limited range,
their signal routed
to a recording unit...
In a vacant apartment...
A motor home.
A van.
It could be anywhere.
Ohh.
Jordan Chase is up
to his ball sack in this.
I fucking know it.
Just means we keep digging.
You coming in?
Uh, I got to grab something
from my car.
I'll be right up.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
My union appeal's been denied.
I am now officially terminated.
So how's your day?
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Don't want your pity.
Good, then...
30 years of putting
bad guys away,
this is what them cocksuckers
upstairs do to me...
take my pension,
wipe their ass with it,
and just flush it right on.
Look, I got to get inside.
I need your help on a bust.
A bust?
What are you talking about?
Something big,
something big enough
to make them stand up
and take notice,
something big enough
to make them give my my job back
on the police force.
Your boy Dexter...
What the fuck?
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear me, Quinn?
I'm not a cop anymore.
Now, I need a cop
to make this bust.
No.
Forget it.
You little fucking wimp.
You're up to your ass
in alligators with this thing,
whether you like it or not.
So you're gonna make this bust,
and I'm gonna call you.
You'd best come running.
[Car door opens, closes]
[Engine turning]
[Tires squeal]
What are you in the mood for?
I'm thinking seafood.
It's a perfect night to grill.
I'll go check
what's in the fridge.
Harrison's baby monitor
made it easy to pinpoint
where this was hidden,
but the bigger problem
remains...
what exactly has Jordan heard,
and where are those recordings?
On second thought,
let's go out to eat.
[Whispering]
It's not Jordan. It's worse.
It's someone
from my own station.
What?
Why would somebody
from the police department
bug your apartment?
I don't know,
but there's a serial number
on the camera.
I'll go in tomorrow
and find out who checked it out.
I don't understand.
This could have something
to do with...
My sister's theory.
What are you talking about?
She has this theory about...
Vigilantes hunting down
the rapists.
So you think
she planted cameras?
No, it's not her.
I'd know.
It could be anyone.
But how could they be onto us?
We've been so careful.
I don't know yet.
The one good thing
is that no one has seen
those recordings yet.
How do you know?
Because
we haven't been arrested.
Jordan is gonna get away
with everything,
and we're gonna be arrested?
We don't know that.
Look, for now, we just pretend
like everything's okay.
If we have something
to talk about,
we talk about it out here,
where it's safe
but we were so close.
It can't end this way.
It's not going to.
I checked
with the apartment manager,
then the neighbors.
That motor home is gone.
It's got to be
one of these vans.
You said there were
four vans last night.
It's down to three now.
[Cell phone ringing]
I'll keep checking back.
Sonya, everything all right?
Everything is great.
Astor and Cody are spoiling
Harrison silly.
Good.
He's taking a little nap now,
so I was just making a list
for Sunday,
and I wondered, do you have
any special requests?
- Sunday?
- Harrison's birthday party.
Of course!
Right.
Harrison's birthday.
Astor and Cody
can't wait to see you.
I'm looking forward
to seeing them too.
But hold on a second.
It's not safe
to bring everyone here.
- We can go to them.
- You're coming?
I just invited myself.
Sonya, we're gonna have
the party in Orlando.
Oh.
Uh, okay.
It's... it's just easier than
making everyone drive down here.
Perfect.
[Cell phone beeps]
Come on, I got to get to work.
Keep an eye on these vans
and call me if you see anything.
[Elevator bell dings]
No torches, no pitchforks,
no one looking at me
any differently.
Dex, I need you.
In a minute.
I have something I need to do.
Find out who planted
those cameras.
We're all waiting on you.
That doesn't sound good.
[Indistinct chatter]
So, as I was saying,
everything keeps leading
back to Jordan Chase.
Why would he be running
a rape club with these putos?
I don't know. But I'm
pretty fucking sure he is.
Where are we on the banker,
Alex Tilden?
He's gone.
He disappeared.
We got his DNA
from a toothbrush...
ties him to the barrel girls,
like the others,
but no connection to Jordan
that we can find.
Then I suggest
you find that connection.
I'm on it.
- And the dentist, Mendell?
- He's the odd man out.
He doesn't seem
to have any connection
to any of the other guys.
Well, again,
let's find that connection.
Morgan, Quinn.
We got it.
Phone the neighbors.
Wake the kids.
Kick the dog.
Remember that muddy
female boot print
outside of Tilden's house?
Yeah, we found it.
Well, my brothers in blue,
it...
has a twin.
Found it outside
the vacant house next door.
Let me see that.
Naturally, I went inside.
The dining room was spotless,
and I mean recently cleaned
kind of spotless,
unlike the rest of the house.
My schnoz also detected
the smell of bleach.
One more day, and the smell
would have dissipated.
My guess...
the vigilante brought
your missing banker over
and offed him right there
in the dining room.
Excuse me,
did I hear the word...
"Vigilante"?
[Chuckles]
It was a theory
I was keeping to myself, but...
It's out there, but we may have
a vigilante on our hands.
I sent Masuka over to Tilden's
to see if he could comb
for any evidence
that a homicide
had taken place.
Keep going.
Please don't.
There are 13 DVDs...
And only 12 victims.
So I'm thinking that
one of the barrel girls escaped,
and now she's after the men
that abducted her.
And she is hunting them,
and she is killing them.
How is that even possible?
The barrel girls
are all slight of build.
Alex Tilden was, what,
175 pounds?
Minimum.
Maybe she had help.
Like who?
I don't know.
A...
A man...
Someone she trusts...
Someone who cares about her...
a father, a brother,
husband, boyfriend.
So now it's vigilantes
and love.
Yeah, like Romeo and Juliet,
except they didn't kill anyone.
No, more like, uh,
Bonnie and, uh...
Clyde.
Great.
They ended up dead
in a bullet-riddled car.
We all have our assignments.
Let's go.
Closer to ten minutes.
She likes a cup of coffee
with her smoke.
But that's more than enough time
to see that...
Detective Joseph Quinn
checked out the cameras...
three cameras, to be exact,
two microphones, a recorder...
only three days ago.
Maybe no one's seen
the footage yet.
Case number.
It's from 1982,
when Quinn was in grade school
eating paste.
It's a fake.
No court orders authorized
for my address.
This is off the books.
Quinn's doing this on his own.
Lumen, plans for lunch?
Start with the hard drive.
Yeah, any storage devices,
video files,
flash drives.
Wow, this thing is ancient.
Who is this guy?
Quinn...
My sister's partner.
Oh, wow.
Are they close?
They used to be.
You got anything?
Not much in the way
of video files.
Anything of us?
No.
Just a cat
that hiccups and farts
at the same time.
[Cat hiccups, farts]
Cute.
Check the bedroom.
You take the closet.
I'll check the drawers.
Oh, shit.
What is it?
- Us.
- The marina.
That's the night
we dumped Cole.
He's been watching us
for weeks.
He knows everything.
Wait, you're not gonna
take them with you?
Tip him off that we found them?
No, he'll just print more.
We have to find
the digital source.
Right.
Find the recording equipment.
We're not open anymore.
Mrs. Mendell?
Laura Mendell?
Yes?
I'm Detective Morgan.
This is Detective Quinn.
We'd like to ask you a couple
of questions about your husband.
Please, okay?
Just no more questions.
We've been through this, okay?
I don't know anything.
Of course, I should have.
Why is that?
I mean, I was very naive,
but now it all makes sense.
Those weeklong fishing trips
he used to take?
- He'd go without you?
- Of course without me.
It was just him
and his buddies.
He called it
his "man time."
But, of course, that has
a whole other meaning now.
Did he ever give you names
of the men on those trips?
No.
I never met any of them.
He kept me completely
in the dark
about his whole
closeted gay life.
I mean, why didn't he
just tell me?
Actually, Mrs. Mendell,
we have information
which leads us to believe
your husband wasn't,
in fact, gay.
The crime scene
may have been altered
to give that impression.
But he was linked
to a series of rapes.
And murders.
My God.
Who is this man I married?
I'm sorry to bring you
that news.
But do any of these names
sound familiar?
Boyd Fowler.
Cole Harmon.
No, I don't know them.
Alex Tilden.
Jordan Chase.
- Jordan Chase?
- Yes.
Well, that's him, right there.
"Best 2 man sailing team...
Dan Mendell and Eugene Greer"?
Jordan Chase is Eugene Greer...
Or he used to be.
Dan knew him
when they were kids.
It was a really big deal
to him.
That's our connection.
Why do you think the wife
never had a clue
about what was up
with her husband?
I mean,
this barrel-girl stuff
has gone on the entire time
they were married.
He was probably
a really good liar.
Men sometimes have
that ability, you know?
It was his fault, not hers.
How do you want to go
at this Eugene Greer thing?
Just pull up
everything we can...
school records, juvie records.
I fucking knew Chase
was full of shit.
Who creates a new identity
for themselves?
A dirt bag
who has something to hide.
I've got it.
[Elevator bell dings]
Jordan Chase lied
about knowing Alex Tilden.
In the past ten years,
Tilden oversaw six properties
purchased
by Chase's corporation.
Well, Dan the dentist
also knew him,
and Jordan Chase is an alias.
That whole bullshit persona
that he built for himself
is a lie.
Yeah, his real name's
Eugene Greer.
Mendell and Chase
were friends as kids.
So wait...
That ties Jordan directly
to each
of the barrel girls' rapists.
Yeah, but still
all circumstantial,
not enough to bring him in.
Yeah, but it's enough to bring
his lying ass in
for questioning.
We just got to keep pushing
at him, scare him a little bit
till he starts making
some mistakes.
Deb's closing in on Chase.
Quinn's closing in on me.
Time's running out
for both of us.
Hey, any good news?
Uh, yeah,
we've connected Jordan Chase
to all of the rapists,
so I'm about to nail
this fuck to the wall.
Good.
What... what's up?
I'm kind of busy.
Just wondering
if you want to go with me
to Orlando on Sunday
for Harrison's birthday.
Oh. Well...
I do, but...
You have other plans
with Quinn?
What?
No, it... it's with work.
It's the case.
Besides, Quinn's the last person
that you'd want to have there.
- Oh?
- Trust me.
So it's over?
Yes.
No.
Fuck, I don't know.
It's complicated.
You don't have to tell me.
He lied to me about something.
Must have been something big.
He lied to me about you.
About me?
What do you mean?
Quinn had this...
Idiot notion that...
You were somehow connected
to Rita's death.
[Scoffs]
That's...
It's crazy, I know.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because...
Because you've been
through enough.
And I just found out.
When he finally told me,
I felt so betrayed,
because...
As much as I don't want
to admit it,
I really care about him.
"Care," present tense?
It's complicated, remember?
I thought I knew him,
and he kept telling me
he loved me.
But what he did,
I mean, I can't have
somebody like that.
You know, you don't lie to
somebody that you're close to.
You have their back.
I need someone
I can trust 100%.
Like this.
[Laughs]
A boot print?
The vigilante...
She has someone in her life,
a guy who's helping her,
someone that would do anything
and everything for her.
How do you know that?
Honestly, I don't know, but...
What they're doing
takes devotion.
To kill someone together,
that's some pretty serious shit.
Is that what Lumen
and I have... Serious shit?
He's risking his life.
He's putting everything
on the line
to make what happened
to her right.
As crazy
as that sounds, what...
what word would you use
to describe that but "love"?
[Laughs]
It's pretty fucked up,
isn't it?
Yeah, pretty fucked up.
Kind of beautiful too.
Just got this in.
It's handmade.
It's very chic.
- Um, it's not quite me.
- Perhaps one of the rings.
How about that?
It's nice...
Small enough to carry,
locking pin,
stainless-steel blade.
How's it feel?
Good.
We'll take it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
It's just an hour or so
till Quinn gets off work.
If he decides to check
his recording equipment tonight,
I should be there.
What is Quinn after?
What does he want with us?
He doesn't want us.
He wants me.
He was coming after me
before we even met.
I didn't mean for you
to get caught up in this.
You should leave.
You tried that
once before, remember?
You tried to ship me away.
That was different.
I don't want you to leave...
For good...
Just till I deal with this.
Deal with it how?
I don't know...
whatever needs to be done.
[Sighs] I appreciate the offer,
but I'm not going anywhere.
- Lumen, it's getting dangerous.
- [Scoffs] Getting dangerous?
I'm not walking away.
We're a team.
We have serious shit.
What does that mean?
It's just something
Deb said about us.
You told her about us?
No, she was talking
about the vigilantes.
She was talking about us
without knowing
she was talking about us.
Oh.
[Sighs]
Maybe...
We should both take off.
Get on a cruise ship.
Hop a freighter.
Steal a tugboat.
You said that
you didn't want me to leave.
Does that mean
that you want me to stay?
I do.
We should go.
Okay, so Eugene Greer
grew up in some redneck town
near Tallahassee.
He had a single mom,
now dead, no siblings,
pretty nondescript childhood.
Moved to Miami when he was 18,
dropped about 100 pounds,
changed his name
to Jordan Chase,
pretty much reinvented himself.
Take a look at these
before-and-after photos.
Ooh.
Like a different person.
I think he might have had
some plastic surgery
along the way.
Look at this.
When they'd be off doing
their thing at the same time,
each of the barrel girls
disappeared.
Fuck, they did this for years.
Mm-hmm.
[Cell phone vibrates]
I got to take this.
I'm, uh, having
a really tough time here.
Doing what?
This...
Being with you.
Yeah, well, you should
have thought of that before.
I'm sorry.
I fucked up, I know.
I do dumb things.
I'm a dumb guy.
But the one thing I did right
was to get you
to almost like me...
- 'Cause I really love you.
- Don't, Quinn.
No, I mean it.
There aren't
many women like you.
I know that.
You're more like...
- A guy.
- A guy?
You don't play games
where I have to figure out
what it is
you're really thinking.
You just say it,
usually with a lot
of really filthy words
that I've never heard before.
You're the first woman who's
ever called me on my bullshit...
And made me take
a hard look at myself.
It's made me
a better person, I think.
I just don't want to lose you,
that's all.
Bad news.
Not only has Jordan
declined our request
for another interview,
but he just booked a multi-city
speaking deal in Europe.
Sounds like he's on the run.
No fucking way.
As of tomorrow,
he is untouchable,
unless we can find a way
to keep him here.
But like we keep saying,
we still don't have enough
to arrest him.
No, but, uh...
We can ground him
as a material witness.
We just have to get
a court order.
- Should we go to LaGuerta?
- No.
She shoots me down every time.
She won't help.
I can get it myself.
The only van that remains
after 24 hours
just happens to be a rental.
Judging by the amount of dust,
it's been sitting there
close to a week.
And here comes Quinn,
checking in before he heads
to the station.
I never wanted it
to come to this.
[Stun gun buzzing]
[Groans]
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello?
[Voice trembling]
Lumen, it's me, Emily.
What's wrong?
I got a call from Jordan Chase.
He knows I talked to you.
What? How?
I don't know.
You tell me.
I didn't talk to him.
What is going on?
I'm scared.
He scared me.
Emily, I have no idea
what's going on.
I'm going to the police.
I'll tell them everything.
No, no, don't do that.
Why?
They'll protect me.
Emily, it'll just make
things worse.
We'll protect you.
How?
Jordan is too powerful.
He has people.
Emily...
You know what he did to us.
Just stay in your house.
Wait for us.
We'll be there
as soon as we can.
Please, just tell me
that you'll wait for us.
Okay.
I'll wait, but hurry.
Please hurry.
[Cell phone beeps]
Very nice.
You're quite the actress.
[Line ringing]
Dexter Morgan.
Please leave
a message at the tone.
[Beep] Dexter, where are you?
Emily called, and Jordan knows
she talked to us.
We have to go see her.
[Groans]
[Cell phone ringing]
I hope you got voice mail.
[Ringing continues]
You're Quinn's friend.
That would be me.
F.Y.I., Stan Liddy is my name.
What are you doing?
I just need you to relax.
I'm taking us
to a little place,
have a little private chat,
that's all.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
'Cause our mutual friend,
Joey Quinn,
hired me to look into you,
and I guess you know
I found out some things.
So I just need you
to lie there and relax.
I don't want to zap you again,
but I will if I have to.
[Cell phone ringing]
What?
Come on, now, Joey.
Is that any way to talk
to your new best friend?
I told you, I don't want...
Shut up and listen up.
You get your ass in your car
and you drive on down
to the fuel docks
at Bayfront Park.
That big bust
I want you to make...
I need you to come down here
and make it now.
I don't know
what you think you're doing,
but you got to stop it
with this shit.
Aw, horseshit.
Nobody's stopping nothing.
You're the one who hired me.
And then I fired you.
Listen, boy, this is going
down with or without you.
Now, you don't get down here
faster than
a fucking jackrabbit,
I'm calling in another cop,
and then there's no telling
how this is gonna spin out.
Jesus, Liddy, just...
Jesus ain't got
nothing to do with it.
Old fuel docks,
Bayfront Park, now.
[Cell phone beeps]
Fuck.
Your buddy Quinn is on his way.
Didn't sound
like he wants to come.
[Cell phone chimes]
Well, you're
a real popular fella.
Sonya.
Who's Sonya?
My nanny.
Nanny.
Well, Sonya wants to know
if you want a magician
for the party.
Of course you do.
"Yes to magician."
Well, now...
There's something
I want to show you.
Looky here at this.
Ain't that neat?
And that's just a tiny bit
of what I recorded.
But I only got
one problem here.
I didn't have
no search warrant,
and these people
are sticklers for rules,
which is why...
You're gonna give me
a full confession.
[Knocking]
Where's Dexter?
He's not here.
No, I need you both.
You said you would protect me.
Emily, it's okay.
Calm down.
You have to call him.
Make him come, now.
Okay.
Okay, maybe I should
just go get him.
Maybe not.
I ain't stupid.
I know you're thinking,
"I got no reason
to make a full confession."
So I'm gonna give you a reason.
Lumen walks free.
Why should I trust you?
'Cause I don't give a shit
about her.
And I don't give a shit
about you either.
I just want my goddamn job
on the police force back.
I bring in somebody like you,
I get my picture
in the news and television,
everybody thinks
I'm a goddamn hero,
everybody loves me,
and they have to hire me back.
So I don't need your girl.
[Camera beeps]
What do you say?
Ooh!
Shit!
Liddy!
[Dexter grunting]
[Groans]
Go away, Quinn.
Don't make this any worse.
[Door handle clicks]
Liddy, where the fuck are you?
[Lock clicks]
[Door handle clicking]
[Number pad beeping]
[Panting]
[Line ringing]
Leave a message.
[Beep] Liddy, it's Quinn.
You're really starting
to fucking piss me off.
[Cell phone beeps]
[Engine turning]
[Car departing]
[Cell phone beeping]
Dexter, where are you?
Emily called.
Jordan knows she talked to us.
We have to go see her.
[Cell phone beeps]
[Camera whirs]
I don't have time
to deal with you.
[Splash]
[Number pad beeping]
- Please leave a message.
- I'm on my way.
Morgan...
My office.
I got a call earlier
from the judge
you petitioned
for your court order.
When's it coming?
It's not.
What?
Your request
to detain Jordan Chase
as a material witness
was denied.
That fuck is scheduled to fly
out of here one-way today.
This was our shot.
I understand why you're upset,
but what I don't understand
is why you didn't come to me.
- You're kidding.
- I'm asking.
You are the last person
I think of
when I need support.
Detective, you've been
on the force long enough
to know that situations
are rarely black and white.
Politics come into play.
That doesn't mean
that I signed up to be used.
We all get used,
and in this instance,
you should have used me.
You made it very clear
that you don't support
my vigilante theory.
And I'm still not sure
that there's anything to it,
but I have always trusted
your instincts as a cop.
Hoo.
[Sighs]
You know, at one point,
I actually thought
we were friends.
Well, detect...
Debra, I'm sorry...
If I betrayed that friendship.
Okay.
Wait.
What? What?
What is it?
Here.
- What is this?
- It's your court order...
From a different judge
who owed me a favor.
[Sighs]
Fuck me.
Now I'm the asshole, right?
You better get going
if you want to catch Jordan.
Right.
[Door opens, closes]
Lumen?
What could he be doing
that is so important
that he would let you
come here by yourself?
I don't know.
Yes, you keep saying that.
You're surprisingly
short of answers.
Maybe you should let me
call him.
Yes, brilliant,
because you certainly
wouldn't tip him off in any way.
I could try calling him.
Quiet, please.
Are you mad at me?
I did exactly
what you told me to do.
Please, shut up.
- I'm just trying to...
- Shut up!
It's not my fault.
Of course it's your fault!
- [Grunts]
- [Screams]
[Groaning]
[Growls]
I find this
profoundly distasteful.
I've never had
to do anything before!
Now I have no choice.
I can't leave any witnesses.
No, you said
you wouldn't kill her.
[Gasping]
Lumen.
Lumen?
Is this the only kind of love
I'll ever find...
The kind that ends in blood?
[Sirens wailing]
[Jet engines whirring]
[Wailing stops]
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for Jordan Chase.
I have a court order that
prevents him from leaving Miami.
Well, I guess
I can go home, then.
Is he on the plane?
No. I have no idea
where he is.
We were scheduled
to fly out over an hour ago,
and he never showed up.
Emily was killed
with two blows.
Lumen was here...
multiple footprints
in the blood,
a scuffle.
More blood, not from Emily,
leading out.
She was running.
She's putting up a fight.
Lumen.
Sync by n17t01
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Sync by n17t01
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com