Previously on Dexter...
We are going to...
All: Take it!
Cole Harmon,
Chase's chief of security...
torturer, rapist, killer.
It's time to tap into
my primal self.
Why did you want to see me?
I am very interested
in what happened to you.
I would like to discuss your
situation in-depth at another time.
Our informant, Yasmin Aragon,
was shot and killed.
This is a fucking disaster!
If mistakes were made, they
most certainly were not mine.
I can confirm
that Detective Morgan
was in charge of the operation.
As of today, she's being placed
on immediate suspension
with pay.
It's just your word
against mine.
Some people don't agree
with your version of the events.
Who did you get to lie for you?
It was you.
Don't you want to know
about this girl
shacked up with Dexter Morgan?
Name: Lumen Pierce.
Lumen shows up here
in Miami one week
before your boy's wife,
Rita Morgan, is murdered.
Aah!
You fuckin' bitch!
Who are the others?
The guy who held a watch
up to my ear.
Tick-tick-tick.
"That's the sound
of your life running out. "
It's what I tell my clients.
Tick-tick-tick.
That's the sound
of your life running out.
Jordan Chase is one of them.
We're gonna take down
Jordan Chase?
On a good day, when I run, the
voices in my head get quieter
until it's just me, my breath,
and my feet on the sand.
Pick up the pace, Dexter.
Today is not one of those days.
When I scheduled a private
session with Jordan Chase,
I wasn't looking for advice.
Just proof.
Evidence of exactly how he was
involved in Lumen's torture,
because the code
requires certainty.
Faster, Dex.
I just wanted access
to his office,
the inner sanctum
where I could find clues.
Instead, I'm stuck here,
running in place.
Look, I get it.
You're frustrated.
You feel like you're not getting
what you came here for.
Yeah, a bit.
Intense exercise works.
Tears down your defenses,
brings out your feelings.
Well, I have the feeling
that I'd be more comfortable
talking on a couch.
Trust me, this is the way
to build a new you.
At the seminar, we went over how
tragedy fractures us, right?
Yeah.
We're like Humpty Dumpty.
And the big fall.
What I'm telling you now is
trauma is also opportunity.
Tragedy tears us apart, sure.
But it's your one chance
to recreate yourself.
You get to put yourself back
together again any way you want.
Okay.
Don't be skeptical.
I know it for a fact.
How?
What happened to you?
You didn't come here
to talk about me.
Something big
must have happened
if it inspired
your entire philosophy.
Okay, I'll tell you
where it started
if you promise
to keep it between us.
Plato.
What?
The notion of a fractured self.
It's from Plato's Symposium.
You ever read it?
Maybe in college.
But you don't remember it,
right?
Most people don't.
But for me,
it was a revelation.
It was exactly what
I needed at the time.
So... I took it.
I took Plato's idea
that we are fractured creatures,
trying to become whole,
and I ran with it.
Boom, a million copies sold.
So... Now you know my secret.
You ready to tell me yours?
Over your dead body.
An hour on the treadmill,
and I came up empty.
Not a clue.
Only upside is I got in
my cardio for the day.
Jordan is one tough nut
to crack.
You're one tough nut to crack,
you know that, Dexter?
I wish he'd stop doing that.
We ran for an hour.
You didn't give up anything.
I know you're in killer shape,
but you can't outrun me forever.
You have to give me
something to work with.
Otherwise...
How can I help you?
Maybe you can't.
Or maybe you can.
Is that blood?
No pressure.
It can take several meetings for
us to have a real breakthrough.
But I do need your commitment.
I need to get my hands
on that vial.
Otherwise, we're just
wasting our time.
I really think
I can help you, though.
I think so too.
When can I get in
to see you again?
Check with my receptionist
on the way out.
I think I may have an opening
tomorrow morning.
Well, that was lucky.
10:00 A. M. tomorrow.
He doesn't have anything else
for the next two weeks.
- Perfect.
- See you tomorrow.
I didn't notice you last time.
You new here?
Just started three days ago.
I don't remember
so much security either.
Mr. Chase says
he's beefing things up.
That's no surprise.
Lumen and I have been knocking
off his friends one by one.
How many security guards?
I don't know.
Maybe a dozen.
But you think
that you can still
get to the blood
necklace thing, right?
Yeah. While Jordan's
in the shower.
Won't he notice
if it's missing?
No, I'm not gonna swipe it.
I'm just gonna extract
a sample.
I'll run it for DNA,
hopefully get an I. D.
Run it for DNA.
God, I love that
you can do that.
So whose blood
do you think it is?
- If it is blood.
- Most likely a victim.
Whatever it is,
it's important to him.
He's wearing it around his neck.
It's definitely
some kind of trophy.
Are you there?
- Oh, my God.
- What? What is it?
There's someone
at the kitchen door.
- They're trying to get in.
- Go out the front door.
I'll be there in a few minutes.
Dexter, there's someone
there too.
Hide.
- Where?
- In the bathroom.
I'll get there
as fast as I can.
What's happening?
They're inside.
What?
They're coming!
Put the phone down.
Leave the line open.
Jesus!
Who the fuck are you?
Who the fuck is she?
You wanna try that again,
Astor?
Who is she?
Her name is Lumen.
I mean who is she?
Why is she here?
She's... Renting the house.
You said the house was empty.
Thought it was.
How was I supposed to know
he got a girlfriend so fast?
First of all,
she's not my girlfriend.
She's a tenant, like I said.
Second of all, who are you?
I'm Olivia.
I live near her grandparents.
Anyone wanna tell me
how you got here?
Taxi.
It's 215 miles.
From a bus station.
Where'd you get the liquor?
- Does it matter?
- Yeah, I'd say so.
- You're 12.
- You said you were 14!
Thanks a lot.
If you really wanna know,
we stole it from my house.
That's reassuring.
I think I need to sit down.
Do your parents know
where you are?
My mom thinks I'm at Astor's.
Oh. Let me guess, your grandparents
think you're at Olivia's.
Don't call 'em.
Please.
At least not until tomorrow.
They should really
stay the night and sober up.
Then I'll stay too.
With her?
Oh.
I think I'm gonna...|
Here. Come with me.
I'll get you to bed, okay?
Quite a situation we have here.
Unless you have advice
on dealing with teenage girls,
I don't want to hear it.
My advice...
Get Astor out of here.
Tomorrow morning
you're collecting evidence
on a violent murderer
you plan to kill.
You really want a hung-over
preteen in the middle of that?
- She came here.
- Drunk!
I can't just turn her away.
Dexter, there's a reason serial
killers don't have children.
You can't be killer and dad.
Haven't you learned anything?
Her mother is dead
because of you.
Which is why I need to make things
right and be a good father.
A good father would get those
girls as far away as possible.
Harrison's still
at the apartment with Sonya.
I'm gonna go get him,
bring him back here.
Deb.
You're gonna break something.
Relax.
You relax.
You're not about to have
the worst meeting
of your career.
It's a union rep.
He's on your side.
You know, just be professional
and don't freak out
until you actually know
what's gonna happen.
I know what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna get fired...
No, you're not.
Even Laguerta said
this isn't gonna stick.
- I'm supposed to trust her?
- No.
But you can trust me.
Everything's gonna be okay.
You know why?
'Cause you're gonna get
your job back.
You got everyone
at the station on your side.
You got a boyfriend
who loves you.
Seriously? You're gonna
drop that on me now?
It's just an expression.
It slipped out.
- I gotta go.
- Fine. Forget I said it.
What?
Good morning to you, too,
sunshine.
- You alone?
- Yeah. What's up?
Your pecker.
Soon as you take a look
at these snaps I took
of your boy Dexter Morgan
and his gal pal on some kind of
middle of the night boat run.
- Wanna meet for a beer?
- It's 7:00 A. M.
Beer is good anytime.
- Yeah. I gotta work.
- Then I'll come to you.
What'd I just say?
I can't now!
I'll call you later.
You sure you wanna keep
your appointment with Jordan?
Well, I need to.
There's not gonna be another
chance to get the blood.
Besides, it's something
I actually know how to do.
You were a teenage girl,
right?
How do I deal with Astor?
Try talking to her.
Last time I did that,
she said she hated me
and moved to Orlando.
Well, now you get
a second chance.
Share something with her...
What you did when you were her age.
I killed the neighbor's dog.
Well, don't tell her that.
Seriously, what do I do?
Just... Cut her some slack.
All kids that age
make mistakes.
Trust me, the hangover
will be punishment enough.
Oh, is that your brother?
Harrison.
He doesn't even recognize me.
Well... You didn't look like a
raccoon the last time he saw you.
Eat.
It's hangover food.
It'll soak up the alcohol.
Talk to her.
Share something.
So I need to go
to a meeting in a few minutes.
But I was hoping after that we
could spend the day together,
'cause we really should talk.
So is that okay?
Can Harrison come?
Sure.
I'll call the babysitter,
tell her
there's a change of plans.
Mama.
I have no idea
why he said that.
- I barely know him.
- Stop lying, okay?
I'm not stupid.
She's not your mama.
- Your mama's dead.
- Astor.
I'll tell you this.
If you were the one who died, I
really doubt my mom would have
brought in a tenant so fast.
- I should go.
- I know.
We'll only be a couple hours.
I can handle it.
My family is pretty weird too.
Hey.
How'd it go
with the union suit?
They're sticking me
in the file room.
Till after my hearing.
You're not fired.
It's good news.
Yeah, it's great.
Except everybody still thinks
I'm responsible
for that girl dying
and all those kids getting
wounded in that nightclub.
For the record, my report
backed your story 100%.
Not that it mattered.
The brass backed my wife.
Matters to me.
Thank you.
Anybody needs
a real fucking detective,
I'll be in the file room.
Detective scapegoat
reporting for duty.
They said you'd be joining me.
Come on.
I can get you started.
Right over there.
So... How's it going
with that man of yours?
This morning out of the blue, he...
Told me he loved me.
Oh!
You say it back?
No. I ran.
What? What's the problem?
You don't feel the same way?
No, the problem is is that...
I'm afraid I might.
Oh!|
What is this,
the barrel girls case?
- File it under creepy?
- Under closed cases.
Not read, honey. File.
That's what I get paid to do,
and for the next few weeks,
So do you.
Good session.
Another hour
of running in place.
You seem more open.
You feel the difference?
Yeah.
I feel like I might...
Take away something valuable this time.
Mm. Good.
Well, I gotta tell ya.
I still feel like you're not
being completely honest with me.
Really?|
- 'Bout what?
- About what you really want.
What I really want...
Just a drop.
A 30-gauge needle should
slide right in undetected.
He won't even notice
it's missing.
What do you mean?
What you want out of life.
Whatever it is,
you have to tell me
so that I can help you
construct a plan to get there.
I have a plan to get there.
Lumen and I follow
this blood trail.
We take you out.
Believe it or not,
you're helping me already.
I hope so.
I really do.
Each of us...
Deep down, we know what we really want.
It's just a matter
of actually doing it.
Yeah.
Oh.
I gotta get back to work.
New evidence to process.
But, uh, thanks again
for everything.
So when's our next appointment?
I'll check with
the receptionist.
What did I tell you?
You're supposed to be filing
things away, not makin' a mess.
Wait, wait.
I was reading that.
- Yeah, that's the problem.
- Just give me one more second.
Holy shit!
Look at this.
What am I lookin' at?
DNA results.
Multiple DNA results.
- The barrel girlsase?
- Mm-hmm.
We pinned this on one guy
and...
Looks like there are
multiple perps.
I'm just gonna...
Tell me what you see.
DNA sequencing report, uh...
Partial sequences on three,
maybe four perps?
What case is this?
Barrel girls.
Didn't we... Didn't we
pin this on one guy?
Yes. Boyd Fowler.
But the coroner found trace DNA
on the girls that wasn't Boyd's.
There were partial sequences
from multiple people.
It's all in the file.
Why am I only hearing
about this now?
Because by the time the final
coroner report came through,
we'd already closed the case.
The only reason
I came across this
was because I was
filing it all away.
Look.
This is Cole Harmon,
our original suspect.
Jordan Chase's security guy.
We let him go.
We got DNA samples on him.
Tell me what you see.
There are enough common markers
that Cole Harmon
is looking pretty good
for the barrel girls' murders.
At the very least,
he can't be excluded.
What are you saying, that Cole
and Boyd did this together?
Yeah.
With maybe three
or four others.
We gotta reopen this case.
I know.
But I can't tell Laguerta.
I'm supposed to be
on file clerk duty.
Wh... I'm not tellin' her.
This case was solved.
If I ask her to reopen it, I may
as well put my balls in a vice.
And not in a hot way either.
Well, that just leaves... Me.
Hey. You're late.
Yeah. Tough morning.
Astor showed up on my doorstep
last night drunk with a friend.
How old's the friend?
Just kidding.
What's that?
Blood sample?
Yes. It's a blood sample.
Top secret, huh?
I get it.
So... What is it?
Blood alcohol for Astor?
She vomited all over the floor.
Further testing's
kind of unnecessary.
STD panel?
Vince, she's 12.
I meant for you.
It's a homicide victim I'm supposed
to have processed already.
I made a mistake,
forgot to submit it, okay?
Morgan.
Dexter, the girls are gone.
Gone where?
I don't know.
But they're missing.
They felt terrible, and we didn't
have any Advil in the house,
so I took Harrison
to the store.
- You left them alone?
- I was trying to be nice.
And when I got back,
they were gone.
- Maybe they went for a walk.
- I don't think so.
The back door was wide open,
and their cell phones
are still here.
Dexter, what 14-year-old girl
willingly leaves
her cell phone behind?
Don't move.
I'll be right there.
I'm so sorry.|
What's going on?
I went to the neighbor's house
to see if he saw anything.
- What?
- Hey.
So I saw some guy
near the house.
Light hair, average build,
mid-30s.
Like Cole and Boyd and Dan.
Oh, he had a white panel van.
And it was weird enough
I checked out the plate.
N4b something.
Why didn't you stop him?
I didn't know
the girls were in the house.
I mean, I didn't even know
you had a tenant.
Just thought he was a...
a painter or something.
Which is why you thought
to check the license plate?
Well, no, that's just habit
from neighborhood watch.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
What are you doing?
Looking for signs
of a break-in.
An abduction... That's what
we're thinking here, right?
Yeah. But it doesn't
make any sense.
It does if someone
came looking for us.
Like one of Jordan's guys.
There's a reason
you were worried last night
when you heard noises
in the house.
But I overreacted.
It was nothing.
Only this time there was someone
lurking around the house.
I shouldn't have stolen
that blood sample.
Not with the girls here.
We need to call the cops.
They'll just start
asking questions.
And if it does have to do
with Jordan,
they'll probably trace it
all back to us.
Metro.
This is Dexter Morgan
from Homicide.
I'd like to report
a probable child abduction.
It's a white panel van.
I have a partial plate.
We've issued a blanket
APB on the van.
NCIC has started a file
on the girls.
Until we get them back safely,
Detective linker will be
our liaison to missing persons.
Did you call Olivia's parents?
I tried.
I couldn't get a hold of them.
What about Astor's
grandparents?
They hadn't heard from her.
I didn't tell them
she was missing, though.
Didn't want to worry them.
- Yet.
- Most missing children
are abducted by someone
the parents know.
Is there anyone
you can think of?
No. Nobody.
You sure?
No one new?
Where were you, anyway,
when they were taken?
I can't lie about this.
Not with Astor's life
on the line.
I was with Jordan Chase.
He... offered me some private
sessions to help deal with...
Rita's death.
What?
A lot of fucked up people
circling that guy, Dex.
A lot? Who?
Besides Boyd Fowler.
Well, his head of security
for one.
I thought we cleared him.
May have been premature.
Okay... What's going on?
The barrel girls case might
not be as closed as we thought.
Can we just find the van?
- Don't move!
- Show me your hands!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What... what's going on?
On your knees!
Hands on your head now!
Yeah, right there.
Who is he?
Name's Barry Kurt.
No priors.
They found him at
a gas station on Coral.
- Where's Astor?
- Hey... Easy!
If you hurt her, I'll kill you.
- I'll kill you.
- Get your hands off of me.
- You understand me?
- He's looking for the girls
- just like you.
- He's what?
I'm Olivia's father.
Sort of, anyway.
I live with her mom.
I'm Astor's stepfather,
Dexter Morgan.
Yeah. You should
try to calm down.
He thought something
happened to his daughter.
Something is gonna happen
to them when I find them.
Olivia broke into
our liquor cabinet,
stole money from her mother,
and took off.
We've got GPS tracking
on her mobile phone.
I followed it to your house,
but they weren't there.
I figured I'd gas up the van
and go back.
Next thing I know,
I'm on my knees in cuffs
like some loser on cops.
So where are they?
Probably causing trouble
somewhere.
Ever since Astor
moved down the block,
Olivia's been nothing
but a pain in the ass.
Morgan.
Is he always this violent?
They found the girls
at Bayside.
They're holding them
for shoplifting.
Astor?
Thank God.
We had the whole department
looking for you.
We were so worried.
You have no idea what you
put us through today.
- I'm sorry.
- What were you even thinking
- running off like that?
- Shoplifting?
That figures.
We didn't steal anything.
I swear.
I just tried on a ring
and forgot about it.
It was a mistake.
I gave it back.
I'm Detective Debra Morgan
from Miami Metro Homicide.
Mind if I take it from here?
Just make sure I don't
see these two again.
- Come on, we're going home.
- No!
- Now.
- My stuff's at Astor's.
- I need to go with her.
- You need to come with me.
- I don't want to.
- Tell you what.
Their stuff is at my house.
Why don't I take them there,
get them packed.
We'll meet you in an hour.
You're gonna need to get your
van out of impound anyway.
Which you're paying for,
by the way.
We'll meet you
at the Roadside Cafe.
- It's right near impound.
- Great.
Teenagers.
They can make you homicidal.
I know what you mean.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yeah.
You wanna tell me what's going on
with you and Detective Morgan?
Nothing.
What do you mean?
Obviously, you've been talking
about the barrel girls case.
We found some new evidence.
You and Detective Morgan.
She did.
In the file room.
I was going to tell you.
What?
You really don't see
what's going on?
I send her to the file room
with one assignment... file.
And then she magically
finds evidence
to reopen a case
she knows I personally closed.
Maria... It's DNA.
It's not like she made it up.
She's trying to get back at me.
We pinned this on Boyd Fowler.
I had five detectives
tell me he's the one.
And now I am telling you
that it's more complicated.
- You need to reopen the case.
- I disagree.
Changing five names
on the murder board
from black to red isn't
gonna help this department.
The department?
Or you?
What happened?
Uh... There were at Bayside.
- Oh, thank God.
- Shoplifting.
You gonna introduce us?
That's the one I was
telling you about.
His new girlfriend.
She's my tenant.
Lumen, this is my sister Debra.
Deb, Lumen.
I didn't know he had a tenant.
Didn't know he had a sister.
I'm gonna...
Go check on the girls.
Seriously?
That's your tenant?
- Yes.
- Oh.
Where's all her stuff?
She hasn't really moved in yet.
But you know her well enough
to trust her with your son.
It was an emergency.
I thought the girls
had been taken.
Why are you keeping her
a secret?
I'm not.
Really?
'Cause at the station
we asked you who you were
spending your time with.
You didn't think to mention
the hot blonde
that's living in your house?
Didn't seem...
Like it mattered.
Obviously,
she didn't take the girls.
That's not the point.
I'm not judging you.
Believe me, I understand rebound
as much as anybody.
But don't you think
it's a little soon?
I'm not on any rebound.
Come on.
She's your tenant?
Really?
There's nothing going on.
Fine.
I give up.
I gotta get back
to the station.
Deb knows about
my partner in crime.
The whole station knows
I'm seeing Jordan Chase.
This is not my day.
Astor!
Just... Stay cool.
No matter what.
You want to tell me
what's going on with you?
No.
'Cause nothing
is going on with me.
Something is.
You're drinking, shoplifting.
I already told you,
we didn't steal anything,
and it wasn't me anyway.
You want to tell me
why Barry thinks
you're the bad influence here?
'Cause he's an asshole.
Stop.
This is not a good path
you're headed down here.
Look, just tell me
what's wrong, okay?
I'm actually a good listener.
You want to know what's wrong?
My mom got murdered,
and you move her into our house
and tell me she's your tenant?
She is.
She's more.
I can fucking tell.
Astor, you cannot
talk to me that way.
Oh.
I thought you said
you were this great listener.
I don't want to
talk about this anymore.
Then we'll just sit here
till you do.
You ready to go home?
Not really.
You know I ran away once, too.
I ditched out
on my own wedding.
I didn't run away.
Who did that to you?
The bruises on your stomach.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Actually, I really do.
I think we have a problem.
Yeah, I'm in a battle of wills
with my drunk, shoplifting
teenage step-daughter,
and she's going to win.
Olivia has bruises
all over her stomach and back.
Someone's been hurting her.
She told you?
No, I saw.
Wait, you knew about this?
Don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
I'm just, um...
I don't know what I am.
I'll be with Olivia.
Promise you won't say anything?
I don't want him
to hurt her more.
Who?
Barry.
Who do you think?
He is an asshole.
Does her mom know?
He only hits her
in places that don't show.
He gets all crazy over nothing.
He doesn't like her hair,
she's two minutes late.
I thought she'd be safe here,
but then there's Lumen,
and Barry showed up,
and we just... ran.
Why didn't you tell me?
'Cause I didn't think
you'd care.
Of course I care.
Even when we all lived here,
you were so busy
out doing stuff all the time.
Olivia's my friend.
My only friend since mom died.
I wanted to help her, and...
I didn't know what to do.
You did know what to do.
You came home.
I'm gonna take care of this.
Okay?
Everything okay with Astor?
Nothing turning 20 won't fix.
What'd Laguerta say?
She's not gonna
reopen the case.
She thinks that you have some
kind of vendetta against her.
That's fucking ridiculous.
Give her a day to cool off.
We'll try again tomorrow.
You're not gonna
reopen the case?
Are you serious?
Come right in, detective.
There are at least
five dead girls in barrels.
And now there's DNA evidence
saying that some of the people
that are responsible
are still out there.
And you think that's about me
trying to get back at you?
Did you even read the file?
There's fucking proof.
Just watch your tone.
You know...
You throwing me under the bus
for the Fuentes brothers,
using your husband
as a chess piece,
putting Quinn
on bogus vacation days
so that I don't have
a fucking partner?
If that's all just some game to
you, I'll try to understand it,
but those girls are dead.
Don't you want to make sure
that that doesn't happen again?
I mean, what the fuck
are we doing here?
Enough!
Okay.
Okay what?
I'm reopening the case.
But you need to hear me,
because you have no idea
what you're talking about.
I made the Fuentes situation
go away.
I was trying to help Batista.
As far as Quinn goes,
he wasn't on vacation.
I suspended him.
To protect your brother.
Protect him from what?
You're so interested in
the truth, ask Quinn.
Hey.
Can I talk to you?
In private?
Look, if this
is about this morning...
Last month, when you told me
that you were taking
some vacation days,
were you actually
on suspension?
Why?
Who told you that?
Were you?
Did Laguerta say something?
She told me
I should talk to you.
Did it have something
to do with my brother?
Yeah.
But it was nothing.
Then why did you lie?
I was investigating Rita's
murder, trying to help.
I had a lead on Kyle Butler.
I figured if we could find
the person who knew Trinity,
then maybe we could
track down the creep
who killed
your sister-in-law.
Laguerta told me to back
off, leave it to the FBI.
When I didn't,
she suspended me.
What was the lead?
It doesn't matter.
It didn't pan out.
Laguerta told me that she
was protecting Dexter from you.
Why would she say that?
You remember those composite
sketches of Kyle Butler?
I got this crazy idea that
maybe it was your brother.
Nothing came of it,
so I dropped it.
I'm an idiot, okay?
Yeah, you are.
Deb, I...
Shit.
What's this?
Where's Olivia?
I just wanted to...
Speak to you first, parent to parent.
Oh.
You talk to Astor?
Yeah, I did.
Honestly, I'm not sure
what I should do.
I feel for you, man.
It's tough looking after
somebody else's kids.
Sometimes you just gotta
show 'em who's boss.
Is that what you do with
Olivia, show her who's boss?
What's that supposed to mean?
I know about Olivia's bruises,
how they're strategically placed
so they won't show.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
No?
Let me show you?
That's your solar plexus.
Right now, your diaphragm
is partially paralyzed,
which is why you're having
trouble catching your breath.
What are you, man,
some kind of psycho?
Not today.
Just a concerned parent.
Aah!
Ohh!
That's your liver.
The nice thing
about the liver is
if you hit it just right,
you get the vagus nerve,
which tentacles out
to the rest of your body.
Your brain short-circuits,
your body shuts down,
and you feel,
what's the word, terror?
Which is what Olivia felt
every time you hit her there
just so the bruises
wouldn't show.
I want you to listen
to me carefully.
Listen to me carefully, because
this is what you're gonna do.
You're gonna call
Olivia's mother.
You're gonna tell her
you're sick of her fat ass.
You can't stand
to look at it anymore.
And you're gonna
make her believe it,
because if you don't,
she may take you back one day
and let you near her kid
or mine.
And I can't let that happen.
You're not even gonna swing by
to pick up your stuff.
You're just gonna leave.
Tomorrow, when I drop Olivia
off, you will be gone.
If you ever come back, believe me,
I won't go so easy next time.
By the way, that's your kidney.
I can't believe it.
I don't want to hear it, okay?
"This isn't your business,
Dexter.
"Don't get involved, Dexter.
You put too much
at risk, Dexter. "
That's not
what I was gonna say.
I'm proud of you.
You are?
You protected Astor, put yourself
out there for another person.
I had no idea
you had that in you.
I underestimated you.
Assumed you were a monster
when you were capable
of so much more.
If only I'd seen that,
maybe I wouldn't have
led you down this path.
Deb?
Hi, honey.
Get the fuck
out of my apartment.
I brought you a present.
Don't you
want to see what it is?
Your boy Dexter Morgan
and his lady friend
on his boat
at 3:00 A. M. in the morning,
and they are not fucking.
What's in the bags?
Something heavy.
I'm thinking narcotics,
maybe a body.
Are you crazy?
Yeah, but that's
beside the point.
Point is that when they came
back, those bags were gone,
so whatever they're hiding,
it's something big.
This was a bad idea.
Here. Consider this
your severance package.
We're done.
Really?
What? You think you
can just pay me off
like I'm the corner whore?
I'm just saying,
it's time to stop.
And I'm sayin' bullshit.
If this thing is as big
as I think it is,
Laguerta and all them
other douchebags in homicide
are gonna be kissing my ass.
Back off, Liddy.
I mean it.
I told you don't fuck with me.
You know, I just think I may
call up that sister.
Give her a ring, see
if she wants to get together,
have a drink,
maybe talk about the brother.
What do you say?
Stay the fuck away from me!
And stay the fuck
away from Deb!
So you really did
change your mind.
I read the report.
Thank you.
Does this mean...
You'll stop sleeping
on the couch?
We still got a long way to go
between the couch
and the bedroom, Maria.
So, what, now you're
not even talking to me?
Deb, look, I had an idiot
theory and I dropped it.
Yeah, because
Laguerta suspended you.
No, because I was wrong.
Look, what I said
yesterday is true.
I love you, and I'm
not taking it back.
You don't even know
what that means.
It means I'd never do
anything to hurt you.
Ever.
I trusted you.
And while you were fucking me,
you were spreading shit
about my brother behind my back.
You think
that's not hurting me?
Fuck you.
You want us
to come inside with you?
No, I'll be okay.
I could barely understand
my mom on the phone
with all the crying,
but she actually said
Barry did her a favor leaving.
He definitely did me a favor.
He told her she has a fat ass.
He is not coming back.
Thank you.
Call you later.
Are you gonna tell
grandma and grandpa?
About you getting drunk
in Miami and shoplifting?
Nah, that's up to you.
We all have our secrets, right?
Thanks.
- But if it ever happens again...
- It won't.
- And if Barry ever shows up...
- I'll tell you, I promise.
I'm proud of you.
You are?
Yeah. You... put yourself out
there for another person.
I want you to know something.
If Lumen's your girlfriend,
I want you to tell me.
Okay.
But she's not.
She's not just
your tenant, though.
She's a friend who's been
through some really...
Really bad stuff.
I'm helping her deal with it.
Does it make you feel better?
What do you mean?
About mom.
Being there for Lumen,
does it make you feel better
about what happened to mom?
I love you.
You know that?
You should come in, say hi to Cody.
It'll blow your cover, about Miami.
Mama.
This is mama?
Okay, bud.
Jordan Chase told me to
figure out what I want most.
The answer is simple.
To be a good dad.
But now that Astor's safe,
what I want most
is Jordan on my table.
I need to get
an I. D. on that blood.
- Hey.
How was Orlando?
Uh, it was
pleasantly uneventful.
Astor's back with her grandparents,
Cody grew about a foot.
Oh. Glad to hear it.
Your blood results
are in, by the way.
So did you get back an I. D.
on your homicide victim?
No.
Then what's that?
She's not a victim.
She's alive, boozing it up
in Coral Gables.
Two D. U. I. s in three years.
I guess I messed up.
If she's not a victim,
then who is she?
No worries.
When you mess up, it makes
me feel better about me.
Dexter?
No, it's Jordan Chase.
But I'm looking for Dexter.
Is he there?
He...
He's not available right now.
Can I leave a message?
Uh-huh.
Tell him I'm just checking in,
and I'd like him to schedule
another appointment
as soon as possible.
Okay.
I will. Bye.
Hang on a second.
Tell Dexter one more thing.
Okay.
Tell him time
is of the essence.
Tick tick tick.
That's the sound
of his life running out.
Could you be sure
to tell him that?
Take care, Lumen.