[Quirky music]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
So how the hell was your date
with Rita last night?
Great. I think I met
the right woman for me.
She's perfect, because Rita
is as damaged as me.
I can't believe I found
the one good,
truly decent man
left on the planet.
- I have a dark side too.
- Somehow I doubt that.
I watched my mother die
when I was three.
Aah!
She was murdered
in front of me.
You have your demons,
but I know that you don't
have to be a slave to them.
I wish that were true.
I want to someday be content
like everyone else.
I want...
A normal life.
- I wanna marry you.
- Yes!
You guys are my family.
Now I have a partner for life.
I'm content.
Maybe even happy.
I hope you're not taking
any of this seriously...
the wife, the kids.
It's all great camouflage.
It's gotten more
complicated than that.
I'm pregnant.
You want to see him
come into the world.
Yes.
Raise him with Rita.
I know.
I've never wanted anything
so much in my life.
Wanna know a secret?
Daddy kills people.
[Muffled scream]
There's a monster
walking around free.
I call him the Trinity killer.
Kills in threes.
Trinity's a husband, a father.
He's...Like me.
What kind of father
keeps blood slides in his shed?
If I don't figure out
how to hide this,
I'm gonna lose my family.
Arthur's kept this up
for what... 20 years?
My family
may not last 20 minutes.
Arthur Mitchell.
Kyle Butler.
Only way it was gonna work
is if I jumped in
with both feet.
Jump in with both feet, huh?
This is your
new role model, Dex?
Get that ax from him.
Kill him now.
I still have things
to learn from him.
You're juggling
too many people, Dexter.
Blood tech, husband, father,
serial killer.
Now Kyle Butler.
Which one are you?
All of them.
Hello...
Dexter Morgan.
Hello, Arthur Mitchell.
[Crunch]
[Beep]
Rita: Hey, sweetie.
The moon tonight
is gonna be amazing.
So take a moment.
We love you. Bye.
[Harrison crying]
Rita?
Born in blood.
Both of us.
I thought I could
change what I am,
keep my family safe.
But it doesn't matter
what I do.
This is fate.
[Crying echoes distantly]
[Siren wails]
[Tires screech]
[Crying sounds normal]
Sir, did you call this in?
Sir.
What happened here?
[Crying grows distant, echoes]
I've watched 67 people die...
And at the moment of truth,
I looked into their eyes
and they knew and I knew
they got what they deserved.
But what if that's not
what happens?
If you don't get
what you deserve?
If what you deserve
is a white picket fence
and your kids all around
and a husband who loves you?
What if the least you deserve
is a real human being
and what you get instead is me?
Sir. Sir, we're going to take
the child into safe custody now.
Sir, hand me the child.
What are you doing?
Back off!
Ma'am!
Miami homicide.
He is too.
I said back the fuck off!
What happened?
[Harrison crying]
[Quietly]
Oh, my God. Dexter...
Rita's inside.
It was me.
[Crying echoes, fades]
Skin's wrinkled from hours
in the alkaline water.
Rigor mortis full-blown.
Epidermal mottling.
I imagined her naked
plenty of times,
but never like this.
Single cut
to the femoral artery.
We're looking at
Trinity's M.O. here.
Did he ever kill a married
woman in a bathtub?
First time for everything.
Unfortunately for Dexter.
We're still waiting
on the coroner to move the body.
But overall lividity
puts time of death
somewhere between
8 and 12 hours...Ago.
[Police radio,
background chatter]
[Sirens]
You okay?
Dexter came home to that.
He's gonna need
our support here.
Obviously.
What do you want us
to do with him?
The first thing
I want you to do
is pack up and get outta there.
- Well...
- What?
The FBI's here.
Trinity's their case.
I already ceded jurisdiction.
What are you looking
at him for?
It's what I was saying
on the way over.
Rita's one of ours.
She's family.
We should be working
on this for Dexter.
Damn it, Angel, it's done!
Just do what I say.
She's stressed.
We all are.
[FBI guys chattering]
[Helicopter blades thrumming,
siren wailing]
[Heartbeat thumping,
sounds muted]
My father Harry
taught me a few simple rules.
Never hurt an innocent
and never make a scene.
Harry?
Where are you, now,
when I really need you?
When it's my wife
in the body bag,
everybody's looking,
and it's the neighbor crying,
not me?
[Heartbeat thumping,
sounds muted]
[Sounds back to normal,
police radio chatter, sirens]
[Helicopter blades thrumming]
Sir?
We're ready for you.
The first responders told me
when they went inside
and found your wife
you said, "it was me."
You sure?
That's what was reported
to me, yeah.
I don't know what I said.
It could have been anything.
I'm very upset.
Of course you are.
Who wouldn't be?
Mr. Morgan,
before you came home
and found your wife,
where did you say
you were again?
Dexter, take off your clothes,
then we're going home.
- I was asking him a question.
- He already said he came home
and he found her there.
If you wanna help,
why don't you find Trinity?
Or is doing something
actually useful
not in your fucking
job description?
- Detective Morgan.
- FBI?
Fucking bunch of idiots.
Stop.
Finish up here,
then take your brother home.
You wanna talk to Dexter,
schedule an appointment.
I'll do that.
He can sleep on the floor
until we can bring his crib
over from the house.
It'll be safest,
don't you think?
[Dexter grunts]
I gotta tell you, Dexter,
don't say things like,
"it was me."
People will misunderstand.
In fact, I don't understand.
What did you even mean?
Dexter.
[Calmly] This is Dexter Morgan.
3319 Meadow Lane.
What is your emergency?
I just got home and found
my wife dead in the bathtub.
[Click]
What is this?
The 911 call Dexter made.
Listen.
[click]
I just got home and found
my wife dead in the bathtub.
Did you say your wife is dead?
Yes, I did.
She has an approximately
1-inch incision
midway up her right thigh,
dissecting the femoral artery.
Right. That's enough.
He obviously's in shock.
"Midway up her right thigh?
Dissecting her femoral artery"?
- Habit of precision.
- His wife just died.
He's submitting a lab report.
Seriously,
the next door neighbor,
the guy with the,
you know, forehead?
He was more broken up about
Rita than Dexter was.
- So?
- So it's weird, that's all.
What are we working on here?
Not Rita.
It's Dexter's 911 call.
Did you hear me or not?
I said the case
is with the FBI now.
You should have taken her
on a honeymoon.
You were right
about one thing...
that neighbor Elliot
being all broken up about Rita.
I'm thinking now
there's some things
I shouldn't have told Dexter.
What? What shouldn't you
have told him?
About a significant
exchange of saliva
I witnessed at Thanksgiving.
As in a kiss.
Elliot and Rita?
Dude was totally
in love with her.
- And Dexter knew.
- Yeah.
If I'd known she was gonna...
I should have kept
my big mouth shut.
[Cell phone rings]
[Ringing]
Could someone get that?
Deb?
[Ringing]
Oh. Damn it.
Hello.
Dexter, it's Maura.
[carnival music in background]
Hello?
I'm sorry if I woke you,
but I have got two very
excited kids here,
and Rita's not answering.
Yeah, there's something
you need to know.
Okay. Okay, okay.
But first somebody really
wants to talk with you.
[Giggling]
Dexter!
Hey, Cody, you okay?
We've been having the best day.
I had cotton candy
for breakfast.
That's great.
Astor: Here, give me the phone.
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
Hey, Dexter.
Can I talk to mom?
- Not now.
- Why not?
She's, uh...
She's in the shower.
Well...Can you tell her
we miss her?
Cody: We miss you too,
Dexter, and Harrison.
Astor: Here's my grandmother.
[Laughing]
So there was something
that you needed to tell me?
When you bring them home
tonight, uh...
[Harrison fusses]
Come to Deb's apartment
instead of the house...Okay?
What happened,
did you miss your flight?
Something like that.
I'll explain when you get here.
You sure you don't want
to tell them about Rita?
[Exhales]
I just want them to have
one more good day.
Look, I know
this is really difficult...
But there are a lot of things
that need to happen
before Rita can be buried.
I've been on the phone
all morning
with a funeral director
who does a lot of cops.
And he's willing to see us
right away.
You willing to do that?
I'm sorry for your loss.
How does he do that?
My sincere condolences.
He sounds like
he actually means it.
Thank you.
Would you like
something to drink?
Coffee?
Water?
No. I'm fine.
[Harrison fusses]
There are kleenexes here...
If you need them.
What we need to do now,
Dexter...
M-may I call you that?
What we need to do now, Dexter,
is make some very
important decisions
about how your wife Rita
will be remembered.
Okay.
We like to start with
the obituary.
It's a good way to let people
know about services
and where to send remembrances.
But most importantly,
it's a chance to express
your feelings about Rita
in your own words.
'Scuse me.
I'll get you something
for the paper.
What else do you need?
So this is how
normal people do it.
No hefty bags.
No diesel fumes.
[Sobbing]
This is what
she would have wanted...
a grieving spouse...
For once doing what
a person's supposed to do.
Dexter Morgan?
Rita?
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
That's no problem.
There was traffic, of course.
I went to the wrong cafe.
I went to the one in town.
I didn't know there was
anything even out this far.
How did you find this place?
I, uh...
Tracked it down.
So I... your sister...
Debra's told me
so much about you.
- Uh-oh.
- Oh.
Nothing bad, of course.
She omitted the fact
that I'm an ax murderer?
No. She said that
you were a...
Bloodstain pattern analyst...
Which I have no clue
what that is.
Believe me, I barely do either,
and I do it 40 hours a week.
She seems nice, your sister.
You seem nice too.
Thank you.
[Chuckles]
So, um, what's good here?
I mean,
there must be something special
to bring you
all the way out this far.
I...
I usually play it safe
and go with a Caesar salad.
But I don't see one on here.
You know, I think
I'm gonna get the special,
the mushroom ravioli.
Dexter?
Do you know what you want?
Yes, I do.
[Woman sobbing]
Dex.
What are you doing?
I was just thinking
about Rita, how much...
How much you miss her?
How much I lied to her,
from the very beginning.
Funeral's
the day after tomorrow.
I chose an oak casket.
I hope that's all right.
White roses.
I think she'd like those.
They want to know
if there's a particular dress
you'd like her to be buried in.
Not really.
Okay.
I'll find something.
Quinn called, and the FBI
has released the crime scene
at your house,
so there are some things
I want to do there and...
I'm gonna drop you two off
at the apartment.
Is that okay?
Yeah, that's fine.
[Woman sobbing]
You're worrying me.
I really didn't
expect you to come.
We're partners.
I'm here.
What are we looking for?
Nothing.
Trinity wouldn't leave
anything behind.
What are we doing then?
I wanted to clean the place up.
Make sure Dexter
didn't see it like this.
The FBI left it this way.
They have people
who'll do that.
This much blood,
usually you call Dexter.
How you holdin' up?
Okay. I guess.
I mean, you know my brother.
It's a little hard to tell.
No, I mean you.
How are you holding up?
Oh.
Fine.
Not used to having to be
the strong one, you know?
It's always been Dexter.
And now...
He's the strong one?
To me it's always seemed
the other way around.
Swear to God, I can't even...
Tell what he's thinking.
[Whispering] Sorry.
I didn't mean
to make things worse.
[Whispers] It's okay.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
[Knocking, kids' voices]
Hurry, come on, open up!
Dexter!
[Knocking continues]
Maura: Are you there?
[Knocking, chattering]
Dexter, you came back early!
Oh!
Hey, guys.
Did you have fun?
- It was awesome.
- We got you stuff.
[Laughter]
- Perfect.
- There's one for mom too.
Where is she?
She's not here.
Well, where is she?
Just...Sit down.
I need to tell you something.
Dexter?
Is everything okay?
What's going on?
You're freaking...
you're freaking me out.
Something happened to your mom.
Cody: Something bad?
Yeah. Something bad.
Is she okay?
A man came into our house,
and your mother came home and...
He killed her.
Cody: What? She got killed?
Somebody killed her?
Astor: No, she's fine.
Maura: Dexter.
What...
Astor: You're kidding, right?
Maura: I don't understand.
You said spend the day
at Disney world.
[Crying]
I'm sorry for your loss.
[Maura crying]
Astor?
Go away.
I mean it!
Leave me alone!
Just...Listen to me.
Everything's gonna be okay.
It won't be.
She's dead!
I know.
And it doesn't even
matter to you.
How can you say that?
'Cause it doesn't.
I can tell just by looking
you don't even care.
Where were you?
Where were you
when someone was killing her?
You should have been there
to protect her.
You're right.
- That was your job!
- I know.
I should have been there,
and I wish I could
take it all back.
I wish...That none of this
had ever happened
and your mom was still alive.
Wanna know what I wish?
That it was just my mom
and me and Cody and Harrison.
'Cause we all would have been
so much better off
if she hadn't met you!
I wish you were dead!
- Do you mind?
- What?
Look somewhere else.
What are you doing?
Jesus, Quinn, you can't
grab a sheet or something?
Oh. Sorry.
So...What are you doing?
Trying to find a dress
for Rita.
You gonna bury her
in one of those?
You got something better?
Great. I-I gotta go.
I gotta go home now.
You might wanna
put some pants on there.
You wanna talk about it,
or you just gonna act weird?
There's nothing to talk about.
Okay.
I mean...
You show up here,
which I didn't even
ask you to do, so...
Yeah. To help.
Is that what you call it?
Morgan.
[Engine turns]
Elliot?
That's your name, right?
Yeah.
Hi. Quinn.
Metro homicide.
Hey.
You have kids, I take it.
Yeah. They're with
their mother.
Um...We're divorced.
Plus, it just seemed
better for them to get away
after what happened next door.
Um...You know, I already
talked to the FBI.
I told them
I didn't see anything.
What did you need?
How well did you know Rita?
I don't know, you know.
We were neighbors.
Yeah. I just...
Couldn't help but notice
how torn up you were
about her the other night.
She was a friend, you know?
It was upsetting.
A friend.
I, uh, was told
she might have been more.
[Sighs] Christ.
All right, look,
I don't know what you've heard,
but just so you understand
the actual facts,
all Rita and I ever did
was kiss...once.
That was it.
It was nothing.
I mean,
her husband was never around.
Anyway,
Dexter found out about
the indiscretion and, uh,
came over and punched me out.
Hmm.
[Door opens]
Dexter.
[Whispers]
Shh! He's sleeping.
Brought some dresses
for you to look at.
Where are Astor and Cody?
At a hotel
with their grandparents.
How'd it go talking with them?
Astor's upset.
They got me a hat.
She'll be okay.
I don't see how.
Her mother's dead
because of me.
No, she's not.
She's dead because of Trinity.
I know you keep blaming
yourself, but you can't.
There's nothing you could
have done differently.
I could have killed
Arthur Mitchell
the first chance I got.
You loved Rita.
You never would have let
anything hurt her.
She was lucky to have you.
She told me that
all the time...
How lucky she felt
to have found you.
I was wondering
what you were doing
sitting here by yourself
for so long.
Now I see.
I paid her to say that.
You did?
No, I was...Just kidding.
Me too.
So what does a...
Blood spatter analyst do anyway?
'Scuse me.
Is this yours?
[alarm chirps]
What's the deal here?
I have to go.
Uh, is everything okay?
It's a stomach bug.
It's going around the station.
I'm really sorry.
It was nice meeting you...
[Whispers] Lucky to have me.
I wouldn't say so.
She trusted me,
and now she's dead.
Like your sister says,
I'm toxic.
You'd all be better off
without me.
Delete the past.
Leave nothing behind.
You're up early.
What are you doing over there
that's so important?
Getting rid
of every trace of me.
Nothing.
Dexter...
Look, I know this is tough
to talk about, but...
The funeral's tomorrow,
and there's still a lot
of stuff you have to do.
Like sign the coroner's release.
I need to grab my tools.
And go over the guest list
one more time.
- And torch the container.
- And the eulogy, Dexter.
I can't do that for you.
That really
has to come from you.
I need to top off my boat.
I'm low on fuel.
Yeah.
And the FBI interview,
or the...debriefing
or whatever they're calling it...
that's really important.
They're total dicks
for wanting to do it today,
but maybe you're better off
just going in there
and getting it over with.
You sure you don't want me
to come with you?
No. I'm fine.
All right.
I'm off.
I've been thinking
about Harrison.
How he needs his mother.
Someone decent in his life.
You've done everything for me.
Not just now.
My whole life.
But...
I need to ask you
this one more favor.
For that person to be you.
That you...
Love him...
As if he were your own.
He is my own.
And he has me in his life.
Of course he does.
But more importantly,
he has you.
You're decent and good.
I'm not.
You are.
[Harrison fusses]
What's her mood?
How would I know?
I don't know, there's
this rumor floating around
the two of you are married.
Look, I just need to talk
to her about something.
I was wondering
if this was a good time.
Just remember...
She's the boss.
[Mutters]
No. No further comment.
Serial killer
murders cop's wife.
The press won't let up.
They want all the gory details.
- So what do you tell them?
- Same thing I told you.
It's not our case.
So what can I do for you?
There's, uh, something
I think you should know...
Having to do with Rita.
Okay.
- And Elliot,
the next-door neighbor.
I was at the house
with Debra...
[clears throat]
Detective Morgan... cleaning up.
And this Elliot and I
struck up a conversation.
Turns out he and Rita
had like a...
Mini-fling.
What's that mean...Exactly?
- W-well,
nothing really happened.
But apparently,
Dexter found out about it.
Why are you telling me this?
What are you implying?
I'm not implying anything.
And what are you doing
interviewing witnesses?
I wasn't interviewing.
I was there...
What... cleaning?
Please.
Look, if this were
anyone but Dexter,
we'd at least be thinking
like detectives.
Which means what?
What do you always say?
When the wife is dead,
90% of the time,
the husband did it.
[Telephone rings]
Laguerta.
Um...Hang on for a second.
I need to take this.
We'll finish later.
Okay.
Can you repeat that?
[Cell phone rings]
Yeah.
I just got a call from the FBI
about your brother's interview.
Don't tell me.
What'd he say?
Nothing.
He didn't show.
So now they're asking for
his personnel files.
Oh, God damn it.
I knew I should have
gone with him.
Morgan?
I so did not fucking need this.
- Yeah, you and me both.
- Well, I'm headed home now.
I'll figure out what happened,
and I'll get him down there.
Okay.
Dexter?
Who the fuck are you?
Excuse me?
Who...The fuck are you?
- Uh, 10-a.
Downstairs?
You're the sister, right?
- Yeah, I live here.
- Well, I'll be leaving then.
He said
you would know what to do.
He said what?
Don't... don't go.
Wait.
[Numbers beeping]
[Line ringing]
Dexter Morgan.
Please leave a message
at the tone.
[Beep]
Guess who I just met.
The fucking cat lady
from downstairs.
She was feeding ice cream
to your son.
So...I don't know
where the fuck you are
or why you think you can
fucking run away from the FBI,
but you better get back here...
[Beep]
Fuck!
Dexter, where are you?
Hope you don't mind
I chose that dress.
You were wearing it when...
We first met.
So I thought since I won't
be at your funeral,
since I don't deserve to be...
Kids'll be fine with Deb.
Way better off without me.
I think we agree about that.
I was never really
honest with you.
I'm a serial killer.
That's what I am.
I know I led you to believe
I'm a human being,
but I'm not.
That's a lie.
There are only a few things
you really need
once you decide to move on,
what you'll require
wherever you land...
a fine suit of clothing...
The tools of your trade...
And some token of your past,
a reminder
of who you really are.
Everything else...
You just don't need.
So where are you, Harry?
Speak now,
or forever hold your peace.
[Latin big band music]
? ?
[man singing in Spanish]
I've disappeared
so many people.
My turn now...
To disappear myself.
[Singing in Spanish continues]
? ?
Fucking FBI.
[Numbers beeping]
Damn it, Dexter, don't do this.
[Line ringing]
[Ringing]
The sea breeze
has always brought me clarity.
It's hard to get enough
oxygen on land.
It's hard to...Breathe.
[Echo of ringing]
[Cell phone ringing]
[Grunts]
[Ringing]
[Beep]
Hey, you.
Hey...You.
It's Rita.
Yeah, I know.
I was just checking in.
Wanted to see if you were
feeling better.
Much better.
Glad to hear that.
[splash]
The way you left
the restaurant so quickly,
I don't know, I felt maybe I...
Said something to offend you.
No, you were fine.
[Splash]
Uh, very understanding.
- I-I wasn't completely
honest with you. Um...
You didn't really
get stuck in traffic?
[Laughs]
I have two kids.
Astor and Cody.
They're 9 and 7.
I like kids.
You do?
Yeah, they're fun.
Besides, Deb already told me.
- And my ex-husband
and our...Problems?
Did she tell you?
Yeah.
So you know all about me.
I'd like to know more.
[Laughs]
So...
So maybe we should
get together again sometime.
I would like that.
A lot.
[laughs]
I know I should
hang up right now,
but I just need to say it.
Um, I don't know
why exactly, but...
You make me feel good.
Like things could be different.
So do you.
Make me feel that way...
Too, I mean.
Glad I called.
I don't know, I felt...
Up in the air
the way things ended.
You know, like we never
said a proper good-bye, so...
- Good-bye, Rita Bennett.
- Good-bye, Dexter Morgan.
- Good-bye.
I'm sorry.
[Engine sputters]
[Wind chimes clanging]
[Bell dinging]
[Pounding on counter]
Where's the key
to the fucking bathroom?
Or should I just dump
out on the floor?
What's your problem?
Nothing.
Fucking retard.
Get the fuck outta here!
He's right.
I should keep moving.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
I said...
What the fuck is your problem?
I've had a bad week.
My wife died,
and it was my fault.
Well, I'm real sorry
for your fuckin' loss,
but your dead wife
can suck my dick.
I never meant to hurt her.
[Wet crunching sound]
That's the first human thing
I've seen you do
since she died, Dexter.
I thought you'd left me.
I'm here.
It's okay, son...
to show what you're feeling.
[Whimpering]
[Louder groaning]
[Shrieking]
[Screams]
They're not better off
without you.
You're not better off
without them.
You need to go back.
Deb says
she's sure he'll be here.
Better be.
If we don't get going soon,
we'll be burying Rita
by candlelight.
So you're not...
Talking to me now?
Is that it?
I have been
trying to talk to you.
You're right. You have.
I just need you
to understand...
So tell me.
I could have fought
for this case, but...
Part of me didn't want to.
Rita...died.
She died, and it scared me.
We've been married, what,
ten hours?
Dexter was the witness
at our ceremony.
For all I know,
he was there with us
while she was...
Being...
I know.
Well, I didn't want to be
reminded of that.
I didn't want to investigate.
I just wanted...
I just wanted it to be
our wedding day.
Oh...
I don't like it, Angel.
I don't like the way
this makes me feel.
I don't know what to do
with any of it.
- Maria.
- [sobs]
What?
No one does.
What's more important
than his own wife's funeral?
People are getting restless.
Thank you for reporting in
with the obvious, Quinn.
Like I'm such a moron
that it's lost on me.
You ever given a eulogy?
No.
Well, I can't do it.
And those agents,
those vultures
are just waiting for him.
Look...
There's something
you should probably know.
What?
It's not exactly
an easy thing to say.
The next-door neighbor Elliot,
I spoke to him the other day.
- What the fuck?
- I know I shouldn't have...
She had a big heart.
Big enough for both of us.
Had to be.
I wasn't even human...
When we first met.
I never expected that
to change.
She reached out
and found something
I didn't even know was there.
She never hurt anybody.
She was innocent.
And she died a brutal death
and...
And I can't...
Fix it.
But I know I have to try...
Here in Miami with the people
who knew her
and who... who...
Who cared about her.
And who loved her.
Like I did.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com