Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
Cut him, and I'll blow
your fucking head off.
Ah!
Medic!
I need a fucking medic!
We were wondering
if there's anything
you can tell us
about the man who injured you.
I know where Carlos and his
brother have been hanging out...
At a local club
called the Mayan.
You got your lead.
Congrats.
Yeah, we stake this place out,
they show up,
and then we take
these Santa Muerta no-dicks
down for good.
- Are you and Quinn...
- We're fuck buddies.
Don't bring him around
when Harrison's here.
Would you like some coffee?
That would be wonderful.
Thank you so much.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey!
Sergeant!
Angel, let him go.
This is a sting!
I.A. needed my help
to bust a narcotics cop
on the take,
and I said yes,
to close the books
on your bar fight!
Fuck those I.A. rats.
And your boss.
That bitch put handcuffs on me.
I might have a job for you.
You got a name?
Dexter Morgan.
Boyd wasn't the only one
who did this to me.
There were others.
What are you gonna do if you
actually find one of these guys?
- What you won't.
- You gonna kill him?
You don't get to tell me
what to do.
What are you doing?
You were about to murder
the wrong man.
Go home.
Okay.
Okay, okay, I'll go.
You're doing the right thing.
Your parents will be happy
to see you.
Thank you.
Maybe this is one problem
I can check off the list.
Welcome to Miami.
I've always tried to keep
the different parts
of my life separate.
Becoming a father made that
much more difficult.
And as a husband, I failed.
But I'm a very neat monster...
Who won't make
the same mistake again.
I packed up
Rita's wedding dress.
I thought Astor
might want it someday.
Feels like it took you guys
months to move in...
Only a day to pack up.
The realtor suggested
we paint the walls white.
She wants to stage the house
Miami chic.
No evidence that a family
ever lived here.
Or died here.
You have to disclose that,
don't you?
The hope is that
a ridiculously low listing price
will help a buyer
see past that.
Any idea
where you want to live?
I'm sorry.
That was a stupid question.
You... you should take
the apartment.
- No. No, that's yours.
- No. I insist.
It's really always been yours.
I'll move out.
I thought you already did.
I didn't move in with Quinn.
Well, you're never around.
I'm at Quinn's,
but I don't live there...
No clothes in any drawers.
There's no
his-and-hers-toothbrush action.
Quinn's place is all Quinn.
A vast, empty space?
I don't remember Rita in these.
Because they belong to Lumen.
Me either.
Lumen is home in Minneapolis...
Another part of my life
packed away.
Life seems different now...
Manageable.
Everything in its right place.
Soon, Lance Robinson
will be on my table.
Lance trolls the Internet,
engaging in casual encounters
with innocent men...
Who never suspect
those encounters
could turn deadly.
Four times
Lance deliberately pushed
someone's fantasies too far.
He will be an easy kill,
just like old times.
Tonight's the night.
Okay, people,
let's go over our positions
at club Mayan.
Everybody be in place
by 10:00.
Batista and I'll be
in the van, as usual.
Quinn, you'll watch the door.
Cira...
Yes, chief?
Don't let me stop you.
Officer Manzon,
you'll be on the floor
watching foot traffic
at the v.I.P. room,
in case the Fuentes brothers
roll through.
And what if they don't?
Then we'll work
the operation until they do.
You were face-to-face
with Carlos Fuentes, right?
Yes, sir.
Well, then that means
he knows that we're onto him.
Tell me why they would ever
return to this club.
The only reason
the Fuentes brothers
are forcing people
to withdraw cash from the atm
is to pay for table service
at this club.
We ran the dates
of the ATM holdups
past the club managers.
And they confirmed
that in each of those nights,
the Fuentes brothers
showed up at club Mayan
and took over
the V.I.P. lounge.
So if the Fuentes brothers
do show up at this club,
which is highly unlikely,
it means that someone
is possibly lying on the floor
of their living room
without their head.
We're working
the only lead we have.
All you're doing
is drinking and dancing
on the taxpayer's dime.
I would have expected
more from you, Morgan.
Chief...
We don't have
a lot of options here.
Without this operation,
we're effectively stopping work
on this case,
which we cannot do
to this community.
Did you even know
this operation was happening?
Of course I knew.
Why wouldn't I?
Well, it seems
you've been spending
an awful lot of time lately
with internal affairs
bailing your new husband
out of hot water.
Bravo, Mrs. Batista.
I'm keeping my name.
And I think working club Mayan
is a valid allocation
of my squad's resources.
It is your squad, lieutenant.
- How you manage it is up to you.
- Thank you.
But if another murder
goes up on the board,
it's your ass on the line,
not mine.
You have one more night
at club Mayan.
Make something happen.
Matthews doesn't have
much faith in us, does he?
Yeah, well, that fight you had
at the bar didn't help anything.
- He knows about the bar fight?
- Of course he knows.
A narcotics officer
got suspended
because of that bar fight.
No. A narcotics officer
got suspended
because of you.
- Me?
- You ran to I.A.D.
You cooked up the sting.
You basically
got Stan Liddy fired.
And got all the charges
against you dropped.
I didn't ask for any of that.
I could have handled whatever
I.A.D. had coming my way.
Oh, so anything
that happens is fine?
When it happens to me, yes.
I can take care of myself.
But now that we're married,
whatever happens to me
happens to you.
That's right.
That's exactly right.
- We're married.
- Here's what's bothering me.
You weren't looking out for me
out of some sense
of compassion.
You were taking care
of yourself.
God forbid your name should lose
some of its shine.
- Get out of my office.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey.
I thought you might want
a debriefing
before we hit club Mayan.
Um, sort of not a good time.
Where's Quinn, and what have
you done with him?
I know, I know.
Um...
Just give me an hour.
- An hour?
- Yeah.
Who's naked in your apartment?
Uh, no one is naked.
Then what?
- I'm such a fucking idiot.
- Debra, wait.
Come here.
Debra, come here.
Debra Morgan.
This is Stan Liddy.
Liddy had a run-in
with I.A.D.
and, uh, got suspended.
We're prepping him
for his union-rep meeting
tomorrow.
Sorry.
All clothes are staying on.
- I'll just...
- Uh, meet me there?
Yeah, I'll meet you there.
You are boning
our target's sister?
Just tell me what you
found out on Dexter Morgan.
Well...
Your boy's squeaky clean
on paper.
He's only been out
of the country once, to Paris.
Pays his bills on time,
keeps to himself.
I'll tell you,
it's all too neat
and a little too phony.
You see drug dealers
with the very same profiles
all the time.
Oh, that's exactly
what I'm thinking.
I mean, what's he hiding?
Peekaboo.
Bye-bye, daddy.
Peekaboo!
Oh, thank you.
You're really very good
with him.
I wish I didn't have
to work tonight.
The lab fell so far behind
while I was out.
Night's the only time I can ever
get anything done.
Well, I hope the lieutenant
appreciates your dedication.
I'm pretty sure she does.
Although tonight
will be dedicated to Lance.
So you think
about midnight, then?
I'll try to make it sooner.
Can you say
"bye-bye, daddy"?
Die-die.
Did you hear that?
He said, "die-die."
Don't be silly.
He said, "bye-bye."
Harrison's first word.
There's your good boy.
I hope so.
Die-die.
From the mouth of babes.
I rented an RV,
placed an ad online,
saying I was cruising
down to the keys,
and just like that...
My victim came to me.
You must be ten inches
of pure steel, hmm?
You betcha.
Oh...
Compartmentalization began
as an architectural theory...
Divide buildings into sections
which can be closed off to
prevent a fire from spreading.
Life can also be divided
into closed-off sections.
Makes everything much simpler.
Lumen Pierce.
Again?
This is the life
Harry wanted for me...
Carefully divided.
Shh...
What the hell?
Dexter, I...
I shot one of them.
I killed him.
I'm at the marina...
Bayshore Biscayne or something?
You're in Miami?
I never left.
Oh, there's so much blood.
What do I do?
Hello?
Dexter, don't hang up on me!
Please, help me.
Don't move.
Don't do anything.
The M-99 will wear off
in a few short hours...
Not much time to contain
the situation...
Not much time to protect
my simple life.
? ?
First, for good luck...
Let me see your neck.
? ?
I fucking love my job.
Look, I'm gonna go
take a lap through the V.I.P.
- She's cute.
- Yeah, she's all right.
I could do you both.
That's the sixth girl
that's hit on him.
Wow.
Let's focus on camera three.
That guy, is he hooked up
with the Fuentes brothers?
Hey, I'm gonna stay on Quinn.
He may need some backup.
He is supposed to he focusing
on the Fuentes brothers.
He's not supposed to be playing
with her fun bags.
Sounds like someone's jealous.
Why on God's green earth
would I be jealous?
Quinn's a good guy.
I'm not interested.
Out there on the dance floor,
shaking his tail feathers.
Really not interested.
Stay single as long as you can.
- Says the newlywed.
- Don't remind me.
You've been married
for five minutes.
What happened to
the honeymoon phase?
I blinked.
Show me where he is.
There was so much blood
I had... I had to walk away.
The body's in here.
- Anybody see you?
- I don't think so.
- Oh, God, I hope not.
- You killed somebody.
Because you
wouldn't do it for me!
But you call me
to clean up after you.
I didn't know what to do
with the body!
- I don't believe this.
- Just go if you want to go.
Go?
I'm responsible for you.
Everything you do leads
right back to me.
I didn't think it would be
so hard to kill someone.
- Where is he?
- Here.
Oh, shit!
- He was right here.
- Are you sure?
He was dead.
- Apparently not.
- Don't get mad at me.
This isn't how I was planning
to spend my evening.
Me neither.
Would you do me a favor?
- What?
- Stop talking.
He's lost a lot of blood,
at least a pint.
One...Two...
Three...Four.
You're a terrible shot.
But you never shot
a gun before.
You didn't anticipate
the kickback...
One of the many things
you didn't anticipate.
Give me the gun.
You must have hit him once.
Where was the point of impact?
Where were you standing?
He was standing here.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
I go down, you run away.
I get back up,
and where do I go?
Here.
Come on.
How'd you even find this guy?
You can talk now.
The night that I was taken,
I had gone to a bar.
I thought that
they spotted me there,
so I went back to that same bar
night after night,
hoping that one of them
would walk through the door.
- I wore a disguise.
- Disguise?
A wig, so they
wouldn't recognize me.
I know what a disguise is for.
So you went to the bar.
You waited for one of them
to show up.
Where? What bar?
Hurricane 26.
Hurricane 26 is all the way
over on Ocean Avenue.
How'd you get all the way
out here?
That's what I've been trying
to tell you.
So go on.
Tonight one of them showed up.
He didn't know it was me,
so I-I flirted with him.
I asked him if he wanted
to go someplace else.
We got in the car,
I pulled out my gun,
and I forced him to drive.
This place seemed deserted,
so we stopped,
and I marched him inside.
- And you shot him.
- No.
I asked him for the names
of the other men.
He called me a cunt.
Then I shot him.
How'd you know
he was one of them?
I just...
I just knew.
You recognize his face?
No. They kept me blindfolded
most of the time.
So how?
I felt it the minute
he walked in the door.
One of the guys
had this smell...
Like old sweat or,
I don't know, chlorine.
When I got in the car
with this guy,
there it was,
the exact same stench.
You shot someone
based on a feeling and an odor.
I shot the right guy.
You were willing to shoot the
wrong guy under Tuttle Bridge.
This guy was one of them.
- What's his name?
- I don't know.
Did you check his wallet?
No.
- Did you take his cell phone?
- Uh...
He could have already called
the police, you know.
I'm new to this!
You don't even know
who you shot!
I shot one of the creeps
who raped me.
- You don't have any proof.
- I'm the proof!
My memory!
My experience!
Hardly the most reliable tools.
- Fuck you!
- Fuck me?
Wow.
Just go.
I can find him on my own
and kill him.
Like you killed him
the first time?
I have no idea
which direction he went...
If he turned right or...
Blood swipe.
He stopped here
to catch his breath.
Leaned against the post,
put his hand here.
The directionality
of the blood leads which way?
This way.
You sure know a lot
about blood.
So hypothetically,
an office romance is just
the worst idea ever.
Yeah, I would advise
against it.
But hypothetically...
I can see how you and Quinn
make a lot of sense.
So you would advise against it,
but we make a lot of sense?
What can I say?
I'm a romantic at heart.
Then why don't you do something
to patch stuff up
with your wife?
- It's not that simple.
- It is that simple.
Get your head out of your ass
and do something nice for her.
Buy her a card, some flowers,
get her a puppy.
A puppy?
Batista.
Where?
Baywater marina.
Warehouse 12.
I'll be right there.
- Possible homicide.
- I'll get it.
No, I'll go.
This is your baby.
We've been on this for weeks
and had nothing but our asses
handed to us.
And if for some reason
the Fuentes brothers
show up tonight, then they've
already seen my face,
so I'm useless.
And you won't have to see
Quinn hitting on other women.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Yeah. Good luck.
- Yeah, you too.
Mm...Who are you?
No dial tone.
He didn't call anybody.
Who even uses
a pay phone anymore?
People who don't have
cell phones.
We caught a break.
But he could have gone
anywhere.
What are you doing?
- It's luminol.
- Luminol?
No relation.
The hydrogen peroxide
and sodium hydroxide react
with the iron present
in hemoglobin
and exhibit A...Blue glow...
See?
Why do you have that
in your purse?
It's not a purse.
And I use this almost
every day.
Oh...
What is it?
A crime scene.
A crime scene?
- Are you...
A police officer?
"Baywater marina,
warehouse 12."
Isn't that...
Here?
Shit.
Somebody did see you.
- Oh, fuck!
- We still have time.
Patrol can't move until homicide
arrives on the scene.
That's at least 15 minutes
from now.
How long have you been a cop?
- I'm not a cop.
- Well, what are you?
Complicated.
This way. Hurry up.
Running pumps the heart faster,
and more blood is spilled.
Look here, how the drops
are pooling...
Getting closer together.
- He's slowing down?
- Yeah.
This way.
This started out
as an ordinary day.
In one second,
everything changed.
Lumen happened.
Why are you here in Miami?
You were getting on a plane
to Minneapolis.
I tried to get on that plane.
I couldn't.
I had to stay.
The guy I shot tonight,
he would take
these three fingers...
- You don't have to tell...
- And shove them in my mouth.
It tasted like metal.
He would keep them there,
so I couldn't scream.
The other guys would just stuff
a dirty rag in my mouth,
but not this guy.
He liked
to hold me down himself.
I saw everything.
How?
You were blindfolded.
Is this your monster?
Pardon me,
but I couldn't help noticing
that you've been hanging out
with a fool.
Mm. How do you know?
'Cause whoever stood you up
es un idiota.
- I'm Angel.
- Yasmin.
- My favorite flower.
- Ooh.
- No?
- Mmm.
Okay.
Do you want to get
out of here, Yasminita?
Yeah.
It hurts!
Oh, my God!
Calm down!
God. Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna inspect your wounds.
Yeah, one gunshot wound
penetrated the abdominal cavity.
Oh, God.
Can't let me die.
Come over here and hold this.
You're gonna save him?
I don't know who this man is.
My name's Dan.
Dan Mendell.
This woman right here,
she shot me.
I have no idea why.
You know exactly
what you did to me!
I've never seen this woman
before in my life.
- You're a fucking liar!
- You're fucking crazy!
Look, you can't let me die.
I got a wife.
I got a daughter.
Please. Just look.
Dan Mendell, D.D.S.,
kids' dentist.
He's a rapist.
I never did anything to you.
We met in a bar.
But she came on to me.
And then we get in the car,
- she pulls a gun on me.
- You panicked.
Because
you were gonna shoot me.
No, because you recognized me.
No. I've never seen you before
in my life.
- You know exactly who I am!
- She's crazy.
We got a mental situation
going on here.
- You in the corner.
- You believe him?
She needs help.
- This woman needs help.
- You're a piece of shit.
- Full of shit!
- Over there.
I have to take this call.
Stay there till I get back.
Don't leave me alone with her!
Do not move from this spot.
Ah, help!
- Everything okay?
- Die-die.
Hi-hi. Harrison.
I know you're working,
but I thought you might want
to take a break.
- It's wild hearing him talk.
- Isn't it?
I put him down,
and he was up two hours later
talking up a storm,
weren't you?
? Flies in the buttermilk,
shoo fly shoo ?
Here, let me get you
on the speaker,
and you can sing to him too.
? Lost my partner,
what'll I do? ?
Dexter.
? Lost my partner,
what'll I do? ?
? lost my partner,
? skip to the Lou, my darling ?
Well, I don't want to keep you.
I'm afraid to ask, but...
You want me to stay
a few more hours?
I'll be home as soon as I can.
There's no place
I'd rather be right now.
- Believe me.
- Die-die.
Die-die.
I love you.
- Who are they?
- Get off of me!
What are their names?
I don't know
what you're talking about!
Huh?
He's a fucking liar!
He knows who they are!
Who are they?
What are their names?
You are ruining my life!
They ruined mine.
If we don't get help,
Dan the dentist is going
to expire.
I don't care.
It's what he deserves.
- It's what they all deserve.
- Shh.
They should all get...
He's saying something.
- He's talking to someone.
- She fucking shot me.
- My phone.
- Can you hear me?
She shot me.
She's alive.
You hear me?
That last fucking bitch
is alive.
They're gonna find you...
You cunt.
Die-die.
Lumen didn't witness
her mother's murder,
but she was born in blood...
Like me.
Some experiences are so big,
they change your DNA.
What now?
We clean up.
Homicide will be on us soon.
Hose this area down.
Make sure everything flows
through the grate.
Where are you going?
To get my car.
We have to move this body.
About time.
Come on.
A hooker
called in some gunshots,
but didn't actually see
the shooter.
- Where's the body?
- Well, haven't found it yet.
Then what are we doing here?
Hey.
Blood.
Bullet holes,
lots of blood,
a significant amount of blood...
definitely some sort
of homicidal situation here.
A homicidal situation
requires a body.
Why don't we let the EMTs
handle it?
Your average person
won't survive
this amount of blood loss.
There.
That blood trail there.
See it? Good chance that trail
ends at a dead body.
- Dexter's en route, but...
- I get it. We can't wait.
Will you two guys follow us in,
in case this bleeder's alive?
Whoa.
This dude is a half liter
from dead.
Yeah.
Hey, fuckwad, are you taking
the scenic route?
Sorry. I was, uh,
with Harrison.
He said his first words...
"Bye-bye."
- Yeah? That's sweet.
- Yeah, it was.
I remember your first words...
"Shoes."
You were very girlie
once upon a time.
That's funny, 'cause I always
remember my first words as being
"hurry the fuck up."
Almost there.
Masuka and I tracked
this dude's blood
to a pay phone
inside a warehouse.
- You did?
- I think this way.
Yeah.
We're gonna keep going.
- So find us.
- Will do.
You changed your clothes.
Here.
This is all I have.
Thanks.
The police are close.
You have to get out of here.
Go to this address...
3319 Meadow Lane.
It's near Kendall.
Say it back to me.
3319 Meadow Lane, near Kendall.
This'll get you
in the front door.
Run six, seven blocks.
Catch a cab.
Get cleaned up and wait for me.
I have it from here.
- You want me to go now?
- Yes.
No, I'm not leaving you.
Yes, you are.
I-I can help you move
the body.
Who the hell is that?
Go, now. Go!
Compartmentalization is a joke.
Fires rip through buildings
all the time
no matter how closed off
parts of them are.
Life is the same way.
It cannot be contained.
Fuck. Maybe we should
double back the way we came.
Is that...?
Dexter's car.
Dexter.
You will not believe
what I found.
What in the mother of fuck
went on in here?
I know exactly what happened.
Two words...
autoerotic mummification.
See, Mr. Plastic Man
shot Captain Bloody Underpants
while underpants
was in the choke.
Mr. Plastic Man has hammocks
between underpants' man chop...
Thanks to Masuka's
keen expertise,
Debra will be able
to close this case.
Evidence will go into a
banker's box and be filed away,
eventually transferred to a
storage facility in Bradenton,
and that is where it will stay,
locked away
forever in the dark.
If only everything
were that simple.
Thank you for the visual.
Asphyxiation
heightens the high,
but it's not without its risks.
Either way, I wouldn't touch
the nozzle of that hose.
Anything to add?
The blood is consistent
with Masuka's theory.
If there's any follow-up,
I'd be happy to do it.
We're good here?
You just landed.
I have to relieve Sonya.
Yeah, we're good.
Drive safe.
What a night.
You sure you want to do this?
I'm here, aren't I?
Angel?
This is Yasmin Aragon.
What is she doing on my couch?
Miss Aragon is friends
with los hermanos Fuentes.
She also has a boatload
of drug charges
against her.
Seems like a trade is in order.
So are we gonna do this or not?
Give us a minute.
Excuse me.
I saw that she was wearing
a Santa Muerte necklace,
so I introduced myself.
If we agree to drop
her drug charges,
she thinks she can get
the Fuentes brothers
in the club.
That is...
If you're willing to give us
another chance.
I'm sorry about everything...
About losing my temper,
about what I said earlier.
You were right.
Say that again?
- You were right.
- I like the sound of that.
I did go to I.A.D.
because I didn't want
my husband disciplined.
I really like
being married to you, Angel.
And I you.
It's something I never thought
would happen to me
because I've been so busy
making a name for myself,
and now I'm this close
to making captain.
And I would never do
anything to stop you.
Not on purpose, I know.
But get a stink on you,
and I start to stink too.
We'll stock up on deodorant.
Nice job bringing in the girl.
Yeah.
Better than a puppy?
I'll see you back at home.
Hello?
Hey.
Last one.
Sorry.
You got glitter on your face.
Yeah...
Hazard of the job.
I'm not sure
it's in the job description
that you have to put your face
in Boobie McGee's tits.
Well, you know,
the first rule of working
undercover is to blend in.
You disappeared.
I did, didn't I?
It's not funny.
Fuck.
I...
I have feelings for you.
You do?
I tried not to.
I like you too...
Uh, more than "like."
You do?
Yeah.
I mean, you're the one
who keeps putting the brakes on.
Well, what if I don't want
to do that anymore?
That'd make me very happy.
If this is gonna end badly...
Will you please
just tell me now?
Morgan, I just said
I want to be with you.
I mean, what more do you want?
Well, I mean,
sometimes you mumble,
and it's kind of hard
to understand you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
How's this?
I tried to send this woman
1,500 miles away,
and she boomeranged
back into the house
I shared with Rita.
Lumen?
So much for keeping
the different parts
of my life separate.
Sorry, I'll just be in here.
There are towels...
Somewhere.
I found some in a box.
I also found this robe.
Is it okay if I borrow it?
Sure.
The tub's not draining.
Sometimes
the thingy gets stuck.
Are you okay?
Do you need to sit down?
Yeah, for a minute.
I know you...
What you are...
Deep down...
aside from your police job
and your
extracurricular activities.
You're a father.
I saw the pictures out there.
Three children?
The two oldest
are with their grandparents...
Their dad's mom and dad.
You have a son?
Harrison.
He just started talking...
Today.
He's tremendous.
It's...
Just the two of you?
And an Irish superhero nanny.
Never thought my life
would turn out like this.
I had imagined...
A totally different life
for myself too.
I always did everything
by the book, you know?
Go, go, go.
Never stopped to think.
There was high school and
college and graduate school...
Owen.
We were gonna get married
at the house that I grew up in.
On my wedding day, I...
I tried on the dress,
and I looked out the window
at the backyard
where the aisle was, and...
I saw everything
that that aisle was leading to...
babies and...
Matching dinnerware...
Sunday barbecues.
And I couldn't breathe.
I had to get
out of there and...
Find something...
More.
Then everything happened,
and...
I actually thought,
"this is what I get
for trying to...
Live my own life."
Do you have any idea
what I'm talking about?
A little.
But tonight
I felt this, like...
This...
Peace.
And it's because he's dead.
And I know
that it's not gonna last.
And when it wears off,
I'm gonna have to find
the rest of them...
Because that's the only way
that I'll find
that peace again.
I don't even have a name
for what I'm feeling.
I do...
The dark passenger.
I can't get revenge
for Rita's death,
but I can help Lumen
avenge what was done to her.
How many more were there?
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com