Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously, on Dexter...
- What'd you get?
- Two guys in their 30s.
Strong accents.
Possibly recent immigrants
from Venezuela.
Masuka found a match
on the print
we had from the cigar butt.
Carlos Fuentes.
He's got a brother, Marco,
and I got the address.
Cut him and I'll blow your
fucking head off.
Ah!
Medic!
I need a fucking medic!
Don't you dare let him die.
I apologized, he accepted.
It's assault and battery.
Batista could
not only lose his job,
he could serve time.
According to sergeant
Lopez's deposition,
you give the best blowjob
in Miami.
Do you recognize this man?
Jonah, is this Kyle Butler?
Back away!
You're on unpaid suspension
until further notice.
Suspension?
Just tell everyone you're
taking a few vacation days.
I don't want
to be alone tonight.
I'm no good for you.
I'm not looking
for good right now.
I just want to find out
who that girl is
before the m99 wears off.
Lumen Ann Pierce.
Why didn't you take me
to the hospital?
Because you saw me.
I didn't see anything.
We both know that's not true.
Every one of these barrels
has a body in it.
Look at this.
No.
This is what happened
to the girls before you.
This is what was gonna happen
to you.
I saved your life.
I was locked up and I thought
it would never stop.
But it has stopped.
He's dead.
It's over.
Boyd wasn't the only one who
did this to me.
There were others.
We all have something to hide.
Some dark place inside us
we don't want the world to see.
So we pretend everything's
okay.
Wrapping ourselves in rainbows.
And maybe that's all
for the best,
because some of these places
are darker than others.
Carefully.
Whoo!
I want to believe that smile.
That watching your mother die
hasn't changed you
the way watching mine
changed me.
Gently falling.
Sweetheart!
Sweetheart, what is it?
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.
He's got a scratch.
Looks like someone was playing
a little rough.
That's a little too familiar.
- Let's get a band-aid on him.
- Okay.
That's it for today!
But I use a scalpel.
All you have are your fingers.
Wiped clean.
Not even a year old, you're
already destroying evidence.
And having to flee
the scene of the crime.
Aww, it's okay.
Every time you see me,
you look disappointed.
Like you were hoping
to find an empty table.
Guilty.
Still think you need
to consider my advice.
Leave town?
Go home to people
who care about you.
I told you why I can't do that.
If you stay in Miami,
you'll never get past this.
If you had something
horrible happen to you,
could you just forget
about it and move on?
I would want to.
What if you couldn't?
If you really want to help me
get past this,
help me find those guys
and kill them.
I saw you kill Boyd.
You knew what you were doing.
Usual?
Thanks.
Going after those men won't
help you get past this.
It'll only make it worse.
How could it get worse?
It'll open up something
inside you
you don't want
to know is there.
Trust me.
Trust you?
I don't even know
your last name.
The less you know about me,
the better.
Better for who?
For the both of us.
If you're not gonna help me,
why do you keep
coming back here?
I'm trying to help you.
Minneapolis.
Yeah, I used some miles.
Wow.
You really want to get rid
of me, don't you?
I want you to get on
with your life.
Lumen.
She took the ticket.
Maybe this is one problem
I can check off the list.
And maybe it'll snow this week.
Whoa.
Where's the fire?
Got to get my ass in gear
or I'm gonna be late.
I could take that ass
back to bed.
What part of "late"
don't you understand?
I mean, at least let me make
you breakfast or something.
I have no time.
I've got to meet Batista
at the hospital.
We're interviewing that kid
Fuentes sliced open.
Good luck with that.
"Good luck with that"?
Fuentes has killed
three people.
I'm running down leads and
you're sitting around
in your boxer shorts
watching TV all day.
Oh, is that why you're,
like, all,
"let me get the fuck
out of here,"
'cause I'm taking
a few days off?
Just drop it.
This wasn't even my call.
Laguerta said
I had too many days.
I had to use 'em or lose 'em.
That's bullshit.
No argument here.
I got to go.
Quinn's my partner.
He should be here.
Not you.
No offense.
Look, what do you
want me to do?
He put in for his time.
No, he told me he was forced
to take his leave.
- That doesn't make any sense.
- Exactly.
So will you talk to Laguerta...
Oh, shit.
What?
It's the mother.
What is she doing?
She's coming this way.
Oh, fuck me so bad.
What am I supposed to say?
"I'm sorry.
It's my fault your son
got his throat slit"?
No, let me do the talking.
De nada, de nada.
Uh, if it's okay with you,
we'd like to ask your
son some questions.
Si.
Yes.
Gracias.
Jandro, how you feeling?
- A little better.
- Bueno.
We were wondering
if there's anything
you can tell us about
the man who injured you.
Uh...
He's seen him around,
but he didn't know
who he was.
No. Nada.
I asked if he had
heard anything
about Fuentes around
the neighborhood.
Does he remember
anything about that day?
Anything Fuentes said or did?
Anything at all?
He doesn't remember
anything else.
He was really scared.
Fuentes said he
was going to kill him.
Okay.
Gracias.
Uh...
He had a mark on his hand.
- A small one.
- Like a tattoo?
Can you draw it for us?
Lumen needs to stay away
from the darkness.
I, on the other hand,
always need names for my table
and there are few people
more deserving
than Boyd Fowler's accomplices.
Nothing in Boyd's arrest record
even hints he had help.
Zero to go on.
I'll have to look elsewhere.
Yours.
Thanks.
You didn't have to do that.
No, it really is yours.
You left it on
the hood of your car.
Oh.
My head's in 50 places.
Masuka didn't even begin
to keep up the case load.
Well, good luck getting
the midget porn
off your hard drive.
He might have shown it to me.
How was Mommy and Me?
Harrison break any hearts?
No, but he drew
his first blood.
I think his little black book
still has a few blank pages.
Well, not for long.
He missed you this morning.
He's used to having
his aunt Deb
feed him his mango oatmeal.
Yeah, sorry.
You didn't come home
last night.
No, it was late and I didn't
want to wake you,
so I just crashed
at a friend's house.
Oh, what friend?
What, are you mom now?
You want to do lunch?
I think I'm gonna
be dining on backlog.
And paying a visit
to Boyd's house.
Hmm.
All right, well, I'll bring
you something back.
Bye.
Wait a second.
What?
Give me your opinion
as a female.
- As a female?
- As a woman, you know?
McCourt.
What about him?
Do you find him attractive?
Do you?
I mean, would you ever?
I would rather
put a campfire out
with my face.
Okay?
I checked in with Cira.
She's gonna stay on
the ATM video surveillance
while I track down the tattoo.
Let me see that again.
See, it still looks
like a UFO to me.
- Who the fuck knows, right?
- Yeah.
We need to talk to an expert.
- An expert, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
The dragon lady represents
the dualities
of my inner warrior.
Or your inner idiot.
Hey, if you can't muster up
the appropriate respect,
I'm dropping the curtain.
When did you get this?
I've been adding
to it over time,
but the main work started
about two years ago.
I was having a bit of a crisis
and this was my way
of working through it.
Viagra probably
would have been cheaper.
This was a crisis of the soul,
Morgan.
Don't you have to have a soul
before it could be in crisis?
Point is you know
a little about this world.
I know a little.
The person you want to talk to
is my body artist
Michael Angelo.
You're kidding?
Michelangelo?
Two words.
Michael Angelo.
And, yes, I'm serious.
If your tattoo were done
by anyone local,
Michael Angelo will know.
You can lower the curtain.
From the outside, a normal home
is indistinguishable
from the home
of a monster who puts women
in barrels.
But step inside...
There must be something
around here
that will point me
to Boyd's accomplices.
Somebody's been here.
Oh, great.
Blood.
They were going through
Boyd's files.
Whoever Boyd was working
with must have panicked.
Tried to cover up any trace
of their existence.
Amateurs.
Here he is, freshly bathed,
clean as a whistle,
and ready for bed.
- Thanks.
- I'm gonna get going.
Check's on the counter.
Sonya, can I ask you
a question?
Sure.
Have you ever noticed
Harrison being...Aggressive?
Aggressive?
What do you mean?
Uh, scratching.
Stuff like that.
No.
He's a very gentle child,
really.
Why?
There might have been
an incident
at one of the Mommy
and Me classes.
Can't be sure
it was Harrison or not.
He's a little boy.
My little brother used
to bite people.
Bloody little cannibal.
Now he's a vegetarian.
Works for Greenpeace.
Well, that's comforting.
Not to worry.
You've got a little angel
on your hands.
Nothing can change that.
See you tomorrow morning.
Night.
No match for daddy
in the criminal database.
You're absolutely right.
Maybe he drives.
Let's check the DMV.
Minnesota.
Lumen Ann Pierce.
She broke into Boyd's house.
She beat me to it.
Oh, my God.
Dexter.
This seem like the product
of a stable mind?
A closet was the only place
she felt safe from them.
She's remade it here.
Dexter, are you listening
to me?
Yes, I'm listening.
She's not a killer.
She's not you.
She's coming undone.
What's that now?
This is the letter she took
from Boyd Fowler's house.
From his ex-cellmate
Robert Brunner.
"Getting paroled next week.
Need a place to 'sleap'."
S-l-e-a-p.
She's found a target.
You don't know
what she's planning.
I know this isn't gonna
end well.
She keeps going this way,
she's gonna get herself killed
or thrown in jail and you're
gonna be right there with her.
Dex, she's gonna
bring you down.
I know what you're doing.
Having breakfast?
You're looking
for the men who hurt you.
So, what,
you're spying on me now?
What are you gonna do if you
actually find one of these guys?
Maybe...
What you won't.
Are you gonna kill them?
Is that it?
I'm sorry.
You don't get
to tell me what to do.
I asked for your help.
You turned me down.
For your own good.
Look...
You saved my life.
I'm grateful for that.
But what I need from you right
now is to leave me alone.
Lumen...
Don't touch me!
These men put five women
in barrels.
They're not gonna want
to be found.
Please...
Stop this before it's too late.
She's not going to stop
until she finds Brunner.
My favorite color.
Help you, sergeant?
Morgan has been all over me
the last two days about Quinn.
What about Quinn?
The vacation
he's being forced to take.
She's feeling short-handed
without her partner,
and to tell you the truth,
we need him.
Well, it's the union.
Not my call.
That all?
Is there anything
I need to know
about my case with I.A.?
Mm-mm.
Is there anything
I need to know
about anything else?
I'm sorry, Angel,
but I got to go.
Sure.
I'll see you tonight?
Yeah... Um, I might be late.
Okay, so I'll let you know.
Okay?
Hope you didn't have
to dig too deep.
Only eight boxes,
but I always remember
to lift with my back.
Well, here's the guy
you asked for.
Robert Brunner.
Nuh-uh-uh.
Like we agreed.
Right.
Hmm.
There you go.
Ahh, aww.
That face.
Abduction, torture, rape.
Mmm, he's so big.
Is he a year yet?
- Ten months.
- He's beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Seven years for sexual assault.
Out in three for good behavior.
Mmm.
Good behavior.
You ever seen scars like that?
Yes.
On Lumen.
And he's out now.
Thank you, state of Florida.
Looks like she stumbled onto
the right guy.
Says he's living under
Tuttle Bridge.
Is this current?
Mm-hmm.
Sex offenders can't live
anywhere near kids.
Tuttle's the only place
they can go.
Can I keep this?
At depends now.
You gonna bring this little
cutie by to see me?
- Will do.
- Okay.
Tuttle Bridge
is the perfect place
for Brunner to hide
in the dark, but not from me.
I've got to get
to him before she does.
Tramp stamp.
I think I'm in love.
She's into needles.
Why don't you
show her your dick?
That's disgusting.
You are so judgmental, Morgan.
I mean, come on.
We all have our own ways
of expressing ourselves.
I have my ink
and you have your...
Man-boots.
Yeah?
Well, expect my man-boots
up your ass
if you're wasting
my time, okay?
Vincent?
Now what can I do you for?
That's Michael Angelo?
The one and only.
M, how are you?
Come here.
- Good to see you.
- Always good to see you.
M, this is the detective
I was telling you about.
Detective Morgan.
Enchante.
Right.
Mind taking a look
at something for us?
Any friend of sugar's
is a friend of mine.
"Sugar"?
Okay.
We interviewed this kid who saw
this on the hand
of a suspect we're looking for.
Any idea what it means?
Crude, simplistic, but...
It's definitely an eye.
Look.
The similarity.
See?
And that would mean?
Eyes symbolize
the third eye in our minds,
like the God horus
and also...
Just like...
The back of a dollar bill.
Hmm.
Have you ever done something
like this?
Well, if I had,
I would have remembered it.
Anything else you can tell us?
We're kind of desperate here.
Without it in front of me,
that's the best I can do.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
M, thank you so much anyways.
Always for you.
And you...
You come see me anytime, okay?
Okay, thank you.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
Bye.
I'll be in soon.
Hey, I think she likes you.
Don't ever speak about this.
Since we're already here,
why don't you get Quinn's
name put on your...
Hey, I have a gun.
I'll just wait in the car.
Okay.
Hello?
- Cira, it's me.
- Any luck?
Just a steaming pile
of fuck all.
Please tell me you have
something.
I've gone through most
of the bank's ATM footage.
Eight names and counting.
They're all freaking out
about something
while they're withdrawing
maximum amounts
from their accounts just like
our first
Santa Muerte vics.
I want addresses
for all eight names
and any others you can find.
I'll pick you up on my
way to work tomorrow
and we'll check 'em out, okay?
Poor Julia Tuttle.
The mother of Miami.
They named this bridge
after her in her honor.
Now it's crawling with
pedophiles and sex offenders.
So much for honor.
Japan's total area
is slightly smaller
than the U.S. state
of Montana.
You mind if I watch?
The kid fuckers stay over
by the tracks.
That's not why I'm here.
And why is that?
Stuck-up little co-ed and I
had a legal disagreement
concerning
the meaning
of the word "consent."
Take a load off.
Appreciate it, brother.
Where'd you do your time?
Okeechobee.
My last stretch was
in that shithole.
Rough place.
Yeah.
Told everyone I was in
for armed robbery
to keep a target off my back.
You from Miami?
Used to be.
Guy I bunked with
lives down here now.
Thought I'd let him show me
the town and have some fun.
Did that fun include Lumen?
That is until
my parole officer,
the cunt,
started giving me shit
about staying with someone
from the joint.
Wound up here.
Mmm.
Beats a cell.
Barely.
Once my parole is done,
fuck Florida.
I'm going north.
Get me some of that
farm-fresh pussy.
You ever tap that?
Can't say that I have.
A couple weeks ago...
I had this hot little blonde
on all fours.
A few of us did.
Believe me, that bitch
got every fucking inch
- of my motherfucking...
- That's enough.
This room was meant for Boyd,
not his cellmate.
They were co-workers, partners.
Basically the same.
You're sure?
I need to kill him
so Lumen doesn't have to.
I don't want her
down that road.
Think about what you're doing.
I am.
- He's a sex offender.
- I know.
On parole.
What are you saying?
Think!
Are you listening?
Okay.
He's wearing an ankle bracelet.
It couldn't have been him.
She had the wrong guy.
I was ready to kill him.
I was ready to kill him!
Robert Brunner isn't one
of the men who hurt her.
Harry's right.
I have to convince Lumen
to do what I never could.
To move on.
You're home early.
Where's Sonya?
I sent her home.
She said you were gonna
be working late.
Hope you don't mind,
I grabbed a beer.
What's he doing here?
He wanted to...
Borrow...
A book.
He reads?
Yeah, he does.
Here.
Thanks.
Little vacation reading.
Quinn was just leaving.
What she said.
I will call you
in the morning, Joseph.
Oh, okay, Debra.
Kind of warm for gloves.
Good night.
Thanks for the book.
What was that about?
It's late,
so I'll take the couch.
Are you and Quinn?
We're fuck buddies.
That's it.
You need Quinn for that?
I know it's insane.
I... I know it's...
Wrong for a fuck-ton
of reas...
Will you please stop looking
at me like that?
It's your life, Deb.
Just don't bring him around
when Harrison's here.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, he's at
an impressionable age.
We don't know what might
rub off on him.
What will rub off on him?
Just keep Quinn away
from my son.
Fine.
You know, you're wrong
about Quinn.
He's...
Not that bad.
Hey.
Sorry.
Long day.
Dinner's in the oven.
You mind if I hop
in the shower first?
You never called.
Yeah, I know.
I just lost track of time.
Why so late?
Budgets are due at
the end of the month, so.
I'm gonna...
I'll set the table.
Okay, thanks.
She's not there.
You just missed her.
Did my wife say where
she was going?
You two still not
seeing eye to eye?
Look, I really need
to find her.
It's important.
She was asking
about Tuttle Bridge.
I told her that is the last
place she wants to be.
What the fuck, asshole?
Nice.
Where you going, baby?
What are you doing?
I'm taking you out of here.
- Give me the gun.
- No.
Give it to me!
You have no idea what those
animals did to me.
Passing me around.
I couldn't move.
I couldn't stop them.
- It wasn't Brunner.
- It was.
He was Boyd's cellmate.
He raped three women!
He tortured them just
like he did to me.
- That's impossible.
- You weren't there!
Just listen to me.
He's wearing an ankle bracelet
as part of his parole.
If he leaves this place,
it gets reported.
I checked.
He was here the whole time
you were taken.
Robert Brunner's
never seen you before.
He's never touched you.
He never hurt you.
You were about to murder
the wrong man.
Oh, fuck.
You see?
This is where it leads.
But it's not too late.
There's still no blood
on your hands.
I just want to feel better.
I want all this to go away.
It will.
I don't see how it can.
Go home...
Back to your family.
If you don't
put this behind you,
I swear what you're feeling now
will only get worse.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll go.
Okay.
Next one on our ATM list.
Oh-for-fucking-five.
That's how I like
to start my fucking day.
You want to make
a bet why this one
was taking a wad of cash
out of the ATM?
Gambling? Hookers? Drugs?
You're very cynical.
It's called being a detective.
And blow me.
You have to put positive energy
out into the universe.
Right.
Blow you.
You smell that?
Holy shit.
Little help here?
Any time you're ready.
Yeah.
This is detective
Morgan requesting CSI
and body transport
at 2075 Ocean Way
for a possible double homicide.
And you need to tell
Masuka and Dexter
that they need to bring
a bug kit...
And some fucking crackers.
You good?
You son of a bitch.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Angel!
Hey, sergeant,
you're making a big mistake!
The only mistake I made
was not kicking your ass
when you first laid eyes
on my wife.
Angel, let him go!
This is a sting!
Let him go!
You're wearing a wire?
No shit, you idiot.
What would have happened if he
barged in here a half hour ago?
I know.
Just give us a minute, Jim.
You just don't learn,
do you, Batista?
Have you completely
lost your mind?
- I thought...
- What?
That I was fucking him?
What am I supposed to think?
You barely talk to me.
The late nights.
The sneaking around.
How'd you find us?
Wait.
You...
I don't even want to know.
I.A. needed my help
to bust a narcotics cop
on the take and I said yes.
Why?
To close the books
on your bar fight!
So I don't want to hear
about sneaking around
and late nights!
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you trust me?
Maria, I...
Morgan needs us on site.
Double homicide.
My car's outside.
I'll ride with patrol.
Fuck me.
Come on, Liddy.
Lieutenant, any comment?
- Not now.
- Lieutenant Laguerta...
It's like the fucking food
chain in action in there.
Flies... the blow flies are
attracted by the smell
and they lay eggs
and the beetles,
they're drawn by the larvae,
and they burrow
into every orifice...
- I get it.
- What do we know?
The vics' names are Daniel
and Awilda Ortiz.
ATM footage showed
Daniel trying
to make a maximum withdrawal
about four weeks ago.
Officer Manzon and I show up
to interview him
and we find the bodies.
The remains have already
started to mummify,
but the wounds are consistent
with a machete.
I can make sure when
I get them back to the lab.
We like the Fuentes brothers
for this.
Only weird thing
is we can't find
any Santa Claus Muerte
mumbo jumbo bullshit.
We might be looking
at the Fuentes brothers'
first victims.
The defensive wounds
and heavy smearing
suggest our killers
were still inexperienced.
Beheading requires skill.
So we got their goddamn
training wheels kill?
Means we're back
to fucking square one.
Little downwind, please.
Oh, yeah.
That's never coming out.
I liked this shirt too.
I'll get a jacket out
of my car.
All right.
It was never a tattoo.
It was a stamp
from a nightclub.
It was a fucking nightclub!
It's a nightclub!
What's gotten into her?
Find out, sergeant.
I'm gonna go deal
with the press.
Nice to have you back, Dexter.
Good to be back, lieutenant.
Reports on my desk,
first thing.
All together once again.
One big happy family, eh,
Dexerino?
Yeah.
You don't have to wait.
I don't mind.
I can pay you back
for the ticket.
I'll send you some money.
Except...
I still don't know who
to send it to.
Dexter Morgan.
And it's not necessary.
The ticket.
I came to Miami
for a fresh start.
Somewhere warm.
You're doing the right thing.
Your parents will be...
Happy to see you.
I tried to call them,
but I couldn't.
What would I say?
Just give it some time.
I can't tell them what
happened to me.
I can't tell anyone.
You're the only one who knows.
You have my number.
Call me if you need
to talk about it.
I should...
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Go ahead.
Put it through.
And your bags.
Make sure everything's
out of your pockets.
Jewelry, belts.
Step to the mat, ma'am.
Is there a problem?
I can't let you through
to your gate
unless you consent
to a hand search.
Lift your arms.
I need you to stay still.
Spread your legs.
Are you home?
Not quite.
Are you at a bar?
I had to gas up the car.
My fault O'Malley's
is on the way?
So ask me how my day was.
How was your day?
It was better than yours,
slacker,
'cause I know where Carlos
and his brother
have been hanging out.
At a local club called
the Mayan.
You got your lead.
Congrats.
Yeah, we stake this place out,
they show up, and then we take
these Santa Muerte
no-dicks down for good.
How about I get some steaks
and beer and we celebrate?
Well, there's nothing
to celebrate just yet,
but I have a good feeling
about this one.
Now get your ass moving.
I'm starving.
On my way.
Thanks for the cuervo, stud.
No problem.
I heard what happened.
Fuck those I.A. rats.
And your boss.
She's the reason I'm here.
Unpaid leave.
Why?
For doing my fucking job.
That bitch put handcuffs on me
and then that no-nuts
McCourt parades me
around that station like I'm
a goddamn carnival prize.
Well, they can both go
fuck the dog.
They think I'm gonna cop a plea,
they're both
cracking walnuts up their ass.
I'm gonna fight this thing
to my last damn dime.
You need some extra cash
for those lawyers,
I might have a job for you.
Really?
And what would that be?
- Looking into someone.
- Who?
Guy I work with.
Interested?
I don't know if I should be
considering who's sitting
in front of me making the offer.
What are you talking about?
Have I ever fucked you over?
No, but Laguerta just taught me
there's always a first time.
Look, Quinn,
you fuck with the bull,
you get the horn.
You understand?
Yeah.
Do you?
You got a name?
Dexter Morgan.
Dexter.
What the fuck kind of name
is "Dexter"?
Rainbows are an illusion.
Refracted light to make us think
something's there
when it's really not.
Is there darkness in Harrison
or is it just my own fear
being reflected back?
I just know he's the one
who scratched Teddy.
He was right next to him.
Did you read about
what happened to his mother?
That boy will never
be the same.
There's nothing wrong
with my son.
I'm sorry for ever thinking
the worst, Harrison.
You'll always be my son.
Whatever we have to face,
we'll face together, okay?
Ow!
Hello, ma'am.
Where you headed
this afternoon?
You need a cab?
Welcome to Miami.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com