Previously on Lost:
Two days after I found out
I had a fatal tumour on my spine,
a spinal surgeon fell out of the sky.
We had such a wonderful plan
to break you, Jack.
My wonderful plan
got shot to sunshine
when you saw my X-rays
and figured out I was dying.
You want me to save your life.
I want you to want to save my life.
All I can ask is that
you think about it.
Police. Open the door.
Everything's all right here.
We have reason to believe
someone dangerous is in the motel.
We're conducting
a room-to-room search.
I'm alone, officer.
You could be held at gunpoint,
forced to say that.
- Please open the door.
- I don't think I should.
Ma'am, you have three seconds
before I break this door down.
One... two...
Hey.
Wanna get it on?
Hell, yeah.
Warning.
Hey.
Hey yourself.
- Warning.
- Whatcha doing?
Throwing rocks.
Warning.
- I thought you had to pull the lever.
- I know how to get a fish biscuit.
Then get me one.
What, you trying to keep me
feeling productive?
You took these blood tests
and made all the notations?
- How old are the X-rays?
- A week.
The tumour on your spine
is borderline inoperable.
At the rate it's growing,
that borderline goes away in about...
...one week.
The O.R. We were in,
is that fully equipped?
Yes.
- Anaesthesia? Sterile?
- Yes.
You need to be in surgery yesterday.
All right, then.
Whatever you need, it's yours.
I'm ready.
No, I think you misunderstood me.
I didn't say I was gonna do it.
I just wanted you to understand
how you're gonna die.
You think I believe you people?
You think I trust you?
That I'm gonna just do the surgery
and hope that you let me go?
- Jack...
- No, don't!
Well, Jack, I'm very disappointed
in your decision.
Well, Ben...
...at least you won't
have to be disappointed for very long.
You shouldn't have come here.
Yeah. You're right.
I've made a huge mistake.
I am just full of regret right now.
Seriously!
It's bad luck to see
the bride before the wedding.
It's bad luck to see the bride
in her dress before the wedding.
You, my friend, are naked.
Have you tried it on?
I have to hold my breath to get
the claspy things to clasp, so...
I'm waiting till the last minute.
Well, that's in about 12 hours,
you might wanna get clasping.
Hey.
I know it's...
It's been fast.
But this is right.
I know it's real.
And I love you, Monica.
I love you too, Kevin.
Come on. Time for work.
- What about him?
- Oh, he's got the day off.
- If he's not working, neither am I.
- You're not?
Just go, Freckles.
Man wants to give me a day off,
let him give me a day off.
No, Sawyer. We're a team.
You break the rocks. I haul 'em.
All right. Fine.
Lord knows I wouldn't
wanna break up the team.
What happened to him?
Must've been an animal.
Maybe one of the bears.
- Are we gonna carry him back?
- No.
We're gonna bury him here.
- Are we?
- The people back at camp...
There's just been a few
too many funerals lately.
Nobody needs to see him like this.
I'll slip back to the beach
and get shovels.
- I'll come.
- No, I'll be back...
It's not safe to go alone, John.
I appreciate your concern.
So, what killed Eko?
Folks back at the beach
call it the monster.
I don't really have a name for it.
- You don't believe in monsters.
- I believe in what I can see.
But obviously, you have.
- Tell me what you think it is.
- Might be what brought us here.
So you believe this monster
decided that Eko was meant to die?
I believe Eko died for a reason.
I just don't know what it is yet.
Is that why you lied?
We're not headed back
towards the camp, are we?
Sure, we are.
Just need to take a little detour first.
- Compound breach.
- Someone's on the grid.
Where is she? Someone's on the grid.
I want him on the ground. Her too.
If he moves, you shoot him.
Yeah. They're here.
Did the doctor get out again?
You sure?
Well, does he know?
How the hell did she get over here?
- Get up! Come on, get up! Go!
- Alex! Alex!
- What do you think you're doing?
- You gonna shoot me?
You're not supposed to be here.
Just calm...
What did you do to him, Danny?
Where is he?
- I want to talk to Ben.
- Sure. That sounds like a great idea.
- Why don't we lower the slingshot...
- Where is he? Tell me!
- Get off of me!
- Get her out of here.
Get her out of here!
Put me down! Listen,
whatever they say, don't believe them,
they're gonna kill your boyfriend!
Just like they killed mine!
I don't understand.
It's supposed to be two weeks.
- Our schedule moved up.
- Is that an order?
- That's stupid.
- It's not my call. It's the way it is.
I would like for you to put this on
and come with me, please.
You think I'll do it
because you said please?
No, you'll put a hood over your head
because the man standing behind me,
the one who's burning a hole in my back,
that man is going to kill Sawyer.
But if you put this on
and you come with me,
there's something you can
do for us that will save his life.
Come in.
Oh, sweetheart, you're beautiful.
Absolutely beautiful.
- How is it out there?
- There are a lot of excited policemen.
I've asked them not to shoot their guns
in the air when you say "I do. "
You know, mothers-in-law
aren't supposed to be so nice.
Monica, I have something for you.
Suzanne, you shouldn't have.
My mother gave that to me
on my wedding day.
She told me someday
I'd give it to my daughter,
but... since I had four boys...
Here.
It's perfect.
Kevin's been coming to the church
since he was about yea high.
When I first met you, Monica,
I was struck by your honesty
and your devotion to Kevin.
When I asked him what
he loved most about you, he said,
"Because what you see
is what you get. "
With that being said,
you've got the rings,
you've vowed your vows...
...and I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Thanks, Mom.
Step.
I'll give you two some privacy.
Hey. You OK?
Yeah. You?
Yeah, I'm... I'm great.
Where are they keeping you?
Outside. In a cage.
- Sawyer?
- He's in a cage too.
They're making us work.
Work? On what?
I don't know what it is, but it's big.
- We're hauling rocks, and...
- Hey...
...did they hurt you?
Kate, hey.
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
It's gonna...
Jack.
- You have to do it.
- What?
This thing that they told you to do,
this operation.
- She said, if you do it, they would...
- What'd they do to you?
- What did they do to you?
- Nothing.
How did they get you to ask me?
What did they offer?
- Nothing.
- Then why are you here?
They're gonna kill Sawyer.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, but she said that if you
do it and do it soon, they'll let us go.
And you believe them?
I have to.
Jack?
Please.
We're done here.
- Jack...
- Hey!
We're done in here.
Jack, I'm sorry. You have to do this.
They said that they couldn't...
Get her out of there.
Jack!
Jack, please.
- Hey, you.
- Hey, what's for dinner, gorgeous?
- It's taco night.
- You're making tacos?
Yes. And you better like 'em.
- Or what?
- Or no dessert.
- I'm leaving now, I'll be home soon.
- Love you.
I love you too.
Agent Mars.
It's me.
I'm glad.
I realized it was the Feast
of the Ascension and I was feeling bad.
Lot of holy days have come
and gone since you last called.
- I thought you and I were friends.
- I don't wanna run anymore.
What's his name?
Does he know who you are?
Edward, please.
I know you don't want to spend
the rest of your life chasing me.
Please, I love this guy.
Just let me go.
I'll tell you what...
...if you can really stay put...
...really settle down...
...then I'll stop chasing you.
But you and I both know
that's not gonna happen.
Sawyer...
...you really care about him?
Where is he?
I'm sorry you weren't able
to help us, Kate.
Move it, Ford.
Danny.
- Danny!
- You son of a bitch!
Right. Sorry, Jules.
You got anything you want
to say to your girl...
...you best say it tonight.
And how was your day, honey?
When the hatch exploded,
your prayer stick fell out of a tree,
right on top of me.
So Sayid and I went to get it
because it didn't feel right
to bury you without it.
I'd like to think
you died for a reason, Mr Eko.
Just hope it's not too long before
we find out what the heck it might be.
Rest in peace, Mr Eko.
And thank you for helping me find my...
I saw Jack.
They brought me in to see him.
- They want him to do surgery on Ben.
- Who's Ben?
Henry, the guy who brought us in.
He's sick. And they say if he does it,
they're gonna let us all go.
- And you and me are what, bait?
- Something like that.
At least the doc ain't
dumb enough to do it.
I told him he had to.
Why would you do
something so stupid?
- To save your life.
- My life don't need saving.
You wanna die?
'Cause that's what's gonna happen!
Pickett is waiting for his chance.
I've seen him look at you.
Damn it, Freckles, stay put!
And you know what he's gonna do.
So don't pretend...
...like you don't care.
- Get down, we've been through this!
- Shut up, James.
You don't want Jack to save your life?
Then you're gonna save your own.
We're getting out of here, now.
Stop it! Damn it, Kate!
- Go! Get out of here! Run!
- You're out of your cage.
Why don't you run, Kate?
Because me, I ain't running...
...because there ain't no place to go.
What're you talking about?
We ain't on our island.
We're on another island, like Alcatraz,
a couple miles off shore.
So unless you're a mermaid
or you got a boat...
...there ain't no point.
When were you planning
on telling me this?
- Never.
- Why not?
Why wouldn't you?
'Cause I wanted you to believe
that we had a damn chance.
- What was that for?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
Very nice.
OK, now it's your turn.
Look under your place mat.
- What did you do?
- Just look.
What is it?
You know that honeymoon
I've been promising you?
You are holding in your hand
two tickets to Costa Rica.
So get your passport ready, baby.
Hey...
...what's wrong?
Nothing.
I just love you so much.
Come here.
Let me ask you something, Freckles.
The day Blockhead was beatin' on me...
...and you said,
"I love you,"
that was just to...
...get him to stop, right?
I love you too.
Who is this?
Hello?
Hello!
Try it. The door.
If it helps, I was surprised too.
If I were a betting man,
- I would have picked her and you.
- Shut up!
Well...
...this would be the proverbial
nail in my coffin, wouldn't it?
Tomorrow.
- Sorry?
- Tomorrow morning.
First thing.
And everything I mentioned before.
The instruments, anaesthesia.
Someone who can hold a clamp.
Yes. Of course.
I'll get it out. Your tumour.
And I'll keep you alive.
But I need your word.
I need what you
promised me before.
I need to get the hell off this island.
Done.
What you working on?
Just finishing some IRs on that
fugitive recovery out of Tampa.
That's what being a cop is,
endless paperwork. Thank you, sweetie.
What if I told you
I was a fugitive?
What if I told you I was
on the run for blowing up my father,
and it was only a matter of time
before you found out.
- This isn't funny.
- It's not a joke.
I almost had a baby, Kevin.
Me! A baby!
I can't do this.
- Taco night? I don't do taco night!
- OK, calm down, Monica.
My name's not Monica!
I love you.
But I can't stay.
No, wait, hang on.
- Something's wrong with me.
- I drugged you.
- You what?
- I had to.
Otherwise they would think you knew.
People are gonna ask questions,
I didn't want you to lose your job.
This is gonna be
a very tricky procedure.
If I tell you to do something,
I need you to do it, no questions asked.
Is that understood?
You may find this hard to believe,
but I'm very good at following orders.
Is that a yes?
Yes.
Good. Let's go.
Do you get nervous?
Before you do surgery?
I used to. But not anymore, no.
Whatever happens...
...everything will be
very different, won't it?
No doubt about it.
Juliet...
...did Alex ask about me?
No.
We took her home last night.
I don't know where she is now.
Well, see ya on the other side.
I'm ready.
I need you to count down from 20.
Twenty...
...19...
...18...
Scalpel.
Let's go.
- Ben's just gone into surgery.
- Ben put his life in the hands of them.
Shephard wasn't even on Jacob's list.
- Sawyer. Sawyer!
- Well, look who got out of her cage.
Should've run when you had the chance.
- Let's go, James.
- Don't! You don't have to do this!
He's coming with me. There's
nothing you can do about it! Step away.
Give me another haemostat.
Swab again.
Clamp.
- What happened? Is he OK?
- His blood pressure's dropping.
- Should he be bleeding like that?
- Nope. No, he shouldn't.
Back away from the table.
Back away from the table! Now!
- Can you hear me in there?
- Yeah.
Good.
I just made a small incision
in Ben's kidney sack.
Now, if I don't stitch that back up
in the next hour...
...he's dead.
Now get in here
and bring that walkie-talkie.
- Step away!
- No!
You let go or I do her too.
- Let go.
- Don't you let go!
Don't even think about it, Sawyer!
You fight!
No! No!
Sawyer! No!
Sawyer, please!
You get your hands off of him!
Get down on your knees.
Please! I will do anything you want!
I want you to watch.
- Close your eyes, Freckles.
- Stand up!
Close your eyes!
Don't you give up!
No! No! No!
This is for Colleen,
you son of a bitch!
Danny! You there? Pick it up!
Pick it up, Danny! Pick it up, damn it!
I'm here. What?
You anywhere near the cages?
Yeah. You could say that.
- Give your walkie to Kate.
- Now, why the hell would I do that?
Because if you don't,
the doctor's gonna let Ben die.
What are you talking about?
What's beeping?
Just hand her the damn walkie, Danny!
Do it. Just do it now!
Let go of her.
Jack?
Jack!
Kate, you have about an hour head start
before they come after you.
Wait, where are you? Where are you?
Do you remember what I told you
on the beach, the day of the crash?
Do you remember what story I told you
when you were stitching me up?
- Do you remember it?!
- Yes! Yes! I remember!
When you get safe,
you radio me and you tell me that story.
Jack, please.
If you don't call in the next hour, I'll
know something went wrong and he dies!
- I can't leave without you!
- Yes you are. Go.
- Jack, I can't!
- Go! Now!
- I can't!
- Kate! Damn it! Run!