Previously on Lost:
You brought me to operate.
You think I trust you,
that I'm gonna just do the surgery
and hope that you let me go?
Jack... you have to do it.
How did they get you to ask me?
What did they offer?
- Nothing!
- Why are you here?
They're gonna kill Sawyer!
Tomorrow morning, first thing.
I'll get it out,
and I'll keep you alive.
I'm ready.
No! No! Sawyer, please!
You get your hands off of him!
I made a small incision
in Ben's kidney sack.
Now, if I don't stitch that back up
in the next hour, he's dead.
Now get in here
and bring that walkie-talkie!
Hello.
I fell asleep?
With candles burning.
That's real safe.
We don't have to
keep doing this, you know.
Are you saying that because
you don't think it's gonna work?
Or because you're afraid
he'll find out?
Lift up your shirt.
OK.
- Some doctor you are.
- I'm not doing this as your doctor,
I'm doing it as your sister.
I don't like you being here alone.
Come stay with me.
I like living on the beach.
This is Miami, Rachel.
Everything's on the beach.
You have an hour head start
before they come.
Take the walkie, take Sawyer, go.
Wait, where are you?
Kate, just listen to me! Do you remember
what I told you on the beach?
Do you remember what story I told you
when you were stitching me up?
- Do you remember it?
- Yes! Yes! I remember!
When you get safe,
you radio me and you tell me that story.
Jack, please...
If you don't call in an hour, I'll know
something went wrong and he dies!
- I can't leave without you!
- Yes, you are. Go.
- Jack, I can't!
- Go! Now!
- I can't!
- Kate! Damn it! Run!
Juliet, stop the bleeding
and stitch him up.
She's not a surgeon.
She can't fix this.
He's right.
Let's go.
- Warning.
- Sawyer, let's go!
- Sawyer!
Then what the hell
do you suggest we do?
Go get Danny,
then find Austen and Ford
and bring them back.
No. You do that and Ben dies.
- Go.
- No, you think I'm lying?
You think that this is a bluff?
I will let him die.
No. Jack. You won't.
Go. Get them back.
If you have to...
...kill them.
- Hello?
- Dr Burke?
- Yes.
- It's Diana from Mittelos BioScience.
- Confirming your appointment tomorrow.
- 2.00, right?
2.00. Dr Alpert asked me to tell you
he's looking forward to meeting you.
- Me, too. Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Stay here.
- Hello, Juliet.
- Hey.
Hey, Ed.
Why exactly are you here?
Oh, today's lab work,
I got home and I realized
that I inverted some numbers.
It couldn't wait until morning?
- Edmund?
- I'm sorry.
How rude of me.
Juliet, this is Sherry.
Sherry, this is Juliet...
...my ex-wife.
Juliet's leaving.
I am.
Jules...
...could you please turn off the lights?
You haven't thought this through.
Your plan's not going to work.
Yeah? Why's that?
Your friends won't make it to your side,
because we're not on that island.
We're on a smaller island,
two miles off shore.
Afraid so.
So, why don't we see if we can come up
with some kind of peaceful resolution.
- A peaceful resolution?
- That's right.
Is that what you call asking me to kill
Ben while on the operating table?
- "Make it look like an accident"?
- Ridiculous.
- What are you trying to do, Jack?
- She said if I did, she'd protect me!
Enough!
Juliet, get out.
- Tom, he's lying!
- You said you can't stitch him up?
Then you don't need to be in here.
Go, Julie.
Don't let him fool you.
He'll never let a patient just die.
Hey!
Hey! Can anybody hear me?
- What happened?
- Open the cage!
- Where's...
- Just open the damn cage!
That's our island?
You didn't believe me before?
We need a boat.
And a couple of towels
and a buffet lunch.
We'll follow the beach.
There's got to be one.
How else do they get back and forth?
Well, why don't we just
stop and ask for directions?
- Jack, are you there?
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
- Tell him I said hi. Get to the point!
Jack, we need a boat. We need
some way to get off of this island.
You heard her.
How do they get off this island?
What's he doing?
Kate? Kate!
Kate!
Come on!
Come on! Go! Go, go!
This way!
Jason, you all right?
They're over there!
Come on! Get inside! Get inside! Go!
Come on!
Be quiet, be quiet, be quiet!
Be quiet...
Where'd they go?
That way.
Nice to meet you, Sheena.
Is it true?
- Is what true?
- What you said.
Did Juliet really ask you to kill him?
Yeah, and in about 40 minutes,
she's gonna get her wish.
Hey...
That's not helping...
...anything.
Now...
...could somebody please get Juliet?
Juliet?
Edmund wants to see you in his office.
Do you work here?
I'm the new research assistant.
Of course you are.
I want in.
- In on what?
- I know what you're doing, Juliet.
- I'm not really sure what you...
- I read your notes.
I know what you took from the lab.
The only thing I don't know is...
...who's your guinea pig?
Ed, I've...
I've been doing my research
in my own lab on my own time.
- I don't really see how...
- It's your sister, isn't it?
Jules, there's two ways
this plays out.
One is your research is potentially...
...genius.
And the other...
...it raises some very
serious ethical questions.
Maybe even criminal concerns.
But if you collaborate with me...
...based on my reputation,
all this is viewed
as cutting-edge science.
And we will win prizes
and drink champagne...
...and do a lot of good for people.
Why don't I give you time
to think about it?
Juliet.
Ben's awake.
How?
Shephard says he's a spinal surgeon,
not an anaesthesiologist.
Ben's asking for you.
This a hobby of yours,
Underdog, digging holes?
Yep. That and basket weaving.
Want one?
- Have a tunnel to the mainland?
- No, but I've got a boat.
- Can we use it?
- Yeah.
- But we've got to hurry.
- Hold on a second, sister.
You happen to find us
in the woods, you have a boat
and you're gonna let us use it?
There's something we need to do first.
My boyfriend is being held prisoner.
If you help me rescue him, I promise
I'll get you back to the other island.
Your boyfriend,
his name happen to be "Karl"?
Yeah.
Come on.
- I stopped the surgery.
- I know.
I've been able to hear you
for a few minutes now.
It's very clever of you.
I should have seen it coming.
- Are you in pain? I can...
- No.
But thanks all the same.
I'd like to speak to Juliet alone,
please, Jack.
No, no, I'm sorry.
Please. I'm asking you.
One gentleman to another.
It won't hurt you to give me
three minutes, will it?
Knowing I have only 27 left.
- If you touch him, if you try to...
- I won't.
You've got three minutes.
I'm Tom, by the way.
They've got history.
I would like for you
to go back in there,
put Ben under and finish the surgery.
And why would I wanna do that?
Because I'm going to go
help your friends escape.
Thank you for taking the time to
let us make our pitch, Dr Burke.
Mittelos BioScience is based in Oregon,
we're just outside of Portland.
These shots might seem cheeseball,
but our people really are this happy.
Now, why? Because we're privately
funded. Privately funded means freedom.
We organize trips every week
in and around the Portland area,
which is just awesome for hiking,
and biking, and river running.
Look, when your company
reached out to me, I was flattered,
but I don't really know why
you would want me.
Is it true that you successfully
impregnated a male field mouse?
Well, he didn't carry to term.
- You mind if I ask you something?
- Sure.
What do you see?
Well... it's a human womb, obviously.
Judging from the decomposition of the
endometrium, I'd say the woman was 70.
- Actually, she's 26.
- What happened to her?
What if I told you that you could have
complete freedom and money to find out?
We think you're special, Dr Burke.
We want you to lead a team
of highly trained people
because we think
you're just that good.
I can't.
Why can't you?
My ex-husband wouldn't let me.
- He wouldn't give you this opportunity?
- No.
He would never give the OK.
- We could reach out to him.
- Don't bother.
- Must be something he'd respond to.
- If he were hit by a bus.
That would work.
- That was totally inappropriate.
- No.
I'm sorry that I wasted your time.
- Dr Burke, please, you...
- No. I'm sorry.
Whatever you think I am, I'm not.
I'm not a leader, Mr Alpert.
I'm a mess.
Oh, hell.
Karl's gotta be in there.
What, you mean you ain't sure?
It's the only place I haven't looked.
- You know the guard?
- Yeah.
- His name's Aldo.
- "Aldo"?
OK, Lollipop, tell me how we're gonna
get by him with one gun and no bullets?
I've got an idea.
Of course you do.
- Open the door!
- Alex?
What the hell are you doing?
They got out of their cages! I caught
them in the jungle. Now open up!
Just stop! You're not supposed to be
here. Your dad's gonna kill you!
My dad was the one who told me
to bring them here, to you.
Look, maybe you should call him.
I'm sure he's got nothing better to do.
- Danny, I need Ben.
- Why?
I got Alex here, she's got
Austen and Ford with her...
Damn it! Whatever she says
don't believe it!
You hold them right there,
I'm on my...
Don't get mad at me because you fell
for the old Wookiee Prisoner gag.
- Where's Karl?
- What are you talking about?
Shoot him in the knee.
- What?
- We don't have time. I'll do it.
OK! All right! He's at the end of the
hall! Room 23! Keys are in my pocket!
Good con, I almost believed
you're gonna shoot him.
It wasn't a con.
Here it is!
Help!
You're OK. You're OK, Karl.
Is he OK?
We got your boyfriend back.
Where's your damn boat?
Idiot.
- Where are they?
- I don't know. Alex was with them.
Danny!
We're letting them go.
- Letting 'em go?
- Ben gave the order.
- Ben's in surgery.
- He woke up.
- He woke up?
- Shephard won't do the surgery
unless he knows his friends are off
the island. Do you want Ben to die?
I know Ben would rather die
than let them go!
Hey.
How was the interview?
It's not for me.
- What?
- It's fine.
They're too far away anyway.
It's Portland.
- You didn't say no because of me?
- Why would I want to go to Portland
for research that doesn't even work?
Because it does work.
I'm pregnant.
- What?
- Look, look...
I took a blood test, too.
I didn't want to tell you
till I was sure.
- It worked.
- Yeah.
My whole life,
all I ever wanted was to have a baby
and now because of you I can!
God, now I just need to get healthy!
Now I just need to get healthy
so I can see the bugger
get into an Ivy League school.
Of course you will. You will.
Now you can tell that bastard ex-husband
of yours what he can do with his ethics.
Because you're insufferable,
and you're mean.
You asked me for the truth,
Mom, and that...
Ed.
Let me call you later, OK?
OK, bye.
- Hello, Jules. What's up?
- She's pregnant.
- Excuse me?
- It worked. Rachel's pregnant.
Wow.
I need to see your labs.
We'll have to verify the data.
No.
I'm not interested in publishing, Ed.
It's my sister.
Fine. If you're not interested,
why are you concerned if...
- You OK?
- Yeah.
I just don't like blood too much.
Well, then you probably
won't want to be looking at that.
So, if you really
can get off the island,
why didn't you just
take him to a facility?
Why all this?
Because ever since
the sky turned purple, we...
- What the hell happened?
- I just nicked an artery.
- Isn't that what you already did?
- Yeah, well, that was on purpose.
Can you fix it?
Damn it!
- You got him?
- I got him.
- Karl?
- Nice ride.
- Karl, we're gonna go now, OK?
- Help me.
Can you stand? OK. Come on.
So... you're the boss's daughter?
I never saw that coming.
Let's go, Cheech.
We're going for a little ride.
- Careful.
- All right. Easy.
I'm gonna put you in the boat,
all right?
Wait, wait.
- Are you OK?
- Danny.
No. "Sawyer. "
Danny!
- No!
- Danny!
- What happened?
- I can't see.
- What?
- There's too much blood.
All right, get over here.
Tom, he is going to die
if you don't get over here now.
Go.
Get out of here.
You heard the lady.
- Let's go!
- Not you, Alex.
- You're staying.
- Why?
We both know your father.
And the only way he'll let Karl live
is if you're here when he wakes up.
I'm sorry, Alex.
Hey, Alex.
Hey.
I missed you.
I know. I missed you, too.
You have to go away now...
...but I'll see you real soon, OK?
I love you.
I have to go to sleep now.
Wait.
Easy. OK. Easy.
Wait, wait...
Keep it steady, damn it!
Hold it steady.
Jack, are you there?
All right, hold that up to me.
The walkie. Hold it up to me.
- What about the suction?
- Just do it!
Yeah, I'm here, Kate. You OK?
Yeah, I... We've got a boat.
They're letting us go.
Who's letting you go?
The blonde woman.
- So you're safe? You and Sawyer?
- Yes! Yeah.
- Tell me.
- Tell you?
On the beach, the day of the crash,
the story I told you.
If you're safe, tell me.
- You think this is the best time to...
- Shut up!
You... were doing a surgery on a girl.
And you messed up.
You made a mistake.
You tore something on her back
and all the nerves came loose.
And you said you were so afraid.
And you said the fear was so...
...real.
And you didn't know what to do.
So you counted to five.
And then you weren't afraid anymore.
And then it was just gone.
And you fixed her.
You saved her.
I need you to make me a promise, Kate.
Jack?
Promise me that you'll never
come back here for me.
Don't come back, Kate.
- Jack, where are you?
- Turn it off.
Jack? Jack! Please, where are...?
Trades are coming up.
We gotta go.
- Let's go.
- OK.
We have some paperwork
we need you to sign...
...but take your time,
there's no rush.
Thank you.
Were you able to remove the tumour?
Yeah.
You'll want to do a biopsy,
see if it's malignant.
So, what now?
I just go back to my cell?
Until they figure out
what to do with you.
"They. "
What'd he say?
- I'm sorry?
- Ben.
What did he say that made you
want to save his life?
It doesn't really matter what he said.
It matters to me.
After everything that
I have been put through...
...you owe me an answer.
And I wanna know what he said.
Tissue?
Thank you. Thanks.
- Have we met?
- Hello, Dr Burke.
- Mr Alpert?
- I'm... so sorry for your loss.
What are you doing here?
I saw what happened on the news and
your office said you were down here.
I just wanted to express
my condolences in person
before I went back to Portland.
This is Ethan,
he's one of my colleagues.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
He was hit by a bus.
I know. They say you were there
when it happened. It must...
No, no. In our interview...
I said that I wanted him
to get hit by a bus.
Dr Burke, I realize you're
a little shook up right now,
but this is just a tragic accident.
You can't blame yourself.
I don't even remember you saying that.
Why are you here, Mr Alpert?
Look, I know the timing is horrible,
but we came because we're that serious
about getting you to come work with us.
Just give us six months.
If you need to, you can be back
before your sister gives birth.
- How did you know that my?
- We're very thorough
in our recruitment process.
Can my sister come?
Won't work, we're pretty remote.
She wouldn't have access
to the treatment that she needs.
But it's Portland.
There's plenty of clinics and...
We're not quite in Portland.
I want to know what he said.
I've been on this island
for three years, Jack.
Three years, two months, and 28 days.
He said that if I...
...let him live...
...and I helped you...
...that he would finally
let me go home.