Previously on Lost:
Stop! I'll shoot.
No, you won't, Sun.
Jack, I need your help.
Those aren't hers.
She's gone.
The plane was loaded with heroin.
- Where did you find this?
- I found it in the jungle.
Take me there.
Eko? Who's that?
He's my brother.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
Here. Eat.
It's OK, Yemi.
Eko.
All right, Eko. Go.
Did you hear me? Go!
Confess that you have stolen.
Yemi was hungry.
That is not an excuse.
You have sinned, Eko.
Hunger does not matter.
Now go.
Ask God for forgiveness.
Confess!
How long has he been like this?
Couple days now.
Eko?
Can you hear me?
What happened to him?
Before or after we saved him
from the polar bear cave?
Come on. Locke will want to know
you guys are back.
Stay alive, dude, OK?
What are you doing here?
I have come to give my confession.
- Hello, Eko.
- Hello, brother.
I have some merchandise
that I need to get out of the country.
You mean drugs.
You will make us priests.
We will fly the drugs out ourselves.
My signature does not
make you a priest, Eko.
You could never be a priest.
- No more! Stop! No more!
- Yemi!
Yemi! No!
Father?
Are you OK, Father?
Eko. Eko, wake up.
It is time to confess.
To be judged, brother.
I will be waiting.
You know where to find me.
You guys smell smoke?
- Get him clear!
- Eko! Help me!
- Pick him up.
- Eko. Come on.
- We got to get you out of here.
- Cover him with a blanket. Careful.
Lay him down. Lay him down.
You're OK. You're all right.
My brother.
- Brother.
- You're all right. It's OK.
- My brother.
- You're all right.
I'll be back.
Brother. Yemi. Yemi.
Charlie, is everyone OK?
- Yeah, we're good.
- Where's Eko?
Hurley and I pulled him out over...
He was right there.
Eko?
Good evening, Jack.
Good evening, Ben.
I was hoping you
might join me for a walk.
What?
Well, you say that like...
...you won't throw a bag over my head
and drag me out of here if I say no.
Then don't say no.
Why don't you put this on.
I'll wait outside.
Does it hurt?
Sorry?
Your neck. Does it hurt?
Any numbness in your fingers and toes?
Like pins and needles when
your foot falls asleep, but permanent?
Why are you asking me
these questions, Jack?
Because, Ben...
...you have a tumour on your spine.
An aggressive tumour...
...that is going to kill you.
I don't know when
those X-rays were taken,
but unless they were very recent...
...you're not gonna be
taking walks much longer.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
OK. My mistake then.
I'm ready whenever you are.
Stay here.
As we prepare to send
Colleen on her way,
- I'd like to take a moment to...
- I hate funerals.
He let you out?
Gave me a new shirt too.
Bye, Jack.
Why did you show him my X-rays?
I didn't tell him they were yours.
But I guess you did.
I think I know how to find
Jack, Kate and Sawyer.
Can I ask why he's being
included in the conversation?
Is that supposed to hurt my feelings?
Tell him what you told me.
The computer in the hatch
wasn't only for pushing the button.
Now I'm pretty sure
that it could be used
to communicate with other stations.
This is fascinating,
but you just told
me the hatch exploded.
One of them did.
You want to try and
communicate with The Others.
Yep.
No luck, dudes. We looked everywhere.
Eko's gone.
There was no trail.
Not that we know
what a trail looks like.
When you pulled him out,
did he say anything?
Nothing coherent.
He was just mumbling.
"My brother, my brother. "
Sayid, pack your gear.
We're going to that computer.
- Wait, what about Eko?
- We'll catch up to him.
We're all going to the same place.
You are home, Father.
Father?
Oh, I was looking for Father Yemi.
Father Yemi is gone.
He was called away quite suddenly.
An emergency
at a refugee camp down south.
I am Amina. I work at the clinic.
This is my son, Daniel.
He's the altar boy here.
Are you taking his place?
Yes.
Will Father Yemi still go to London?
- London?
- He was leaving the end of the week.
He was going to continue his studies.
I will take his place there too.
Don't! No! Please!
No!
Confess.
We're heading out to the Pearl Station.
There's a computer there
that might help find our people.
Anybody want to come along?
What do you mean,
"Anybody want to come along?"
If you'd like to join us,
it's a free island.
Yeah, see, Jack would
go and do stuff alone...
...or he'd take Sayid or Kate.
Yeah, well... I'm not Jack.
- The more the merrier.
- I'll go!
- Great.
- What?
Anybody else wanna come, meet at the
tree line in ten minutes. Bring water.
You're not serious.
What? You always whine
about not being included.
Now's our chance.
Would you mind
if I ask you a question, brother?
- Shoot.
- Are we going to poke at a computer...
...or are we going after your man Eko?
Two birds, one stone.
Eko's heading for the plane that
crashed on top of the Pearl Station.
That's quite a coincidence.
Don't mistake coincidence for fate.
You're not supposed to do that.
That's holy water.
I'm washing away my sins.
- Father Yemi would never...
- I am not Father Yemi.
Wait there.
Where is Father Yemi?
Who wants to know?
Perhaps you did not hear me.
Where is Father Yemi?
The shipment is late.
I just got off the telephone.
- They assure me it will arrive Friday.
- What shipment?
You should explain our arrangement
to your new priest.
We receive shipments of vaccines
from the Red Cross. We keep 20 percent.
The rest we give to Emeka and his men.
In exchange for protection.
So you see, Father...
...everybody is happy.
Everybody's happy.
Everybody benefits.
So I hope you will continue
to honour our arrangements.
I am not afraid of you.
I'll be back for the vaccine
on Friday, Father.
You don't want more
lives on your conscience.
Hello, Eko.
You want to guess what's for lunch?
I'm not big on mysteries.
Of course you're not.
You people have cheeseburgers?
You have no idea what I went through
to make this for you.
I killed the cow.
Processed the meat.
Baked the bun. And the fries...
...try rendering animal fat.
No ketchup?
- I'd like to talk to him.
- OK. So talk to him.
- Alone, please.
- I'm fine with her being here.
And I'm thrilled that you're fine,
Jack, but it's private.
Doctor-patient confidentiality.
Sure.
Of course.
Mind if I eat?
We had such a wonderful plan
to break you, Jack.
Break me?
Wear you down until you were convinced
we weren't your enemies.
Get you to trust us.
And then, of course, we'd lead you
to believe that you were choosing to do
whatever we asked you to do.
All of this, of course,
assumed that you would get invested.
Invested in what?
Has it not occurred to you Juliet bears
a striking resemblance to your ex-wife?
Why are you telling me this?
I'm telling you this, Jack,
because my wonderful plan...
...got shot to sunshine
when you saw my damned X-rays
and figured out I was dying.
All of this...
...you brought me here
to operate on you. You...
You want me to save your life.
No. I want you to want to save my life.
But we're beyond that now, so...
All I can ask is that
you think about it.
Do you believe in God, Jack?
Do you?
Two days after I found out
I had a fatal tumour on my spine,
a spinal surgeon fell out of the sky.
And if that's not proof of God,
I don't know what is.
Hey. You sure you're all right?
We can stop for a bit
and catch our breaths.
I'm fine.
You're heading for
the plane wreckage, aren't you?
Charlie heard you call out for
your brother before you left the camp.
Is that what you're doing out here?
Looking for Yemi?
Do not speak my brother's name again.
What are you so afraid of, Eko?
You need to come back in two days.
Father, what can I do for you?
The vaccines that you spoke of,
how often do these shipments come?
Every six months, if we are lucky.
What makes you so interested
in our shipments of vaccine, Father?
You agree to give most of it
to the militia?
The vaccines fetch
a high price on the black markets.
Whatever you are thinking,
do not cross these men.
Before Father Yemi, we got nothing.
We owe whatever vaccines we have
to his work.
You remind me of him, you know.
You're a good man too.
I hear you have some vaccine to sell.
I do, but it has to be done by Sunday.
I'm leaving the country.
No problem.
The hatch is over here by the plane.
Why don't you take everybody down.
And you?
I'll be there in a minute.
- What's Eko looking for?
- His brother's body's in that plane.
So, what exactly did you see back there?
I saw it once, you know.
- And what did you see?
- I saw a very bright light.
It was beautiful.
That is not what I saw.
My brother's gone.
You set the plane on fire.
Yemi's body could've burned or...
not to mention animals or...
So you don't want to
come down there with us?
No. I will wait here.
Well...
Oh, I forgot.
I found this when I was looking for you.
Hello, Father.
I hear you have
a shipment of vaccine for sale.
If you thought you could do this
without me knowing...
...you don't know who I am.
You know... you're lucky, Father.
I'm a superstitious man.
I don't relish taking the life
of a holy man.
That is why, today...
...I'm only going
to cut off your hands.
No!
Please, no! No!
You do not know who I am.
I'm Dr Mark Wickmund,
and this is the orientation film
for Station 5 of The Dharma Initiative.
Station 5, or The Pearl,
is a monitoring station
where the activities of participants
in Dharma Initiative projects
can be observed and recorded...
- Well?
- The wiring is only one-way.
It's a closed system. A dead end.
Hey, guys?
What are these other TVs for?
- Sorry?
- All these TVs.
This guy says
that there's six stations.
Wait, here, check it out.
...is a monitoring station
where the activities of participants
in Dharma Initiative projects
can be observed and recorded...
"Projects. " More than one.
So maybe some of these TVs
are connected to the other hatches.
Well, I'm suddenly feeling very stupid.
Perhaps I could patch in
one of the other feeds,
see if we can get another picture.
The toilet still works.
Anything yet?
Nothing.
What about now?
- John?
- Yeah, we got something.
Wow.
- What is it?
- That's a good question.
Those are computers.
Great.
That's what you're looking for.
Now we can get out of here.
I guess he'll be expecting us.
- You don't trust me anymore?
- I trust you just fine.
Just thought I'd put a movie in.
- I'll pass on the movie.
- You'll like this one.
To Kill a Mockingbird.
It's a classic.
- I don't want to watch a movie now.
- I'll turn the sound down then.
I felt like I should apologize,
say I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for bringing you here.
And for everything that's
been done to you and your friends.
You have to know...
...we were desperate.
It was all so we could save his life.
Ben.
He's a great man.
I know you find that
hard to believe, but he is.
You probably feel like...
...you don't have a choice...
...but you do, Jack.
Free will is all we've got.
Anyway, I just wanted
to put in my two cents.
I told you before you can trust me.
I want you to trust me...
...now when I tell you that
doing the surgery is absolutely
the right thing for you to do.
It's the right thing because
he deserves to live.
- Turn the movie off.
- Jack.
Turn it off! Now.
All right. It's off.
Think about what I said. Please.
- Where are you going?
- London.
Are you a bad man?
My mum says you're a bad man.
Only God knows.
I see you have your vaccine.
Do you expect me to be grateful?
I know what you were planning to do.
- Those men, I helped you...
- They will be replaced by others!
What are they doing?
What is the meaning of this?
We are boarding up the church.
We can no longer use it.
This is Yemi's church.
- You have no right to do this.
- It is no longer sacred.
And one day you will be judged
for what you did.
If I were you,
I would start making my peace now.
I would go to London
and begin to repent
because you owe God
for every life you've taken.
And you truly believe this is Yemi's?
You owe him one church.
Yemi.
Wait.
You say you want to hear my confession.
Why? Why now?
Show yourself. Where are you?
Where?
Are you ready, Eko?
Yes.
I am ready, Yemi.
I ask for no forgiveness, Father.
For I have not sinned.
I have only done
what I needed to do to survive.
A small boy once asked me
if I was a bad man.
If I could answer him now,
I would tell him
that, when I was a young boy,
I killed a man
to save my brother's life.
I am not sorry for this.
I am proud of this.
I did not ask for
the life that I was given...
...but it was given, nonetheless.
And with it...
...I did my best.
You speak to me as if
I were your brother.
Who are you?
Who are you?!
The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
He leadeth me in paths
of righteousness...
Eko.
Oh, Eko.
It's OK. It's OK.
What did he say, John?
He said... we're next.