Previously on "Lost"...
I don't know how it happened,
but you seem to have some
communion with this island,
John,and that makes you very,
very important.
In time,you'll have a better
understanding of things.
Kwon is pregnant.
The fetus is healthy--
- What's that?
- Juliet is gathering information
for us at your former camp.
She's determining if any
of the women are pregnant.
Then we're gonna go in and...
take them.
Juliet is a mole.
She's working for Ben.
- We're moving.
- Moving? Where are we going?
We are not going
anywhere, John.
You are going to stay behind.
We'll leave a trail--
One you can track.
And,John,
unless you're carrying
your father's body
on your back...
Don't bother.
Come on! Damn it,push!
Something's wrong. I can't...
Emily-- it's not coming!
You can do this! Now push!
-Come on. Come on,baby.
-You can do it. Now come on.
Come on.
There you go! Come on!
Aah!
It's a boy.
You did it.
It hurts.
Oh,you did it.
Roger,it hurts.
Emily,no one knows
we're out here.
We gotta get back,
okay,honey?
Can you hold on to the baby?
Emily,can you hold the baby?
Hold him tight.
Hey!
Help! Help!
Help!
Come on. Help me.
Hey,what happened,man?
We were hiking.
She went into labor,
and she wasn't due yet.
She's bleeding.
-Okay. Okay,look. We'll put her in the car,okay?
-Okay.
We're gonna get you
to the hospital.
-Oh,okay.
-Okay,honey.
-Okay,it's all right.
Let's keep her warm. All right?
-How's the baby?
-Fine,i guess. I don't know.
Roger...
-Roger...
-i'm right here.
Call him Benjamin...
Stay with me.
Stay with me. Emily!
Emily! Oh,god,no!
What you got there?
It's a birthday present.
Mine just happens
to be today.
You do remember birthdays,
don't you,Richard?
So do you want me to bring the,
uh, tape back to Juliet?
What?
The tape with your
instructions for Juliet--
Do you want me to bring it back
to the medical station?
I recorded it yesterday
before we left.
-I thought you already took it.
-No.
Where's Tom?
Tom!
Have you seen
my recorder?
You said that if i killed
my father,
you'd tell me everything
i wanted to know
about the island.
So why don't you start
at the beginning?
---www.opensubtitles.org---
Revision by jenilim
---"LOST" Season 03 Episode 20---
"The Man Behind the Curtain"
I know i promised to
tell you everything,John,
and i wish it was as simple
as me taking out a dusty
old book and opening it up.
But it's not that simple.
How about you just tell me?
You probably think
i'm the leader of
this little community,
but that's not entirely true.
We all answer
to someone,John.
And who might that be?
His name is Jacob.
Okay,then. Take me to Jacob.
I can't do that.
-Where are you going?
-Hell,Ben,if you don't want to take me,
maybe someone else will.
I'll just go and ask Richard.
Why would Richard take you?
He doesn't know where Jacob is.
-He doesn't talk to Jacob.
-Well,who talk to him?
-I do.
-Oh,you're the only
one who talks to him?
-That's right.
-And no one else knows where he is?
I was born here on this island.
I'm one of the last that was.
Most of these people you see--
i brought them here,
so Jacob talks to me,John.
He tells me what to do,
Trusts me.
And no one else
has ever seen him?
That's right.
How convenient.
You know what i think,Ben?
I think there is no Jacob.
I think your people are idiots
if they believe you take
orders from someone else.
You are the man behind
the curtain...
the Wizard of Oz...
and you're a liar.
And what might you based
that theory on, John?
Because if you were
telling the truth,
your hand wouldn't be shaking.
Namaste.
Thanks.
Hey, Welcome to
the island,man.
Namaste.
So what do you think?
Wow,this is some place.
Thanks again for the
opportunity, Mr. Goodspeed.
Horace,please.
Horace. And this must be Ben.
-Yeah.
-Mr. Goodspeed was there the day you were born.
Yes,i was.
-He's doing us a big favor here.
-He gave your old man a job.
Uh he don't say much.
That's okay.
I bet he will when he has something to say,
Right,Ben?
Hey,you hungry,kiddo? Huh?
-Huh?
-Great. All right, well,i tell you what.
After you're done processing,
we'll have some lunch.
-How's that sound?
-Uh,thank you.
You're gonna love it here.
Welcome to the Island.
For your own comfort
and safety,
we ask that you stay
within the confines
of your new living
quarters.
Our barracks
are surrounded
by a high-frequency
sonar fence
to protect us
from the island's abundant
and diverse wildlife.
You are now a member of
the Dharma initiative.
What kind of wildlife
you think this fence is
protecting us from?
-Roger Linus?
-Roger Linus. Yeah.
Every morning you will
be given a new code
which will allow you to
cross outside the fences
if you so desire.
There are properties
on this island
that exist nowhere
else on earth.
Our mission is to study
these properties
for the betterment
of mankind
and advancement
of world peace.
Most of you will be working
on the mainland.
Should you be assigned
Ological study...
Hey. You're new,huh?
I'm Annie.
Want one?
We can have as many
as we want.
"Work man"?
What is this? Work man?
I'm a Janitor?
- I'm sorry,Mr. Linus. Goodspeed
told me you people were
doing experiments,
Changing the world.
I didn't come here to
clean up after you.
Look,if anything else opens up,
you can feel free
to apply for it.
Come on.
You don't think it's too big?
Dude,be honest. It can't
be worse than Haggis.
Oh,i could go for some
Haggis right now.
Hey,Sayid.
What happened to you?
-I was with Locke.
-Well,where is he?
He went back.
-Back where?
-With them.-Don't ask me where the hell it is,
'cause it don't matter right now.
What does matter... is this...
Where is Ben?!
Where is he?!
I thought you were dead.
I'm fortunate the Pylons
were not set to a lethal level.
What is he doing here?
It's all right.
He's the one who
tried to kill me.
He's with us now.
Where have you been, Mikhail?
I encountered several
of his people in the jungle.
They had an injured
woman with them.
Apparently,she had just
parachuted onto the island.
-What? -Her helo
crashed in the water.
She says her ship is
approximately 130 clicks
to the west of us.
She has a radio-telephone.
Where is she now?
I assume they have taken
her back to their camp.
We'll be visiting their camp
day after tomorrow.
-We'll take care of it then.
-Day after tomorrow?
-We have to go now.
-Ben's not going
anywhere with you.
-Excuse me?
He and i are going
to see Jacob.
Please tell me this
isn't true,Benjamin.
Sorry. I have to deal
with this now, John.
Our excursion wi have to wait.
Since when do you explain
yourself to him--an outsider?
Tom.
Richard?!
So when do we leave?
You know,you didn't have
to beat Mikhail senseless
to make your point, John.
Yes,i did.
Locke...
i hear you're
gonna go see Jacob.
You're gonna need this.
Thanks.
Happy birthday,Dad.
So once water is added
to the bicarbonate,
we will get our very
own volcanic reaction.
Yes.
Is that what happened to
the volcano on this island?
Exactly,Annie,
but that was a long time ago.
Okay,let's get ourselves
an eruption.
Oh,cool!
Just add water,and voila!! Wow!
Now i know it's not lava,but--
what was that?!
Oh,no. They're coming.
Okay,everyone,
into your positions.
Everyone,get down! Hurry!
Get over here!
That's right,all together.
Annie,lock the back door,
please.
Come on!
He's just sitting there!
Ben,come on,honey,
you gotta move. Ben!
Come on.
Uhh!
Come on!
Don't worry.
It's just the hostiles.
We'll be okay.
Get down!
Hey,man,i heard you ran
into a little trouble.
We were driving
back from the plane,
and we hear
this huge explosion.
Next thing i know,
there's a siren wailing,
and we're driving through
the middle of a shootout.
Look,we're having some
skirmishes with the natives.
What do you mean,natives?
Well,we're not exactly sure
who they are.
Well,this ain't what
i signed up for.
Roger, i did you a favor,man.
You were having trouble
finding work,
and don't forget about Ben.
He's getting a quality education.
I don't give a damn
about his education.
If i'm gonna get shot at,
i want hazard pay.
-I want another 30 grand.
-Calm down,man.
And don't try to tell me
you don't have it.
You hear me?
Now get the hell out
of my house.
Uhh!
I thought i told you
to go to bed.
She's not here.
I noticed.
What are you doing?
Looking for Juliet.
Well,you're not gonna
find her in there.
-She left with jack.
-Juliet left with jack?
He took off right after
i told him about Naomi.
Who's Naomi?
And why would you
do that,Kate?
Because she's hurt,
because he's a doctor
and because he has
a right to know.
Where is he now?
-I don't know,Sayid.
-Of course you don't.
It might be time for you to
tell everybody else
about Naomi,too.
Play her the tape.
What tape?
There's something you
should know,John,
before we go.
Whether or not you think
he's the Wizard of Oz,
i can assure you that
Jacob is very,very real.
And we're gonna go see him,
and he's not gonna like it.
In fact,i have a feeling
he's gonna be very... angry.
And that's why my
hand was shaking,
because this is not
a man you go and see.
This is a man who summons you.
Well,i guess there's a
first time for everythg.
It's us.
That's you,and that's me.
Now we never have to
be away from each other.
Happy birthday,Ben.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
It's your birthday.
Sorry i forgot.
It's kinda hard to celebrate
on the day you
killed your mom.
She was just seven
months pregnant.
We went for a hike,
but you had to come early.
Now she's gone...
and i'm stuck here on
this island... with you.
Happy birthday,Ben.
Mom?
Ben,don't!
Mom!
It's not time yet,Benjamin.
Let's go,John.
John.
So,what,the whole world
thinks we're dead?
-That's not important right now.
-Not important?
-What do you mean,
it's not important,Sayid?
-Excuse me.
-I'm sorry. -Don't you people
want to be rescued?
We kept her a secret
to keep her safe.
Safe from what,Sayid?
Safe from Jack. He spent
a week with the others,
and he brought one of
them back with him,
here,amongst us,
and every time we try to get
answers from this woman,
he prevents her
from giving them.
But it's Jack.
He would never do
anything to hurt us.
-And Juliet-- i believe
she's a good person.
-Good person,huh?
-You're basing that on what?
-Wouldn't involve her taking you
to one of their medical stations,
would it now, Mrs. Kwon?
-How...
Kwon is pregnant.
The fetus is healthy and
was conceived  island
with her husband. He was
sterile before they got here.
I'm still working on getting samples
from the other women.
-I should have Austen's soon.
I'll report back when i know more.
Where'd you get that?
Where have you been,Jack?
I asked you where you got it.
You really think
you're in a position
to be asking us questions?
Turn the tape over.
-Stay out of it.
-You wanna burn me at the stake? Here i am.
But first,turn the tape over.
Press "play."
Juliet,it's Ben.
I'm sending three teams
to extract Kwon
the night after tomorrow.
Won't have time to run
Austen's sample,
so if you determine that
she or anyone else is pregnant,
mark their tents,
and we'll take them,too.
Good luck.
The night i saw your
baby on the ultrasound,
i told Jack what they
were making me do.
Why didn't you tell us?
Because i hadn't decided
what to do about it yet.
"Yet?"
I think we got some
catching up to do.
Mom?
Mom!
Whoa,whoa,whoa,whoa.
Whoa,whoa,hey,hey.
Whoa,i didn't mean to scare you.
-Wait,wait. -Are you lost? Wait.
Are you one of them?
One of who?
A hostile.
Do you even know what
that word means?
What's your name?
Ben.
-Ben. So you wanna tell me
what you're doing
in the middle of the jungle
all by yourself?
I left home, and...
i'm looking for my mom.
You think she's out here?
You wouldn't believe me.
Try me.
She's dead.
Did she die here... on the island?
No.
When i was a baby.
Did you see her...
out here,Ben, in the jungle?
She talked to me.
What did she say?
That i couldn't come with her.
She said it wasn't time yet.
You should go home now.
Your people will be
looking for you.
I don't wanna go back there!
I hate it there!
Take me with you.
Maybe that can happen...
maybe,i mean,if that's what
you really want,Ben,
if that's what you want.
I want you to think about that...
and you're gonna have to be very,
very patient.
We're here.
You'll want to turn off
your flashlight,John.
Why?
Jacob feels the same way about
technology as you do.
Once i open this door,
there's no turning back.
Are you sure this is
what you want?
So be it.
Jacob...
i'm here with John Locke.
We're coming in now.
Jacob...
this is John.
Aren't you going
to say hello,John?
What?
I told you he wouldn't.
Who... what are you
talking about?
You can't see him?
See who?
Jacob.
He's sitting right here in this chair.
Yes,i know, but he insisted.
What is this?
You wanted the secrets
of the island?
Well,here they are.
This is the man who can
answer every single--
i am not.
He made me bring him here.
Did you think that
that was my--
-Sorry,may i finish?
-You're crazy.
Excuse me?
You don't know anything
about the island,do you?
You just made it all up.
Jacob,please, i can't hear him...
stop.
-If you're gonna talk over
what he's saying--
stop. -Shut up!
You're putting on a
show for me?
Or do you...
do you really think there's
someone there?
I know there's
someone there.
You don't know anything.
I'm sorry you feel
that way,John,
and i'm sorry that you're
too limited to see.
You're pathetic.
Help me.
What did you just say?
I... i didn't say anything.
-Oh,yes,you did. I heard you.
You said that--
that's enough!
You've had your fun!
What was that?
That was Jacob.
What did you hear in there,John?
What did Jacob say to you?
He didn't say anything to me.
You did.
What are you talking about?
There is no Jacob,ben.
I'm not gonna be taken in
by the little...
show you put on last night.
You're a fraud,
and it's time your people
were told the truth.
And this is not
the way we came.
I'm taking us back
another way.
I wanted to show you
something first.
I've seen enough.
You know,John,
you're not wrong.
Some of the things i've told you--
some of the things i've
told everybody--
are simply not true.
Like what?
Well,for starters,
i wasn't born
on this island.
Then where did
you come from?
That's what i want
to show you.
Morning.
Okay,wait.
Put it right...
right down there.
What's the problem now?
You're usually chatty
Cathy in the morning.
It's my birthday.
I don't know why i keep fooling
myself into thinking
that one of these years you're
actually gonna remember.
Well,i tell you what.
All we gotta do this morning
is run this stuff
outo Pearl Station.
Why don't we go up
to the Mesa,
drink some beers?
Have some...
i don't know...
Father and son time?
I'd like that.
Okay.
Well...
you sure can't say
it ain't beautiful.
Do you really blame me?
What?
Do you really think it's
my fault that she died?
What do i know?
Why do you keep looking
at your watch?
You got a date?
Listen...
if it makes you
feel any better,
i will do my best
to remember your
birthday next year.
I don't think that's
gonna happen,dad.
What do you mean?
You know, i've missed her,too,
maybe as much as you have.
But the difference is
that for as long as
i can remember,
i've had to put up with you.
And doing at
required a tremendous
amount of patience.
Good-bye,dad.
Ben...
you want us to,uh,
go get his body?
No,leave him out there.
Okay.
This is where i came from,John.
These are my people...
the Dharma Initiative.
They came here
seeking harmony...
but they couldn't
even co-exist
with the island's
original inhabitants.
And when it became clear
that one side had to go,
one side had to be purged...
i did what i had to do.
I was one of the people
that was smart enough
to make sure that i didn't
end up in that ditch...
which makes me considerably
smarter than you,John.
Uhh!
What did Jacob say to you?
Why did you do this?
Because you heard him.
Now i need to know what he said.
"Help me."
John...
I'm not gonna ask you again.
What did he say to you?
He said...
"Help me."
Well,i certainly hope
he helps you, John.
---"LOST" Season 03 Episode 20---
"The Man Behind the Curtain"
---www.opensubtitles.org---
Revision by jenilim