???
???? ALL THE WAY TO PORTLAND
FOR RESEARCH
THAT DOESN'T EVEN WORK?
BECAUSE IT DOES WORK.
M PREGNANT.
MY WHOLE LIFE, ALL I'VE EVER
WANTED WAS TO HAVE A BABY,
I KNOW THAT YOU DON'T CARE,
BUT THE PEOPLE
I SPENT THE LAST THREE YEARS OF
MY LIFE WITH--THEY JUST LEFT ME.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
SHE IS NOT COMING WITH US.
YES, SHE IS.
WHY?
BECAUSE THEY LEFT HER BEHIND,
TOO.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
THIS IS A GOOD PLACE
TO MAKE CAMP.
I'LL GET SOME FIREWOOD.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
DO YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT IT?
TALK ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT THE WEEK
YOU SPENT OVER THERE WITH THEM.
WELL, AFTER YOU LEFT,
I'D, UH...
I'D MADE A DEAL WITH THEM--
IF I TOOK CARE OF BEN,
THAT THEY'D
LET ME OFF THE ISLAND.
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST KEPT MY HEAD DOWN,
DID WHAT I WAS SUPPOSED TO,
AND I DIDN'T
ASK ANY QUESTIONS.
AND THAT'S IT?
THAT'S IT.
OKAY. LET'S HAVE IT.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU PEOPLE
ARE DOING ON THIS ISLAND,
WHY YOU'RE TERRORIZING US,
MAKING LISTS,
KIDNAPPING CHILDREN.
I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING.
BUT THE FIRST THING
I'D LIKE TO KNOW IS...
WHO ARE YOU?
(Petula Clark's
"Downtown" playing)
HI. I'M JULIET BURKE.
I'M WITH MITTELOS BIOSCIENCE.
I'LL LET MR. ALPERT
KNOW YOU'RE HERE.
THANK YOU.
WOW.
(both laugh)
I THINK THEY'RE TAKING THIS
WHOLE "CORPORATE SECRECY" THING
A LITTLE TOO SERIOUSLY.
I'M NEVER GONNA FIT IN
WITH THESE PEOPLE.
(knock on window)
HEY THERE, DR. BURKE.
IF YOU POP THE TRUNK,
I'LL GET YOUR BAGS.
THANK YOU.
(gate rattling)
HEY.
AH, YOU MANAGED TO FIND US.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THEY HAD AN AIRPORT OUT HERE.
I KNOW. IT SURPRISES EVERYONE.
HI. YOU MUST BE RACHEL.
RICHARD ALPERT.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
THANK YOU FOR LETTING US BORROW
YOUR SISTER FOR A FEW MONTHS.
JUST PROMISE ME YOU'LL
BRING HER BACK IN ONE PIECE.
WELL, WE'LL DO OUR BEST.
UM, SO LISTEN, IT'S A...
A SECURITY THING, YOU KNOW?
WE HAVE TO TAKE YOU IN
THE REST OF THE WAY, SO...
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY,
WE'LL BE WAITING
RIGHT OVER HERE, BUT PLEASE TAKE
YOUR TIME. PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
THANKS.
THANK YOU.
IT'S BETTER THIS WAY.
IS THIS A MISTAKE?
I SHOULDN'T GO.
WHAT IF YOU GET SICK AGAIN?
I WON'T.
THE CANCER'S GONE,
AND I'M 100% PREGGERS,
THANKS TO YOU.
I'LL BE BACK...
YES, I KNOW.
BEFORE YOU GIVE BIRTH.
I PROMISE.
I KNOW. DON'T WORRY
ABOUT US, OKAY?
OKAY.
YOU SPENT YOUR WHOLE LIFE
WORKING TO GET HERE,
SO DON'T BLOW IT.
(laughs)
I LOVE YOU.
(whispers) I LOVE YOU.
(blows kiss)
OKAY.
GO MAKE US PROUD.
(gate rattling)
MA'AM...
(Juliet) BYE.
WHO ARE YOU?
IF I TOLD YOU WHO I WAS,
IF I TOLD YOU
EVERYTHING THAT I KNOW,
YOU'D KILL ME.
WHAT DO YOU THINK I'LL DO
IF YOU DON'T?
(firewood clatters)
(Jack) LEAVE HER ALONE.
SOONER OR LATER,
SHE'LL ANSWER MY QUESTIONS.
SHE'LL ANSWER YOUR QUESTIONS
WHEN SHE'S READY,
AND YOU'LL WAIT UNTIL SHE IS.
SHE'S UNDER MY PROTECTION.
www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@MAOREN
Sync:FRM@????  KevinVan
lost 316
CLAIRE?
(wailing)
OH, OH, WHAT IS IT?
OH, IT'S OKAY.
SHUSH. I KNOW.
IT'S OKAY.
YEAH, 'S OKAY.
CLAIRE, HEY.
CLAIRE, YOU OKAY?
CHARLIE.
WHAT'S--WHAT'S GOING ON?
DIDN'T YOU HEAR AARON?
IS HE OKAY?
NO, HE'S OKAY, HE'S OKAY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I JUST...
I JUST FEEL A LITTLE BIT OFF.
I DIDN'T SLEEP WELL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DIDN'T HEAR HIM CRYING.
WELL, MAYBE YOU'RE COMING DOWN
WITH SOMETHING.
BUT WHY DON'T YOU LET ME
TAKE AARON,
AND YOU GET SOME MORE REST?
YEAH. DO YOU MIND?
ABSOLUTELY. HEY.
(moans)
I WON'T SLEEP... LONG.
(Juliet) I GUESS IT'S NO USE
ASKING THEM TO WAIT UP, HUH?
THEY'LL COME AROUND.
JUST GIVE THEM SOME TIME.
MY PEOPLE KEPT SAYID CHAINED
TO A SWING SET FOR THREE DAYS.
THEN I DRAGGED KATE
INTO THE JUNGLE,
HANDCUFFED MYSELF TO HER
AND LIED ABOUT IT.
HOW MUCH TIME
DO YOU THINK THEY NEED?
WE'LL BE BACK TO OUR BEACH
A COUPLE HOURS.
THEY'LL PROBABLY
BE OVER IT BY THEN.
YOU NERVOUS?
HELL, YES.
I KNOW THAT, UH, SIX MONTHS
SOUNDS LIKE AN ETERNITY,
BUT YOU'RE
GONNA BE AMAZED
AT HOW TIME FLIES
ONCE YOU'RE THERE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO FIND OUT
WHERE "THERE" IS.
(Ethan) DR. BURKE,
WANNA HAVE A SEAT?
I'D LIKE TO TAKE
SOME OF YOUR VITALS,
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU.
D@G@, SURE.
EVERYONE AT THE COMPANY
IS REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT YOU COMING DOWN,
DR. BURKE,
AND I THINK YOUR RESEARCH
IS REALLY GONNA HAVE
A MAJOR IMPACT ON US.
WHAT IS THAT?
THAT IS ORANGE JUICE
WITH A CONSIDERABLE AMOUNT
OF TRANQUILIZER MIXED IN.
YOU WANT ME TO DRINK IT?
OH, YES. YOU'RE GONNA WANT TO BE
ASLEEP FOR THE TRIP, DR. BURKE.
IT CAN BE
KIND OF INTENSE.
O-OKAY. I OKS FINE WITH SIGNINGALL OF YO
FINE WITH AGREEING TO NOT TALK
TO ANYONE IN MY LIFE
FOR SIX MONTHS,
FINE WITH THE FACT THAT NO ONE
IN THE MEDICAL COMMUNITY
HAS EVER HEARD
OF MITTELOS BIOSCIENCE--
WHY WERE YOU FINE?
WHAT?
WHY WERE YOU FINE
WITH THOSE THINGS?
IT SEEMS LIKE QUITE A LEAP
FOR A JOB OPPORTUNITY,
AND WE'RE NOT
PAYING YOU THAT MUCH.
I THINK YOU'RE FINE BECAUSE
DEEP DOWN, A PART OF YOU KNOWS
THAT THE PLACE
WE'RE TAKING YOU TO IS SPECIAL.
SPECIAL, HUH?
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING,
JULIET.
YOU TOOK A WOMAN--
YOUR OWN SISTER--
WHOSE REPRODUCTIVE SYSTEM
WAS RAVAGED BY CHEMOTHERAPY,
S STERILE,
AND YOU MADE HER PREGNANT.
YOU CREATED LIFE WHERE
LIFE WASN'T SUPPOSED TO BE.
THAT'S A GIFT, JULIET.
YOU HAVE A GIFT.
NOW DON'T YOU FEEL
YOU'RE MEANT TO DO SOMETHING
SIGNIFICANT WITH IT?
WHERE WE'RE GOING,
YOU CAN DO JUST THAT.
WHERE EXACTLY
ARE WE GOING?
I CAN'T TELL YOU THAT,
BUT WHAT I CAN TELL YOU
IS THAT
YOU'LL SEE THINGS THERE
THAT YOU NEVER IMAGINED.
NOW NO ONE IS FORCING YOU
TO DO ANYTHING,
SO IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND,
WE'RE HAPPY
TO TAKE YOU BACK TO--
UM, YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
HAVE DRUNK THAT SO FAST.
GOOD MORNING.
(gasping)
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY. YOU'LL BE
HOARSE FOR A FEW HOURS,
BUT IT GETS BETTER
ASHE DAY GOES ON.
SORRY I HAD TO STRAP YOU IN,
BUT THE LAST LEG
IS ALWAYS A LITTLE BUMPY.
WATCH YOUR HEAD.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
WE'RE HERE.
(hoarsely) HERE WHERE?
(birds chirping in distance)
HELLO, DR. BURKE.
MY NAME
IS BENJAMIN LINUS.
I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO WORKING WITH YOU.
WATCH YOUR STEP HERE.
HEY, WHOA,
THAT'S TOO MUCH WAR.
IT'S GONNA BE ALL SOGGY.
IT'S OATMEAL, DUDE.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE SOGGY.
WELL, IF IT AIN'T
THREE MEN AND A BABY.
I COUNTED HUGO TWICE.
OH, WHAT?
COME ON. I USED YOUR NAME.
HEY...
DOES ANYBODY KNOW
WHERE THERE'S ANY ASPIRIN?
CLAIRE,
YOU DON'T LOOK SO GOOD.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
YOU'RE MEANT TO BE IN BED.
YEAH, NO, I KNOW.
I JUST... MY HEAD IS POUNDING.
I GOT YOU COVERED.
TWO ASPIRIN COMING RIGHT UP.
THANK YOU.
(woman)
CAN YOU GIVE ME A HAND?
(man) YEAH. I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
(under breath)
SON OF A BITCH.
JACK. IT'S JACK!
(woman) COME ON! COME ON!
IT'S JACK!
IT'S JACK.
(Sun) SAYID!
HURLEY!
DOC.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY.
WHAT THE HELL
IS SHE DOING HERE?
HEY.
SO...
YOU'RE, LIKE,
ONE OF THEM, HUH?
I'M JULIET.
I DON'T REMEMBER YOU
FROM THE DOCK...
WHERE YOU PUT
BAGS ON OUR HEADS...
AFTER YOU SHOCKED US.
I HAD THE DAY OFF.
SO I HEAR
YOU'RE A DOCTOR.
I'M REALLY
MORE OF A RESEARCHER.
UH-HUH.
THEY SEND YOU OVER HERE
TO KEEP AN EYE ON ME?
OKAY.
THE LAST ONE OF YOU GUYS
THAT CAME OVER HERE--ETHAN...
HE KIDNAPPED CLAIRE,
AND CHARLIE GOT UPSET.
WE BURIED HIM OVER THERE.
(man)
GO AHEAD AND DISCONNECT.
SHE'S GONE, JULIET.
SHE'S DEAD.
IT'S OKAY. YOU TRIED.
(man) I'LL GET THE TRAY.
(woman) DISASSEMBLE.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD
AND TAKE OFF?
I'LL TALK TO BEN.
(waves crashing loudly)
IT WAS SABINE'S OICE
TO GET PREGNANT.
SHE KNEW
SHE WAS TAKING A RISK.
I THINK IT HAPPENS
AT CONCEPTION,
AND IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO
ABOUT IT,
AT LEAST NOT HERE.
I'M NOT SURE I UNDERSTAND.
THE ONLY WAY TO SEE
IF I'M RIGHT
IS TO TAKE A WOMAN OFF
THE ISLAND, BACK TO MIAMI.
NO. YOU'RE NOT TAKING
ANYBODY OFF THE ISLAND.
IN THAT CASE,
THERE'S THING MORE I CAN DO.
I KNOW YOU PUT
A LOT OFAITH IN ME, BEN,
AND I'M SORRY
I COULDN'T HELP YOU.
MY SISTER'S GIVING BIRTH
IN THREE MONTHS...
AND I HAVEN'T EVEN
BEEN ABLE TO CALL HER.
IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO GO HOME.
YOUR SISTER WON'T BE GIVING
BIRTH IN THREE MONTHS, JULIET.
SHE'LL BE DEAD BEFORE THEN.
HER CANCER'S BACK.
WHERE DID YOU GET THIS?
MIKHAIL. I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU SOONER.
I JUST DIDN'T SEE
WHAT GOOD IT WOULD DO--
WHAT GOOD IT WOULD DO?!
COULD HAVE GONE HOME!
I COULD HAVE BEEN WITH HER!
YOU STILL CAN.
YOU CAN GO HOME, JULIET,
BE WITH HER IN HER FINAL DAYS,
OR YOU CAN STAY HERE
AND HELP ME WITH OUR PROBLEM.
WHY WOULD I STAY?
BECAUSE IF YOU DO, I WILL CURE
YOUR SISTER'S CANCER.
I'M SUPPOSED
TO TAKE THAT ON FAITH?
YOU'VE BEEHERE
FOR SIX MONTHS.
YOU'VE DONE EXTENSIVE WORKUPS
ON ALL OF US.
HAVE YOU SEEN
EVEN A TRACE OF CANCER?
THAT'S HERE,
AND BEING THAT YOU WON'T
LET ME BRING MY SISTER HERE,
I'M GONNA NEED MORE--
JACOB SAID HE WOULD
TAKE CARE OF IT HIMSELF.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
YOU DON'T HAVE FAITH IN HIM.
EVERY WOMAN ON THIS ISLAND
NEEDS YOU.
IF YOU CHOOSE TO STAY,
I PROMISE YOU,
WE WILL SAVE
RACHEL'S LIFE.
TRUST HER?
SHE'S ONE OF THEM.
NOT ANYMORE.
THEY LEFT HER BEHIND.
OH, YEAH? WHERE'D THEY GO?
I TOLD YOU. I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE WE BETTER ASK HER.
(Jack) SHE DOESN'T KNOW EITHER.
HERE'S A WACKY IDEA. LET'S SIC
OUR RESIDENT IRAQI ON HER,
LET HIM DO WHAT HE DOES,
THEN SEE WHAT SHE SAYS.
NO. I DON'T DO THAT ANYMORE.
WELL,
AIN'T THAT CONVENIENT?
BUT I DON'T TRUST HER, JACK.
IF SHE'S SO INNOCENT...
HEY.
WHY WON'T SHE ANSWER
OUR QUESTIONS?
JUST GIVE HER SOME TIME.
SHE'S AFRAID.
HOW MUCH TIME?
(Jack) LOOK, THE FACT THAT
I TRUST HER SHOULD BE ENOUGH.
IT'S NOT.
WHERE DID LOCKE GO?
HE WENT WITH THEM, RIGHT AFTER
HE DESTROYED THE SUB--
THE SUB THAT WAS GONNA TAKE ME
OFF THIS ISLAND.
WHAT?
THEY WERE GONNA LET YOU GO?
YEAH.
SAID WHO?
BEN.
BEN...
WHOSE LIFE YOU SAVED.
SAWYER, LAY OFF.
SHOULDA LET
THAT BUG-EYED BASTARD DIE.
HE DID IT FOR US.
SOUNDS LIKE
HE DID IT FOR HIM.
JAMES.
IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU WANNA ASK ME, SAWYER?
YEAH, JACK. I WANNA ASK YOU
WHY YOU'RE FIGHTING
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US
AND STICKING UP FOR ONE OF THEM?
LOOK, I SPENT EVERY MOMENT
OVER THERE TRYING TO FIND...
CLAIRE?
A WAY OFF THIS ISLAND.
I WAS TRYING TO HELP ALL OF US.
I WAS TRYING TO GET US RESCUED.
CLAIRE? JACK!
SOMETHING'S WRONG WITH CLAIRE!
(wan) OH, MY GOSH.
CLAIRE?
(man) IS SHE OKAY?
GRAB HER, GRAB HER.
LET'S GET HER UP.
CLAIRE? CLAIRE!
HOW LONG HAS SHE
BEEN LIKE THIS?
UH, SHE STARTED
FEELING BAD THIS MORNING.
BEFORE WE GOT BACK, WAS SHE
SHOWING ANY SYMPTOMS AT ALL?
NO, SHE WAS FINE.
WHAT ABOUT WATER? HAS SHE
BEEN DRINKING ENOUGH WATER?
I THINK SO, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, KEEP THAT HEAD UP.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
(speaking Korean)
HE SAID,
"WHAT DO YOU CARE?"
KATE! I NEED YOUR HELP.
I NEED YOU
TO GO AND GET JACK.
WELL, HE'S BUSY RIGHT NOW.
PLEASE,
I HAVE TO TALK TO HIM.
YOU WANNA TELL ME
WHY YOU NEED JACK?
BECAUSE I THINK I KNOW
WHAT'S WRONG WITH CLAIRE.
WHY?
BECAUSE I DID ITO HER.
GIVING YOU A BAD FEELING
IN YOUR STOMACH?
YEAH, ME, TOO.
CLAIRE'S IMMUNE SYSTEM
IS TURNING ON HER.
SHE'S HAVING
A LATENT REACTION
TO A MEDICATION
IN HER BLOODSTREAM.
WHAT MEDICATION?
IT WAS DESIGNED
TO KEEP HER ALIVE
DURING THE LATE STAGES
OF HER PREGNANCY.
DESIGNED BY WHO?
BY ME.
FOR SOME REASON THE WOMEN HERE
CAN'T HAVE BABIES.
THE MOER'S BODY
TURNS ON THE PREGNANCY,
TREATS IT
AS A FOREIGN INVADER.
I SAW IT HAPPEN
OVER AND OVER.
EVERY PREGNANT WOMAN
ON THIS ISLAND DIED...
THAT IS, EVERY PREGNANT WOMAN
UNTIL CLAIRE.
WHAT DID YOU DO TO HER?
ONE OF OUR PEOPLE
INFILTRATED YOUR CAMP
AND BEGAN TAKING
BLOOD SAMPLES
RIGHT AFTER
YOUR PLANE CRASHED.
AAH!
SHH.
ETHAN.
EVEN THOUGH CLAIRE DIDN'T
CONCEIVE ON THIS ISLAND,
WE FOUND THAT
HER SYMPTOMS WERE CONSISTENT
WITH PREVIOUS MOTHERS,
SO WE TRIED TO SAVE HER LIFE.
BY KIDNAPPING HER?
NO, THAT WASN'T
SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
SHE WAS OUR CONTROL CASE.
I HAD DEVELOPED A SERUM
THAT I THOUGHT WOULD REVERSE
WHAT WAS HAPPENING TO HER.
ETHAN WAS ADMINISTERING
THE INJECTIONS,
BUT THEN YOU FOUND OUT
THAT HE WASN'T ON THE PLANE.
THE CENSUS--
I INTERVIEWED EVERYONE.
ONE OF THEM
ISN'T IN THE MANIFEST.
HE WASN'T ON THEPLANE.
SO... HE IMPROVISED.
(Ethan) HELLO THERE.
(Juliet)
HE KIDNAPPED HER ON HIS OWN.
THAT WAS NEVER THE PLAN.
(Claire screams)
LOOK,
I KNOW HOW THIS SOUNDS,
BUT WITHOUT THOSE INJECTIONS,
CLAIRE WOULD HAVE DIED.
THOUT THE SERUM, SHE'S GOING
INTO A FORM OF WITHDRAWAL,
AND IF I DON'T
TRT HER QUICKLY,
HER IMMUNE SYSTEM
COULD SHUT DOWN ENTIRELY.
JACK, I CAN FIX THIS.
I JUST NEED THE SERUM.
ETHAN KEPT A STASH
OF MEDICAL SUPPLIES
NEAR THE CAVES
WHERE YOU USED TO LIVE.
IF I GO RIGHT NOW,
I CAN BE BACK
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
DO IT.
GET MOVING.
(opera music playing)
(man) WHERE ARE YOU?
IN BED... WITH YOU.
UH-HUH.
EN WHERE WERE YOU?
I WAS JUST REALIZING...
THAT TOMORROW I WILL HAVE BEEN
ON THIS ISLAND FOR THREE YEARS.
HMM. MWAH.
WELL... THEN I BETTER
BAKE A CAKE.
HMM.
(knock on door)
STAY HERE.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
KARL DEVELOPED
SOME X-RAYS FOR ME.
WHAT'S WRONG?
(woman)
...TAKE THE LADDER?
(man) YEAH!
MORNING, JULIET.
(man) I'LL BRING IT BACK!
(woman) DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
HI.
CAN I COME IN?
OF COURSE.
I WAS
JUST FINISHING "CARRIE."
I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHY YOU PICKED IT,
BUT, BOY, IS IT DEPRESSING.
YOU HAVE A TUMOR.
WHAT?
WHEN YOU TOLD ME
ABOUT YOUR BACK PAIN,
I SAID THAT I WOULD
TAKE SOME X-RAYS TO SEE
IF IT WAS A SMALL FRACTURE
OR A HERNIATED DISC,
BUT THAT'S NOT YOUR PROBLEM.
YOUR PROBLEM IS A LARGE TUMOR
SURROUNDING YOUR L4 VERTEBRA.
YOU'RE SURPRISED.
WELL, YOU'VE JUST TOLD ME
THAT I HAVE CANCER, JULIET.
OF COURSE I'M SURPRISED.
NO, I TOLD YOU
THAT YOU HAD A TUMOR.
WHY ARE YOU SCARED?
I'M NOT SCARED.
WHY ARE YOU SCARED, BEN?
YOU SAID NO ONE ON THIS ISLAND
EVER HAD CANCER.
YOU TOLD ME AT--
I KNOW WHAT
I TOLD YOU, JULIET.
YOU TOLD ME YOU COULD FIX IT.
YOU SAID THAT.
YOU SAID THAT YOU CURED
MY SISTER. YOU LIED TO ME.
NO, I DID NOT LIE TO YOU.
IF YOU CAN CURE CANCER, BEN,
THEN WHY DO YOU HAVE IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
(glass shatters)
I WANNA TALK TO HER.
I WANNA TALK TO RACHEL.
I WANNA TALK TO HER NOW!
THAT'S NOT
GONNA HAPPEN, JULIET,
BUT I CAN PROMISE YOU
THAT RACHEL IS FINE.
YOU NEVER CURED HER!
I DID!
YOU'RE A LIAR!
NO, JULIET--
YOU LIED TO ME!
I TOLD YOU THE TRUTH!
I GAVE YOU MY WORD.
PLEASE... I WANNA GO HOME.
I WANNA GO HOME, BEN.
PLEASE.
CAN'T YOU PLEASE
JUST LET ME GO HOME?
NO.
(Sayid)
STEP AWAY FROM THE CASE!
LISTEN TO ME, SAYID--
STEP BACK.
IT'S FULL OF MEDICAL SUPPLIES.
THEY'RE FOR CLAIRE.
JACK KNOWS ALL ABOUT IT.
WELL, JACK AIN'T HERE
RIGHT NOW, IS HE?
I'TELLING YOU THE TRUTH.
YOU SAID EARLIER IF YOU TOLD ME
EVERYTHING YOU KNEW,
I'D KILL YOU.
I'M GOING TO TEST THE VALIDITY
OF THAT STATEMENT.
HE MEANS, "TALK."
WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
WE CLEARED OUR SCHEDULES.
WE GOT ALL THE TIME
IN THE WORLD.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S INTERESTING...
THAT YOU TWO ARE NOW
THE CAMP'S MOR POLICE.
I'M CURIOUS, SAYID.
HOW LONG WAS IT
BEFORE YOU TOLD
EVERYONE ON THAT BEACH
EXACTLY HOW MANY PEOPLE
YOU'VE TORTURED IN YOUR LIFE?
DO THEY KNOW ABOUT BASRA?
AND I'M SURE
THE FIRST THING YOU DID
WHEN YOU GOT HERE, JAMES,
WAS TO GATHER EVERYONE
IN A CIRCLE
AND TELL THEM ABOUT THE MAN
YOU SHOT IN COLD BLOOD
THE NIGHT BEFORE
YOU GOT ON THE PLANE.
SO WHY DON'T
WE JUST SKIP THE PART
WHERE YOU TWO
PRETEND TO BE RIGHTEOUS?
I'M TAKING THAT MEDICATION
BACK TO AIRE,
AND YOU'RE GONNA LET ME,
BECAUSE IF SHE DOESN'T GET IT,
SHE'S GONNA DIE.
AND THE LAST THING
THAT EITHER OF YOU NEED
RIGHT NOW...
IS MORE BLOOD ON YOUR HANDS.
GOODWIN! ETHAN, THERE Y
ACTUALLY BE SURVIVORS,
AND YOU'RE ONE OF 'EM--
A PASSENGER. YOU'RE IN SHOCK.
LISTEN. LEARN.
DON'T GET INVOLVED.
I WANT LISTS
IN THREE DAYS. GO.
SO I GUESS I'M OUT
OF THE BOOK CLUB.
JULIET. JULIET.
I WAS LOOKING FOR YOU
THIS MORNING.
YOU AND I NEED TO TALK.
NOW?
WE HAVE SOME TIME.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
TAKE A WALK WITH ME.
MIKHAIL, WE'RE HERE.
HE NEVER
HAS HIS WALKIE ON.
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
SOMETHING I NEED TO SHOW YOU.
MIKHAIL?!
IT'S B!
I'M HERE WITH JULIET!
WE'RE APPROACHING THE HOUSE!
DON'T SHOOT US.
(Mikhail)
WELL, HURRY UP, THEN!
DID YOU SEE IT?
A PLANE FELL OUT
OF THE SKY, MIKHAIL.
OF COURSE WE SAW IT.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE SO FAR?
OCEANIC FLIGHT 815--
LEFT SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA,
HEADED FOR LOS ANGELES,
324 PEOPLE ON BOARD,
INCLUDING THE FLIGHT CREW.
I WANT DETAILED FILES
ON EVERY SINGLE PASSENGER.
ALREADY WORKING ON IT.
CAN WE UPLINK TO RICHARD
IN ACADIA PARK, PLEASE?
YESTERDAY
YOU CALLED ME A LIAR.
I WAS HURT BY THAT.
HELLO, RICHARD.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
NOTICE TODAY'S DATE.
THIS IS LIVE.
OKAY, RICHARD.
OH, MY GOD.
OH!
(Ben) A LITTLE OVER
TWYEARS AGO,
TO EVERYONE'S SURPRISE,
RACHEL'S CANCER WENT
INTO COMPLETE REMISSION.
SHORTLY AFTER, SHE GAVE BIRTH
TO A HEALTHY BABY BOY.
HIS NAME IS JULIAN.
OKAY, THANK YOU, RICHARD.
YOU'LL WANT TO GET BACK HERE
AS SOON AS YOU CAN.
????
OH, GOD! NO, NO!
NO! (sobbing)
I'M NOT A LIAR, JULIET.
I WANNA GO HOME.
THAT'S NOT OUR AGREEMENT.
YOU NEED TO STAY HERE
UNTIL YOUR WORK IS FINISHED.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THE MOTHERS KEEP DYING.
EN WE'LL FIND
MORE MOTHERS.
WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE THERE'S EVEN ONE
ON THAT PLANE.
WAIT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SHE'S NOT TOUCHING CLAIRE. SHE'S
THE ONE WHO DID THIS TO HER.
SHE CAN HELP HER, CHARLIE.
SAYS WHO? HER?
HOW CAN YOU EVEN TRUST HER?
????
DO YOU TRUST ME?
YEAH.
JUST GIVE US
A COUPLE MINUTES HERE, OKAY?
HOW LONG BEFORE
THIS TAKES EFFECT?
WE SHOULSEE RESULTS
IN A FEW HOURS.
JULIET...
IF THIS DOESN'T WORK,
IF SOMETHING
HAPPENS TO HER...
I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO PROTECT YOU ANYMORE.
YOU'LL BE ON YOUR OWN.
I'M ALREADY
ON MY OWN, JACK.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I'VE GOT A TARP,
COUPLE OF BLANKETS,
AIRLINE PILLOWS.
IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT... IT'LL GET YOU STARTED.
CLAIRE'S AWAKE.
THERE'S A LEAN-TO THAT
WE'VE BEEN USING FOR SHADE,
AND EVERYONE SAYS
THAT IT'D BE ALL RIGHT
IF YOU SET UP CAMP THERE
FOR NOW.
THANK YOU.
THEY'RE GOOD PEOPLE,
AND THEY'RE WILLING TO GIVE YOU
THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT.
BUT EVENTUALLY THEY'RE GONNA
NEED SOME ANSWERS.
WHY DON'T YOU?
YOU KEEP TALKING
ABOUT THEM.
WHY DON'T I EVER HAVE
TO EXPLAIN MYSELF TO YOU?
YOU WERE THERE.
YOU WERE STANDING
RIGHT NEXT TO ME
WHEN THAT SUBMARINE
EXPLODED...
AND IN THAT MOMENT,
I SAW IT IN YOUR EYES.
YOU WANNA
GET OFF THIS ISLAND
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE
IN THE WORLD.
THAT MAKES YOU ONE OF US.
(Ben)
LET'S GO OVER IT AGAIN.
(Juliet) I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
LET'S GO OVER IT AGAIN,
JUST TO BE SURE.
I DRAG AUSTEN
OUT INTO THE JUNGLE,
HANDCUFF MYSELF TO HER,
THEN TELL HER I WAS GASSED
JUST LIKE SHE WAS.
AND IF SHE CATCHES YOU
IN THE LIE?
I'LL ADMIT TO IT,
TELL HER IT WAS THE ONS  WAY
TO EARN HER TRUST.
GOOD. WHAT THEN?
THEY'LL KE ME
BACK TO THE BEACH.
I KNOW YOU WANT ME
TO GO THERE,
BUT AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE DONE TO THEM,
IT'S GOING TO BE A PROBLEM.
WE'VE ACTIVATED
THE IMPLANT IN CLAIRE.
SHE SHOULD BE SYMPTOMATIC
WITHIN THE NEXT 48 HOURS.
BY THE TIME
YOU GET TO THAT CAMP,
YOU'LL HAVE
A NICE BIG CRISIS TO SOLVE.
I'LL NEED SUPPLIES.
PRYCE IS ALREADY ON HIS WAY.
HE'LL HIDE THE CASE
AT ETHAN'S OLD DROP POINT.
TELL JACK
THAT YOU CAN SAVE HER.
HE TRUSTS YOU.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M FINE.
SEE YOU IN A WEEK.
welcome to www.1000fr.com