Previously on Lost:
Desmond said I was gonna die.
He told me he has
these flashes, visions.
When I saw the lightning hit the roof,
you were electrocuted.
When you heard Claire was in the water,
you drowned.
I dove in so you never went in!
No matter what I try to do,
you're going to die, Charlie.
There's a woman in Hurley's tent who
parachuted onto the island yesterday.
The boat she took off from
is 80 miles off the coast
and that if she can find a way
to contact it, we'll all be rescued.
- Why didn't anyone tell me this?
- They don't trust you.
- Kwon is pregnant.
- Where'd you get that?
You're in a position
to be asking us questions?
I told Jack what they were making me do.
Why didn't you tell us?
Because I hadn't decided
what to do about it yet.
Anyone want to guess
as to what Jack's gonna be showing us
out in the middle of nowhere?
I don't know... stuff?
Probably secret stuff.
Why does everything
have to be a secret?
How about some openness for a change?
- We kept the parachute lady secret.
- That's different.
Different how?
Because we weren't out there
playing football with them.
- What?
- Nothing.
Wait. You had one of your flashes
again, didn't you?
No, Charlie. I didn't.
We're here.
A couple of nights ago, Juliet
came to me and she told me everything.
Ben sent her here to find out
which of our women were pregnant.
You guys were doing tests on us?
No. But that's what he wanted me to do.
I've been leaving tapes
at the medical station.
You all heard what he said.
They're coming tomorrow.
Sun, I'm sorry
that I lied to you.
While I appreciate your honesty, Jack,
it doesn't explain
why you brought us out here.
Danielle!
Show them.
When Juliet told me they were coming,
the first thing I thought was,
"Where the hell
are we gonna hide this time?"
But hiding is pointless.
They're just gonna keep coming back.
So I went out and I found some help.
The past few days, she's been bringing
dynamite back from the Black Rock.
For the very first time,
we know exactly what they want,
when they're coming to get it,
and they have no idea
that we're gonna be waiting for them.
So Juliet's gonna mark the tents with
white rocks, just like she was told to.
But there's not gonna be
any pregnant women inside.
There's gonna be plenty
of what we just used on that tree.
So tomorrow night... we stop hiding.
We stop running.
We stop living in fear of them.
Because when they show up...
...we're gonna blow them all to hell.
Bloody hell! Why are we even doing this?
- Chin up, mate. We're headlining.
- Headlining?
We're playing Clitheroe,
the arse end of nowhere.
A gig's a gig.
We're building our fan base.
Will our fan base
pay for a new sodding tire?
Only if we show up.
So let's just get on with it, shall we?
You know what, Liam?
You get on with it. I quit.
You're giving up?
There's nothing to give up on!
We're broke!
The album's not selling!
We're a joke.
Hey! Shut it!
Listen!
That's us.
We're on the radio.
- That we are.
- On the bloody radio!
Oh, yeah!
- Hey!
- Oh! I told ya, baby brother.
We're gonna be bloody rock stars!
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Who are you people
about to go to war with?
That's a long story.
Want to ask me something else?
- You having a laugh?
- No, of course not.
I'd never disrespect a fellow Mancunian.
- You're from Manchester, then?
- I am.
My band got its start
at the Night and Day bar
on Oldham Street.
- What band?
- We were called Drive Shaft.
- Yeah, yeah. I know you.
- We had our moment in the sun.
No, not that. The crash.
You're the dead rock star.
They made a big deal out of you
when they found the plane.
- Huge memorial service, new album...
- There's a new album?
Yeah. God, it was everywhere.
A greatest hits thing.
Hey, look on the bright side.
You're not really dead, right?
Yeah, right.
We need more wire so that we can trigger
these from a safe distance.
I can get people to start stripping
the plane wreckage.
We should be able to finish rigging
these tents in the next 24 hours.
We'll be ready by tomorrow night.
- We need to talk about Naomi's phone.
- Not now.
If you are angry I doubted you,
I'll make an apology later. But now...
Look, I'm a little bit
busy right now, Sayid.
And I'm trying
to get us off this island, Jack.
I can't transmit using this phone
because Danielle's distress signal
is overriding the frequency.
If you tell me where the radio tower is,
I can switch off your message
and call for help.
My signal has been playing for the last
16 years and nobody has heard it.
- What makes you think you'll have luck?
- Naomi's boat is 80 miles offshore.
I know if we eliminate
Danielle's signal, they'll hear us.
No, they won't.
And why is that?
- We're jamming it.
- What?
Ben is using one of the Dharma Stations
to block all of the signals
off of the island except ours.
- What station?
- They call it the Looking Glass.
- The Looking Glass?
- Yes, it's underwater.
I have no idea where it is.
I believe I do.
Look, I know Jack thinks it's best,
but what if they're coming
for him again?
Claire, listen to me.
I'm going to protect you.
I'm going to protect Aaron.
I promise.
Everything is going to be fine.
Sorry.
Charlie, can you give me
a hand with something?
Yeah, Desmond, of course.
So, you ready to tell me
what you saw this morning?
Aye.
Right. So how does it happen this time?
Come on, Des.
You can tell me. I can take it.
What I saw, Charlie, was...
...Claire and her baby
getting into a helicopter...
...a helicopter that...
that lifts off, leaves this island.
- Are you sure?
- Aye.
Rescue helicopter? On this beach?
This island? That's what you saw?
We're getting bloody rescued?
I thought you were gonna tell me
I was going to die again!
You are, Charlie.
Wait. What?
If you don't, none if it will happen.
There won't be any rescue.
I'm sorry, brother.
But this time...
This time you have to die.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on, Charlie.
Jump in. I'm gonna catch ya, boy.
No. You're just gonna back away.
Don't be daft. Jump in.
- No!
- I promise. I'm gonna catch ya!
No, he won't!
Zip it, you!
Don't listen to your brother.
Just jump on in.
There's nothing
to be afraid of, Charlie.
I'll catch ya. I promise.
I did it!
- You got it!
- I did it!
You're swimming, Charlie!
You're swimming.
What're you writing?
Nothing.
All right, tell me.
You sure you want to know?
- It might be easier if you just...
- Yeah. I want to know.
You're inside a hatch. It's...
...a room full of equipment.
There's a blinking yellow light
above a switch.
You flick the switch.
The light goes off.
And then you drown.
When?
I don't know.
You're sure you saw Claire and Aaron
get on that helicopter?
Aye.
So...
...before I... drown,
I just have to flick the switch?
That's right.
Where is it then?
This is the Looking Glass.
It's an underwater Dharma station.
Please, can you tell me anything
you might know about this place?
I've never been down there.
I don't know anyone who has.
Why not?
There was some accident. Ben told us
that the station was completely flooded.
- If it's flooded how does it work?
- How it still works is irrelevant.
The question is
how do we get it to stop working,
so we can use the satellite phone.
The diagram shows that the Looking Glass
is connected to the island by a cable.
I feel sure that this is
the very same cable down the beach
which runs into the ocean.
If we follow the cable,
it should lead us to the station.
- So how're we gonna get in?
- We swim in.
There's a moon pool,
a room with an open floor
at the base of the station,
big enough for a submarine to dock.
Even if the station's flooded,
I think I'll be able to find
the relay switch and disable it.
What about swimming back out?
No.
I'm not letting you go on some
suicide mission just to flip the switch.
Someone has to do it,
or we'll never leave this island.
I'll do it.
Swim down, turn off that switch,
swim back up. Piece of cake.
You don't know what we're talking about.
I was junior swim champion.
I can hold my breath for four minutes.
I know exactly
what you're talking about, Jack.
No. And there's no reason
to do this now.
We're gonna focus on the Others,
- then deal with this.
- Wait.
We have a chance
to signal for a rescue.
For 90 days, I've been asked
to make decisions for this camp.
There you go. I just made one.
Rose, that's a sailor's hitch.
It's not gonna hold.
- You wanna do a sheet bend like mine.
- Now you're a knot expert?
Well, trust me, it's...
How did you do that?
Watch and learn, dear, watch and learn.
Hey! Look, there! Look!
- Get off him! It's OK!
- What?! He's one of them!
I know! I know, it's OK.
He was in the cage next to me!
I know this guy!
What the hell are you doing here, Karl?
They're... coming. My people...
Sorry you came all this way,
but we already know.
Then why are you still here?
When your people
show up here tomorrow, we're ready.
Tomorrow? No!
No, they're coming tonight!
They're coming right now!
Hey!
- When'd you get back?
- Just now.
Where's Locke?
Here's your gun back.
- Ben, what's going on?
- Where's Ryan?
- He's at his tent. Are you alone?
- It's time to get them.
- Wait a minute. But you said tomorrow.
- Jacob wants it to happen now.
What happened out there?
Did John see?
John had an accident.
- Ryan!
- Yes, sir.
If you leave now, how long
will it take you to reach their camp?
If I take my ten best
we can hit them by nightfall.
- Then you better get going.
- No, Ben. Moving up the schedule...
Juliet may not be ready. What if...
Then we'll take all their women.
And we'll sort out
the ones we need later.
And the men?
If any of them are stupid enough
to get in your way, kill them.
All right.
Karl!
It's me.
- I thought you were bringing rabbit.
- You have to go. Now.
What? Did he find out I was out here?
No. He's sending Pryce
to their beach camp right now.
- You warn them!
- Warn them?
- Go now!
- They were gonna take pregnant women.
Take the outrigger, you'll get there
a few hours before them.
- Wait, Alex.
- He's gonna kill them, Karl!
Austen and Ford saved your life.
You owe them.
You'd better take this.
If I get caught,
your father's gonna kill me.
Is he my father?
Now, go.
- Is that everything?
- Yeah.
Do you trust him?
You don't trust me? What about her?
She's a spy.
She's supposed to mark the tents
of the pregnant women with white rocks.
They know, Karl. But, thanks.
- So what're we gonna do?
- We have to leave now, hide.
Where? It's their island.
If they wanna kill us, they'll find us.
Sun's gonna go down in a few hours.
We have enough wire yet?
Not even close.
We gotta figure out a way
to set the dynamite off.
- We can shoot.
- We don't have enough guns.
- He said that ten of them are coming.
- The tents.
We camouflage the dynamite
next to the tents,
target it from our positions
at the tree line.
Juliet marked three tents.
That means we need three guns.
Here. You can have mine, too.
I'll be your third.
We'll take your gun,
but you're not staying here.
You're gonna lead everyone
to the radio tower.
Radio tower?
We can't risk losing the chance
to contact with Naomi's boat.
So everything has to happen
at the same time.
Charlie, you still up for a swim?
Yeah, I believe I am.
I'll go with him.
OK. We better get to it.
It's here, baby brother!
Christmas is here!
Are these the birds from row two?
Well done, mate.
Well, as you have spent another year
as the only drug-free rock star
in the world,
I am going to share
a little known fact with you.
Father Christmas lives
just down the street from here.
- Father Christmas lives in Helsinki?
- Indeed he does.
In case you haven't noticed,
baby brother,
Finland is the bloody North Pole.
Therefore, a very special gift for you
this year.
Liam, no. Mum gave you that.
You're the first born.
It was her father's
and his father before that...
And it's a family heirloom,
and that's why we named the band
after Dexter bloody Stratton. I know.
But Charlie, let's be honest.
We both know I'm a sodding mess.
But you, you're different.
You're gonna get married,
have a family, a baby.
- I'll be lucky if I hit 30.
- Don't say that, Li.
The ring has to stay
in the family, Charlie.
So please, take it.
Mum would've wanted it this way.
Pass it on to your little one someday.
I need to know it's safe.
I'll hold on to it.
But I won't take it.
Hey, it fits. Look at that.
Happy Christmas, baby brother.
You need some help?
Why didn't you tell me
you were going to do this?
I didn't want you to worry.
Well, it's dangerous, isn't it,
swimming into some underwater station?
It's what needs to be done
to get us all rescued.
I'll be fine, Claire.
You gotta promise me something.
While I'm gone...
...don't worry about me.
OK.
I'll take him.
Thanks.
Hey...
All right, turnip head.
You take care of your mum,
while I'm away, OK?
I love you.
See you soon.
Be careful, Charlie. OK?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, guys.
Thanks, man.
Help! Help me!
Help! Please! Please!
- You, stop!
- Hey!
Get the hell away from her!
What're you doing? Leave her alone!
You OK, miss?
Yes. I think so, yes.
Here you go.
Pardon me while I have a heart attack.
Last time I was in a fight,
I was eight years old.
And I lost.
Well, that makes you
even more of a hero, doesn't it?
- I just did what anyone would do.
- Three people walked by the alley.
- What?
- They saw me...
...but they just kept on going.
You are a hero, sir.
And don't let anyone
ever tell you differently.
- What's that?
- It's weight belt.
It should bring you down
quicker than swimming.
Well, every second counts.
So I just take it off when I hit bottom,
swim up through the moon pool
into the station,
swim into whichever room has
the yellow blinking switch,
flip it.
Nothing to it.
So how long can you really
hold your breath for?
Does it matter?
- You want me to hit another one?
- No. You've made your point.
Bernard, this is not pheasant hunting
in Montgomery.
- I know what I'm doing.
- Pheasants don't shoot back.
Nothing's gonna happen to me, Rose.
I just have to shoot a tent.
- And I'll be right behind you.
- Then I'm staying, too.
No, you're not, Rose.
Everyone's gathering down
at the south end of the beach.
- No one's staying but the shooters.
- Says who?
You wanna give me your word that
nothing's gonna happen to my husband?
Then I'll go.
If we don't kill everyone
who shows up here in about an hour,
it's not gonna matter where Bernard is.
I like you better since you got back,
Jack. You're almost an optimist.
Come on.
If you're gonna be hiding in the bushes,
let's get you into something dark.
You better get going.
Rousseau says it's a day's walk
up to the radio tower.
I'm not taking them to the tower,
you are.
- Excuse me?
- You're not staying behind.
- This was my idea.
- I'm capable of executing it.
- I owe them!
- What are you more concerned with?
Killing the Others
or getting our people off this island?
This afternoon
you said you were our leader.
It's time for you to act like one.
Lead them to the radio tower, Jack.
And then take us all home.
Dudes! Wait!
I heard.
I heard what you're doing.
I wanna come with.
Everyone, they're all goin'
to the radio tower,
and I'm sick of trekking,
and, you know, explosions.
I think I can help you guys out.
I'm a really good paddler.
You can't go, Hurley.
Why not?
Because...
...you're too big.
You won't fit in the boat.
That's uncool, man.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Dude. It's fine. I don't even
wanna go on your stupid boat.
I'll catch up with you later.
- Just remember I love you, man.
- Yeah, whatever. I love you, too.
You got water in there? Good. Good.
How about you? Lot of water? Good.
Hey.
- Hey.
- So here we go again.
Here we go again.
- The tents are all marked. We're set.
- Sayid find a third shooter?
Ready, Claire?
Need a hand with the little guy?
No thanks, I'm OK.
How's my little sweetheart?
We're just gonna go for a little walk,
so hold on to Mum, OK?
This is it.
Ready?
Hiya.
Do you want a blanket?
Oh, thanks, I've got one.
Well, you're warming for two. Take mine.
Thank you.
So, first plane crash?
- What gave it away?
- You can always spot the newbies.
We're gonna be OK, you know.
Are we?
We're alive, on a beautiful island.
We'll sleep under the stars,
and before you know it, the helicopters
will come and take us all home.
You really think they'll find us?
Well, yeah, why wouldn't they?
Thanks.
- I'm Charlie.
- I'm Claire.
- Nice to meet you, Charlie.
- It's nice to meet you.
We're here.
I want you to give this
to Claire for me.
What is it?
It's the five best moments of my...
...sorry excuse for a life.
My greatest hits.
You know...
...memories... are all I've got.
You don't have to do this, Charlie.
What?
- I'll go.
- No, your flashes...
Maybe I keep seeing you die
because...
...I'm supposed to take your place.
What about your girl? Penny?
What about your girl?
Besides...
...I might be luckier than you.
Keep your memories to yourself.
I'll take it from here.
I don't know what to say.
Well, you can tell me
where the weight belt is.
Right there behind you.
You and I both know you're not
supposed to take my place, brother.
I'm alive. I'm alive!