Previously on "Lost"
- Is that a helicopter?
- Is that how a helicopter supposed to sound?
Get away from her!
Desmond..
- What's wrong ?
- What's wrong is i'm married.
Right...
You're pregnant...
Good morning, Jack.
Need a hand ?
thank you.
I came by your tent earlier.
Is jin gone ?
Oh... Jin went off with Charlie,
Hurley and Desmond.
Did you need him ?
Actually, i was looking for you.
and uh... see how you were doing.
Your pregnancy
Oh... I'm doing fine.
- I felt tired, but thats normal right ?
- Sure.
- Any morning sickness ?
- Not anymore.
Any bleeding ?
Why are you asking me all these questions, Jack ?
i'm just checking.
Now that i'm back,
i wanna make sure that you are doing ok.
Thank you.
I'm ok.
Great.
.
-Who is she?
- I have no idea.
- She seems to know you,dude.
she just said your name.
I have never seen her before in my life.
She's waking up.
She's trying to talk.
We should get her some water
- Give me a hand.
- yeah.
Estoy muriendo
- What she saying?
- don't know.
Spanish,dude.
What, do you understand her then?
Estuy morriendo.
Estoy murriendo.
- She said she's dying.
- Estoy murriendo.
- Oh my god.
- its a branch!
She must have hit it on the way down.
uh, get her pack.
We haven't got much in the first aid kit.
- See if there's anything we can use in there.
What if this is a rescue ?
what if she came for us.. ? i mean...
- is She gonna be ok, we can't let her..
- then just go and start looking!!
We 'll get  Jack.
Jack.
We have to get her to Jack as soon as possible!
- She could be our way off the island.
- No,if we move her,it'll make it worse.
So we gonna just let her bleed to death ?
No, we need to bring Jack here.
It's an 8-hour walk one way!
Then i will run.
You're out of your mind
It's not safe
Its going to be dark soon,
Who knows who's out in this jungle?
In case you have forgotten,
there are people on this island trying to kill us.
Nobody knows we're here!
Oops.
---www.opensubtitles.org---
transcripted by jenilim
Lost Season 3 epi 18 - D.O.C
How's this ?
that's perfect.
thank you.
what do you think happened to jack?
while he was with the others.
Since he's been back...
he seems different.
He says that he was pretty much a prisoner, and...
the reason why he cooperated...
bcos he thought they would let him off the island.
do you believe him ?
why wouldn't i ?
he came to me.
asking about my pregnancy.
- what would that have anything to do with...
- what if...
what if the others want my baby ?
he's been there alone for over a week.
How do we know he isn't talking with them ?
he's not working with them.
Do you know something, Kate ?
It's Julliet.
she was their doctor. their...their fertility doctor.
studying pregnant women and...
when Claire was sick,
she told me and Jack...
the reasons the others wanted her baby.
was for research.
Sun.
wait, you don't have to do this.
Go away, Kate.
i wanna know about your research.
- Sun.
- what happens to pregnant women?
You're pregnant.
Are you sure ?
how do you know ?
I asked you a question.
Everyone else might be alright with you
washing your clothes and
eating our food. but i want to know whats going on.
I want answers.
What are your people doing ?
Why are you taking children ?
What happens to pregnant women on this island ?
- What happens...
- They die.
They all died.
Sun, come on let's go.
What she saying ?
- Chinese, not korean
Maybe we should just pulled out?.
- No, you'll just make it worse...
Have you forgotten what's at stake here?.
Or is this just another one of your flashes?
Who's getting an arrow in the neck this time?
unless you forget, she said my bloody name!.
she had a photo of me and my girlfriend..
do i understand? i understand
better then the lot of you.
Hey, guys.
Chill...
We wasted enough time already.
Hey,you're not leaving us.
- Just get out of my way,Charlie.
- No!
- Jin!
who are you?
I said,who are you?
He's the guy who shot Sayid.
Kate told us.
He lived out in that station that locke blew up.
- He's an other..
- I thought locke killed that guy with .
with the electro-fence thingy.
You've got five seconds to talk,or I fire this gun,brother.
- That's a flare gun.
- And how do you think it'll feel...
taking a flare to the chest at this range?
As your friend pointed out,
I already died once this week.
Estoy murriendo.
You understand her.
She's speaking italian
She said she's dying. She needs help.
I was a soviet army field medic.
I can offer you my services.
- Wait.What are you doing?
- I'm saving her.
This branch has punctured her lung.
It's filling with blood.
If it is not ventilated soon,she's going to die.
Well,do it.
Help her.
If I fix her,you must let me walk away
as if I never came upon you.
What do you need??
..
be quiet.
don't move
You want me to help you and your baby?
I have answers to your questions,
but you ha to come with me right now.
Just you and me,nobody else
if what you said was true
,that means I'm already dead.,.
Why should I go anywhere with you?
Because there may be hope for you yet
Where are we going?
There's a medical station near here.
They have an ultrasound machine.
Claire and Kate told me
about that place.
It was abandoned.
They found nothing there.
Well,that's because they didn't know where to look.
What are you going to do to me?
I'm gonna look at your baby and
determine the D.O.C
Um,date of conception.
The ultrasound will tell me when you got pregnant,give or take a day.
If you got pregnant off the island,then you and your baby will probably be okay,
but if you got pregnant here...
we'll cross that bridge when we come to it.
When was the last time you and your husband had sex?
I would rather not talk about that.
Look,I know that it's personal,but if I know when,then I can figure--
isn't that what the machine will do?
Yeah.
Then let's keep walking.
.
What else do you know about this woman?
Did she have anything on her besides the flare gun?
Just a book,a fancy radio-phone thingy...
does it work?
Like I'd tell you.
One of you must help.
The rest,clear the way.I need space.
I'll do it.
Wipe away as much of the blood as you can.
need to evacuate the air now!
Hold her steady.
Steady!
Yeah,I-I heard you.
is that... normal?
gauze.
Tape it. Be careful.
The covering needs to be hollow.
The wound needs to breathe.
what did she say?
"Thank you."
She said,"thank you for helping me."
It's right down here.
why are you doing this?
What?
Helping me.
Once upon a time,
I told women that they were pregnant,
and their faces...
it was the best news they ever got in their entire life.
Then I came here.
I've lost...nine patients...
in the last three years.
I'm helping you because I want to tell you
that you and your husband got pregnant before you came here.
I'm helping you because I want to give good news again.
I slept with another man...
Before we got to the island.
Jin and I,we were having...
trouble.We weren't...
and I had a friend.
It was a mistake.
We all make mistakes.
Which way?
will you help me move this forward?
good.
why is this room hidden?
Don't worry about it.
What is this place?
Tell me.
It's where we brought the women to die.
She's fine.
Keep the wound as clean as you can.
She should be better in a day.
A day?
Her lung was punctured.
On this island,the rules are a bit different.
Maybe a day and a half.
I did as I promised.
She will live.
- You can't seriously be considering letting him go. - Just go.
Are you kidding?He's one of them!
So what would you have me do,Charlie?
We've t to make a stretcher and carry her.
How are we gonna do that and bring a prisoner?
- Give me some rope.
- I'll take responsibility.
Phone. Phone!
- Wait,jin!
- Phone!
- Jin,it's all right!
-  no,let him!
- Jin,come back here!
- Oi,let him!
- jin,it's all right! Jin!
- Phone!
Jin,let him go.
Jin,let him go!
Phone!
You stole this?
How could you respect me if I didn't try?
How about I take your other eye?
Would you respect that?
Sorry. I--
Charlie,don't!
Charlie!
Charlie,let him go!
This is a mistake!
We can't keep letting these people go!
We gave him our word!
Go on.
Get out of here.
The baby isn't jin's.
We tried to have a baby back in korea and couldn't.
And the doctor...
he told me Jin was infertile.
And then you came here.
What?
Did you know that the average male
sperm count is between
60 and 80 million?
But on this island,
it's five times that.
We call that good odds.
you ready?
Yes.
Okay,you wanna lift up your shirt a little?
It's cold.
will I see the baby?
Maybe.
It's your first trimester,so it's a little iffy.
If you don't see a heartbeat,
don't worry about it.It's just early.
How does it work?
Well,I take a measurement
of the fetus,and that will tell us
when your baby was conceived,
and then we'll know who.
are you okay?
I lose either way.
If I'm going to live...
that means the baby's not jin's.
Do you still want to do this?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Moment of truth.
.
There it is.
There's your baby.Can you see?
I can see it.
is it a boy or a girl?
Oh,it's--it's a little early,
but,um,do you see that little flutter?
that's the heart beating.
it's very strong.It's very healthy.
Okay.
you crashed here 90 days ago.
The baby was conceived about eight weeks ago,
so... around 53 days.
you got pregnant on the island.
I am sorry.I'm so sorry,sun.
I will do everything that I can.
it's jin'S.
I was starting to think you wouldn't come.
Why didn't you tell me you were Jin's mother?
I gave birth to him.But hat doest not make me his mother.
You know how powerful my family is.
My husband believes that you are dead.
Do not force me to make that reality.
so how long do I have?
Most of the women made it into the
middle of their second trimester.
Nobody made it to their third.
That gives me two months.
I am...very happy the baby's jin'S.
You gave me good news,juliet.
It was my pleasure,sun.
I'm gonna go back inside and
make sure that I didn't miss anything.
I don't wanna take the chance
that we didn't cover our tracks.
Do you wanna wait out here?
All right.
Juliet?
Thank you.
ben,it's 6:00 A.M.On saturday morning.
Kwon is pregnant.
The fetus is healthy and was conceived
on island with her husband.
He was sterile before they got here.
I'm still working on getting samples
from the other women.
I should have austen's soon.
I'll report back when I know more.
I hate you.
- You can't trust 'em,you know.
- What's that?
The others--the one you let go.
He'll be back tomorrow with five of his mates.
Should've killed him.
Charlie.Uh,tight.
Oh,okay.
You know,brother,
by my count,
you've killed more of them than they've killed of you.
They started it.
You know,just 'cause one comes traipsing back
with Jack and Kate doesn't mean that we can trust them now.
Mom?
where am I?
Take it easy.You just had a giant branch in your--
- where am I? - I don't know.
You're on an island.
Are you here to rescue us?
Are there more of you?
Can you make your phone work?
- Who are you?
- Hugo Reyes.
I crashed here on oceanic flight 815.
A bunch of us survived.Is that why you're here?
Were you looking for us?
815? Flight 815?!
- The one from sydney?
- Yeah!
- No. That's not possible.
- Yeah,I know.
- It wasn't easy,but we found food -
- no,no.
- In the hatch,more food-
- no,flight 815--they...
they found the plane.
There were no survivors.
They were all dead.
What?