Lost Season 03 Episode 23
You okay?
Yeah, I just...
got a rock in my shoe.
He didnt mean it, you know.
- What?
- Sawyer.
When he said that he didn't want you to go with him...
he didn't mean it.
If he didn't mean it, why'd he say it?
He was trying to protect you.
That's why I asked you not to come back for me.
Hey.
Why are you sticking up for Sawyer?
He'd never do it for you.
Because I love you.
You've reached 310-555-0...
can I help you?
Sorry. I, uh...
actually, I came, uh...
is the funeral over?
There was no funeral, Sir.
Only a viewing.
Nobody showed up.
Nobody? You sure?
Just you. My deepest condolences.
Friend or family?
Neither.
Would you like me to open it up?
No.
Take your time.
Damn it.
Danielle.
How much further?
About an hour.
The radio tower...
when was the last time you were there?
The day I recorded the message.
I'll take you to the tower,
but I'm not leaving the island.
What?
There's no place for me back there.
This is my home now.
Hello, Jack!
We need to talk.
What did Ben say?
Can we kill him?
Is it possible to turn this equipment off?
What?
The equipment that's jamming the island...
can you turn it off?
Sure. Ben gave us the code.
You are the only ones who have it?
Yeah. Why?
What would happen if the station were to be flooded?
Nothing.
The casing for the equipment is waterproof.
It'll keep going forever.
Then why do you need to be here?
Because Ben told us to.
We were following orders.
And you never asked why?
No, because I trust him,
and I trust Jacob,
and the minute I start questioning orders,
this whole thing...
everything that we're doing here... falls apart.
She makes an excellent point.
No!
Please...
I'm sorry, Bonnie.
I, too, am following orders.
Hey!
No, Des! Des! Don't!
We need her.
Hi. I'm Benjamin.
I don't believe we've had the pleasure...
don't talk to him!
What do you want?
Just a moment of your time...
to talk, you and me, alone.
For what?
Jack, you've just killed seven of my people.
The least you can give me is five minutes.
Is he alone?
There's only two sets of tracks... his and hers.
Five minutes.
I'm sorry, sir there are no more refills left on this prescription.
Well, that... that's a mistake. I, uh...
I only refilled it twice.
Could you check again?
I did check it again, Dr. Shephard,
and that was the third refill,
so there's nothing I can do.
Fine. I've got another prescription right here.
Hey, I know you.
- You're the hero.
- I'm not a hero.
Yeah, we... we saw it on tv.
Hey, lady, what's wrong with you?
Just give this guy whatever he needs.
Do you know what he did?
Here, just... here...
Oxycodone.
Dr. Shephard,
you can't write a prescription for yourself.
That's not me.
That's Dr. Christian Shephard.
I'm Dr. Jack Shephard.
He's my father.
I'm gonna have to call your father's office to confirm...
well, he's out of town right now.
Well, I'm sure somebody in the office
don't bother.
Have a seat.
Not so long ago, Jack, I made a decision
that took the lives of over 40 people in a single day.
I'm telling you this because...
history is about to repeat itself right here, right now.
Let me guess. You've...
you've got us surrounded,
and if I don't do what you say, you're gonna...
you're gonna kill all my people.
No, jack.
You are.
And how am I gonna do that, ben?
The woman you're traveling with...
the one who parachuted onto the island from a helicopter...
she's not who she says she is.
She's not, huh?
No, she's not.
Then who is she?
She's a representative of some people
who have been trying to find this island, Jack.
She's one of the bad guys.
Oh.
I almost forgot. You're the...
you're the good guys.
Jack, listen to me.
If you phone her boat,
every single living person on this island will be killed.
So here's what has to happen.
Get that device...
the phone she carries with her...
and give it to me.
I will turn around.
We'll go back to my people.
You will turn around, go back to your people.
I'm not going anywhere.
- May I have my walkie back?
- What?
There's something you need to hear.
Please?
Thank you.
Tom, are you there?
Yeah, I'm here.
Your plan killed seven of my people,
but the ones that you failed to kill
are now holding your friends
Jin, Sayid, Bernard... at gun point.
Jack, don't give him any... uhh! Stop!
Leave him alone!
I said shut up!
And what's to stop me from snapping your neck...
tom, unless you hear my voice in one minute,
shoot all three of them.
Got it.
I said don't move!
Bring me the phone, Jack.
Don't negotiate!
40 seconds.
No.
I'm getting them all off the island... all of 'em!
Let me ask you something, Jack.
Why do you want to leave the island?
What is it you so desperately wanna get back to?
You have no one.
Your father's dead.
Your wife left you, moved on with another man.
Can you just not wait to get back to the hospital,
get back to fixing things?
It's 20 seconds now.
- Just get me the phone, Jack.
- No.
Ten seconds.
- Bring me the phone.
- No.
- I'm not bluffing.
- I won't do it!
Five... four... three...
no.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
Tom, are you there?
Yeah, Jack, I hear you.
I'm gonna lead my people up to the radio tower,
and I'm gonna make a call,
and I'm gonna get 'em all rescued... every one of 'em.
And then I'm gonna come find you...
and I'm gonna kill you.
What's the code?
Go away.
Bonnie, let's just get this over with, okay?
What's the code?
She's not gonna tell you, brother.
Yeah, she's gonna tell me.
What makes you say that?
'Cause you said it's my destiny to turn off that jammer.
Okay, Bonnie, we're both gonna die down here, all right?
Let's be perfectly honest.
That one-eyed maniac just killed your friend.
He shot you in the back.
It would appear that your glorious leader, Ben,
put him up to it.
Are you a sobbing idiot?
You have the opportunity to make Ben very, very angry.
Why would you not take that?
- 5-4-5...
- what?
- 8-7-7-
- is that a code?
- 5-5-4-3-7...
- Wait. Start again, start again.
- 6...
- start from the beginning. Bonnie.
- 1-1-3.
- Start again. Bonnie! Bonnie, start again.
Bonnie! Bonnie!
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
Start again. Start again.
- Good vibrations.
- What?
Beach boys.
"Good vibrations."
On the keypad.
The numbers...
they're notes.
It was programmed by a musician.
Tie him up.
He's coming with us.
What?
Alex...
this is your mother.
Will you help me tie him up?
What happened? What'd he say?
It's not important right now.
- Just get everybody together.
- Jack, your knules.
Here.
What happened?
He killed them.
Bernard...
Jin, Sayid... all three of them. He...
he radio-d the beach.
And I let it happen.
I had to let it happen.
We can't tell Rose...
or Sun, not yet.
We gotta keep moving.
I promised Sayid that we would keep moving.
So why did you bring him back?
Why didn't you just kill him?
Because I want him to see it.
I want him to experience the moment that we get off this island,
and I want him to know...
that he failed.
And then I'll kill him.
It was an order, Tom.
We had to follow it.
Ben didn't know what the hell he's talking about.
He's lost it.
I mean, look at what they did to us.
Instead of putting three bullets in the damn sand,
we should've killed them for real.
All they got left is 3 guys and 4 guns.
And all we've got, James, are two people and no guns.
So we'll wait till night.
That isn't gonna change the fact that we're unarmed.
If you wanna kill yourself, that's fine,
but before you go and try...
shh-
you hear that?
Ryan!
Stay in the bus, hero.
Stay right there, Tom.
Okay.
I give up.
That's for taking the kid off the raft.
Dude, it was over. He surrendered.
I didn't believe him.
What are you doing, Dr. Shephard?
I was just, uh...
I was just checking the, uh...
the Arlen's charts. Just wanted to...
wanted to see how the operation went.
I left three messages on your voice mail.
You didn't get them?
My phone's broken.
Let's go to my office, Jack.
- For what?
- We need to have a talk. Come on.
You know, I know that
you're... you're new around here,
- So you don't know much about me-
- I know enough.
- So let's just walk down to my office-
- if you got something to say to me, you can say it to me...
right here.
Will you excuse us, please?
Mrs. Arlen, the woman you saved,
woke up in recovery about two hours ago.
She was in some pain but highly responsive
to the reflex tests and entirely lucid.
Well, that's... that's great.
But then she described the series of
events that caused her accident.
She says she was driving over the bridge
when she saw a man standing on top of the railing
about to jump off.
She was distracted and lost control of her car.
She ran into the median, rolled over
and was hit by the van behind her.
So the obvious question here, Jack...
is how did you get to that flaming car so fast?
What were you doing on that bridge?
Do you know how many years
I've worked at this hospital?
Do you know... anything about me?
Do you have any idea...
what I've been through?
How much have you had to drink today, Jack?
Okay, I'll tell you what.
You do this... you get my father down here.
Get him down here right now,
and if I'm drunker than he is, you can fire me.
Don't you look at me like that.
Don't you... pity me.
- I'm trying to help you...
- you can't help me!
Attention, others. Come in, others.
If you're listening to this, I want you
to know that we got you bastards,
and unless the rest of you wanna be blown up,
you best stay away from our beach.
Hurley?
Jack?
Where are you? What's going on?
- Dude, I'm back at the beach.
- What?
Yeah, I went back to help Juliet and Sawyer.
I... I saved them.
You're... they're okay?
- Juliet..
- everyone's fine.
Me, Sawyer, Juliet, Sayid, Jin, Bernard.
- We're all...
- w-wait.
Bernard and Jin and Sayid... they're with you?
Yeah, dude, I told you. I saved them all.
Hey... stay where you are.
We're almost up to the tower.
- You'll be safer there.
- Yeah, I gotcha.
We'll stay put until you,
like, you know, phone home.
What about Charlie?
Did he make it back yet?
Not yet, but they're probably
paddling home as we speak.
Don't worry. I'm sure he's fine.
Des...
there's diving gear on those racks, yeah?
Aye. It's plenty.
Why don't you take care of that?
I'll tap out good vibrations.
All right, mate.
- Hey, Des.
- Aye?
You get any flashes?
No. Nothin'.
- I'll meet you back here, then.
- Aye.
So much for fate.
"Incoming Transmission" ?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Yes! Yes, I can hear you.
Who is this? Who am I speaking to?
Charlie! Uh... oh, Charlie pace.
I'm a survivor of flight 8-1-5...
Oceanic, flight 8-1-5.
Uh, wh-where are you?
- We're on an island. We're alive.
- An island? Well, where?
- What's the location?
- I don't know. Who's this?
This is Penelope... Penelope Widmore.
How did you get this frequency?
Desmond!
- Did you just say,"Desmond"?
- Yeah, he's here. He's with me.
- Is he okay?
- He's brilliant.
- Hey, are you on the boat?
- What... what boat?
Your boat... 80 miles offshore.
- Uh, N-Naomi, the parachutist.
- Well, I'm not on a boat.
Who... who's Naomi?
Can you hear me?
Penny! No!
Charlie!
"NOT PENNY'S BOAT"
Hey, Aaron, it's okay, sweetie.
- What's the matter?
- I don't know.
I think he's just a bit scared.
- Hard to blame him.
- What is it?
What's your boyfriend's name...
the rock star who swam down to the station?
Charlie. Why?
Charlie just got us rescued.
Jack! Jack, he did it!
Your friend bloody well did it.
- What?
The green light... it's on. The jamming stopped.
- Use it, then.
- All right.
4-4-2.
Il Est Dehors. II est dehorset
brennan pris les clefs.
What's this?
It's Rousseau's message.
It's still blocking the signal.
It doesn't matter. We're here.
Iteration 1-7-5-5...
iteration 1-7-5-5-0-4-4-5.
Il est dehors. II est dehors et
brennan pris les clefs.
Veuillez nous aider. Ils sont morts.
Ils sont tous morts. Aidez-nous. Ils sont morts.
Iteration...
I recorded this16 years ago.
Three days before you were born.
Il est dehors. II est dehors et brennan
pris les clefs. Veuiez nous aider.
I guess we don't need it anymore.
Aidez-nous. Ils sont
All right. Do it.
I can't get a signal in here.
I'm getting something.
It's gonna work. It's happening.
We're gonna get off of this island.
We'll celebrate when we're home.
Jack!
I know you think you're saving your
people, but you need to stop this.
- It's a mistake.
- The mistake was listening to you.
This will be your last chance, Jack.
I'm telling you, making that
call is the beginning of the end.
I've got it! I've got a signal!
Jack, please! You don't knowwhat you're doing!
I know exactly what l'm doing.
John!
Step back, Jack.
- What did you do?
- What I had to.
Now step back.
Stay away from the phone.
- What are you doing, John?
- I don't want to shoot you.
Do it, John! Shoot him!
Please, put the phone down.
No. You're done keeping me on this island.
I will... kill you if I have to.
Then do it, John.
Jack.
You're not supposed to do this.
Minkowski.
Hello?
- Who is this?
My name's Jack Shephard. Are you...
are you on the boat... the freighter?
How'd you get this channel?
Naomi. Naomi told us about your
search team, about the boat.
Naomi? You found her?
Where is she? Who are you?
I'm one of the survivors of Oceanic flight 815.
Can you get a fix on our location?
Hell, yeah, we can. Sit tight.
We'll be right there.
Hello?
- It's me.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait.
Don't... don't hang up, please.
I know what you said. I just...
I just need to see you. Please.
Yeah. Yeah, out at the airport.
You know where.
Thank you.
- Hey.
Saw you on the news.
Still pulling people out of burning wreckage, huh?
Old habits.
- You look terrible.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Why did you call me, Jack?
I was hoping that you'd heard,
that maybe you'd go to the funeral.
Why would i go to the funeral?
- Been flying a lot.
- What?
Yeah, the golden pass that they gave us.
I... I've been using it.
Every friday night, I...
I fly from L.A. to Tokyo or...
Singapore or... Sydney.
And then I... I get off, and I...
have a drink and then I fly home.
Why?
Because I want it to crash, Kate.
I don't care about anybody else on board.
Every little bump we hit or...
turbulence, I mean, like, I actually close my eyes,
and I pray that I can get back...
- this is not gonna change
- No, I'm sick... of lying.
We made a mistake.
I have to go. He's gonna be wondering why I'm
We... were not supposed to leave.
Yes, we were.
Good-bye, Jack.
We have to go back, Kate.
We have to go back!
---www.opensubtitles.org---
---LOST Season 03 Episode 23---