Previously on Lost:
This is not your island.
This is our island.
They've attacked us, sabotaged us,
abducted us, murdered us.
We're not the only people
on this island, and we all know it.
They came the first night,
took three of us.
Then they came back
and took nine more.
They're smart and they're animals.
You're coming with us.
I burnt my hand. And my muffins.
- Still hasn't fixed your plumbing yet?
- It's a work in progress.
It's not even literature.
It's popcorn.
Why isn't it literature, Adam?
I'm dying to know.
There's no metaphor. It's religious
hokum-pokum. It's science fiction.
- Now I know why Ben isn't here.
- Excuse me?
I know the host
picks the book, but, Julie,
he wouldn't read this
in the damned bathroom.
Well, Adam, I am the host,
and I do pick the book.
And this is my favourite book,
so I am absolutely thrilled
that you can't stand it.
Silly me for sinking so low as to select
something that Ben wouldn't like.
Here I am thinking that freewill
still actually exists on...
- Whoa.
- The doorway. Get under the doorway.
Goodwin.
- You see where the tail landed?
- Probably in the water.
You can make that shore in an hour.
Ethan, get up to that fuselage.
There may actually be survivors.
And you're one of 'em.
A passenger. You're in shock.
Come up with a story if they ask.
Stay quiet if they don't.
Listen. Learn. Don't get involved.
I want lists in three days. Go.
So, I guess I'm out of the book club.
Hey!
Kate!
Can you hear me?
Rise and shine, Kate.
Where am I?
You don't really think
I'm going to answer that, do you?
- Where are Sawyer and Jack?
- I'll tell you what.
Why don't you just take a nice
hot shower, wake yourself up,
wash the day off you and start fresh?
Here's a nice clean towel,
shampoo, soap...
I'm not showering in front of you.
Kate, you're not my type.
Hey.
Where are we?
Who the hell are you?
You ain't gonna talk to me?
What, you got
more important things to do?
Warning.
I wouldn't do that.
If I want your advice, I'll ask for it.
Son of a bitch!
Told you.
Stop that.
Hi, Jack.
I'm Juliet.
Hi. I'm Jack Shephard.
I'm here for the...
Where's your lawyer?
You look pretty.
I fired him.
Sarah...
I'm sorry for pushing us to this place.
I know that I...
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Yeah?
No, not yet. He just got here.
I'll call you when I get out.
- I'm gonna say this as simply as I can.
- What's his name?
- Stop it.
- I'm not gonna stop it.
I'm gonna keep asking you
until you tell me.
- I don't ask you what you do...
- Just tell me what his name is.
I wanna know who he is.
Look, you can have everything,
the cars, the house, I don't care.
I just... I just wanna know
the name of the man
that is with my wife.
Jack?
Can you hear me in there?
- Is that a yes?
- Where are my friends?
Come down from the table.
You want me to come down,
come in here and get me down.
- If you wanna talk, I'm happy to.
- Tell me where my friends are!
I will if you let go of the chain.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I don't think you're stupid, Jack.
I think you're stubborn.
Hey!
Where are my clothes?
Come on, Kate. He's waiting.
Sorry. I'm going to have to ask you
to put those on, Kate.
And if I don't?
Then you don't get any coffee.
A little tighter.
Please?
What did you do with Sawyer and Jack?
Now, why Sawyer?
- Why Sawyer what?
- He's the first one you asked about.
"What did you do with Sawyer and Jack"?
- You don't know me.
- Of course I don't.
- I want my clothes back.
- We burned them.
Why did you bring me here?
Why did you make me put on this dress?
Why are you feeding me breakfast?
I brought you here so you'd look out
at the water and feel comforted,
comforted that your friends
were looking out at the same ocean.
I gave you the dress
so you'd feel like a lady.
And I wanted you to eat your food
with a real live fork
and feel civilised.
I did all those things so that you'd
have something nice to hold onto.
Because, Kate,
the next two weeks
are going to be very unpleasant.
Yeah, hi. I met a woman
on the train, Sarah,
and she dropped her cell phone
and I don't even know her last name,
but your number was in her phone,
so I was just wondering...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Forget it.
- Hey.
- Just give me a minute, Dad.
I asked you to give me a minute here.
What's this? Why are you dialling
all the numbers on Sarah's cell phone?
- Because one of them is him.
- You gotta stop this, Jack. It's over.
Not until I know his name,
where he works, where he lives,
when they first kissed.
I wanna know what it is about him.
Why is Sarah calling you, Dad?
I think it's time that you let this go.
- Why is she calling you?
- Because she was afraid for you.
I wanna know exactly
why the hell she was calling.
You were slipping, losing your grip.
- My grip is not the problem here.
- Which is exactly what's happening.
I think I know something
about being obsessive.
No. Being a drunk is not obsessive.
Let it go, Jack.
What?
If you're trying to talk to me,
I can't hear you.
Let it go, Jack.
I know you're hungry.
I brought this for you.
This is how it will work.
You sit there, across from the door,
back against the wall.
I open the door and leave the tray.
Can I trust you to do that, Jack?
- I don't want your food.
- It's a delicious sandwich.
Tell the guy who's trying to talk to me
through that intercom he can give it up!
Maybe you're hungrier than you think.
That intercom hasn't worked in years.
What's that for?
The button, what's it for?
- It's for emergencies.
- Who's watching me?
Are you going to sit against the wall
so I can open the door?
It's just off the frying pan.
You can have it.
What do you do, Jack?
What's your profession?
I'm a repo man.
You know, when people don't pay
their bills, I go in for the bank
and I collect their possessions.
I'm a people person,
so I really love it.
Are you married?
No. I never saw the point.
What about you?
What's your job,
besides making sandwiches?
I didn't make it.
I just put the toothpicks in.
When your plane crashed,
where were you flying from?
Sydney.
What were you doing there?
I was bringing my father home.
- Why go all the way to Australia to...
- Because he was dead.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm sure you are.
Thanks.
You can trust me, Jack.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
What the hell is going on here?
Hey!
Hey, how long would it take
to get to your camp?
What, you're talking to me now, Chachi?
From where they got you,
how long a walk was it?
Day? Two days?
Hey, what are the people like,
from your plane?
They're just awesome.
Last one of you boys came for a visit
got tortured by our Iraqi.
He tortured me, too.
But, hell, you don't know any better.
Subject escape.
- Hey
- Whoa.
Subject escape. Subject escape.
Hey, how'd you get out of there?
- Run that way.
- Hold on.
You run that way.
Hey.
Say it. Say it, Karl.
I'm... sorry...
...sorry I involved you
in my breakout attempt.
The drugs we gave you
when we brought you here
have a fairly serious side effect:
Dehydration.
Your head is probably sore,
your throat is raw,
and if you don't eat or drink
something soon,
you're going to start hallucinating.
So you're a doctor, huh?
No. I'm a repo woman.
No strings attached.
You don't have to answer any questions.
You don't have to do anything
but sit with your back
up against the far wall,
let me open that door,
put the plate down and leave.
I know it feels like you're giving up,
like you're losing
if you do anything that I ask you to,
but you're not.
You need to eat.
What do you say?
Thank you, Jack.
Let's take out the epidural catheter
and get him started on a PCA.
Excuse me for just a second.
You sure he's ready
to self-administer his pain meds?
Hello?
Dr Shephard?
Yeah. Bye.
- Jack?
- Give me your cell phone.
- What? What?
- I wanna see it. Now.
Look where you are, Jack.
Just look around you. Please.
- OK?
- Give me the phone.
This is not the place for this.
You must be Jack.
Why don't you grab a chair, join us?
You... you know me?
Yes. Your father's told us
all about you.
What's he told you about me?
What'd you tell them about me, Dad?
That your son never really had it?
Not like the old man.
I didn't have the will to make it work?
My life? My job?
My marriage? What'd you tell them
about my marriage, Dad?
You know how he manages his marriage?
A bottle of Scotch every night
before dinner.
Your father has been sober 50 days now.
We're very proud of that.
Wow, Dad. I wonder what helped you
turn that corner?
Think maybe it was a new lady friend?
You think maybe that's what it was?
- I will not let you talk to me this...
- I will not let you sleep with my wife.
Oh, Jack. Jack, I'm your father.
Jack, please, just let it go.
- Which way out?
- Don't do this, Jack.
Don't... Don't...
- No!
- Open the door.
- I can't. I do that, we die.
- You're lying to me.
- I'm not.
- Open the door!
- I can't. I swear I can't.
- She's telling the truth, Jack.
I swear to God, I will kill her.
OK.
Have her open the door
and she dies anyway. We all do.
No!
Jack! Over here!
- The button!
- What?
The yellow button! The button!
Come here.
Warning.
Gotcha, Doc Brown!
Reward. Reward.
Come on.
Unbelievable.
Keep moving.
Stick your hands out through the bars,
I'll take off your cuffs.
Scratched you up pretty bad,
didn't they?
- I'll bring you some antiseptic later.
- How about you bring me an ottoman?
While you're at it,
I could use a blow-dry.
Hey, you got yourself a fish biscuit.
How'd you do that?
I figured out your complicated gizmos,
that's how.
Only took the bears two hours.
How many of 'em were there?
You OK, Freckles?
Yeah.
- You?
- Just swell.
I requested that cage, but whatever.
Nice dress.
They made me wear it.
You hungry?
It's an aquarium.
- Excuse me?
- This thing's for what,
- sharks?
- Dolphins, too.
- We're underwater, aren't we?
- Yes.
Is this one of their stations,
the Dharma Initiative?
They called it the Hydra.
So you people are just...
...whatever's left over of them?
Well, that was a long time ago.
It doesn't matter who we were.
It only matters who we are.
We know exactly who you are,
Jack Shephard.
You don't know anything about me.
I know that you're a spinal surgeon
based out of St. Sebastian's Hospital
in Los Angeles.
I know you went to Columbia
and you graduated med school
a year faster than anyone else.
I know that you were married only once
and that you contested the divorce.
I know your father died in Sydney.
I know this because
I have a copy of his autopsy report.
How...
- How did you get...
- We got it.
What is that?
This, Jack, is your life.
Do you?
Is it just about me or is it about
my family, too? My... my friends?
It's pretty much about everything.
Do you know about my...
about my ex-wife?
Sarah.
Yes, Jack. We know all about her.
What would you like to find out?
Get ready for the lockdown.
Shephard. Someone posted your bail.
- How'd you?
- Your dad told me you were here.
I called you a cab.
So, goodbye.
- Sarah.
- What?
Is that him?
- What difference does it make?
- It just does.
I wanna know. I need to know who he is.
It doesn't matter who he is.
It just matters who you're not.
Jack, your father,
when he called me,
to help you,
he was so drunk
I could hardly understand him.
Look at the bright side.
Now you have something to fix.
Jack.
Jack, what would you like to find out?
Is she...
Is she happy?
Yes, Jack, she's very happy.
Now, I'd like to bring you
some food and water.
But this time I need to know
that you'll behave.
Can I trust you, Jack?
Put your back against the wall, please.
Good work, Juliet.
Thank you, Ben.