Previously on Lost:
Each one of us
was brought here for a reason.
- And who brought us here, John?
- The island.
It's destiny.
You and your partner will observe a
psychological experiment in progress.
Your duty is to observe team members
in another station on the island.
These team members are not aware
that they are under surveillance,
or they are subjects
of an experiment.
Every single second
of my pathetic little life
is as useless as that button!
As long as we push it,
we'll never be free!
If you're sure it's not real,
then stop pushing the button.
Well, I have, except, unfortunately,
someone else decided to start.
Tomorrow we're gonna
find out what happens
if that button doesn't get pushed.
John!
Who is he, Box Man?
The man out there pounding on the door.
His name is Mr Eko.
Why does Mr Eko carry a stick
covered in scripture?
Because he's a priest.
- We need to push the button.
- No, we don't.
It's all bloody real!
Push the button!
No!
- You've killed us all.
- No. I just saved us all.
System failure.
I was wrong.
When did John get back?
And what's he doing?
Where's he been?
Where's everyone else?
Don't you think you should find out?
So you're gone for a whole day...
after a massive hatch detonation.
You don't call.
You don't write.
Sorry, am I interrupting something?
What? You... can't speak, John?
You're mute?
I am sorry about that.
So, where are Eko and Desmond?
Are they off being mute
and building structures as well?
I know. You can't speak.
You need to speak...
to me?
What do you wanna...
The sand?
You need to speak to the sand?
Trees. Yeah, I've heard they're
wonderful conversationalists.
Hey!
I don't understand.
Who do you need to speak to?
The... church?
The sky.
Island.
Island?
You need to speak to the island?
"I need your help. "
Since when do you need my help?
"I need you to stand guard. "
Yeah, so you can talk to the island.
Sounds dangerous.
Well, amusing as the "mute game"
invariably is,
you are aware, John, that
I detest you, aren't you?
You do remember
repeatedly punching me in the face
and accusing me of using heroin
when I was not?
What the sodding hell
is a "sweat lodge?"
- Where you headed?
- Eureka.
I can get you far as Bridgeville.
Come on. Hop in. Come on.
- My name's John.
- Eddie.
- Hi, Eddie.
- Hey.
- Nasty day to be hitching.
- That's for sure.
You don't mind my asking,
what's in Eureka?
I heard there was
some work there cutting timber.
Oh, is that what you do?
That might be what I do.
All I know is that I had to get out
of where I came from.
Mom's dead, Dad's a drunk.
Hey, look at that. The rain is passing.
What, did you rob a bank?
Afraid so.
Could I see your license
and registration, please?
- Was I speeding, Officer?
- Taillight's out.
Could you both please
step outta the vehicle?
What do you got back here?
Guns and groceries.
The transaction logs and paperwork
is in the red notebook in that duffel.
So, are we free to go?
I could still take you in
for picking up a hitchhiker.
That's my uncle.
I called him and he picked me up.
Get outta here.
So, what is with all the guns... uncle?
Oh, I like the indoor fireplace.
That's very snazzy.
What's that?
You're not taking drugs,
are you, John?
I only ask because of the strict
zero tolerance policy you've enacted,
and I wouldn't want you to have to
start punching yourself in the face.
I get it.
You go in your little magic hut,
and I stand out here
in case you devolve into a monkey.
"Don't come in. " OK.
OK. I get it.
Hi, John.
It's good to see you again.
What's that, John?
You're sorry.
That's OK. But I was
the sacrifice the island demanded.
Don't worry. You'll speak
when you have something worth saying.
I'm here to help you
find your way again.
So you can bring the family
back together.
Come on.
I wanna show you something.
John.
You're gonna need that.
John, someone in this airport's
in serious danger.
You're the only one
who can save them.
Not them. They'll be fine...
for a while.
I think Sayid's got it.
Next, please.
Not Hurley.
Forget it. He's helping himself.
There's nothing you can do for them.
Not yet.
You have to clean up your own mess.
Come up here, John.
Clean it up, John.
They've got him.
You don't have much time.
John!
What happened?
Are you all right?
What are you doing?
I'm going to save Mr Eko's life.
- Eko's cross.
- He was dragged this way.
Dragged?
- By what?
- By the polar bear.
Sawyer killed the polar bear.
He killed "a" polar bear.
What's that, John? Blood?
I'm gonna go on alone,
you go back to Claire.
- Well, I'll take my chances.
- You don't wanna go with me, Charlie.
Bad things happen to people
who hang around with me.
Hey, Bobby.
What's that?
That, Eddie, is our sweat lodge.
A what?
Anybody who wants
can go in there and light a fire
and get it nice and hot...
meditate.
Then what?
Then you figure out
what to do with your life...
...what direction to take. Go in and
figure out if you're a farmer or hunter.
So which are you, John?
- Hey, John.
- Hey, Mike, Jan, this is Eddie.
Looking for logging work, but
I convinced him to come have supper.
- Nice to meet you, Eddie.
- Nice to meet you.
Any friend of John's
is a friend of ours.
John's a very special guy.
Grab a spot.
So, you like Geronimo Jackson?
They're all right.
It's my dad's old shirt.
Your dad has excellent taste.
Listen up, people.
John brought a guest to supper.
- Everyone, this is Eddie.
- Hey, Eddie.
Eddie, this is everyone.
- Nice to meet you.
- John, you wanna say some grace?
Yeah.
Thank you, Lord.
Thank you for the food and the friends.
And thanks for the rain today,
so that Adam'll stop grumbling
about the droughts.
And for me, thank you for helping me
stop being so angry.
And for... helping me...
...find a real family.
They're a hell of a lot better than the
one I used to have. So, let's eat. Amen.
- Amen.
- Let's dig in.
- Potatoes?
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Is that the hatch?
- What's left of it.
What happened?
Looks like it imploded.
What's that?
It's an active kill.
Whatever was eating this
is gonna be back for more.
If you wanna say "polar bear,"
you can just say it.
All right. "Polar bear. "
Run!
Dude.
They kept Jack, Kate, and Sawyer,
and they sent me back to tell everyone
else that we can't ever go over there.
Oh, and that dude
we had in the hatch, Henry...
...he was there,
he's like their leader.
So... what do we do?
Do what they told you. Go back
to the camp and tell the others.
- You're not gonna do anything?
- I am doing something.
- Go back to the beach, Hugo.
- Wait. Where are you guys going?
The island told Locke
he has to save Eko.
- Save him from what?
- Well, apparently a bear's got him.
It just made an active kill.
You may wanna hustle.
Bear?
What bear?
What is that? More fur?
This way.
You know, when I used to get high,
I'd watch nature programs on the Beeb.
Polar bears are meant to be
quite clever. Very clever.
They're like the Einsteins
of the bear community.
- She likes you, man.
- Shut up.
- Yeah, she does.
- She does not.
- She's half my age, man.
- You'd be better off with her.
- No.
Lizzie's too granola for me.
What she really wants is a daddy,
like everyone else here.
- You should take advantage of that.
- That's not really funny, Eddie.
It was a joke. I'm sorry.
How come you never talk
about your dad?
Nothing worth talking about.
What's going on
in that greenhouse over there?
- They need a hand with that fertilizer.
- No. They're OK.
Come on. We got orchard duty.
- What's the big secret, John?
- Sorry?
The greenhouse.
What do you guys got in there?
Every time I go near it,
you and everyone else acts all weird.
You're a guest, things take time.
I've been here for six weeks.
I'm not blind, man.
Did you forget you had
a bag of guns when you brought me here?
Mike and Jan welcomed you here
with open arms. They feed you.
- They give you a place to stay.
- And Mike and Jan
fold their hands every night before chow
and talk about how we're family,
your family's got too many secrets.
Now, I see the fertilizer
going into that greenhouse.
I know what's going on...
...and I want in.
- In on what?
- Whatever you are trying to blow up.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
I'll talk to Mike and Jan.
You really think Eko's in there?
Let's hurry up, maybe the bear's
out finishing his lunch.
- You're not going in there, Charlie.
- What?
I'm gonna do this alone.
Don't tell me what I can't do!
If I want to go, I'll go.
- Why?
- What?
- Why do you wanna go in there?
- I don't need a reason!
- Then go back.
- You don't have a good reason, either!
I'm going in there
because I'm supposed to go in there.
If it all goes to plan, we probably
won't even see the bear, will we?
And hopefully he won't smell us.
Hairspray? Now, I hate to be the one
to point this out to you...
It's not for me.
Bear?
Is that you?
Who's there?
Are you alone, brother?
Yeah.
Dude! I'm not alone.
Beach camp's right over there.
Can you get me some clothes?
What happened to yours?
I woke up in the jungle like this.
So... like, the hatch...
...blew off your underwear?
Fine. You wanna discuss this in
great detail right now?
- Then, let's do it.
- No, that's OK. I got something here.
How do you feel about tie-dye?
Hey, Kim.
Hey, Mike and Jan in?
Yeah. They were looking for you.
Good, good. Good timing then?
Go on in.
- You got all the cash?
- In the bag.
- Which bag?
- The one with the money!
- What about bank records?
- Leave 'em.
- Should we sort what they can trace?
- There is no time, Mike.
What's going on?
What does it look like?
You screwed up, John.
You blew it big time.
What are you doing?
Are you leaving?
- Why?
- That is why, you idiot!
Your friend's a cop.
You know how much time
we'd get for this?
- Nice picture, fresh out of academy.
- He was hitchhiking.
- He told me he was going to Eureka.
- He was waiting for you!
He has been here for six weeks gathering
evidence because you brought him here!
- That's impossible.
- He played you for a sucker. It's over.
No. Wait.
Wait, no, wait, wait. Stop!
We don't know what he's told them.
He hasn't even been in here yet.
If he's gathering evidence
to make a case, it's not too late.
- Not too late for what?
- To protect all of us.
It's not too late to fix this.
I can fix this.
How are you gonna do that?
Eko.
John...
Is he OK?
Is he alive?
Is he all right?
- He's alive.
- Turn him over.
We gotta get outta here.
OK. Let's get him up.
So, when you say "turned a key,"
you mean like a "key" key?
It was a fail-safe key.
That seems kind of convenient.
I'm sorry?
If you had this magic key
the whole time, why didn't you use it?
- I didn't know what would happen.
- What did happen?
Well, the fail-safe key must've
detonated the electromagnetic anomaly,
made the hatch implode.
But you didn't implode.
No.
You're not gonna...
turn into The Hulk or something?
So, is that what made the blender
noise and the sky turn purple?
I'm afraid I missed that.
Right, you were fail-safing.
Well, FYI, the whole island vibrated.
Kate, Jack and Sawyer saw it before
they had bags pulled over their heads.
Don't worry.
Locke's gonna go after them.
- He said so in his speech.
- What?
What speech?
All he said was he was gonna
save Eko and kill bears.
Right.
Right, of course.
I'm sorry. I...
...I'm just a bit shook up.
I burned that bear pretty good.
I don't think
he's gonna be coming after us.
Now that we've survived
this suicide mission...
...do you wanna tell me
what you saw?
- What I saw?
- In your spirit tent.
I saw Boone.
Boone?
What did he have to say for himself?
Told me I had to clean up my own mess.
Well... dead as he may be,
I agree with Boone.
If you kept pressing that
button like Eko told you...
We wouldn't have had to save him, that's
what cleaning up your own mess means.
Spoken like someone who's had
many messes to clean.
- No deer?
- Nope.
You talk to Mike and Jan yet?
- Yeah, sure did.
- What did they say?
They said that I should
bring you by the greenhouse tonight
and that they would explain everything.
Cool. That's great.
What? You see something?
John.
- What are you doing?
- Did you know it would be me?
- What?
- In the truck.
Did you know it would be me driving?
Did they choose me?
"They"? I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I didn't load that one.
So just answer the question, Eddie.
Yeah. They chose you, John.
Why?
You hadn't been here long,
didn't have a criminal record,
and the psych profile
said you would be amenable for coercion.
- "Amenable for coercion"?
- Hey! Lower the gun, John.
OK? This isn't personal.
What's not personal?
Stop, stop.
I'm sorry, John, but you're not gonna
shoot me. You're not a murderer.
You're a good man.
You're a farmer.
Nope.
Not a farmer.
I was a hunter.
I'm a hunter.
I'm gonna walk away now, John.
You hear something?
- It sounds like a stream.
- Yeah.
Put him down.
Maybe we can get some water in him.
I'll go. You stay here.
I'm sorry.
Sorry I ever doubted you.
Sorry I...
...gave up on my faith in the island.
I messed up.
Now our people are captured and...
...if I'd just listened to you...
...if I'd just let you
keep pushing the button...
I could've gone with 'em,
protected 'em.
I could've saved 'em.
You can still protect them.
You can still save them.
I don't even know where they are.
You will find them.
After all, you are a hunter, John.
- You say something?
- He's awake. Eko?
Maybe we should just...
get him back, John.
Yeah.
- You all right?
- Yeah, just keep walking.
John? Charlie?
- What happened?
- We got him.
- Is he alive?
- We need Jack.
- Take him in.
- Jack's not coming back.
- They've got him.
- What are you talking about?
- Jack's gone?
- I don't understand.
- When were you planning on telling us?
- What do you mean, who's "they?"
"They" are the Others.
And, yes, they've taken Jack.
And Kate and Sawyer.
- How? What happened?
- What about Sun, Jin and Sayid?
I don't know.
I'm gonna find our friends.
I don't know how yet, but I will.
We're gonna find them, all of them.
And then we're gonna bring them home.
But first, we gotta look after Mr Eko.
Paulo, Nikki, bring towels and water.
We gotta clean him up, bring all the
first aid supplies you can find.
Not a bad speech.
I just got hit with...
...d?j? vu.
Well... when that wears off,
can you get bandages
from the kitchen?