Previously on Lost:
- What do you want from me?
- Patience, Jack.
Patience.
- Danny, wait!
- Hold up.
Be careful out there.
See these rocks?
You're gonna chop 'em loose.
You haul 'em outta here.
I am not the enemy.
We are not the enemy.
But if you shoot me,
that's exactly what we'll become.
You've got a problem with your roof.
What?
Maybe you should move down the beach,
just for tonight.
That way I can fix it,
make some improvements.
That's really nice of you to offer,
but, Aaron just fell asleep.
- So I should probably just...
- No, it'll be worth it. I promise.
Whatcha doing, brother?
I was just offering
to fix this roof here.
Roof?
Fine. There's a problem, I'll fix it.
I'm quite handy.
I was building a church before...
Eko exploded.
Right.
Well.
Just trying to help.
Thanks.
What was all that about?
I don't know.
We're gonna have to get
that guy another button to push.
- How are you doing today, Jack?
- Great.
You seem frustrated.
Am I gonna keep watching cartoons,
or are you gonna tell me why I'm here?
I hope you like blueberry.
- Should I talk to Benjamin?
- Sorry?
Should I talk to Benjamin?
Because I'm starting to think you're
just the person who brings me my food.
You can talk to him all you want...
but he won't tell you anything.
- You work for him?
- No, I don't work for him.
- He's in charge.
- It doesn't work that way over here.
- We make decisions together.
- Really?
Because... when I was holding
that broken plate at your neck,
he seemed happy to just let you die.
It felt like he made that decision
on his own.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I don't answer to him.
Juliet, I need you.
Can it wait?
The sub is back.
We have a situation.
So come with me now.
Time for work.
Sounding a little stuffy there,
Chinatown.
- Need to blow your nose?
- Give me an excuse.
I thought I did.
What, I gotta talk about your mother?
- Danny, are you there?
- Yeah?
Hold on.
OK, go.
Yeah, listen, Danny.
What?
- Where are they?
- They're back in...
She's hurt bad, Juliet.
Keep her steady.
She's gonna be fine, right?
She'll be, OK?
What happened?
- We happened.
- What?
Been on this rock long enough to realize
they ain't shooting each other.
We did it.
- Our team.
- You smiling?
Damn right I'm smiling.
'Cause we just got
our ticket outta here.
What are you doing?
- Whenever you're ready to fill me in.
- I'm thinking.
Warning!
Reward! Reward!
That chick they brought in
on the stretcher,
that's Broken Nose Man's girl.
They call him "Pickett. "
Well, Pickett is distracted
at the moment.
So?
Watch and learn, little lady.
Warning!
There's juice pumping into this box
from somewhere.
Next time someone comes
to pull me out,
I wait till they
step in my little swimming hole,
then I grab 'em.
They fall back from the shock,
I snag the keys.
Bet the bears never thought of that.
- You're both gonna get electrocuted.
- I felt the jolt. I can take it.
The other guy,
he ain't gonna be ready for it.
- What? You think I'm crazy?
- No, I'm actually impressed.
Well, wipe the stars outta your eyes,
sweetheart, 'cause we're gonna do this.
- So what about Jack?
- What about him?
We don't even know if he's here.
We don't even know if he's alive.
We gotta take care of us.
It's every man for himself, Freckles.
All right, Ford. That's enough.
All tier two inmates are
required to report to your cells.
Mandatory down time.
Problem is I was following your hands,
not your eyes.
Problem is you old and dumb.
- Where did you hide it?
- I don't know!
Who's the punching bag?
- Tell me something!
- Just got here, name's Munson.
Rumour has it he ripped off
the government for ten mil.
But they never found the money.
Well, I'll be damned.
If your buddy the warden didn't keep
breaking up the fights, he'd be dead.
Get off of him! Hey!
I didn't do anything!
That son of a bitch.
Get little mints
on your pillow at night, too?
- Sorry?
- You been here a week
and you're on tote bag duty? Been here
nine months, I'm still pushing trash.
Well, what does that mean?
You think the warden's breaking up those
fights cause you're cute, Costanza?
He's making a play for that ten mil.
First step, butter you up.
Give you a plum job.
Step Two, warden'll reach out
to your wife, use her against you.
Textbook con.
And you're telling me this
out of the kindness of your...
Advice is free, Murgatroyd.
Past nine months that warden's
made my life a living hell.
He gets that ten mil you ain't got,
I just might have to kill myself.
Hey.
Well, howdy, Warden.
He bothering you, Munson?
So what brings you
to the sewing shop, boss?
Don't think I can't
extend your stay, Ford.
All it takes is one call.
One call.
Now, how about you get that trash.
Oh, yeah. The Big Kahuna.
- Lunch already?
- What do you weigh?
- What?
One-eighty, give or take.
- How old are you?
- Thirty-two.
Don't lie.
Thirty-five.
Good.
Sayonara, sucker!
- What did you do?
- We turned it off.
Sawyer!
Hey!
Where do I start?
In the two days since the sky
turned purple, we've been blind.
Our coms are all down,
and I can't get 'em back up again.
And, Colleen's in critical...
Juliet's taking care of her.
Where am I?
What the hell are you doing to me?
Let me out!
Jason?
- Bite down on this, please.
- You bite down on it.
It's for the pain.
God, I hate needles.
No! No! What are you doing?
Wait! What are you doing? No!
What are you doing?
Let me outta here!
No, you have to go
through the sternum.
- Like in the movie.
- I know.
- No!
- One...
- What are you doing?
- Two...
Wait!
Don't mind me.
I'm gonna take one of your clubs.
Hurley said it'd be all right.
Hurley?
Must mean you're off to save the day.
So, I can take one of these?
Take the five iron. I never use it.
That way when you die in the jungle
doing whatever,
I don't have to go looking for it.
Thanks, mate.
You might wanna square
your shoulders a bit more.
- You play golf?
- I'm Scottish. Cheers.
What the hell's...
Hey!
Hey, come on!
Hey, move! Let's move!
- Hey, come on, come on, come on!
- What are you doing?
Did you just kill that bunny?
- You know what a pacemaker is?
- What?
They stick 'em in tickers
of people who have bypass work,
whose hearts need just a little jump,
a... kick start.
The rabbit had a pacemaker to deliver
a kick start should it get too excited.
Or anxious or frightened.
Or should it try to escape.
Assuming that you were telling the truth
about your age and weight,
your resting heart rate
should be about 70 beats per minute.
Your active heart rate, however...
that would be about 140.
Which is the point
at which your pacemaker...
...will cause your heart to explode.
Which is how I know
that you're gonna start behaving now.
The watch monitors your pulse.
If you get within 15 beats of
your danger zone, it'll start to beep.
If and when it beeps,
you're gonna wanna relax yourself.
Do some deep breathing, some yoga.
If you want me dead, why don't you
just shoot me and get it over with?
Because we're not killers, James.
And one other thing.
- Kate.
- You touch her, I swear...
Tell her what we put in you,
that we're watching you...
...you tell her any of these things...
...we'll put one in her, too.
Sawyer?
Are you OK?
That's so you can clean yourselves up.
If any of that doesn't fit,
you just give me a holler, OK?
What happened?
What did they do to you?
Nothing. They just asked me questions.
- It ain't important.
- Talk to me. What happened?
Look, I told you. Nothing happened.
So quit asking me.
Turn around.
- What's that?
- It's just my watch. It's busted.
- When did you get a watch?
- Look, I don't tell you everything!
Just leave me alone, damn it!
Put some clothes on!
A reminder that the services
will be held in the chapel at 9:30.
Hello, Sawyer.
It's James Ford.
I know you know, cause you
got it right when you pressed charges.
- You're mad at me?
- Well, look where I am.
What did you want me to do?
You conned me.
Something you want?
Yeah. Yeah... there is.
Come on. I got license plates to make.
What's this?
This is your daughter.
What do you want?
- First I wanted you to know.
- Then what?
I take one look at this picture
and turn into Father Knows Best?
We're living in Albuquerque.
- Near the university.
- Why are you telling me?
I just thought you could
write her a letter.
- Her name's Clementine.
- What the hell am I gonna write?
She's a baby. She ain't mine!
Sawyer, she is...
I ain't got no daughter!
I've been checking out my cage,
and I think...
...if I climb to the top
I can squeeze through the bars.
They're spaced farther apart up there.
Don't bother.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about being smart.
Think we should chill out awhile,
get the lay of the land.
Everything's under control.
Yeah? You know what he's doing to Karl?
He knows what he's doing.
It was a mistake
bringing those two here.
- What did you do to Sawyer?
- Nothing.
I heard him yelling.
You've got blood on your clothes.
It's not his blood!
Then whose blood is it?
It's the blood of a woman who's dying.
Jack, I need your help.
It's Jack!
- Jack!
- Doc!
Have you lost your mind?
- Bring him here?
- He's a doctor. He can help.
- This is not why...
- Do you want her to die?
Come on.
- What happened?
- Gunshot wound. To the abdomen.
Those aren't hers. Come on.
- What's he doing here?
- He's here to help.
- Tell him who did it. He oughta know!
- I need him out.
Get out. Go.
- Danny, they got it.
- No way! She's my wife!
I got the bullet out,
but she's still bleeding.
Right upper quadrant.
It's flowing badly.
No, I padded it.
Clamp under the liver
so I can look back there.
I'm not a surgeon.
I know. But I need you to do this.
Here.
Retrohepatic caval bleeding, behind
the liver, that's why you missed it.
I need lap pads,
as many as you've got.
A crash cart. Now!
Juliet, I need paddles.
It's broken.
We haven't had...
we haven't had anything happen before.
Time of death at...
She's gone.
They did this! They did this!
Danny, wait. Danny, wait, wait. No.
Take it easy, hoss!
Take it easy!
Shut up!
You love this guy?
What?
- I said do you love him?
- Stop!
Do you love him?
- Do you love him?
- Leave him alone!
- What are you doing? Stop!
Do... you...
...love... him?
- Yes, I love him!
I love him! Please!
Lock him up!
- I need to talk to you.
- Sorry, I'm busy.
It's important.
Please.
You were right. I loved her.
And I really thought she...
Ten mil's a lotta greenbacks, killer.
Tends to change things.
That's why you never get attached.
'Cause once you care,
that's when they can come at you.
Well, what did yours want?
I saw you the other day with a woman.
What did she want?
Something I ain't got.
That all?
You had yourself a good cry?
Mind if I go back
and see if George gets his farm?
I need you to move it.
The money.
The money you didn't steal?
We both know I did.
Lila's hired a P.I.
She's gonna find it.
Do this for me. You have to.
No. It's too dangerous.
I'll be a walking target.
If you don't help me,
the warden'll get it all. He'll win.
Please. Please.
Are you OK?
Dandy.
Guy hits like a girl.
No offence.
Why did he do that?
Hell if I know.
These people ever make
any sense to you?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What does it look like?
Hang on a second, Freckles.
I told you, the time ain't right.
You're the one who said we had to go.
- Well, that was before...
- Before what?
I don't know what they did to you, but
you're scared enough to lie about it.
And that scares me more than anything
they may have done to us before.
Wait!
- What are you doing?
- Getting you out.
- Don't!
- I'm not leaving you, Sawyer.
- I can get it open.
- You're already out. You gotta go.
- You gotta leave me!
- What?
Run!
- What did they do to you?
- Will you go!
- What is that thing?
- You run.
- Just go. It's every man for himself.
- Why didn't you fight back?
Tell me the truth,
for once in your life!
If you really love me...
...go.
I only said that
so he'd stop hitting you.
Run. Hurry!
What the hell are you doing?
Kate!
Damn it, Freckles, don't.
Every man for himself!
Live together, die alone.
You know Danny wants to kill him.
Danny can wait.
Should I bring Shephard back?
No.
I want him to sit with her
for a while longer.
I'm sorry they
had to put handcuffs on you.
I'm a fertility doctor.
I'm not used to death.
- What was her name?
- Cole.
Short for Colleen.
I shouldn't have...
I should've come to get you sooner.
It wouldn't have mattered.
There wasn't any more
that you could've done.
She was dead
before you put her on the table.
Are you saying that
to make me feel better?
I don't care about
making you feel better.
I'm gonna take you back now.
I'm sorry for bringing you here.
Whose x-rays are those? Outside?
Those are spinal x-rays, and they belong
to a man about 40 years old.
And whoever he is, he has a very large
tumour on his L-four vertebrae.
And I just happen to be
a spinal surgeon.
So, you tell me, Juliet.
Who am I here to save?
Is that...
...art?
No. Just an experiment.
OK.
- You want some fruit salad?
- Thanks. I'm not hungry.
You might want to wait a minute.
Why's that?
Good morning.
Let's go for a walk.
I have to be honest, Ford.
They first brought you here, I thought
you were nothing more than a dumb hick.
Now I know better.
You're a dumb hick
that knows how to steal.
Can we just get this over with?
Yeah, let's.
You remember Agent Freedman
from the Treasury Department?
So, what do you got?
The ten million's in a red Bronco in
a Store-It-Quick facility in Sawgrass.
Right off 441.
Unit 23-C.
That's where your money is.
As agreed,
the last six years of your sentence
have been commuted.
Soon as the truck is recovered,
and the funds confirmed,
your commission will be processed.
Now, how would you like that?
Set up a new account.
Don't matter what bank.
Just make it in Albuquerque.
OK.
Put it in the name
of Clementine Phillips.
OK. Clementine Phillips.
And I want it so there's no way she
can ever find out who the money's from.
Who's Clementine Phillips?
We done?
Congratulations, Ford.
You just lied and cheated
your way outta prison.
You're a free man.
Not much further, James.
Just to the top of the next rise.
What's up there?
Something I want you to see.
"Is it that little place
you always wanted, George?"
Sorry?
What, don't you read?
It's from Of Mice and Men.
You'd like it. Puppies get killed.
Bring me up here to kill me?
Make that thing you put inside me...
...blow up my damn heart?
Your heart's not gonna blow up, James.
The only thing
we put inside you was doubt.
The watch is
a heart rate monitor, but...
...nothing more.
Look.
We gave him a sedative,
not a pacemaker.
How do I know that's the same bunny?
That you didn't just
paint an eight on another one?
You don't.
You son of a bitch.
The rabbit wasn't the thing
I wanted to show you.
What the?
You ever been to Alcatraz?
Take the tour?
You're standing on a small island
roughly twice the size of Alcatraz.
And that over there?
That's your island.
The one you've come to know and love.
I just wanted you to know...
...there's nowhere to run.
You did all this just to...
...just to keep me in a damn cage?
We did all this because the only way to
gain a con man's respect is to con him.
You're pretty good, Sawyer.
We're a lot better.
Funny thing is, the pacemaker
wasn't what kept you in line.
It was when I threatened her.
You work so hard to make her think
you don't care,
that you don't need her, but...
"A guy goes nuts if he ain't got nobody.
It don't make no difference
who the guy is...
...long as he's with you.
I tell you...
I tell you a guy gets too
lonely and he gets sick. "
- What are you talking about?
- It's from Of Mice and Men.
Don't you read?
Come on.
Let's get you back to your cage.