Previously on Lost:
I think Michael has been compromised.
This camp Michael is leading you to
is where they will set their trap.
- I can go ashore undetected.
- How?
We will sail the boat and scout them.
This time, they will know
that we are coming.
- Hi, Jack. I'm Juliet.
- Where are my friends?
Tell me where my friends are!
My husband says it's time to leave.
Jack and the others aren't coming.
It's been over a day
since we lit the fire.
- They should be here by now.
- Jack knows we're out here.
He's counting on our signal.
Perhaps he's not able to see the smoke.
If he's north of us,
the mountains would block his view.
We need to sail along the coast, clear
the mountains, and start another fire.
No.
I told Jack I would light a fire.
I'm not abandoning him.
My husband thinks
we have to do as he says,
because he's the only one
who knows how to sail.
But he's wrong.
I can help you sail the boat.
Are you feeling any better?
I made the soup myself, but I won't take
it the wrong way if you don't like it.
You never made soup for me.
- Am I interrupting something?
- Would it really matter if you were?
We have a situation. Brian radioed in.
The Iraqi found the decoy village.
- Good. That's what we wanted.
- Brian followed him back to the shore.
- Ben, they have a sailboat.
- How?
I have no idea.
So they have a boat.
Sailing in circles will keep them busy.
They could find us.
- Ben...
- I'm thinking.
- How quickly to gather a team?
- Within the hour.
Then don't waste time talking to us.
Hey, Colleen.
I want that boat.
- Nice alarm clock.
- I've woken up to worse.
You want half a fish biscuit?
- What's this?
- Lunch.
- We need you to keep up your strength.
- Is that right?
- Danny, wait.
- Hold up.
They have a boat.
OK. Be careful out there.
What are you looking at?
What's wrong?
What's wrong is I'm married.
Right. That.
I don't wanna share you anymore.
Your English is excellent now.
You can go to America.
- Does anyone know you're?
- No.
All right, here's the jig.
You see these rocks here?
That's where you two come in.
You're gonna chop 'em loose
and you're gonna haul 'em outta here.
- You expect me to work in this dress?
- It's up to you.
You can take it off if you want.
How dare you.
Now, if you need anything,
you raise your hand.
- Ten minutes for lunch...
- I got a question.
- No questions.
- She asked a question.
If you try to run off,
you will be shocked.
- Shot? We don't even get a warning?
- Shocked. I said shocked.
If you talk to each other,
touch each other,
if you're slacking,
you're gonna get shocked.
You do anything at all that pisses me
off, you're gonna get shocked, OK?
- Let's get to work.
- Not until I see Jack.
Now, that was a quarter charge.
You got any more questions?
Soon as you're able to walk,
wheelbarrow's right over there.
Why should there be a dock
all the way out here?
Others.
The dock's decaying. It's overgrown.
It looks like it hasn't been used
in some time.
Whoever built it, they're not here now.
Let's bring the boat in, tie it to
the dock and build a fire on the beach.
The visibility's excellent,
and Jack will be able to see us
from miles around.
- Safe?
- Yes, Jin. Of course it's safe.
Hey! Get back to work.
Whatever you say, boss.
Hey.
Careful. Don't let them see you
talking to me.
Are they keeping you in the cages?
Did you see another guy in there
with you, about my age, named Karl?
No. It's just Sawyer and me.
You're not even supposed
to be in that cage.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Where'd you get that dress?
- They gave it to me.
- It's mine.
You can keep it.
Looks better on you anyway.
Wait.
Having fun yet, Freckles?
Quit staring at my ass.
Give me something else to stare at.
Hey!
Shut up.
Yes, sir, boss.
Thank you.
- What else can I do?
- Help your husband.
We need as much wood as we can find.
We're building quite a large fire.
We have to make sure
Jack will see the smoke.
Why are you lying to me, Sayid?
And what would you know
about lying, Sun?
You're putting our lives in danger.
I'm fairly certain
our friends have been captured.
There are tracks all over the dock.
- They're fresh, as recent as yesterday.
- You said this dock was abandoned.
That would be part of the lying
you mentioned.
You're not building this fire
for our people.
You're building it for The Others.
I suspect that when they see the smoke,
they'll send a scout party
to investigate.
By then, it will be night.
When they arrive, I'll ambush them.
I'll take two of them hostage
and I'll kill the rest.
Two?
One to make the other cooperate.
- What do you need me to do?
- Lie to Jin for another 20 minutes.
Why?
Because once the fire is lit,
it will be too late to go back.
Gun.
I don't think I understand.
- What is it?
- He knows what we're doing.
He knows it's a trap.
He says he understands English
better than I think he does.
He knows I betrayed him.
Gun.
Can you handle one of these?
It's an automa...
I think you'll be safer on the boat.
Sun, if by chance they get past us,
there's another gun.
It's inside the blue tarp
beneath the galley counter.
If they get past you,
that means my husband is dead,
and I won't care anymore.
As I said, the gun is inside the tarp.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Back off!
- James!
Put the gun down right now.
Put the gun down.
I don't think they're coming.
I want you to let me off this boat.
I can't do that.
- Why not?
- It's not my decision to make.
- There are five of my friends up there.
- Lower your voice.
OK.
- Stop. I'll shoot.
- No, you won't, Sun.
I know you, Sun-Hwa Kwon,
and I know you're not a killer.
Despite what you may think,
I am not the enemy.
We are not the enemy.
But if you shoot me,
that's exactly what we'll become.
Stop. I will. I'll shoot you.
Sun!
No!
There!
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
And please communicate
to your husband,
the next time I will listen to him.
We should go.
We have a long walk ahead of us.
- You OK?
- Never better.
- What the hell were you thinking?
- I couldn't help myself.
You just looked so damn cute
swinging that pickax.
- The chain gang looks good on you.
- Sawyer...
Two guards got some real fight in 'em.
The rest of 'em
I ain't that much worried about.
That heavy-set guy
packs a hell of a punch.
Shaggy-haired kid's got
some martial arts training,
but I could take him if I had to.
And FYI, those zapper things
got a safety on 'em.
Did you see the look on their faces
when you got ahold of that rifle?
I'm guessing most of these boys
never seen any real action.
But that blonde
who had a gun pointed at you,
she would have shot you, no problem.
Why'd she call you James?
Because that's my name.
I noticed something else, too.
You taste like strawberries.
You taste like fish biscuits.
So, what do we do now?
Well, Shortcake,
now we wait for these bastards
to make a mistake.
Sooner or later,
they're gonna let their guard down.
And when they do, we're gonna be there
to put 'em in their place.
Hello, Jack.
You know what's crazy, Jack?
A week ago, you and I were
in exactly the opposite situation.
I was the one locked up, and you were
the one coming in for visits.
And I know that you were angry
that I lied to you
about who I was, but...
hell, do you blame me?
I mean, let's face it, if I'd have
told you I was one of those people
you and your friends
have been calling Others all this time,
it would've been
right back to Sayid and his...
...fists.
Wouldn't it?
What do you want from me?
I want for you to change your...
perspective.
And the first step in doing that
would be for me to be decent enough
to introduce myself honestly, so...
Hi.
My name is Benjamin Linus,
and I've lived on this island
all my life.
You're not gonna shake?
Bring it in, please.
- Where are Kate and Sawyer?
- They're fine and they're close.
That's all I'm able
to tell you right now.
- You can tell me anything you want.
- Fair enough.
It's all I want to tell you.
I'm gonna make this really simple, Jack.
If you cooperate, we send you home.
- With what?
- When the time is right...
- You tell me now.
- Patience, Jack. Patience.
Home. Is that where you sent
Walt and Michael?
Yes.
If you could leave this island,
why would you still be here?
Yes, Jack. Why would we be here?
You're lying. You're stuck here
just like we are. You don't have any...
Your flight crashed
on September 22nd, 2004.
Today is November 29th.
You've been on our island for 69 days.
And, yes, we do have contact
with the outside world, Jack.
That's how we know
that during those 69 days
your fellow Americans
re-elected George W. Bush,
Christopher Reeve has passed away,
Boston Red Sox won the World Series.
- What?
- If you wanted me to believe this,
you should've picked somebody else
besides the Red Sox.
They were down three games to none
against the Yankees.
- Then they won eight straight.
- Sure. Sure. Of course they did.
Back to Foulke.
Red Sox fans have longed to hear it.
The Boston Red Sox
are world champions.
A clean sweep
of the St Louis Cardinals,
and the Red Sox celebrate in the middle
of the diamond here at Busch Stadium.
That's home, Jack, right there
on the other side of that glass.
And if you listen to me,
if you trust me,
if you do what I tell you
when the time comes,
I'll take you there.
I will take you home.