previously on "lost"...
hugo, you cango back to your camp.
What about my friends?
Your job is to tellthe rest of your people
they can never come here.
Rest in peace, mr.Eko.
And thank youfor helping me find my...
lift up your eyes and look north,john
I don't care what jack said.
They've got him, and we haveto get him back.
I owe him that.
The pearl is a monitoring station
where the activities of participants in the dharma initiative projects
can be observed and recorded.
I guesshe'll be expecting us.
Ping-pong table?
Where the helldid that come from?
Jin found it when he was outlooking for firewood.
We made legs for itand paddles.
Now all we needis a ball.
Found it?
Must have landed in the junglewhen the hatch exploded.
I thoughtthe hatch collapsed.
Look, dude, all I knowis the sky turned purple.
After that,I don't ask questions, just make myself a saladand move on.
Yeah, I can seethat's working for you.
Hey, you seen kate around?
Wow, she's not back yet?
Hmm.You guys find anythingwe can use for a ball?
no.
Hey,that's my "guns & ammo.
" Where the helldid you get it?
It was in the magazine stack.
We share things now.
Listen, zorro,it was in my stuff--
stuff you all decided to haveyourselves a little party
with while you thoughtI was dead.
Listen, hillbilly, if youwant it that bad, take it.
Just keep it.
we need to eat.
Are we still on course?
We're still heading northon a bearing of 3-0-5.
Yes.
I'm sensinga lack of confidence.
We've been walking for two days,
following a compass bearing provided bythe carvings on a stick.
And?
You really think we're just going to chanceupon where the others are?
I don't know whatwe're gonna chance on, sayid,
but my bearingis the only bearing we got.
I'm goingto find some fruit, and then,
john, we're goingto have a rational conversation regarding our next move.
-=www.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:Mina
www.ydy.com
Lost
Season 3  Episode 11
Y'all looking for something like...this?
Cool, a ball.
We need to do a little quid pro quo first.
I know I've been gone a while,
and y'all thought the general store
was having a going out of business sale,
but now I'm back, and I want whas mine.
Yeah, but it wasn't really yours to begin with.
"A"-- it was mine when I took it.
"B"--who the hell are you?
And "c"--because I'm fair, I'm gonna let you play me for it.
Play ping-pong?
That's right, avalanche.
You bastards put up your best player.
One game, and when I crush them,
y'all gotta bring me every piece of my stash back.
And if you lose?
I ain't gonna lose, but...
if I do, tell you what-- name it.
ooh, looks like crouching tiger and hidden dragon got something good.
Lay it on me.
No nicknames.
If y lose, no nicknames for anyone...
for a week.
Nice.
You're on.
Pick your player.
I'll be back in an hour, then let the slaughter begin.
are you sure it's completely isolated?
I've circled the house.
There's nothing but jungle surrounding it.
Here.
That dish still work?
A satellite dish of that size would have
broadcasting capabilities for thousands of miles.
Danielle, you once mentioned a radio tower.
Is this it?
I have never been here before.
The man in the house--you said you've seen him before?
On a video feed from the pearl station.
So who is he?
Only one way to find out...
we ask him.
What's this for?
If I'm unarmed, he won't feel threatened.
In case he is threatened, you can cover me from here.
Hey, where are you going?
I have no interest in that man inside the house.
I have survived on the island precisely by avoiding these types of encounters.
I'll wait for you by the stream...
for those of you who survive.
najeev.Najeev.
A man******see you.
did you cook this?
Yes, I did.
Well, it's delicious.
My name is sami.
Najeev.Thank you.
Please sit.Sit.
So where are you from, najeev?
I'm syrian.
Please.
You****man.
what do you want from me?
You're an excellent cook, and I...
I have a restaurant much nicer than this place.
Come take a look.
If you like it, I will hire you at twice your pay here.
You're offering a stranger a job because of a single meal?
I'm offering you a jobbecause we are outsiders here,
and because, uh,my chef just quit.
he's bn hit,he's been hit.
Not yet.
You wanna get shot, too?
I didn't cross the line!
We had a truce.
This is my land!
I'm not-- you said I could stay here!
I'm not who you--who you think I am.
My name is sayid jarrah.
I was on a planethat crashed here months ago.
A plane?!
I'm unarmed, I swear!
Stay right the!
drop the rifle!
Drop it right now.
Back up.
Are you all right?
You really did crash here?
Over 40 of us, yes.
I'll go in first,make sure it's okay.
Who are you?
My nameis mikhail bakunin...
and I am the last living memberof the dharma initiative.
watch your step.
please...sit.
here, let me.
You've had experiencetreating gunshot wounds?
I spent some timein afghanistan.
I had experiencewith field medicine...
in the soviet army.
In the kitchen on the top shelfthere is a medical kit.
Will you bring it, please?
It's all right, kate.
How did you get here?
I almost don't knowwhere to begin.
Why don't you beginwith the dharma initiative?
I grew up in kievand joined the soviet army.
I was stationed ata listening post in vladivostok.
After the cold war, after we lost the cold war,
my unit was decommissioned.
I was dismissedfrom my life in the military,
and after years of conductingunpleasant actions against our enemies,
I found myselfwanting to do something good,
so I replied toa newspaper advertisement.
An advertisement?
"Would you liketoave the world?" It read.
That's how I metthe initiative.
They're very secretive,very rich and very smart.
So when did youcome to the island?
11 years now.
I liked computers,communications equipment
and being alonelike a lighthouse keeper,
so they put mein this station.
They called it"the flame.
" What's the purposeof the flame?
To communicate withthe outside world, of course.
ready to play?
Ready to play?
Your move.
What happenedto the dharma initiative?
They're all dead,of course.
They foolishly initiateda war against the hostiles--
a "purge," they called it.
And how did yousurvive this purge?
By not participating in it.
I told you.
I like being alone.
And the hostilesallowed you to stay here?
After it was over, four men appearedin the yard.
They offered a truce.
They saidto imagine a line that extended all the wayaround the valley.
As long as I did notcross it, I would be left alone.
Then they took two cows, and I never saw them again.
They weren't interested inthe satellite dish in the yard?
Why would they be?
It hasn't functioned for years.
Who are they--these hostiles?
I do not know, but they were here fora long time before we were--
a very long time.
I'm looking for sami.
Sami!
Najeev,I'm so glad you came.
What do you think?
It's a simple place,as you can see, but we have good customers.
Ah, here's my wife.
She's in chargeof the kitchen.
Amira, come meet najeev.
Pleasure to meet you.
Are you sure this is him?
Yes.
Look, I don't knowwho you think I am--
what did you just say?
I told nadia to be polite,because you are my guests.
Nadia?
Mm, after nadia comaneci, the greatest athletethe world has ever known.
We havethe same birthday.
what?What?
now...
excellent work,if I say myself.
Thank you, mikhail.
Perhaps I can beginto earn your forgiveness by offeringsome iced tea.
I will also checkon your friend.
don't waste your time.
For ten years I've triedto defeat that game.
But it was programmed by three grand masters...
And it cheats.
Hmm.Wel I've playeda lot of computers,
and I'm pretty surethey don't know how to cheat.
That's what makesbeing human so distinctly...
wonderful.
what's wrong?
it just...it doesn't make any sense.
Why would theylet him stay here,
with all this stuff,all this equipment?
Actually,it makes perfect sense.
What are youtalking about?
The reasonthey let him stay here is becausehe is not dharma.
He is one of them.
He shot you,and you just let him...
why are we stillsitting here?
We are sitting here, kate,
because I am certainhe is not alone.
So...you really the number onedraft pick, grimace?
Yep.Are we playingwith the mercy rule?
Mercy rule?
Yeah, like,if I'm up 11-0, then I, you know,automatically win.
You're gonna go up 11-0?
No, I meaneither one of us.
Sure.
We can havea mercy rule.
Do you wanna volleyfor serve?
I'll tell you what--be my guest.
Take him down, hurley.
come on, hurley.
0 serving 0.
Yeah!Whoo!
1-nothing.
I grow the tea myself, so pardon its bitterness.
Any tea is good tea.
You know how long it's beensince we've seen ice?
I noticed a seriesof thick wires as I walkedaround the station.
This is the hub,but they go underground to
various stationsall over the island.
And these cables--do anyof them run into the ocean?
Yes.There isan underwater beacon that emits sonar pingsto
help guide in the vessels.
By vessels,you mean submarines?
Yes.
The initiativeused one to bring us here,
but I can imagine onlythat the hostiles have
either destroyedor commandeered it by now.
That explains howthey were able to
get round my positionand capture our sailboat.
You have a sailboat?
Till we lost itto your hostiles.
That's very unfortunate.
Well...
at least we were aeto kill one them.
Why are we continuingto play this little game...
when we all knowit has moved to the next stage?
Get some rope.
drink.
you were a torturer,were you not, in the republican guard?
Do you not recognizeone of your victims?
Do you not recognizethe woman that you tortured?
Do youot recognizemy wife?!
No, I've never...
you've confused mewith someone else.
Amira was arrested for harboringan enemy of the state.
She was heldfor three months while she was questioned.
Her arms bear the scars of those questions.
So I assure you, najeev,I am not confus.
My name is not najeev.
I am sayid jarrah.
I wasin the republican guard, and, yes,
I was an interrogator,but I have never seen your wife.
Maybe she saw meat the same facility,
but I do not know her!
I can remember every face of every personI've interrogated.
She remembers your face.
She remembers it so well that she recognized it
from a mere glimpse when we walked by the restaurantwhere you worked!
What do you want from me?
I want you to admitto what you did, and if you don't,
you will leave this roomin that bag.
How do you knowhe isn't alone?
The horse outsideis still saddled,
and the stirrupsare set up for someone much shorterthan thiman.
You think the others sentsomeone to keep him company?
They sent someone out here because they lostcommunications.
Maybe whenthe sky turned purple?
That would be my guess.
Well,if there's someone else here, they're hiding pretty good.
I checked every nook and crannyof this place...
not everynook and cranny, john.
are you readyto tell me the truth?
I have told you the truth.
I do not know you--uhh!
You tortured her.
no.
I would nevertouch a woman--uhh!
do you tnkthis will do any good,
that this will make me confessto something I didn't do?
My wife confessedto something she didn't do.
She confessed when you poured a panof boiling oil over her arms.
No, I did not.You have the wrong--
admit it!admit it!
I cannot admitto something I didn't do.
that is enough for today.
Then I willsee you tomorrow.
your move.
Your move.
what is it?
C-4...
explosive.
The whole place is wired.
Why?
I don't know.
Your move.
your move.
you win!
manual override achieved.
For pallet drop, enter 2-4.
For station uplink, enter 3-2.
For mainland communication, enter 3-8.
the satellite dish is inoperable.
Communications are down.
For sonar access, enter 5-6.
sonar is inoperable.
Has there been an incursion on this station by the hostiles?
If so, enter 7-7.
Keep your voice low and your handsin front of you.
stop right there.
Put the gunon the ground...now.
what are you doing?
It's her.
She was there!
She was at the dock.
She wasthere when we were kidnapped.
She knows where jack is.
Are there any moreof you here?
Let's take her upstairs.Come on.
John, we're coming up!
john!
out here.
Move.
This is simple.
Send her over to me,d I will release him.
Then we all go our separate ways.
Don't listen to him.
If he was gonna kill me,I'd be dead already.
Shut your mouth.
- Listen to me.
- Sayid, do not let her go.
I will execute you right here.
- He's not gonna do it.
- Be quiet, john.
I'm the only thing keeping him alive.
I swear to you-- mikhail.
Calm down, everyone.
- Mikhail!- sayid.
I'll handle thisjohn.
John...
don't let her talk to him!
stop!- Just do it, mikhail!
John!
Finish it!
Kill me.
Sorry I beat youso bad, dude.
Sorry you hustled me,you mean.
My mom had a tablein her basement,
and I played a lotat the insti--
this placeI hung out for a while.
I got kinda good.
Well, hooray for you.
Doesn't look likeat last slam caused
any long-term damageto your forehead...
d you got 3 points,which is better than zero.
Something you want?
Came to give you backsome of your stuff,
'cause, uh, you know, you're the kind of guythat needs stuff.
You a shrink now?
She'll be okay, dude-- kate.
I know you're worriedabout her, but she's with locke and sayid.
She's gonna be fine.
Yeah, well, thanksfor the pep talk, lump-- unh-unh, dude.
It's hurley...or hugo, if you want.
get bent, hugo.
you ready to go, locke?
I'll be there in a minute.
Has there been an incursion on this station by the hostiles?
If so, enter 7-7.
danielle!Danielle!
Tell me something.
Were you ever a memberof the dharma initiative,
or was everythingyou said a lie?
Of courseI'm wasting my breath.
I was never a member, but everything elseI told you was true.
I moved into the station after the purge.
The purge, in which a group of scientistsattacked your people?
Believe what you want,but that is what happened.
Your friends--did he kill them?
No.
They're collecting whatever may be usefulfrom the farmhouse,
and now we have our ticketto where the others live,
where we'll findyour daughter and jack, and finally,
perhaps,a way home.
There is nothingyou could do to me that would make melead you there.
I didn't say you were our ticket, did I?
This is a map showingelectrical and data cabling
running from the flame, here,
to a place called"the barracks," here.
It's comprised of housesand dormitories with water and power,
large enough to accommodatean entire community.
Sounds like a place well worthvisiting, don't you think?
There will come a timewhen your guard is down,
and when it is, I will not hesitate a momentbefore killing you.
- You shouldknow this before- - he's makingan excellent point.
You have a map.
Why keep him alive?
after my husband and ifirst arrived to paris,
I was afraidto ever leave our apartment.
So I would stareout the window into the alley,
and I would see this catlooking for scraps.
One day, some childrencame into the alley and trapped him in a box.
I watched themlight firecrackers and drop them in the box.
I could hear him howlfrom three stories above.
So finally, I had a reasonto leave my apartment.
I rescued this cat, and I brought him home.
He sits with mewhen I read.
He sleeps with me, and he purrs.
but...every once in a while,
he will bite meor scratch me.
He does this because sometimes he forgetsthat he is safe now.
So I forve himwhen he bites me,
because I knowwhat it is like to never feel safe.
And that isbecause of you.
So today...I ask only one thingof you.
I ask you now that you show methe respect of
acknowledgingwhat you did to me...
that it was youwho questioned me, that tortured me...
and that you remember me.
I remember you.
I remember your face.
Your face has haunted meever since I left iraq.
I am sorry.
I am so sorryfor what I did to you.
I forgive you.
When my husband returns, I will tell himI made a terrible mistake,
that it was not you...
and he will release you.
Why?
Why are youletting me go?
We are allcapable of doing what those children didto this cat...
but I will not dthat.
I will not be that.
We should kill him, sayid.
He already told usthat he would kill us.
No.
He's my prisoner.
I will decide his fate.
I can see you didn'tfind anything worth taking.
Actually, I just playedthat silly chess game again,
and now I realize whyyou didn't want me to beat it.
Meaning what?
What have you done, john?
That place was our one hope of communicationwith the outside world!
The computer saidif there was an incursion by the hostiles,
I should enter 7-7, so I entered 7-7.
We should go.
If anyone's around, this explosion's goingto attract their attention.
-=www.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:Mina
www.ydy.com
Lost
Season 3  Episode 11