If the Demon Tablet
can shut the Gates of Hell,
what can
the Angel Tablet do?
I can't let you take that,
Dean.
I just know that I have to
protect this tablet now.
From Naomi?
And from you.
From me?
What are you talking about?
Cass! Damn it.
My name is Naomi.
Oh, I know who you are.
And I know what you did to Cass
after he got out of Purgatory.
They're controlling us,
Castiel!
And now Castiel is
in the wind
with a hydrogen bomb
in his pocket.
God built a series of tests.
When you've done all three,
you can slam the Gates.
What's the second trial?
An innocent soul
has to be rescued from Hell
and delivered unto Heaven.
It's done.
That second trial hit you a lot
harder than that first one.
He's in my head, Dean.
Fear, the hiding.
And if he's in my head,
he knows where I am!
Thought you could
elude me forever?
He's gone.
Little geek
made a run for it.
Yeah, but where?
Kevin, come on! It's us!
Open up.
We're bleeding out here.
Come on, man. It's me.
Now it's wet me.
You forgot the knock.
What's the point of a secret
knock if you don't use it?
Sorry, Kevin.
We got it.
Got what?
Uh, we caught a tip
that Crowley was moving
his earth-side operations,
so we, uh, laid ourselves
an awesome trap.
And it worked.
We got the other half
of the tablet.
What?
It's the light
at the end of your tunnel, kid.
Don't say
we never got you nothing.
Holy crap.
Are you kidding?
We can get the third trial.
We can finally figure out
how to close the Gates of Hell
on Crowley's ass forever.
Sounds good to me.
So, we digging up the other half
of that thing or what?
Don't need to.
So, uh
Special K,
you keep your nose
to the God-stone.
We're gonna drive out
and make a lot of noise
a long way from here,
keep the safeboat safe for you.
We'll be back
as soon as we can, okay?
I guess he's okay.
All right. Don't forget
to lock up after us.
So, it's three trials.
Three trials and the Winchesters
get to lock the door on me.
Ha!
You, fake Sam,
if you're gonna tip our hand,
I'll have to scrub
Kevin's short-term memory again.
And that's risky,
so watch the patois in there.
Patois?
Your slang.
"Special K,"
"nose to the God-stone" --
that's the way Dean speaks.
Sam is...more basic,
more sincere.
Remember, I want two distinct,
authentic characterizations.
Yes, sir.
I was born to direct.
? Supernatural 8x21 ?
The Great Escapist
Original Air Date on May 1, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
All right, here we go --
John Winchester's famous
cure-all kitchen-sink stew.
There you go.
Enough cayenne pepper in there
to burn your lips out,
just like
dad used to make.
You want me to do the whole, uh,
airplane thing with the spoon?
When was
the last time you ate?
I don't --
days, Sam.
It's been three days.
When did you get that?
When did you start
throwing off heat waves?
Here.
Enough! Dean, please.
The bloody handkerchiefs,
the fever, the shaky legs --
this is not good.
Well, I'm not good,
and I'm not going to be good
until we can start moving again,
until I can start
the third trial.
Trial? I wouldn't let you
start a moped.
We're on the rails
with this thing, okay,
and the only way out of it
is through it.
Believe me, I know,
and you know how bad
I want to slam the door
on all those sons of bitches.
But you got to let me
take care of you, man.
You got to let me help you
get your strength back.
This isn't
a cold or a fever
or whatever it is
you're supposed to feed.
This is part of it all.
Those first two trials --
they're not just things I did.
T-they're doing something
to me.
They're changing me,
Dean.
It's Kevin.
Finally.
Sam, Dean,
I've set up this message
with some software
and a remote server
so it'd send itself to you
if I didn't reset it
with a command once a week,
which means I didn't reset it
this week.
And there's only one reason
I wouldn't,
which means if you're watching
this then I --
then I'm -- I'm dead.
I'm dead, you bastards,
so screw you, screw God,
and everybody in between!
Crowley must have gotten to me,
and the one thing I know is
that I won't break this time.
I'm not sure how I know,
but -- but I do.
I've been uploading
all my notes and translations.
I'm sending you the links
so you can get all of it.
You guys are gonna have to try
to figure out the rest.
I'm sorry.
I know it was my job,
but I -- but I couldn't...
I'm sorry.
Damn it!
Yeah. I know you
haven't seen him, Keel.
Nobody has.
All right,
well, if you talk to Garth,
then just
have him call in.
Yeah.
Garth still M.I.A.?
How about the other Prophets
in line?
I mean, if Kevin is, uh...
Is dead, then won't one of them
be activated?
Nothing.
No, not a peep.
Here we are -- no lead,
no tablet, squat.
Well, I mean,
we got all this.
We should have
moved him here.
I guess I've been
acquiring the taste.
Yeah? The coffee's
not too bad here.
You know, I remember
when you first discovered it.
Before you started brewing it,
you'd just chew the berries.
Folktale is true, by the way.
You learned it from the goats.
Uh, been on the road
a long time, huh?
Feels like I've been
on the run forever.
Um, I'm sorry, mister,
but you're gonna have to order
more than coffee
if you want to keep
the table.
Oh, of course. Um...
I'll have the smart-heart
beer-battered tempura tempters.
Of course.
Coming right up.
They're getting closer.
What's that, chief?
I swear to God, Lance,
the guy just disappeared.
You on the crack again,
Perry?
Ion, tell me
that you have good news.
He's using
a clever tactic.
It's a restaurant
called Biggerson's.
The humans have built hundreds
of them, almost exactly alike.
What are
you talking about?
It's their sameness.
Castiel
is using it against us.
Now, we try to
orient ourselves,
but it's as if we're in
every Biggerson's at once,
trapped in a quantum
superposition,
now, he chooses
which to go to next --
that's what's giving him
the edge.
You're saying that
you can't catch him?
There -- there is
just so many Biggerson's.
Very well.
You say
he can't be caught.
Then we will simply have to
make him stop.
Hmm.
There it is again,
every time.
Hmm?
This symbol -- I know it.
Now, Kevin has it down as --
as sort of like a signature
for the scribe of God.
It appears every time
Metatron makes one of his,
uh, like editor's notes.
Okay.
But I think
I've seen it before.
I mean,
it was a long time ago.
It was one of my, uh,
humanities courses at Stanford.
They taught word of God
at Stanford?
No, uh...It was an overview
of native American art.
I think
it's a petroglyph.
A petro-what, now?
This one belonged
to a tiny tribe in Colorado,
more of a-a clan, really.
It says here they held
onto their scrap of mountains
when all the other tribes
fell to the white man.
Uh, so this glyph was
a territorial marker.
Closest translation --
"Messenger of God."
Dean, we have to go there.
On that hunch?
You can barely function.
I'm only gonna get worse.
I mean, until I get back
to the real job,
until we find the third trial --
we're out of Prophets!
We're not gonna figure out
what Kevin couldn't!
I say we go
to this messenger of God
who wrote it
in the first place!
And you think
that this Metatron
is hiding out in the mountains
with a bunch of Indians?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
You're not -- you're not really
supposed to say "Indians."
It's...
We should go.
You are delirious.
You have to stop.
They said
you have to stop.
No.
They said you have to stop.
You have to stop.
No.
They said you have to stop.
You have to stop.
Nice place.
Morning. Hi.
Uh, we'd like a room.
Here, please.
Hmm.
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
He has the flu.
You have to stop.
They said you --
Aah!
Can't hear myself think.
We were supposed to be their
shepherds, not their murderers.
Not always, Angel.
There was that day back in Egypt
not so long ago
where we slew
every firstborn infant
whose door wasn't splashed
with lamb's blood,
and that was just P.R.
Well, I wasn't there.
Oh, you were there.
You just
don't remember it.
How -- how many times
have you torn into my head
and washed it clean?
Frankly, too damn many.
You're the famous spanner
in the works.
Honestly,
I think you came off the line
with a crack
in your chassis.
You have never done
what you were told,
not completely.
You don't even die right,
do you?
Where is the Angel Tablet,
Castiel?
In the words of a...
good friend,
bite me.
Oh, we'll bite.
Don't worry.
Go. Search all
these...Biggerson's.
He must have hidden it
along the way.
I can barely see.
I need food.
All right. Uh, barbecue ribs,
mashed potatoes.
Garlic mashed potatoes.
Garlic mashed potatoes,
mixed greens with baby lettuce,
cornbread,
and, uh, pad Thai.
Garth says there's a good little
place on the other side of town.
What the hell?
Kid's been working hard.
Those guys
aren't half bad.
No, sir.
You chose well.
Of course,
if I wasn't running everything,
I could have played Dean
myself.
Oh, you would have made
a great Dean, sir.
Regular tourist mecca
we got here.
We're the only guests
in this whole place.
Last entry in the registry
was in '06.
Hey,
you remember when, uh...
when dad took us to the bottom
of the Grand Canyon
on that pack-mule ride?
The what?
And your, uh --
your mule kept farting,
just letting go,
like gale force.
Dude, you were like
four years old.
I barely remember that.
You rode a farty donkey.
Okay, uh,
I'm gonna go check out
the Two Rivers Travel Museum
and Trading Post.
Yeah, yeah!
I'm gonna --
I'm gonna, um --
I'm gonna follow
the hotel manager,
D-Dr. Scowley-Scowl.
He's like a villain
from "Scooby-Doo."
No, hey,
uh, little big man,
you should get some rest.
Yeah,
I can do that, too.
The people
of the Two Rivers tribe
came to this land
centuries ago,
a land that
was harsh and stony.
But their mighty leader
told his people
that they must stay here.
He claimed that
this was the home on Earth
of the great spirits'
sacred messenger
and that if
they'd made offerings,
their blessings
would be many.
What were the offerings?
Huh?
Uh, what did the great spirit's
sacred messenger ask for?
Stories.
He asked the people
to tell him stories.
I bet I know
what the blessings were.
Sam?
I've been all over them.
It's not there.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Let us put the tablet
back where it should be.
I need to protect it.
From the Angels?
From all of us.
I'm just going to have to
pull you apart, aren't I?
Naomi, darling.
Miss me?
Get off! What the hell?!
Take it easy, man.
God!
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy. Take it --
Found you on the floor,
passed out.
Your temperature was 107.
I had to force it down
or you were toast.
He's here, Dean.
The Metatron is here.
I know it.
I can hear him.
What are
you talking about?
All I know is that
I'm connected to it somehow.
What, like you got
a link to him, like a Prophet?
I don't know!
I just know he's here.
The Metatron is here.
Okay. Here where?
I can show you.
The manager --
he was delivering books to him.
Books?
Books.
Hard-covers, paperbacks,
novels -- books.
Stories.
Do you like it?
I had my R&D people melt down
one of your Angel blades,
cast it into bullets.
Seems to do the trick.
How dare you.
I am the daringest devil
you've ever met, love.
We've been here before,
haven't we?
Let's see
who blinks first.
Hmm.
Hi, Cass.
That's right, Cass.
I got me
an Angel on the payroll.
It's that kind of universe
these days.
Now grab him
and follow me.
Hey, kid, you okay?
I can't, all right?
It's the break
in the stone.
There's key writing.
I-I can't make it out.
You guys were right.
I-I do need the other half
of the tablet to get the trial.
It's not too far from here.
Awesome.
Uh, well, what's the 10-20?
Just wanted to take a moment
away from the main action...
...to chat
with my old business partner.
I assume
you won't die just yet.
Takes a painful long time
to bleed out from the gut.
You can do
whatever you want, Crowley.
I will never tell you
where I buried the tablet.
I know, Cass.
I know.
Luckily...
I don't believe
you have to.
I've been getting
regular updates
from my expensive friend
here.
Naomi should have caught you
out of the gate,
seeing as lately
she's been knuckles deep
in that melon of yours.
She thinks
that your touching the tablet
has broken her spell over you.
Hmm?
The tablets
weren't meant for the Angels,
and they weren't
meant for you.
She's got
a lot on her plate,
so you can't fault her
for missing it.
I was thinking to myself,
"self,
"if Cass got away from her
by touching the tablet,
why would he ever stop
touching the tablet?"
And then I thought
to myself,
"self...he hasn't
stopped touching the tablet,
now, has he?"
Aha!
Oh, you're a pip, you are.
What?
Oh!
This is the king.
The kid told us
where the other half was,
but it...wasn't.
Dab of crap tricked us,
sent us into some kind
of Hunter mousetrap.
You jackasses.
You're ruining my streak!
Watch him.
I'll be right back.
I should be taking you
to the E.R.
They can't
do anything for me.
You know, I've been
remembering things --
little things
so clearly.
What?
Donkey rides?
You used to read to me,
um, when I was little --
I-I mean really little, from --
from that old, uh
"Classics Illustrated"
comic book.
You remember that?
No.
"Knights
of the Round Table."
Had all of
King Arthur's knights,
and they were all on the quest
for the Holy Grail.
And I remember looking
at this picture of Sir Galahad,
and -- and --
and he was kneeling,
and -- and light streaming
over his face.
And I remember...
thinking, um,
I could never
go on a quest like that...
...because I'm not clean.
I mean,
I-I was just a little kid.
You think maybe I knew,
I mean,
deep down, that...
I had...
demon blood in me
and about the evil of it
and that I...
wasn't pure?
Sam,
it's not your fault.
It doesn't matter
anymore,
because these trials...
...they're purifying me.
They were here, the -- the --
the books, the boxes!
They -- they're gone.
Who are you?
Metatron?
This is Metatron?
Sit down.
Who sent you?
We came on our own.
We're the Winchesters.
I'm Dean. This is Sam.
You work for Michael?
Or Lucifer?
What, you really
haven't heard of us?
What kind of angel are you?
W-we're
the freaking Winchesters.
How --
how far can this go?
Shh. Shut up.
Ion...
How far can we
let it all drop?
This charge
was left to us.
It's our mission.
Do you even know
what the mission was?
They've been
in all our heads.
We aren't machines for them
to program and reprogram.
That wasn't
what this was meant to be.
Nothing matters.
You are so wrong,
brother.
It all matters.
You little prat.
You having fun yet?
Screw you.
Am I seeing this?
How did you
figure it out?
It started when they forgot
the secret knock.
But really, it --
it was the way they acted.
I don't think
on their best day Sam and Dean
would go into town
and get me a barbecue dinner,
n-not when there are
leftover burritos in the fridge.
So...
Demons
were too polite?
Yeah.
Well,
I'll be a son of a whore.
Michael and Lucifer --
t-those -- those dudes
are in the deep fryer.
Yeah. We put them there
ourselves.
What about
Gabriel and Raphael?
Dead.
You really don't know this?
I've been very careful.
Hey, can you --
Can you turn that down?
Turn what down?
Oh.
You're resonating.
Resonating? What --
what do you mean, resonating?
You've undertaken
the trials.
You're trying to pull one
of the great levers, aren't you?
You're pretty far along,
too.
You get that far along, you
start resonating with the word
or with its source
on the material plane --
with me.
You said you were being careful.
Careful how?
I'm not one of them.
I'm not an Archangel.
I'm really
more run-of-the-mill.
I worked
in the secretarial pool
before God chose me
to take down the Word.
Anyway, he seemed very worried
about his work,
what would happen to it
when he left,
so he had me write down
instructions.
Then he was gone.
After that...
The Archangels took over.
They cried,
and they wailed.
They wanted their father back.
I mean, we all did.
But then --
then they started to scheme.
The Archangels decided
if they couldn't have dad,
they'd take over the Universe
themselves.
But they couldn't
do anything that big
without the Word of God.
So I began to realize
maybe they would realize...
they needed me.
So, you get
a ruffle in your feathers
and just decide
to disappear,
go stick your head in the sand
forever?
You have no idea
what's been going on out there?
Nope.
That's the whole point.
You soldiers
down in the Garrison --
at least they let you
believe the lie.
Upstairs, working for Naomi,
working in intelligence,
we had no option
but to live in the dirt.
She never reset me completely.
I always knew too much.
I had to --
I had to do my job.
Ion...
Shut up!
So you have been holed up here
or -- or -- or in a wigwam
or before that,
in some cave,
listening to stories,
reading books?
And it was something
to watch.
What you brought
to his Earth --
all the mayhem,
the murder,
just the raw, wild invention
of God's naked apes --
it was mind-blowing.
But really, really...
It was your storytelling.
That is the true flower
of free will,
at least
as you've mastered it so far.
When you create stories,
you become Gods
of tiny, intricate dimensions
unto themselves.
So many worlds.
I have read as much as it's
possible for an angel to read,
and I haven't caught up.
You know what?
Pull the freaking trigger.
What?
Pull the freaking trigger...
Sam.
...you cowardly piece of garbage.
Hey.
All the time
you've been hiding here,
how much suffering
have you read over?
Humanity's suffering.
And how much of it has been
at the hands of your kind?!
Hey, hey.
You want a story?
Try Kevin Tran's story.
He was just a kid.
He was a good,
straight-"A" kid,
and then he got sucked in to
all of this -- this Angel crap
and became a Prophet of
the Word of God -- your Prophet.
And you should have been
looking out for him, but no!
Instead, you're here,
holed up, reading books.
He's dead now
because of you.
You know the Winchesters are
up to the third trial?
You know they're gonna
shut the door on Hell?
I'm not worried, kid.
You have no idea
what's on this demon tablet,
all right, the power you could
have gotten with this
if you weren't running around like
a chicken with his head cut off.
You think
I can't make you tell?
I know you can't,
and you do, too.
You know what?
I've already won.
I have the Angel Tablet,
you little smudge.
And I got deals and plans
up the jacksie.
And I don't...
Need...You!
Is that it?
Is he good?
Give him a minute.
How did you get past
Crowley's angel warding?
I'm the scribe of God.
I erased it.
But you saw, right?
I mean, you --
you're caught up
on everything
that's been going on,
all the crap
that your brethren's
been doing to humanity
all this time?
I saved the boy,
didn't I?
But are you in?
With us, I mean.
You really intend
on closing the doors of Hell?
Seems like the thing to do,
don't it?
It's your choice.
And that's what this has
all been about --
the choices
your kind make.
But you're gonna have to weigh
that choice.
Ask yourself, "What is it
going to take to do this,"
and, "what will the world
be like after it's done?"
Dean?
Dean?!
Kevin?
Hey.
We thought we lost you, kiddo.
I'm good.
Second half of the tablet,
and I got it.
Third trial.
I didn't tell Crowley.
So what is it?
To cure a Demon.
Yeah.
Who are you?
Cure a Demon?
Okay, ignoring the fact
that I have no idea
what that actually means,
if we -- if we do this,
you get better, right?
I mean, you'll stop
trying to cough up a lung
and -- and --
and bumping into furniture?
I feel better, yeah,
uh, just having
a direction to move in.
Well, good,
'cause where we're headed
doesn't sound like a picnic.
But we're
heading somewhere.
The end.
Cass?!
A little help here.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==