A cross won't repel them.
Sunlight won't kill them.
But the bloodlust --
that part's true.
That was vampire blood
he dosed you with.
Lights are too bright?
Sunshine hurt your skin?
I get so hungry.
Just so you know,
911's on speed-dial.
Krissy, you can trust me.
So your dad's on the road right now?
Been gone a while?
My dad left,
and he didn't come back.
So I'm coming with you.
No. Hell, no.
I'm coming!
Why is that waitress
getting into that truck?
All right. Come on.
Give it up. Good work.
You're a dweeb.
Hold on -- I got you!
Dean!
He can't help you.
No one can.
I guess I'll have
to help myself, then.
I'm retiring.
We're so lame.
Yeah, we are.
Take care of yourself.
? It's cold outside ?
? and I'm not quite ?
? ready for the morning light ?
? oh, oh, oh ?
? my hands are tied ?
? 'cause if I tried ?
? to leave this place,
I'd surely die ?
? hey ?
? I'd surely die ?
What was that?
What?
? Hey ?
There's no one out here but us, krissy.
? hey ?
? I'd surely die ?
What?
No, no. No, no, no.
Okay.
No. No. Don't leave me here!
Aidan!
Don't leave me here!
Oh, God.
You okay?
That was close.
Next time one of you
can be the bait.
It's him.
One down. Two to go.
? Supernatural 8x18 ?
Freaks and Geeks
Original Air Date on March 27, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
so, what are
we looking at again?
"Two young women found
near the freeway
with their throats
ripped out."
Sounds vampy to me.
Yeah, maybe.
Listen, if you want to
take a knee on this one
if you're not feeling
up to it...
What?
You know, the trials,
what Cass said,
that you got
what he can't cure.
Hmm, which means what,
exactly?
Well, I don't know.
You tell me. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Me?
Yeah. Um,
Cass dinged you up pretty good.
And?
And I just wanted to make sure
you're okay.
What,
like my feelings?
If that's what you want to
talk about, sure.
Okay.
I'll tell you what.
Why don't I go get some,
uh, herbal tea.
Okay.
And you can find some
cowboy junkies on the dial.
Eat me, Dean.
And you know what?
We'll just talk it out.
Good talk.
Nay, great talk!
Very healthy!
FBI?
You're here about the lady
killer murders, aren't you?
The lady killer murders?
Yeah,
coined it myself.
Congratulations.
What can you tell us?
Well, both victims were female,
under 21,
and here's the kicker --
they were drained
of all their blood.
Huh.
Exactly.
We found that strange, also.
But then last night,
things got even stranger.
Last night?
Yeah.
We set up a security cam
on Fuller's Point
for safety purposes.
It's where our local young
people like to go make out.
Last night,
things got crazy.
Hell of a thing,
ain't it?
Uh, you I.D.
any of these people?
Well, not yet.
Crime scene was empty
when we got there.
No vic, no nothing.
Uh, I'm thinking it's some kind
of cult or a drug thing.
So I put a statewide A.P.B. out
on these three
about an hour ago.
I'm gonna need you
to call that off.
And we're gonna need
this footage.
What?
Sheriff,
why do you think we're here?
You just crossed streams
with a federal investigation.
Now, I suggest you cooperate,
call off your A.P.B.,
or you're gonna find yourself
in a world of hurt.
Uh...
Right.
So, what was that
all about, G-man?
You remember
Krissy Chambers?
Uh, yeah, the Vetalas case,
right?
They were working
that truck stop by the freeway.
She and her dad
helped us shut 'em down.
Right, and then he promised
to go civilian
so she wouldn't
grow up to be a hunter.
Well, guess who the star
of this snuff film is?
Come on.
Well, maybe he doesn't know
she's doing this.
What, sneaking out
in the middle of the night
to go hunt monsters
with the Apple Dumpling gang?
Is that what kids are doing
for kicks these days?
Okay. Then maybe he knows,
and he's helping her out.
What, get caught
on "Candid Camera"?
Let's just go find her before
she gets into any more trouble.
You're 25?
Actually,
I think I'm 40.
I told you...
I have a boyfriend.
Then how come I couldn't
find him in your cellie?
Because we only Skype.
Right. And let me guess --
he also lives in Canada?
You know, he does, actually.
Oh.
A small town called
"kiss my ass."
Okay.
But...
You sure were giving off
a different vibe in the car.
Good. You're back.
Let's do this.
Vamp was last seen
by an ATM camera
checking into this hotel.
I tapped into the hotel's
security cams and found him.
Room 215.
Okay.
Let's do this.
You transmitting?
You bet.
He alone?
I can't tell.
Hey, how about we start
a new tradition,
and before each job, we give
each other good-luck kisses?
How about I punch you
in the throat instead?
You know you're not gonna
get anywhere with Krissy
with those cheesy moves.
How about you stop
putting salt in my game
and mind
your own business?
Blood?
Hey, Krissy.
What are you two
doing here?
Saving your bacon,
that's what.
Does it look like
my bacon needs saving?
Wait. How'd you find me?
I paid cash everywhere.
Only two hotels
within a 20-mile radius,
and we paid cash, too --
just more.
Freaking clerk.
Krissy,
where's your dad?
Dead.
Well, let's do this again,
like, never.
Now go. We got this.
We who?
And got what?
A vampire.
Sorry. A what?
We're in.
The room's clear.
Nobody here but a vic.
I got him!
You --
son of a bitch.
We need to call an ambulance!
Ambulance is on its way.
She's in shock.
I'll stabilize her.
We'll leave her here
for the paramedics.
Please!
Don't shoot me!
Please, don't --
Please...
It hurts so bad!
How did you drop him
so quickly?
Darts filled
with dead man's blood.
Where's the blue van?
What blue van?
The blue van
that he was Usain Bolting it to?
Never mind.
Wait, stop!
This is not your kill.
What are
you talking about?
Three months ago, this
blood banger snuck into a house
and killed three people
in their sleep.
What?!
No! I didn't do that!
One was a woman --
never hurt anyone!
The other two,
a brother and a sister.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I came home from a friend's
house, and I found them.
They were my family!
This isn't happening.
I didn't do anything,
I swear.
Please, help me!
It's okay.
It's over.
We need to talk to you
privately.
You know this guy?
Yeah.
We have a past.
All right. So, you're
gonna have to catch me up.
What --
did your dad, uh --
he couldn't quit the life,
could he?
No, he did.
For a while,
it was amazing.
We had dinner every night
at a table.
We watched TV, went on walks.
Even went to the mall.
And then?
And then...
The past
came a-knockin'.
I woke up one morning
and found him dead....
...his throat ripped out.
Well, I'm sorry.
Me too.
If it weren't for Josephine
and Aidan,
I don't know
how I would have made it.
So, they both lost
their families, as well?
Yeah, the same vamps
we're hunting together --
a nest.
Well, look, I am sorry
to rain on your parade,
but you are way too young
to be doing this.
You're never too young
to kill monsters,
especially the ones
that kill your family.
Hunting isn't all about killing
and revenge.
I thought we had this chat
last time.
Do you have any, uh --
do you have any family
that's still out there?
An aunt in Cincinnati.
Why?
'Cause you're packing a bag,
and we're taking you there.
I think Victor's gonna have
a problem with that.
Victor?
He took us in,
showed us everything we know.
Wait. So,
what are we talking here?
Some sort of kid's school
for hunters?
Don't be such a dweeb, okay?
We're not the X-Men.
Victor's helping us
get revenge.
Yeah, well, I don't care
what he is. He sucks.
'Cause you and your little crew
here got caught.
And if it wasn't for me,
your faces would be splattered
all over the news.
Well, you know,
so what?!
Maybe it's time
that people know the truth
about what's really going bump
in the night.
Oh, and cause panic?
Create mayhem?
Yeah,
that's a great plan.
Look, I don't need you
to save me, Dean.
I'm not a little kid
anymore.
Wow.
What happened?
Teenagers, that's what.
She tell you about Victor?
Yeah. What do we think?
Well, didn't we meet up
with a hunter named Victor
one time in Spokane?
That's a long time ago.
I haven't heard
about him since.
All right,
so, these kids are --
Dangerous and off their meds?
Yeah, no kidding.
So, what?
We go and talk with Victor?
Ready?
Okay.
Not what I'd call
a compound.
Huh.
What's wrong?
It's just not
what I expected.
And what was that?
A little more
"Lord of the Flies",
less Huxtables.
Sorry to disappoint.
Victor Rogers.
We met -- a Rugaru hunt
in Washington.
I'm Sam. This is Dean.
Oh, yes.
The Winchesters.
Right.
Hey.
Ohh.
Better now?
Much.
And what do
we always say?
Move on,
but never forget.
Good. Now, don't you have
a trig test in the morning?
Oh, I'm good, Vic.
No test.
I'm just gonna chill,
Uh-huh.
play video games.
Yeah, keep dreaming.
Because I asked you to clean
your room twice,
and you
still haven't done it.
Go on.
And you.
A full report about the hunt
on your desk by morning.
Okay.
I'll be in my room.
Drink?
Sure.
So,
these kids go to school --
like, school-school,
real school?
Yes, and they're doing
incredibly well
considering
all they've been through.
Okay,
so how does this work?
What, after --
after soccer practice
and --
and the bake sale,
they, uh,
chop vampires' heads off?
Well, yeah.
I think a balanced approach
is best, don't you?
But they're kids.
They shouldn't be hunting
at all.
You got to break this up
right now.
When I found them,
they were lost, confused, angry.
I gave them family
and purpose.
And you want to
take all that away? Why?
So they
don't get killed.
They know the risks.
Yeah,
but why take them?
Because the next generation
of hunters has to be better.
Better than what?
Better than us.
Oh, come on, guys.
I know your friends.
I mean, Martin was insane.
And somebody obviously dropped
Garth on his head
when he was a baby.
And I know you two loved
that Bobby guy,
but he was
a barely functional alcoholic.
Watch it.
No disrespect meant,
but Josephine is
an all-state athlete
and National Merit scholar.
Aidan is so fast
he could pick your pocket
before you could
even blink.
And Krissy,
oh she's just a natural-born
leader and hunter.
So what?
So these kids are
the cream of the crop.
They are the Beatles.
They are the dream team.
And once they get
their revenge...
...they'll be better hunters
than any of us ever dreamed of.
This is crazy.
Is it?
They got a pretty good life.
Kids aren't
supposed to hunt, Sam.
We did.
Yeah, and look
what that did for us.
Well, maybe
they're doing it right.
Maybe they can hunt
and have a real life.
You know
that's not true.
Why, 'cause it didn't work
for us?
Because it doesn't work
for anybody.
Okay, then what
do you want to do?
'Cause Victor's
not gonna stop this.
They said they were hunting
a nest, right?
Yeah.
Well,
let's hunt it for 'em.
Well, that way,
until we can figure out
what to do with Victor,
they stay safe.
All right, um...
So, what's your move?
I want to talk to that girl
who was tied up at the hotel.
Something didn't smell right
about that.
Why don't you stay here
and look after the Brady Bunch?
Sam, just in time.
Grab a seat.
Waffles?
Yeah, Krissy's fav.
My dad used to make 'em for me
all the time.
I think it was the only thing
he knew how to cook.
Interact.
Yeah, nerd.
And you -- manners.
We're gonna be late.
Come on.
Grab your stuff.
I'll pick you up after school.
See ya.
Wow.
Whirlwind, right?
Yeah.
It's always like that
with kids.
You got any?
Me? Uh, no.
You want any?
Uh, I don't know.
Trust me,
the answer's yes.
These yours?
Yeah.
Well,
until we went camping
and a Wendigo ripped them
to shreds.
Sorry.
Is that why you're doing this,
taking all these kids in?
But you know what I realized,
Sam, is that these kids,
they don't have to live it
the way we have.
You know, crappy hotel rooms,
always moving,
no family, no life.
It's not the only way.
Like I told the cops already,
I'm not sure why Jimmy Day
would do something like this.
Jimmy Day?
Wait, so you knew the guy
that grabbed you?
Everyone in town knows Jimmy.
He's a hero.
We had a parade for him
downtown
when he came back
from Afghanistan.
Uh, sorry.
When was this?
A few weeks ago.
So, uh...
this Jimmy Day guy,
he -- he just grabbed you
and took you to the hotel?
No.
I-I came from work
and was in the parking lot
when this blue van
pulled up.
This guy with a hoodie
asked me directions.
That's all I remember,
till I woke up tied to that bed.
And was hoodie there,
too?
Just Jimmy, and he was crying,
saying he was sorry and all.
That he was sorry?
At first I thought
he was gonna kill me.
But then he just...
he just seemed scared.
Hey.
What happened to school?
Victor pulled us out.
Why?
'Cause we've found
another target.
Who?
The vamp that killed
Krissy's dad.
You ready?
Okay.
Pulled this from a security
camera at a nearby gas station.
Wait, how do we know
this is definitely her?
Police sketch,
victim's accounts...
...and this.
My dad's necklace.
My mom gave it to him
on their anniversary.
Are you sure this is
a video surveillance pic?
It's her!
Excuse me.
Hey. You there?
Yeah. How did it go
with the girl?
Strange. Might be
that vampire wasn't lying.
He was fresh made
within the month,
but Josephine's family
was murdered three months ago.
So, who killed them,
then?
I don't know.
I'd like to talk to whoever's
driving that blue van.
Other than that...You?
Something's up.
Victor says he has
a surveillance photo
of the vampire that killed
Krissy's father.
But, Dean...
I'm not so sure.
Why's that?
There's no time stamp
on it.
Okay.
So you think he's lying?
Well, that, or he's just wrong.
It's hard to say.
Yeah, I never trust a guy
who wears a sweater.
You want me to head
back there?
No, no. I'm good.
Let me do some more digging.
All right. I'm gonna talk to the
hotel clerk, see what he knows.
Hey.
Where did everybody go?
Tracking that vamp.
Well, I think we got a problem
a lot closer to home.
Look at this.
See that blue van?
My brother saw it
outside the hotel yesterday.
We think he's working
with the vampire we popped.
Looks like
we're going huntin'.
Ahh.
Nice to see you again.
Yeah, I bet.
Listen, I need to know
who, uh, checked
into room 215 yesterday.
215.
It was some guy
wearing a hoodie,
so it was hard
to make out his face.
He drive a blue van,
by any chance?
Do I look
like a valet?
He took one of those.
Which one?
The one that says "lodge"
on it.
"Conway Springs Lodge."
Yep, big during
the summer season.
But this time of year,
it's closed.
How far away is it
from here?
Oh, it's a couple miles
down the road.
Hey!
Who the hell are you?!
Answer me!
Please make it go away.
It hurts so much.
What? Wha...
No, shut them off!
They're too bright!
Not till you tell me
what the hell's going on here.
I don't know!
Aah!
What's happening to me?
Come here.
That's never happened
to you before?
No. No, there's
something wrong with me.
That -- that guy,
he did something to me.
What guy?
I don't know!
This guy in a blue van,
he -- he grabbed me.
He took me here.
Oh, my stomach.
It hurts so much.
Dean!
Put those away,
and we can talk.
Why are you with the vampire
that killed my dad?
You're barking
up the wrong tree.
She didn't
kill your pops.
I don't want to hurt you, Dean,
but I will if you don't move.
Listen to me, Krissy.
She's innocent.
And how would
you know that?
Because she's fresh made,
a day or two.
Her dad was killed
months ago.
This whole thing stinks.
That vamp
that we killed last night?
Why was he swearing
that he didn't do it?
Because he was a liar.
Vampires don't beg
for their lives. They attack.
Look, last time
I'm gonna ask you nicely.
Take the damn guns off me,
or somebody's gonna get hurt.
Big talk.
I know.
It is, isn't it?
So, let's say this isn't
the vamp who killed my dad.
She's still a monster
and deserves to die.
Not if we can save her.
What?
She hasn't fed yet.
We can reverse this if we find
her maker and get his blood.
And why should we care
about her?
Like I said, hunting
isn't always about killing.
Oh, please.
Preach to some other choir.
We're not buying it.
You want to kill
an innocent girl?!
I want the blood sucker
who killed my dad to pay.
And we're gonna find out
who that is.
But let's not be so bloodthirsty
that just anyone will do.
But Victor says it's her.
And I say it ain't!
So we're gonna pack her
to go,
and we're gonna ask Victor
ourselves.
Okay?
You're awake. Good.
We don't have much time.
For what?
Picture this.
The kids arrive home
victorious,
only to find you dead
in their living room.
It seems that nest of vampires
they were hunting
were seeking revenge...
...and killed you.
Thus, inspiring them
to hunt even more.
I'm sorry, Sam.
I can't have anyone poisoning
my kids' minds.
Other than yourself,
that is.
I don't need to justify
my actions to you
or your self-righteous ass
of a brother!
You mean like why you're working
with a vampire?
So what's he get out of this?
Free roaming rights?
We are at war --
a war that we are losing.
That Leviathan fiasco
was a wake-up call.
We have to do what we can
to survive.
But I wouldn't expect you
to understand.
You're not a father.
You don't know
what it's like
to hear the cries
of your children dying.
But now I have a second chance
to make it all right,
to create the next generation
of hunters --
stronger, faster, smarter.
Hey, we're home.
What is going on here?
These two
are not to be trusted.
They're
trying to destroy us.
Do you know this vamp,
Victor?
Of course he does!
They're working together!
Is that true?
It's complicated.
No, actually,
it's not.
See, blue van here's been
turning fresh vamps
and setting them up
for you kids as easy kills.
But why?
Because they didn't kill
our families, did they?
No.
Well, then who did?
I did.
And they all screamed...
...and begged for mercy,
especially the little ones.
Enough, Seth!
You have to understand.
I saw a way
to make the future better.
But to get there,
I had to do something hard.
He killed them
off your orders?
You needed motivation.
I scouted
each and every one of you.
And knew it was the only way
to get you to hunt.
So you killed our families?
I know
the deaths are tragic.
But think
of all the future lives
that will now be saved
because you are now together.
So, these fake vampires were
just a way for you to train us
and fill our heads
with lies?!
Don't you see?
This is bigger
than all of us.
We have to learn
to put things in perspective.
Come with me.
We can get past this.
That is unfortunate.
Aidan!
We're leaving.
That's not happening.
I taught you
everything you know.
Don't make me hurt you.
Not everything, Victor.
Krissy, don't.
If we want revenge
for our families' deaths,
he gives it to us!
We don't kill people.
You don't kill people.
He's not a person.
He's a monster.
Krissy, this ends bad,
no matter what we do.
Exactly.
Krissy, don't.
This is for my dad.
For Josephine's family.
For Aidan.
For me.
So, we're just
gonna let him live?
Yeah.
All alone, with himself.
No family. No friends.
Ask me,
that's not much of anything.
Let's save that girl.
Gun!
Just drink slowly.
This will take away
all the pain.
Proud of you.
Shut up,
before I punch you.
So, how's she doing?
Better now.
Oh, um...
I think this is yours.
Thank you.
I'll wait outside.
Okay.
Whenever you're ready,
we'll be in the car.
What are
you talking about?
Your aunt? Cincinnati?
Normal life?
We'll be there
by lunch tomorrow.
Look, I hate how
we were put together, but...
I can't deny
that it feels right.
And why should I let Victor
ruin that, too?
So,
what you're saying is that
you like that boy over there
and you want to stay?
What? Aidan? No.
I mean...
He's like my brother.
It's nothing like that.
Well,
you're all still minors.
Not for long.
Josephine will be 18
in a few months.
And we all have a life
and each other here.
And hunting?
We won't go looking
for it.
But if any monsters show up
around here,
they better look out.
Okay. Good.
Really?
I thought I was gonna have to
fight you way more on that.
Well, you're right.
You're not a kid anymore.
You can make
your own decisions.
You're all right
for an old guy.
I'm really
not that old.
You keep
telling yourself that.
Huh.
All right.
Well, I'm gonna have a, uh --
a guy come and check on you
every once in a while,
okay?
His name is Garth.
He'll make sure that you're all
right and you got what you need.
Garth?
Yeah.
He's a little strange at first,
but you'll come to love him.
Take care, Dean.
Yeah. Goodbye, Dean.
Aidan.
Listen, there's, uh,
something I want to tell you
about Krissy.
I know. I know.
You'll kill me
if I ever hurt her.
Blah. Blah. Blah.
No, no. No.
She'll kill you.
Good luck.
This is good.
Is it?
Could have been
a lot worse.
Will be if we don't shut
those Gates of Hell soon.
What do they have to do
with any of that?
They're hunters now.
You don't just walk away
from that.
There's only one way
out of that,
and you and I both know
it ain't pretty.
Maybe
they'll be different.
Or maybe if we shut that
hell hole once and for and all,
those three
can have a real life.
Maybe they won't be
the only ones.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==