Crossroads are
where packs are made.
- That's serious spellwork.
- Used to summon a demon.
These people are actually making
deals with the damned thing.
They're seeing Hellhounds --
demonic pit bulls.
You can control them?
Sic him, boy!
Garth finally got them
to his houseboat,
but Kevin's having a lot of trouble
reading their half of the tablet.
- So, what is that stuff out front?
- Goofer dust.
You boys think you know
something about something,
but not goofer dust?
What is it?
Hoodoo.
Keeps out demons.
In the box is the key
to every object,
scroll, spell
ever collected for thousands
of years under one roof.
It is the supernatural
mother lode.
If knowledge is power,
then this is the most powerful
place on earth.
Holy crap.
Holy crap!
? Supernatural 8x14 ?
Trial and Error
Original Air Date on February 13, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Hey, Mom.
Wow.
Memory foam --
it remembers me.
And it's clean, too.
There's no funky smell.
There's
no creepy motel stains.
Really?
Sorry.
I'm gonna go fix us
some grub.
What you reading?
Sort of, uh, everything.
Oh, good.
Somebody's gonna have to dig
through all this,
and it ain't gonna be me.
You made these?
We have
a real kitchen now.
I know. I-I just didn't think
you knew what a kitchen was.
I'm nesting, okay?
Eat.
Huh? Yeah.
Wow.
You're welcome.
Yo.
Dean?
Come quick.
What?
Kevin?
Kevin?!
Something wrong?
Guess.
Kevin? It's us.
Found him.
Wow.
You look like hammered crap.
Yeah.
Are you sleeping?
Not really.
Are you eating?
Hot dogs, mostly.
Sure, yeah --
breakfast of champions.
Look, I'm gonna feel dirty
saying this,
but you might want a salad
and a shower.
I know, and I've been getting
bad headaches and nosebleeds,
and I think maybe I had
a small stroke.
But it was worth it.
What was worth it?
I figured out
how to close the Gates of Hell.
You --
Come here,
you smelly son of a bitch.
Okay, okay.
So, what does this mean?
What are we looking at?
It's a spell.
And?
And it's just a few words
of Enochian, but...
Oh, here we go.
...the spell
has to be spoken
after you finish
each of the three trials.
T-trials like,
uh, like "Law & Order"?
More like Hercules.
The tablet says, "Whosoever
chooses to undertake these tasks
should fear not danger,
nor death, nor..."
A word I think means
getting your spine ripped out
through your mouth
for all eternity.
Good times.
Basically,
God built a series of tests,
and when you've done all three,
you can slam the gates.
So, what --
God wants us to take the SATs?
I-I guess.
Uh, he works in mysterious ways.
Yeah,
mysterious, douche-y ways.
All right.
Where do we start?
I've only been able to crack
one of the tests so far,
and it's gross.
You've got to kill a hound
of hell and bathe in its blood.
Awesome.
Awesome?
Yeah.
Hey, if this means
icing all demons,
I got no problem
gutting some devil dog
and letting Calgon
take me away.
Where are
you gonna find one?
Well, Hellhounds like to collect
on crossroads deals.
So all we got to do
is track down some loser
who signed over
his special sauce 10 years ago,
get between him
and Clifford the big dead dog --
easy.
Doesn't sound easy.
It's not.
Look, you get on the net --
see what you can dig up.
I'm gonna go for a supply run
because we need goofer dust,
and the kid needs to eat
something
that's not ground-up hooves
and pigs' anuses --
not that there's
anything wrong with that.
Okay,
I feel a lot better.
Hey, Kevin, buddy,
you got to slow down.
Get some shut-eye.
Take a day off.
Open a window.
No.
You said nuking hell --
that's how I get out.
That's how I go home.
Right, it is,
but you can't live like this.
You think I want to?
I hate it here.
I can't leave because
every demon on the planet
wants to peel my face off.
I can't talk to anyone
except you guys or Garth,
when he swings by,
or my mom.
Right? And when she calls,
all she does is cry.
I just...
I need this to be over.
I know. I do.
But trust me on this --
this whole
"saving the world" thing --
it's a marathon,
not a sprint.
You got to take better care
of yourself.
Hey.
Did you know that there are,
like, 6,000 kinds of tomatoes?
Did you find anything?
Yeah,
demon signs, 10 years ago,
all centered
on Shoshone, Idaho.
Okay, well, big-time mojo
means a big-time freak.
So, anybody have a horseshoe
shoved up his ass?
That's one way of putting it.
Meet the Cassitys,
small-time farmers
who struck oil on their land
in February of '03,
which is weird
because geological surveys --
Yeah,
you had me at "weird."
All right.
We thinking deal?
Best lead we've got.
Well, let's go visit
the Beverly Hillbillies.
You stay here,
work on step number 2,
and, uh, if you come across
anything about Hellhounds,
drop a dime, okay?
'Cause between the --
the claws and the teeth
and the whole invisibility
thing, those bitches can be...
real bitches.
I got you a present.
The, uh, blue ones
are for the headaches,
and the Greens are for pep.
Don't O.D.
Thanks?
You sure about that?
Sam, we are
on the one-yard-line.
It is time
to play through the pain.
All right,
keep an eye out.
Anybody with a Hellhound
on their ass
is gonna be showing signs --
hallucinating, freaking out --
the usual.
And if we find someone?
You get 'em clear.
I spike fido.
The crowd goes wild.
Hey, pal,
who runs this joint?
You're looking at her.
You...own the ranch?
Nope,
just manage the property.
You guys here about the job?
How'd you guess?
We get
our share of drifters.
Ah.
Ever worked a farm before?
Definitely.
We're quick learners.
Ellie...who we got here?
I'm Dean. This is Sam.
Oh.
Carl Granville.
A pleasure.
Pleasure. So you're not a Cassity?
No, my wife is.
Her and her family
own the place.
I'm just one those, uh --
what you call 'em? --
trophy husbands.
So, we, uh,
hiring the fellas?
Not sure yet.
Oh, come on.
They seem like swell guys.
Well, he's right.
We're swell.
You bed down in here.
Breakfast is at 5:00,
dinner is at 8:00,
and in between, you're mine.
Questions?
I miss my room.
We're good.
Okay.
Job is yours if you want it.
But I better warn you --
it's crap work.
Crap --
she literally meant crap.
I hate you.
I don't care.
Do I look like a hippie?
Organic food is better
for the cattle.
My land, my animals, my money,
my way -- end of story.
She's a real piece of work,
huh?
Alice Cassity's
a piece of something, all right?
But what are we gonna do?
She's the boss.
Drink?
So,
what are we thinking?
What, dealwise?
Well, Ellie's the help,
so that rules her out.
And Carl doesn't really seem
like the sell-your-soul type.
So, Alice?
Ding-ding-ding.
Should we talk to her?
Why? So she can lie to us
and then call the cops? No.
No, we're gonna have to go
stalker on this one, Sammy.
The whole horse?
Oh, yes.
Seriously?
Yes.
What does she --
Just a wolf.
Yeah.
Probably spooked the hell
out of the horses.
I should check on them.
Well, all right.
Hurry back.
Okay.
No!
God almighty.
I'm sorry, Ellie.
Carl seemed like a good guy.
The best.
You say his head
was practically ripped off?
And you are?
Just curious.
He's new.
He works here.
Carl died bad --
let's leave it at that.
They've been reintroducing
wolves 'round these parts,
but I never thought...
This wasn't a wolf.
I got to make
some phone calls.
The whole family's
flying in for this.
All the Cassitys
under one roof.
Good luck.
Oh, son of a bitch.
So, what do you think?
I think Carl signed the deal,
and now he's dog food.
Hellhound's gone,
and we were too busy
chasing a pile of Jack
to stop it.
Let's grab our stuff
and get out of here.
You okay, Mrs. Cassity?
Fine.
You sure?
I really am.
And...I know I shouldn't be
because I loved Carl...
I think.
I just can't remember why.
What do you mean?
I mean...
Carl grew up around here.
We went to school together, and
he was always mooning over me.
But I never --
I used to make fun of him.
When did you two
get together?
Valentine's Day, 2003.
I was at this party.
Carl was there,
and it was like
I was seeing him
for the first time.
You know, suddenly he was cute
and smart and funny.
It was magic.
Carl and I were happy
for 10 years.
Now he's dead,
and I'm not sad or angry.
I'm just...fine.
Hey, we, uh,
we have any graveyard dirt?
We should. Why?
Yarrow?
Yeah. No.
Dean, no.
We're not summoning
a crossroads demon.
Plan "A" bombed,
so welcome to plan "B" --
we get some red-eyed bitch
in a trap,
then we hold a knife on her
until she calls us in a pooch --
special delivery.
Yeah, except when Crowley
finds out we're dialing up hell,
he won't send one Hellhound --
he'll send a hundred.
That's not a plan, Dean --
that's suicide.
Well,
you got a better idea?
Yeah, we stay here.
I just talked to Alice
in the barn.
Carl didn't sell his soul
for oil -- he sold it for Alice.
His wife?
He loved her, she barely noticed
him, so he made a deal.
And now that time's up,
it's like
she barely even knew the guy.
You think our demon signed up
more than one schmuck
while he was in town?
Wouldn't be the first time.
Look, Dean,
this family's rich
because someone booked
a one-way ticket downstairs.
And as of tomorrow,
they're all gonna be right here.
And you want to
scope 'em out?
I want to kill a Hellhound
and not die.
How 'bout you?
Two days --
then we do it my way.
Meet Noah Cassity.
He's 71,
worth a billion,
and just married wife number 5,
a 20-year-old lingerie model.
'Cause they have
so much in common?
Alice is his oldest, and that's
Cindy, the middle girl.
She had a single on the country
chart a few years ago.
Then she started hitting
the bottle,
and, well...
Her last album was a bunch
of holiday songs for dogs.
My favorites
were "Jingle Bark Rock"
and "Don't Pee on this Tree:
Happy Arbor Day."
So she's the devil.
Pretty much.
And there's the baby --
Margot.
She ran away just before Alice
and Carl tied the knot,
lives in Paris.
How do you know all this?
I've been working on this farm
since I was 13,
and I've got eyes.
Okay, tonight is
an all-hands-on-deck situation.
I'm gonna need
one of you inside,
serving dinner
and pouring drinks --
a lot of drinks.
Okay. Well, have fun.
I won't wait up.
And somebody's gonna man
the grill.
What kind of grill?
Impressed?
I do like a man
who can handle his meat.
Really?
Keep it coming, Ken doll.
You're the best, Ellie.
Al,
I'm so sorry about Carl.
I mean,
he was the love of your life.
Right.
Please,
she can do better.
Maybe Alice
should marry a child --
take after her father.
Ivanka's not a child.
Right.
She's a prostitute
who looks like a child.
Are you done?
Alice is in mourning.
Oh, I'm sorry, Margie.
I didn't see you there -- you're
too far up on your high horse.
Oh, yes,
but you are right --
we should all take a minute
and say a few words about Carl.
You first.
Was he a good lay?
What?
Oh, you didn't know?
Yeah, daddy caught 'em
going at it in the barn.
Al, it was
before you two got together.
I mean, Carl --
he loved you.
Yeah, that was back when Margie
was fat and Cin was sober,
a long time ago.
Get cancer and die,
old man.
You first, sweetie.
Are they
always like this?
More or less.
How can you work here?
I love the property,
I love the animals,
and I tune out the people.
Well,
I can't remember the last time
we all sat down
and had a meal together.
It was back at the old,
crappy house,
when daddy invited that
traveling salesman to dinner.
Oh, him.
He was so charming.
Yeah, English.
What was his name -- Kenny?
Crow--
hmm?
Crowl--
Crowley?
Crowley.
That's what they said.
Apparently, he swung through
town 10 years ago, to the day.
So, what -- do you think tea
and crumpets made these deals
and now he's collecting?
Or he just sent his dog --
told it to go fetch.
Dude's king of hell. Grabbing
a few souls --
that's got to
be below his pay grade.
I guess. Any idea who signed
the dotted line?
I have no clue.
It's brutal in there.
Hey, Kev, what's up?
Hey, Dean, good news,
uh, I think...kind of.
Don't oversell it.
Sorry.
Um, I found something on the
tablet, uh, about Hellhounds.
Uh,
this mean anything to you --
"the dire creatures may be seen
only by the damned
or through an object scorched
with holy fire"?
Like with holy oil?
It's got to be.
We could use a window.
Or glasses.
I think we've still got some
Jesus juice left in the trunk.
All right, I'll take care
of the, uh, the X-ray specs.
You stay here. Do not let J.R. and
the gang out of your sight, all right?
Right. Hey, Kevin, uh,
you did great, man.
Get some sleep.
Okay. Tha--
Oh, look.
Daddy's drunk and armed.
Must be Christmas.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Where are you going?
Wherever
I damn well please.
The wolf that killed
my son-in-law --
he's a man-eater,
got to be put down.
Doing this for Carl.
Okay, just -- just hold on
a second.
No, going now.
I'll come with you.
You know anything
about hunting, boy?
A little bit, yeah.
Let's do it.
I like it...
...the whole Clark Kent
look.
Ellie, hey.
Hey.
So...
I think
you're really hot.
You want to go to my room
and have sex?
What?
I -- sorry.
I don't usually do this.
I guess
I'm feeling my oats.
I can't.
What?
Okay.
Uh, embarrassing.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, I want to.
Believe me.
No, it's okay --
you don't.
I guess I'm gonna...
Ellie, um...
Rain check?
This is one night only.
Sorry.
Watch yourself, boy.
Where's Margie?
I thought she was with you.
Aah!
Oh, my God! No!
Go back to the house.
Go! Move!
No!
What was that thing?
It was a Hellhound.
See, when you sell your soul
to a demon,
they're the ones that come
and rip it out of you.
Demon?
Crowley.
Poncey guy, about yea big,
mountain of dicks.
We know he was here 10 years
ago, making dreams come true.
Now,
if you didn't sign, great.
That freak out there
won't touch you.
But if you did, I need to know,
and I need to know now.
So, hands up.
So, wait.
T-the British guy
was a demon,
and now there's a Hellhound
after us?
A-are you insane?
They're obviously insane.
Don't play dumb.
Yeah. I'm not playing.
I didn't sell my damn soul.
Well, somebody did,
and the sooner
that idiot owns up,
the sooner
the rest of you can go.
All right, seal 'em in.
Yeah.
What?!
Look, I'm gonna spread goofer dust
around the doors,
the windows.
That will keep the Hellhound
out...for a while.
What is that -- how long?
Long enough for me to stab it
in its throat.
No way. No way.
You can't do this.
You can't --
Yes, I can. You want to know why?
Because it's what I do.
And, buddy, I'm the best.
See,
I gut old yeller out there,
and maybe -- just maybe --
you walk away.
I don't -- you're meat.
So, sit down, shut up...
And put these on.
I don't...
Who are you people?
We're here to help.
Like you helped Margie?
When the Hellhound
gets close,
you might start seeing things,
hearing things.
It's gonna feel like you took
the brown acid,
and it's trying to kill you.
The handcuffs are
so you won't hurt yourselves.
And when one of you
starts bugging out,
we'll know who's on tap
to be puppy chow.
So...what's our play?
Well, you camp here, figure out
who whored their soul.
I'm gonna go scout
the grounds --
see if I can't gank
Huckleberry Hound
before he makes
his next move.
Wait, you're not going alone,
Dean.
I'm gonna come with you.
Wrong.
Uh, they're on lockdown,
and you need backup.
No, I don't.
Yes, you do.
No, I need you to be safe,
Sam, okay?
That's what I need.
What?
What am I --
when are we ever safe?
This is different.
How?
Because
of the three trials crap --
God's
little obstacle course.
We've been down roads like this
before, man --
with Yellow-Eyes, Lucifer,
dick friggin' Roman.
We both know where this ends --
one of us dies...
Or worse.
So, what -- you just up
and decided it's gonna be you?
I'm a grunt, Sam.
You're not.
You've always been the brains
of this operation.
Dean --
And you told me yourself
that you see a way out.
You see a light at the end
of this ugly-ass tunnel.
I don't.
But I tell you
what I do know --
it's that I'm gonna die
with a gun in my hand.
'Cause that's
what I have waiting for me --
that's all I have
waiting for me.
I want you to get out.
I want you to have a life --
become a man of Letters,
whatever.
You, with a wife and kids and --
and -- and grandkids,
living till you're fat and bald
and chugging Viagra --
that is my perfect ending,
and it's the only one
that I'm gonna get.
So I'm gonna do
these trials.
I'm gonna do them alone --
end of story.
You're staying here.
I'm going out there.
If landshark comes knocking,
you call me.
If you try to follow me,
I'm gonna put a bullet
in your damn leg.
? I want you to love me
? when I feel down,
I want you above me ?
? I search myself
? I want you to find me
? I forget myself
? I want you to remind me
? I don't want anybody else
? when I think about you,
I touch myself ?
? oh-oh-oh, I don't want a--
You sold your soul.
Admit it.
Why the hell
would you think that?
'Cause you're
a walking corpse,
and you're married
to a centerfold.
I did the math.
She likes money,
and I'm rich. Do it again.
You sing like crap,
so explain the music career.
Hello -- auto-tune!
All right.
That's enough.
Oh, is it, four-eyes?
Is it enough?
I don't know why you even think
one of us made a deal.
Because you struck oil
where there was no any oil.
That didn't seem weird
to you?
Margie.
Margie used to say that --
that if we were rich,
we'd all be happy.
Right.
We're the damn Waltons.
? I'd get down on my knees
? I'd do anything for you
? I don't want anybody else
? when I think about you,
I touch myself ?
? oh-oh-oh, I don't want an--
Just in time.
Ellie, are you okay?
I'm good.
And I bet you're great.
Yep, great.
Okay.
Listen...
Okay, whatever happens,
whatever you hear,
you need to stay in here
with that door locked.
Sit tight, okay?
This is gonna sound crazy,
but there is something evil
out there.
I know.
You know?
It's coming for me.
I need to take a leak.
Hold it.
Yeah, at my age?
Not really an option,
so either you let me go
or get me a bottle.
Ugh.
You're disgusting.
Wait!
No!
No, no, please.
Just let me go, please.
Please.
No!
Please,
don't hurt my family.
I'm not.
I'm trying to help you.
Get in the house.
What? What?
Go!
Oh, God!
When my parents split up,
my mom took a job here.
This was before
the Cassitys had money,
but it was
the best she could do.
So I grew up
on this farm.
That's
how you met Crowley?
They had this big dinner,
and after,
I saw him kissing Margie.
I ran.
I didn't know what to do.
But Crowley found me.
We talked.
He seemed so nice.
The best con men always do.
He asked me, if I had one wish,
what would it be?
So I told him.
And he made you sign over
your soul.
He didn't make me do
anything.
My mom --
she had Parkinson's --
early stages, and I knew
how that story would end.
So I took the deal.
Ma is retired down in Phoenix
now, plays golf every day.
That was a stupid move,
Ellie.
I did it for my mom,
Dean.
What would you do
for your mom?
You had to know
this was coming.
No. How?
Crowley didn't tell you about
the 10-year ticking clock?
What?
I knew that when I died,
I wasn't going to heaven,
but he never said anything
about that or monsters.
What a douche bag.
He probably didn't say jack
to Carl or Margot, either.
Margie made a deal?
So she's...
She's gone.
Oh, God.
I...
A few years ago,
Carl got drunk.
He told me did some kind
of magic at a crossroads --
summoned a demon.
I put two and two together,
and when I saw what that thing
did to him...
I just never knew
about Margie.
I thought I was next.
And you didn't run?
Where would I run?
All I wanted was one last meal,
some good tunes, and maybe...
I don't want to die.
Dean, what's happening?
Ellie, whatever you're seeing,
it's not real.
It means the Hellhound --
it's close.
Look, you need to stay
inside this circle, okay?
Now.
Dean...
No matter what happens,
you stay inside that circle.
You understand me?
Oh,
so you're Crowley's bitch.
I guess pets really do look like
their owners.
What are you waiting for?
Come and get it!
Ohh!
Mnh.
You need to go
to a hospital.
Oh, I've had worse.
Yeah, he's had worse.
So, what now?
Now we make a hex bag,
and you start running.
If Crowley can't find you,
then he won't be able to sic
another mutt on you.
So I'm not going
to hell?
Not on my watch.
Will you give us a minute?
Sure.
Thanks.
Dean,
even if she can dodge Crowley,
as soon as Ellie dies,
her soul is earmarked for hell.
Not if we shut it down
first.
The spell's not gonna work
for you, Dean.
Kah-nuh-ahm-dahr.
Doesn't matter.
We'll track down another
Hellhound, and I'll kill it.
No.
Sam,
I didn't pass the test.
But I did...
And I'm doing
the rest of them.
My ass you are!
I'm closing the gates.
It's a suicide mission
for you.
Sam...
I want to slam hell shut, too, okay?
But I want to survive it.
I want to live,
and so should you.
You have friends up here,
family.
I mean, hell, you even got
your own room now.
You were right, okay?
I see light at the end
of this tunnel.
And I'm sorry you don't --
I am.
But it's there.
And if you come with me,
I can take you to it.
Sam, be smart.
I am smart,
and so are you.
You're not a grunt, Dean.
You're a genius --
when it comes to lore, to --
you're the best damn hunter
I have ever seen --
better than me,
better than dad.
I believe in you, Dean.
So, please --
please believe in me,
too.
Kah-nuh-ahm-dahr.
Sam.
Sammy?
Sam!
You okay?
I'm good. I'm okay.
I can do this.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==