I think dad wants us to
pick up where he left off --
saving people, hunting things...
the family business.
We have to carry out his legacy.
Aah!
It's a bloodline.
It's in your blood,
your father's blood,
your family's blood.
I like that John kid.
You do?
Yeah, I think you two
were meant to be.
Yeah, the union
of John and Mary Winchester --
very big deal upstairs --
top-priority arrangement.
Are you saying that you
fixed up our parents?
The orders were
very clear.
You and Sam
needed to be born.
Your parents
were just meant to be.
This book.
This is dad's single
most valuable possession.
Everything he knows about
every evil thing is in here.
And he's passed it on to us.
How many people
do you think dad saved?
That's his legacy.
So we got to keep going.
Hey, sport.
Sorry about that.
Where are you going?
Work.
I just wanted to check on you
before I left.
What's that, pops?
One day,
I'll tell you all about it.
Now get some shut-eye.
See you
first thing in the morning.
[ Music box playing
"As Time Goes By" ]
Good night, son.
Good evening, sir.
Josie.
No one told me this initiation
was a formal affair.
Well, someone had to class up
the joint, right, Henry?
Ain't that the truth?
The hard part's over,
right?
We made it.
Ms. Sands?
Secura tibi facias libertate.
Servire, te rogamus, audi nos!
Henry.
Do not
let Abbadon get it.
That's impossible!
How?
Kah-nee-lah...
Poo-goh.
Which of you
is John Winchester?
? Supernatural 8x12 ?
As Time Goes By
Original Air Date on January 30, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Please,
time is of the essence!
Which of you
is John Winchester?
Uh, neither.
That's impossible.
That's absolutely...
What did I do wrong?
Who the hell are you,
mister?
Not now.
I'm thinking.
Please.
I can assure you
there's no need for violence.
One of you
must know John Winchester.
I'll tell you what --
when one of us
falls out of your closet,
then you can
ask the questions.
Yes, my apologies.
Is it absolutely essential,
sir,
that you keep
your hands on me?
Thank you.
Gentlemen,
in the absence of
any and all other explanations,
I'm afraid this has been
a marvelous,
tragic misunderstanding.
I'll be on my way.
That's
not happening.
There are things
of grave importance.
I do not have time to
deal with the likes of you.
You're not going anywhere,
007...
...till we
get some answers.
How did he do that?
You got to be
kidding me!
2013.
My God.
Guess the Mayans were wrong.
Nice taste in wheels.
Yours, I presume?
And there
with the holy water.
He's clean.
I could have
told you that.
Yeah, well, you can start by
telling us everything
before I
beat it out of you.
I'm quite certain this is all
beyond your understanding,
my alpha-male-monkey
friend.
And violence will not help you
comprehend this any easier.
Let me tell you
what I understand!
Some asshat
pops out of my closet
asking about my dad,
smashes up my ride.
So why am I not
getting violent, again?
John Winchester
is your father?
What is that?
Oh, my God.
What?
Run!
Henry.
Silly man,
you forgot to lock the door.
But then spells never were
your best subject, were they?
Why don't you be a doll
and give me what I want?
And I promise to kill you
and your friends here quickly.
You know
I can't do that.
You're not a fighter,
Henry.
Josie.
I know
you're still in there.
You must fight this.
I'm afraid
Josie's indisposed, Pet.
It looks like
it's just you and me.
Ohh! Aah!
Well, that is
no way to treat a lady.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
You okay, lady?
What the hell
are you doing?
Show me
what you've seen.
Thank you.
By the way,
I'm checking out.
Are you okay?
Yes, I will be.
It's just
all the adventures I enjoy
are usually
of the literary nature.
Yeah, well, now that
you're done blowing chunks,
you want to tell us
who Betty Crocker was?
Abbadon.
She's a demon.
No kidding.
Where'd she come from?
Where'd you come from?
She's from hell.
I'm from
Normal, Illinois --
1958.
Yeah, right.
Seriously?
Dude's time traveling
through motel-room closets?
That's
what we've come to?
If you could just
take me to John,
we could clear all this up,
I'm sure.
I've told you
that's not gonna happen.
Why not?
Because he's dead!
No.
What's it to you?
Everything.
I'm his father.
Driver's license says
he's Henry Winchester
from Normal, Illinois.
He knows dad's birthday,
the exact place
where he was born.
Dude,
that's our grandfather.
I'm just saying before we
break out the warm and toasties,
let's not forget that, uh,
H.G. Wells over there
left dad high and dry
when he was a kid.
But maybe he didn't
run out on dad --
I mean, not on purpose.
Maybe he time-traveled here
and, I don't know,
got stuck.
Yeah, well, either way,
dad hated the son of a bitch.
And dad
made up for that how?
By being
father of the year?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Look, dad had his issues,
okay,
but he was
always there for us.
I freaking hate
time-travel, man.
How you doing?
I'll be fine.
After all,
despite everything,
I've just met my grandsons,
haven't I?
Henry Winchester.
It's a pleasure.
Sam.
Hello, Sam.
Dinner.
This is Dean.
Right.
Well, this has been
touching.
How about we figure out
how to clean up your mess, huh?
Abbadon.
Yes.
She must be stopped.
And how come she didn't die
when I stabbed her?
Because demons
can't be killed
by run-of-the-mill
cutlery.
At the very least,
you'd need
an ancient demon-killing
knife of the Kurds.
That's what this is.
Where'd you get that?
Demon gave it to me.
We've been around this block
so many times.
Now, that portal
or whatever it was
you came through --
is it still open?
I highly doubt it.
Why?
I'm just thinking
if we can't kill this Abbadon...
Maybe we can shove her
back where she came from.
How did you do it?
It's a blood Sigil.
Blood leads to blood.
Or their next of kin.
But Abbadon
came through it, also, right?
So can you create
this blood Sigil again?
My blood,
an angel feather,
tears of a dragon,
a pinch of
the sands of time --
I-I would need those
and...
At least a week
for my soul to recharge,
but, yes,
it's possible.
You tapped the power of
your soul to get here?
I thought
only angels could do that.
You should know this.
What level are you two?
What level?
Level of knowledge.
You're Men of Letters,
correct?
I'm a little rusty
on my boy bands.
Men of what?
Men of Letters,
like your father,
who taught you our ways.
Our father
taught us how to be hunters.
You're not.
Are you? Hunters?
Well, hunters are...
Hunters are apes.
You're supposed to --
you're legacies.
Legacies of what?
What's going on here?
No.
All right, well,
this was enlightening.
Let's hit the road,
huh?
Give him a minute,
Dean.
We just spent four hours
driving, okay?
All he did was
stare out the window
and request Pat Boone
on the radio.
He had his time.
It's just a facade,
a way to rook our enemies
into believing
we are housed elsewhere.
Okay, enough with
the decoder talk.
How about you tell us
what this whole
Men-of-Letters business is,
or you're on your own?
It's none of
your concern.
Why,
because we're hunters?
What do you
have against us?
Aside from
the unthinking, unwashed,
shoot-first-and-don't-bother-to-
ask-questions-later part,
not much, really.
You know what?
Wait a second.
We're also
John's children.
You're more than that,
actually.
My father
and his father before him
were both Men of Letters.
As John and you two
should have been.
We're preceptors,
beholders,
chroniclers of all that
which man does not understand.
We share our findings with
a few trusted hunters --
the very elite.
They do the rest.
So you're like Yodas
to our Jedis.
Never mind.
You'll get there.
Okay, but if you guys
were such a big deal,
then why haven't we --
or anyone we know --
ever heard of you?
Abbadon.
Henry. Why?
Why'd she do it?
I think for this.
Okay, what's that?
I wish I knew.
Abbadon attacked us
the night of
my final initiation.
All secrets
were to be revealed then.
Let me
get this straight.
You traveled through time
to protect something
that does you don't know what
from a demon
that you know nothing about?
Good.
Hand me your...
walkie-talkie.
You mean my phone?
Even better.
Operator,
I need Delta 457.
Who are you
not calling?
Our emergency number.
Yeah. Not anymore.
They can't all be gone.
There must be
another elder out there
who can help us figure out
how to stop Abbadon
and what to do
with the box.
Hey, uh, hi.
Can we hijack your computer
for a hot second?
Like you could
fit a computer in this room.
Sure.
Thanks.
Sam.
Yep.
All right, um...
give me a name --
anybody who, uh,
might have been there
that night --
one of those elders.
Um...Ackers, David.
Larry Ganem.
Um, Ted --
Okay, here it is.
Um, August 12, 1958.
A tragic fire
at a gentlemen's club.
Uh, 242 Gaines Street.
This is
242 Gaines Street...
But that was no fire.
Larry Ganem, David Ackers,
Ted Bowen, and Albert Magnus --
all deceased.
Albert Magnus.
He a friend of yours?
Even better.
These were my friends,
my mentors,
our last defense against
the Abbadons of the world.
Here's your buddy
Albert Magnus.
Albertus Magnus.
And he was hardly
a buddy.
He was the greatest alchemist
of the middle ages.
Okay, so why is he
buried here?
He's not.
His was the alias we'd use
when going incognito.
I believe someone planted
his name in that article...
so that if a man of letters
came looking for answers,
he'd know
something was amiss.
So someone wanted you
to come to this grave.
The question is why.
What is this?
Our crest.
The Aquarian Star,
representing
great magic and power.
They say it stood at
the gates of Atlantis itself.
Hmm.
It's on all the tombstones
except for this one --
uh, Larry Ganem.
The Haitian symbol for
speaking to the dead.
This is the message.
You boys ever
exhume a body?
Love what you've done
with the place.
Wrong night.
"Carrie" screening's
on Sunday.
I dig your costume,
though.
What are you doing?
Show me
what you've seen.
Can we
hijack your computer?
Give me a name.
Ackers, David.
Larry Ganem.
Tragic fire.
That was no fire.
Albert Magnus.
Thanks.
Please don't hurt me!
I like your top.
Tell me how we got
stuck doing this?
Hey, was, uh,
Larry a World War I vet?
No.
Well, then,
who's the stiff?
No idea.
Captain
Thomas J. Carey III.
That mean anything
to you?
Well, somebody
wanted you to see this,
so maybe
that somebody is Larry.
So, what,
maybe he, uh,
survives the attack
and hides out
with this guy's identity?
Okay.
What are we waiting for,
then?
Cover this up.
Let's be on our way.
What is that?
I know that tune.
"As Time Goes By."
I hope so.
It's from "Casablanca."
Right.
Dad used to whistle it
from time to time.
Your father saw "Abbott
and Costello Meet the Mummy"
at the drive-in one night.
It scared the beeswax
out of him.
So I got him this little
music box that played that song
to help him sleep at night.
It worked like a charm.
Wow,
it's hard to believe
dad was ever
scared of anything.
Hey, uh,
according to
county records,
Tom Carey
lives in Lebanon, Kansas,
and is a very happy
127-year-old.
I say
we get some shut-eye,
head over
first thing in the morning.
Wait, wait, wait.
Listen to this.
According to dad's journal,
he once tortured
a demon that said
he made his bones
working for Abbadon,
who, it turns out,
is a Knight of Hell.
What does that
even mean?
Knights of Hell are
hand-picked by Lucifer himself.
They are of the first-fallen,
first-born demons.
So very pure,
very strong.
Legend has it that Archangels
had killed all of them,
which, as we have witnessed,
is not the case.
Unless she's
the last of her kind.
You say
that belonged to your father?
Yeah.
May I?
It's a hunter's journal.
I assume
Men of Letters --
you use journals, too?
I intended to.
I sent away for one
the day before my initiation.
As a matter of fact,
judging by my initials here,
this one, I believe.
That was yours?
It must have arrived
after...
I'm beginning to gather
I don't make it back
from this time, do I?
We don't know
for sure.
All we do know is that
dad never saw you again.
What did he think
happened to me?
He thought
you ran out on him.
John was a legacy.
I was supposed to teach him
the ways of the Letters.
Well, he learned things
a little differently.
How?
The hard way.
Surviving
a lonely childhood
a stinking war...
only to get married
and have his wife
taken by a demon...
...and later
killed by one himself.
That man got a bum rap
around every turn.
But you know what?
He kept going.
And in the end,
he did a hell of a lot more good
than he did bad.
I'm sorry.
I wish I had
been there for him.
Yeah, it's a little late
for that now,
don't you think?
It's the price we pay for
upholding great responsibility.
We know that.
Your responsibility
was to your family,
not some
glorified book club!
I was a legacy.
I had no choice.
Yeah, you keep
telling yourself that.
Hey.
Wake up!
What? What?!
Henry -- he's gone.
Where is he?
No idea.
He just left a note saying
he was gonna fix everything.
Yeah,
or screw it all up.
All right.
Satnam.
Welcome, traveler.
What can I
help you with?
I can use
a tear of a dragon
and a pinch of
the sands of time,
but don't bother
wrapping it up.
I'll be using it
right away.
We don't carry
those things here.
But can I interest you
in some kava root?
It's great for anxiety.
In your window --
hunters' signs.
I know who you are
and what you are.
Now give me what I need
so I can be on my way.
I agree.
You should be going,
stranger.
I understand.
You don't know me,
so you're
reluctant to sell to me.
Fine.
But please let me
purchase some chamomile
for my restless nights
before I go.
Bah-rah-gah-doh.
Sleep well.
Now we know what he meant
by "fix everything."
What?
He broke in to the trunk,
stole an angel feather.
I'm guessing
he's gonna whip up
another one of those
blood spells
and Marty McFly himself
back to the 1950s.
To do what?
Stop Abbadon
before she strikes?
Or grab dad
and haul ass.
Look,
point is he's doing it.
How?
He still needs two ingredients
for the spell.
Unless...
Unless there's some place nearby
that sells real hoodoo.
I'll call Garth.
All units, possible
homicide at Astro Comics.
Location...
Hey.
Hmm?
It just hit the wires --
one dead at Astro Comics.
Abbadon?
Yeah, has to be.
Okay,
so she's close.
I'll go find Henry.
You find Larry.
Figure out
how to kill this chick.
So, Henry is dead.
I was so sure that --
that he had survived.
Yes, well, um,
like I said --
I found his journal
and was hoping
you could
fill in the gaps
and explain to me
what happened
that night in 1958.
It doesn't matter.
They're gone. We're gone.
But Abbadon is not.
Abbadon was a hired gun.
She killed us all
that one night.
Everyone but you.
She blinded me.
It's a miracle I survived.
It's okay, dear.
But she did not
get what she came for.
The box.
Listen, Abbadon is here,
and she wants this thing.
So I need to know everything
there is to know about it.
In the box is the key
to every object,
scroll, spell
ever collected
for thousands of years
under one roof.
It is the supernatural
mother lode.
Poo-goh.
Kah-nee-lah....
Henry, wait!
This is a risk
I have to take.
And what if you die,
huh?
Who said you'll even
survive a jump?
You cannot begin to
understand how I felt
after reading
John's journal.
Oh, I think I can.
See, I've read that thing
more times than you can imagine,
and it hurts every time.
Maybe so,
but you didn't let him down!
I did!
Just like you said!
Well, I was wrong.
No!
No, you were right.
And I'm going to go back
and give him
the life he deserves,
not the one
he was forced to live.
What if it's
not meant to be?
Then it will be!
How can you be so sure?
Because it's
the right thing to do!
I can save him
and stop Abbadon!
How?
By going back
an hour before she attacks
and making preparations.
If you do that
and you change the past,
me and Sam
might cease to exist!
I'm aware that time
is a delicate mistress,
but I'm willing to bet on
this being for the best.
I understand that
this is not
your idea of a happy ending,
okay,
and that you're disappointed
that me and Sam
are mouth-breathing
hunters.
But you know what?
We stopped the Apocalypse.
If this works
the way I planned,
there will never be
an Apocalypse to stop.
So...
Abbadon wants the key
so she can
get her hands on it.
Can you imagine
what she would do with that?
So, how do we stop her?
How do we stop Abbadon?
You don't.
If you know
where the key is,
then take it to
these coordinates.
Throw it in.
Shut the door forever.
And walk away.
Wait,
w-why would I do that?
Because it is
the safest place on earth,
warded against
any evil ever created.
It is impervious to
any entry,
except the key.
Right, but then
all that knowledge would be --
would be lost
and gone forever.
And that is
the price we have to pay
for keeping it away
from Abbadon.
You do...
have the key, don't you?
I don't, um...
But, uh, my brother...
...my brother does.
How rude.
You haven't finished
your tea, Sam.
Abbadon.
The years have not
been kind, Larry.
Sammy?
No.
Much sexier.
Try again.
Abbadon.
Good boy.
Now listen up --
I want to make a good,
old-fashioned horse trade.
Henry and the key
for your brother.
Or he dies.
Am I clear?
Crystal.
On the road to Larry's,
there's a processing plant.
Don't keep me waiting.
Abbadon has Sam?
She wants to trade
you and the key for Sam's life.
If I could just go back,
stop this all from happening.
And what if you can't?
I can't take that risk --
not with Sammy on the hook now.
I can't abandon my son,
Dean!
Not again!
I need to do this.
I'm sorry.
Kah-nee-lah...Poo-goh.
Well, I'm sorry, too.
Sorry about that.
No, you're not.
You've wanted to do that
since we met.
Henry, you need to
understand something.
When my dad died,
I couldn't save him...
...no matter
how bad I wanted to.
I never want that to
happen to Sam...ever.
If there's a chance
that I can save him,
I'm gonna do it.
He's my brother.
He's the only family I got.
Don't do it, Dean.
Too late for that now.
That's the problem
with you hunters.
You're all
short-sighted.
Yeah, at least
we're not extinct.
Abbadon!
I'll send Henry here over
with the box.
You do the same with Sam.
No tricks.
My only interest
is Henry and the key.
You two are free to go.
You can do this
standing,
or you can do it
crawling.
Your call.
Henry, I'm sorry.
Save it.
Don't do this, Dean.
This is a bad idea.
Shut your mouth.
Let's go.
Come on.
We had a deal!
Surprise.
I lied.
Henry!
Wait. Wait.
Ohh!
You're not the only one.
I'm gonna do it.
He's my brother.
He's the only family I got.
So, what are you
thinking?
Can you
slow Abbadon down?
Because if you can,
I'll do the rest.
Whoo!
What a blast.
Now, give me the box.
Where is it?!
Okay.
We can do this
the hard way.
Why am I stuck?!
A devil's trap
carved into the bullet.
You're gonna have to
get close.
And "close" means
it could get ugly.
I know.
But you do that for blood.
You still didn't kill me.
No, but you'll wish
we did.
The demon trap
in your noggin
is gonna keep you
from smoking out.
We're gonna cut you
into little steaks
and bury each strip
under cement.
You might not be dead,
but you'll wish you were.
We did it.
No, you did it.
For a bookworm,
that wasn't bad, Henry.
I'm sorry I judged you two
so harshly for being hunters.
I should have
known better.
About?
You're also Winchesters.
As long as we're alive,
there's always hope.
I didn't know my son
as a man,
but having met you two...
I know I would have been
proud of him.
I get it now.
Hmm?
What Cupid said
about heaven busting ass
to get mom and dad
together.
The Winchesters
and the Campbells --
the brains and the brawn.
Well,
I'm glad you see it.
All I see in our family tree
is a whole lot of dead.
Hey, I, uh...
Found this
in Henry's wallet.
Dad looks happy.
Kind of makes you wish
he knew the truth, huh?
I mean, all those years
thinking his old man ditched
when the poor son of a bitch
really came here
and saved our bacon.
Freaking time-travel,
man.
You think it would have
made a difference?
What?
Dad.
If he'd had
his own father around.
What,
in how he raised us?
Sammy,
he did the best he could.
I know that. I-I do.
They all did.
What are the chances
that place is still standing?
A chance we've got to take,
I guess.
I mean, we are legacies,
right?
[ Music box playing
"As Time Goes By" ]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==