I don't hunt anymore.
I found something.
What was her name?
Amelia!
Dean, the year that I took off,
I had something I've never had.
Happy Birthday!
A normal life.
You were in Purgatory?
It felt pure.
Well,
how'd you get out?
- I got something you need.
- Yeah, what's that?
I show you the door,
you hump my soul
to the other side.
[ Cracking ]
We made it, brother.
- What about Cass? Was he there?
- Something happened to him down there.
[ Laughs ]
I'm not leaving here
without you.
Beau: Kevin Tran,
Prophet of the Lord.
It does have
a nice ring to it.
Kevin!
Sam: Hey. What's it say?
That we shouldn't come looking,
and since we lost the tablet,
Kevin figures we don't need him.
Yeah,
but Crowley still does.
[ Bell clanging in distance ]
[ Air horn blows in distance ]
Hello, Quentin.
Benny.
No,
I-it -- it can't be you.
I get the confusion.
You of all people
knew I was really, truly dead.
After all, you held down
my legs, didn't you?
When the old man told Sorento
to saw off my head.
Where is he?
Are you serious?
Did you really think
I'd tell you where he is?
Well, I guess I was
kind of hoping you wouldn't.
[ Chuckles softly ]
On the other hand,
I might show you where he is.
After me and my boys
take off your hands and feet.
Well, don't go through
all that trouble on my account.
Please.
You go and crawl your way
out of God's ass
for another ride
on the merry-go-round?
The old man's gonna want to see
this for himself.
Mm.
Well, they might be able
to kill me.
And that's all right.
'Cause if they do, I know
exactly where I'm going...
and who I'll see
when I get there.
[ Growls ]
? Supernatural 8x05 ?
Blood Brother
Original Air Date on October 31, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
[ insects chirping ]
Well, that is twice
that he's burned us.
Shame on you.
No, no, no, no.
I'm the one who said
he set us up.
No, you said, "I wonder
if Kevin is setting us up,"
and then you started in
with the -- the techno babble.
That was like two states ago.
Yeah, well, whatever.
Either way,
that's another room
billed to one of Kevin's
false credit I.D.s.
And the motel ran his number
today.
Just like
he actually checked in?
Yes.
Kid's like Rain Man.
He's like a crappy little
credit-card-counting...
Criminal prodigy Rain Man.
Well, he was
in advanced placement.
Shut up.
When's that little idiot
gonna stop running from us?
I don't know, Dean.
I mean, you did try to kill
his mother.
I was trying to kill Crowley,
okay?
Who happened to be wearing
Kevin's mother at the time.
Well,
there's a difference.
Apparently not to Kevin.
Oh, I know. Maybe because --
oh, yeah, -- it's his mother.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Hold that thought.
No, actually, you know what?
Don't hold that thought.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Hello?
Uh, hang on.
There's not enough bars.
[ Door opens ]
Benny?
Benny: Hey, Dean.
You, um --
you got a minute?
[ Breathing deeply ]
Afraid I messed up, buddy.
What did you do?
[ Laughs ]
No, man, not like that.
I'm sorry.
You took on how many?
Are you crazy?
Hey.
See, the thing is, my legs --
they ain't working so good.
There's, uh...
a fuel barge
not too far from here.
I'm pretty sure I can make it
at a slow crawl.
I was kind of hoping
maybe I could ask you
for one more favor?
And -- and what exactly
is that supposed to mean,
you've got to go?
Which words are giving you trouble?
We're on the case,
remember, Dean?
The Winchester holy grail,
"shut the gates of hell forever" case.
Sure are.
But in order to close
the Gates of Hell,
we need our Prophet,
am I right?
So step one --
find Kevin Tran.
Well, he ain't here.
But he wanted us to be,
which means we're
probably as far away from him
as he could possibly put us.
So step two --
find Kevin Tran.
You mind if I take
the Toblerone?
[ Door opens ]
Wait.
Dean, seriously?
Hey, the trail is dead,
but the room is paid for.
You got some research to
do, and I got some personal
crap I got to take care of.
That's all.
What does that mean -- "personal"?
Did you have a stroke?
Vocabulary?
Personal, as in my own
grown-up personal --
I don't know -- crap.
Damn it --
What, Sam?
Last I counted, you took
a year off from the job.
I need a day.
[ Car door opens ]
[ Car door closes,
engine turns over, revs ]
[ Whistling ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Whistling continues ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Computer keys clacking ]
You are a wascally wabbit,
Mr. Tran.
[ Sighs ]
Concerned.
[ Clears throat ]
Not stalking...concerned.
[ Rattling in distance ]
[ Click ]
[ Rattling continues ]
Everett.
Hey, buddy, you still on duty?
Yeah, yeah.
How's your dad?
He's kind of having it rough
on the new regimen.
Can't keep anything down.
That sucks.
Yeah.
Listen, um, I'm gonna stay on
another week, okay?
But I need you to run it
on this card,
'cause I just canceled
the one you had on file.
Okay, sure.
[ Screeching continues ]
Figured you'd have moved on by now.
Right.
Well, I'm --
I'm kind of between jobs.
Uh...
plus, uh, dog has
a surgery follow-up on Tuesday.
Yeah, you really messed up
that dog.
[ Chuckles ] Right.
Uh, thanks for that.
[ Rattling continues ]
Oh, yeah,
it's all that thing does --
piss, moan,
and eat up money we ain't got.
Well, you got any tools?
Hell, if you can fix it,
you don't need to go
and look for a job.
You got one here.
[ Click ]
[ Chuckles softly ]
[ Sea gulls squawking,
air horn blows in distance ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Clank ]
Benny!
Benny?
Not lookin' good.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Weakly ] Up yours.
[ Sea gulls squawking ]
[ Chuckles ]
Wow. You, uh...
Look okay.
Getting there.
Dude,
you were double-hamstrung.
Yeah, well,
a little rest,
a half a cooler
full of AB-negative --
most wounds
short of an amputation
will mend up...
vampirically speaking.
Uh-huh.
I'll be 100%
before you know it.
Thank you, brother.
Benny, what's going on?
Oh, your work here is done,
Dean.
You already saved the day.
You know, I got my, uh, deal,
and you got --
what'd you call it?
A family business?
Benny.
What's going on?
You and that whole
"friend" thing, man.
[ Roars ]
Benny: Well, I got to admit, Dean --
he's got his strong points,
but holy hell
if he ain't a magnet.
Well,
before we found Cass,
you said it was my humanity that
was drawing too much attention.
Yeah, that too.
Well, I think we're clear
for the moment.
It does present a curious curl
in the metaphysics, doesn't it?
If you murder a monster
in monster heaven,
where does it go?
And this is the crazy aunt
I want to take on the road?
I am not your aunt.
What? Really?
I have no possible relationship
to your sibling offspring.
Now,
you're kidding me.
Oh,
you two are killing me.
I have to agree
with the vampire, Dean.
The risk of crossing Purgatory
with a seraph --
it's...less than strategic,
and certainly when we have
no reason to believe
that I can pass through the door
that you're headed for.
You see,
you're an intact,
living human being
stuck in Purgatory's craw.
This dimension
wants to spit you out,
which is exactly what's
gonna power our escape pod.
Now, I'm pretty sure
I can squeeze through, too,
because, after all, you take
away the fangs and the fun,
I was born human, too.
But...
I don't think
it would work for me.
You hear what he's telling you,
Dean?
Your buddy is saying --
listen to me,
you undead blood junkie,
I'm the one with the mojo.
I'm the one with the plan.
Cass...
we're gonna shove your ass
back through the eye of that needle
if it kills all three of us.
Obviously, I'm less than
comfortable with that.
Well, it's good to know
you're still dumb as ever.
Yeah, well,
some things never change.
Now, why are you
getting into machete fights
with your own kind?
[ Squawking continues ]
Quentin,
the one I came for?
We were in the same nest.
I'm hunting the vampire
who turned me, my maker.
Well, now,
don't get me wrong.
I'm down with the hunting,
but, uh...why?
Kill him
before he kills me...
Again.
[ Electricity zaps ]
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Computer keys clacking ]
[ Thudding ]
[ Whirring ]
Awesome.
Uh, if you're still
on the clock,
lady in 118
says the sink's backed up.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Door opens ]
What the hell?
What are you doing here?
I knew there was
something off about you,
with your creepy Army-Navy
and your sideburns --
Stop, stop.
Um,
I'm fixing your sink.
What?
Benny: Quentin and I
went way back --
one of the old man's favorites,
next to me, it turns out.
Listen to this.
"Age of Aquarius II, 0800,"
and then there's some
other numbers all crossed out.
Some other weird names here,
too -- the Big Mermaid,
Solitaire --
it's all crossed out,
except this one --
the Lucky Myra.
Yachts.
Names of yachts -- Lucky Myra,
Age of Aquarius II.
Look at this one --
Sea You Later, spelled s-e-a.
I mean, come on.
So, then
these are launch times.
And what -- destinations?
Mm-hmm. Except none of them
ever get there.
The Lucky Myra left
yesterday afternoon.
I guarantee you
it's already been hit.
What do you mean, "hit"?
Boarded, burned,
and buried at sea.
My nest --
that's how we fed...
How we always fed.
We kept a tight little fleet,
maybe a half-dozen boats.
Nothing ostentatious,
just pleasure craft.
I must have circled the Americas
10 times during my tour.
A few of us would act
as stringers
and patrol the harbors,
looking
for the right-size target --
fat, rich yachts
going to far-off ports.
Take down the boat's name
and destination,
radio it to the crew
in the water.
And then we just, uh...
let the ocean swallow up
all our sins.
Vampire pirates?
That's what you guys are?
Vampirates.
[ Laughs ]
You know, all the years
we ran together,
I can't believe nobody
ever thought of that.
What do you mean? It's like
the third thing you say.
No, it isn't.
All right,
so, y-your maker
is set up to feed around here,
right?
Well,
what are we looking for?
he likes to live in style.
He usually rents
legitimately.
Always remote,
always coastal.
So an island, maybe?
You got a cable bill here.
Hmm. Quentin's got
the NFL package.
Prentiss Island.
Heard of it?
Oh, yeah.
Dean: Yeah, so, if you were
your maker's favorite,
why did he kill you?
When you get turned,
it's like you're reborn
into a vampire nest.
Your maker --
he means everything to you.
I mean, you really start
believing he's God.
Now, if your maker happens to
believe the same thing, well...
See how that
could be a pickle.
Mm.
We, uh --
you really have to do that?
I mean, right now?
[ Laughs ]
I'm sorry, brother.
I'm better,
but I'm still on the mend.
Right.
Anyway...our father --
he was a jealous God.
He kept the family
together
but kept us apart from the rest
of the world, always at sea.
I always did
what was best for the nest...
till I met her.
Andrea.
Andrea Kormos.
Beautiful.
I mean, words don't even cut it,
you know?
Greek, heiress.
Come on.
She was sailing a 42-foot sloop
to the Canary Islands.
Now, I should have called
her boat's destination
in to my crew, but instead,
I joined her on it.
Seriously?
Was Fabio on the cover
of that paperback?
[ Laughs ]
My life changed
when she entered it, Dean.
Everything I had been or done
up to that point
just...seemed to vanish...
Into what we had become
together.
I mean...
We found it, man.
Eventually,
we settled in Louisiana.
And then one night,
we were coming home,
and the old man --
he was just there.
Quentin, Sorento,
my oldest nestmates.
It was only that night
I understood
what a crime it was to him --
me leaving him.
They pinned me down,
and they beheaded me.
The last thing I saw
was the old man tearing out
Andrea's throat.
Well, that's what payback's
all about -- am I right?
Docks are up ahead.
Should be able to find
a dinghy to use.
[ Insects chirping ]
We're close.
[ Zipper zips ]
Remind you of anything?
It's weird being back --
in the world, I mean.
Isn't it?
Sure as hell is.
I mean, what do you do
with it all?
All the --
all the everything?
Hell, I don't even know
if this world is real,
if I'm real.
Hey, listen to me.
I see what happens
down that rabbit hole, okay?
We're real.
Benny, this is real.
It's the only way to play
this game, you get me?
[ Insects continues ]
Time to move, Benny.
The old man's harpsichord.
Benny!
No.
No, no.
[ Breathing shakily ]
Benny?
Andrea.
[ Groans ]
[ Punches landing, thudding ]
Idiot.
Gonna make me do this
all over again, aren't you?
Hello, Sorento.
He turned you.
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
[ Ringing ]
Little busy right now.
This is
Dean's other, other cell,
so you must know what to do.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Amelia:
So, that's what you do?
You stalk helpless women
and you break into their motel
room and you fix their plumbing?
Why are you fixing my sink?
Well, because somebody jammed
about 800 limes
down the drain...
and blew out the disposal.
Oh. Right.
Don't touch the produce.
Right.
I thought you were leaving town.
I am.
I'm just helping out
with maintenance at the motel,
you know,
while Everett's dad is sick.
Who's Everett?
[ Scoffs softly ]
How long have you been here?
Three months. Why?
Well, you know, usually when
someone moves into a town,
they actually, uh, you know,
move into the town.
I did.
A motel is not actually part
of the town that it's in.
It's not part of anywhere.
Well, I haven't found
a place yet.
Why am I explaining myself
to you?
You're a drifter
or a handyman.
I-I think
I should just go.
Yeah,
I think you should go.
[ Sighs ]
[ Keys clatter ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
Hey.
Dean: Okay, what?
What?
Why did you call me?
Why are you whispering?
It's kind of hard
to explain,
but I'm sort of in the middle of
cleaning out a vampire's nest,
and it's sort of gone
a little sideways on me.
What?!
Are you an idiot, Dean?
You know better than to go
into a vamp nest alone.
I'm not alone, damn it.
All right? I'm not alone.
I've got backup --
guy who's been tracking the nest
for a while.
What guy? Garth?
What? No.
You don't know him.
He's a friend.
A friend?
Dean, you don't have any --
all your friends are dead.
That's not what I called
to talk about.
Sorento, go.
Tell the old man it's true.
He listens to you?
It's been a long time.
Our father has come to trust
my judgment over Sorento's.
I answer only to him.
Well, sleeping with God
has got to have some perks.
Yes, it does.
Make sure the old man
has everything he needs.
Oh, Benny.
When I heard
you were back --
I don't know --
somehow, I knew it was true.
I had to believe it,
to hope.
Andrea, what happened?
The old man said
he was gonna bleed you dry.
I don't know.
He changed his mind.
I blacked out.
When I woke up,
I was drinking from his wrist.
I'm sorry.
All this is because of me.
No.
It's not your fault.
You never hid anything from me,
Benny.
I chose you.
But why'd you stay...
with them, with him?
Why?
You remember
what it's like at first.
First, everything resets.
Life is blood.
That's all.
And whoever gives it to you --
I know.
It's complicated.
Every damn thing
is complicated.
It doesn't have to be.
Andrea.
Benny, I can't kill him --
none of us can.
But you -- you came back
from the grave.
You're proof that
he's not all-powerful,
that he's not God.
He's scared of scared of you,
Benny -- I know it.
You understand
that I came back
to burn his operation
to the ground,
to stop the killing.
[ Door opens ]
Do what you came for,
and we can be together.
He wants Benny
brought to him.
Sam: I get the separate-lives thing,
but this is a hunting thing,
and we need to
find that line --
Oh, my God, stop talking.
I texted you my 20.
Yeah, I got it.
Look, I'm on my way.
And, listen,
if you handle it, great.
I'll buy your friend
the first round.
But, Dean, listen to me.
Dean?
Dean, are you there?
Dean. Dean.
You kidding me?
Oh, man, come on.
Damn it!
[ Cellphone clatters ]
[ Sighs ]
Hello, father.
Benny.
I have no words.
Now,
I know that ain't true.
Can you help us
understand?
I know you don't owe us
anything, but how?
How are you here,
standing in front of me?
I found a way back.
From Hell?
Right next door,
as far as I could tell.
Next door?
What's that?
Oh, I think
I'll just have to show you.
I know
it won't change anything,
but I regretted
having you killed.
When it was all done,
I wailed when I saw you
in all those pieces.
Didn't I, Sorento?
Didn't I wail like
the ugliest baby in the world?
Sorento: Yes, father.
That's when you decided
to turn his cow.
Poor so-so is bitter because
your "cow" outranks him now.
Why didn't you
let her die?
She meant nothing
to you.
But she meant everything
If that's all I could salvage
from my wayward son --
the woman
he defied his maker for --
I wanted someone
to remember you by.
[ Blade plunges, thud ]
Dean: What the hell do you know
about the value of life?
You're a vampire.
Benny: Yep.
And I think we both know which
of our kinds kills more humans.
Well, statistically speaking,
that'd be your --
Yes,
thank you, Cass.
I get it.
You're worried what I might do
if we make it topside.
I'll start eating
your little piggies.
I already told you, man --
by the time I got iced,
I was strictly on blood
transfusions, donated blood.
Not donated to me,
I'll give you that,
but I paid good
black-market scratch for it.
So, what is that?
Like the vampire zone diet?
Look, all I'm saying
is I started seeing something
in humanity, okay?
Something
that shouldn't be taken.
I drink blood.
I don't drink people.
And why the hell
should I believe you?
What does it matter
what you believe?
You got your head
so far up your ass, Dean,
you don't even realize
we're already done for.
The angel knows it.
We are never gonna make it
with him next to us
glowing like a beacon.
Do I need to remind you
of our deal?
Of what you committed to?
He is gonna get us
killed.
We may get
to test that theory.
- More monsters?
- Leviathan.
Why don't you
blip out of here?
They're too close.
I can't.
Run.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Lock disengages ]
[ Engine turns over, revs ]
[ Barking, panting ]
No, no, no.
Dog, dog, dog!
Oh, no, dog, don't bother
the...angry lady.
Uh, hey, sorry.
"Dog"?
That's what you're calling him?
Uh...
[ Chuckles ]
Well, it's accurate.
Is dog taking
his antibiotics?
Uh, yes, he is.
He's doing much better.
Thank you.
You know, um,
I have to say -- um...
I've seen a lot of stitches
in my time,
and you've got
really good hands.
Thank you.
So,
you think I'm creepy?
I think it's creepy you buy all
your clothing at army surplus.
- White supremacists do that.
- Yeah, but I'm not.
Drifting serial killers do that.
[ Chuckling ] Fair enough.
You come from nowhere,
you appear to be going nowhere,
and you've
"seen a lot of stitches."
It's all pretty solid creepy.
[ Chuckles ]
You have no idea where
you're going, either, do you?
No.
Not really.
[ Chuckles ]
And that's because
you have no one.
I mean, at all, right?
I mean, that's why you're...
here in this place.
[ Laughs ]
I used to --
have someone, I mean.
But that's over now.
It's gone.
You know what that's like,
don't you?
Dean: This is Dean's other,
other --
[ cellphone beeps, clatters ]
[ Engine revs ]
I suppose you coming back
from the dead --
well, that's the definition
of mutiny, isn't it?
[ Sighs ]
All of this has me feeling
so...tired.
You should have let me go.
But, Benny,
I don't let things go.
Really?
You lived so long, how is it
you have so little, hmm?
Nothing but a beat-up old
harpsichord and nest of hyenas.
I have the sea.
- And I have Andrea.
- No.
You don't have her.
At least that much
I know.
Oh, that dumb bitch.
[ Grunting ]
When the hell did you learn
to fight like that?
I've had
a lot of practice.
[ Breathes deeply ]
- You just gonna sit there?
-You're right.
I've been here so, so long,
Benny, seen all the outcomes,
all the patterns
a trillion times.
It all means so little.
This universe is a pyramid
of despair, nothing else.
A little dark.
I am evil, after all.
At least I've had that much
to keep me cold at night.
You never had that,
did you?
Everything had to be
thought about, considered.
You know what Socrates said
about a life unconsidered.
Yes.
But what we have in us?
Benny, that's not life.
That's what
you still don't get.
That's why it's always been
so hard for you,
my poor Benjamin.
[ Growls ]
Get up.
[ Laughs ]
This is the one last thing
I can take from you.
No.
You try, damn it.
You try and kill me again.
This is my story,
you gnat.
Get up!
It ends the way I choose, not you.
Well, at least I can finally
show you something new, old man.
A whole new world.
The old man is dead.
Let's go.
Where, Benny?
What are you talking about?
Anywhere.
You're not leaving here,
are you?
And you never were.
We have everything we need
right here.
The operation
is still perfect.
We can ride the high seas,
plunder together.
We can have the life
we always wanted.
What I wanted was to leave
a burning crater behind.
I wanted to put your memory
to rest.
But I'm not a memory.
Benny, I'm right here.
What I loved --
it ain't here anymore.
It was snuffed out a long time
ago by monsters like me...
like what you've become.
You think
you're better than me now?
No.
I think we're all damned.
[ Hisses ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathes deeply ]
Why'd you do it, Dean?
Do what?
Resurrect me.
You could have drained my soul
into any culvert,
and no one
would have been the wiser.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Hey, you good?
Man...
I don't know what I am.
Oh, great.
[ Grunts ]
I'm Benny.
Heard a lot about you,
Sam.
I can see you two have
a lot to talk about.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==