I don't hunt anymore.
- You quit?
- Yeah.
What could possibly
make you stop just like that?
Was there a girl?
Yeah. There was.
And then there wasn't.
You need to know,
I didn't just drop out.
I found something.
- Yeah, what was her name?
- Amelia.
Professor morrison,
your government needs you, sir.
My God,
where'd you find this guy?
Supposed to be a top expert
in his field.
- Wait, there's another tablet?
- Yes.
So another word of God?
How many words of God
are there?
I just became a Prophet,
like, a year ago.
Well, did this tablet have a name?
"Demons."
What about demons?
As far as I could tell...
everything.
Kevin!
- You've got to be kidding me.
- Hey. What's it say?
Since we lost the tablet,
Kevin figures we don't need him.
Yeah,
but Crowley still does.
What's that kid thinking?!
He was
our responsibility.
Let's find him.
Okay.
Aah!
Congratulations.
You're fast.
I do a lot of cardio.
? Supernatural 8x03 ?
Heartache
Original Air Date on October 17, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Wow.
Guy goes to Purgatory for
a year, all hell breaks loose.
Check this out.
A jogger in Minneapolis
gets his heart ripped out.
I'm guessing literally?
Only way
that interests me.
And then, there's another
article from six months ago.
Same thing happens,
also in Minneapolis.
What does that tell us?
Stay out of Minneapolis.
Two hearts ganked, same city,
six months apart.
I mean, that's got to be
a ritual, man.
Or at least some sort of
a heart-sucking, possessed,
satanic, crack-whore bat.
A what?
It's a case.
Look, I say we hang out
the shingle again and ride.
We're on a case, Dean.
Kevin and the demon tablet
need to be found,
so heart guy
takes a number.
Uh, we just spent a week
chasing our asses
trying to lock Kevin down,
okay?
And look at us. We're --
where the hell are we?
Farmers' market.
Organic.
What?
I had a year off.
I took the time
to enjoy the good things.
While avoiding doing
what we actually do.
Wow, Dean, does it make you feel
that much better
every time you say it?
All right, man,
look, I get it.
You took a year off to do yoga
and play the lute, whatever,
but I'm back.
Okay, we're back,
which means that we walk
and kill monsters
at the same time.
We'll find Kevin.
But in the meantime,
do we ignore stuff like this?
Or are innocent people
supposed to die
so that you can shop
for produce?
Here's what's odd
about this thing --
the guy wasn't chopped
or cut into, no incision.
But his heart was ripped
out of him like a peach pit.
Was he robbed?
Phone, watch,
money all still on him.
What about enemies?
He was in town for a conference.
No local connections.
You guys had another one
of these about six months ago.
Yeah,
and we hit a brick wall.
We had nothing to go on,
really.
Thought maybe
we got lucky here.
A park surveillance camera
picked up something.
Huh.
That chubby guy the last person
to see the vic alive?
Other than the killer.
Name's Paul Hayes.
We pulled him in
for questioning.
So what makes you think
he's clean?
Well, so far,
no reason not to.
I mean, he said he briefly saw
the victim,
he ran out ahead,
that was it.
What, you mean
he didn't fall to his knees
and confess
to gutting the guy?
No. I mean we did
a thorough check on the guy,
not so much
as a parking ticket came up.
I mean, look at him.
I mean, sure, he can run
a little bit, but Thor he ain't.
You think he's gonna grab
Freddy fitness here
and throw him down
and rip out his heart?
I don't think so.
Forgive me if I didn't take him
out back and shoot him.
Okay, uh
so...
...any idea where we can find
this guy?
Sorry.
I kind of try to stick to a
nutrition and workout schedule.
Do you want a hit?
I'm good. Thanks.
Oh.
So, Paul, you passed a runner
who was later killed.
Did you speak with him
at all?
Yeah, I went over this
with the cops.
I-I didn't know him.
I had never spoken to him.
I ran past him.
I never saw him again. The end.
Mm, oh.
It's disgusting.
It tastes like crap,
but it keeps you young.
Thanks, uh -- uh...
Too much fiber.
No such thing.
Thank you.
See?
Now, Paul,
we couldn't help but notice
that the jogger you outraced was
a good deal younger than you.
Yeah, and less, uh...
Uh, full-figured?
You should've seen me before.
Yeah, hugging a desk all day
and watching TV all night,
eating fried everything
was killing me.
I had a health scare
about a year ago.
I'm sorry to hear that.
No,
it changed my life.
I mean, I started taking care
of myself.
Now your body's a temple,
huh?
Where I worship every day.
Ah.
All right,
so...What's the word?
What did you find
poking around at Paul's?
Ah, just the usual --
condoms, hair gel.
No hex bags, nothing satanic,
nothing spooky.
So,
he didn't seem like a guy
who would be voted
most likely to disembowel?
No, they never do.
Wait a minute.
Here's another one.
What, murder?
And a do-it-yourself
heart bypass.
Two days after this one.
What part of Minneapolis?
The Iowa part. Ames.
Well, Paul was here
being questioned.
There's no way
that could have been him.
This guy was a cop.
This is exactly what happened
six months ago.
Minneapolis, then Ames.
Guess you missed that one.
I'm just saying.
Arthur Swenson.
Real top-shelf officer.
20 years on the force.
He'd ordered a pizza,
which the vic delivered.
And then?
The vic didn't make
his next drop-off.
His body was found on the walk
in front of Swenson's.
And he wasn't wearing a heart?
No.
Heartless.
And, uh,
what about Swenson?
Crumpled on the front stoop.
Covered in blood,
crying like a baby.
Ironically, he had been in court
all week, testifying.
Hey, Levitt, line two.
Excuse me.
Go ahead.
So that couldn't have been him
in Minneapolis.
I hate
when this happens.
So, this Arthur guy,
what does --
what does he have to say?
Uh...
it's not real helpful.
So,
you getting his statement?
Uh, yeah, k-kind of.
Probably not.
It's too bad I dropped out
of Lunatic 101.
Whatever it is, it sounds like
he's repeating it.
Look at his eyes.
Hey, Arthur...
Did you do this alone?
Arthur, did some invisible voice
tell you you had to kill?
K'uhul ajaw, Cacao,
shi-jiiy!
Oh,
now you've pissed him off.
Hey, Art.
Can I call you Art?
Listen, I'm gonna sprinkle
your arm with holy water,
and it's gonna steam and burn
if you're possessed by a demon.
He's a mushroom.
Okay, not possessed.
Arthur, you want to tell us
why you did this?
K'uhul ajaw, Cacao,
shi-jiiy.
Okay.
Aah!
So, what do you think?
Personally, I prefer
the Keith Richards version.
Can you actually understand
any of the words?
If they are words.
Sounds like babble to me.
Wait a second.
What?
I bought a translation app.
You bought an app.
Yeah.
Here, play it.
Softly repeating "K'uhul ajaw,
Cacao, shi-jiiy" ]
And babble wins.
"Language unknown."
Mm.
Agent Sambora.
What?
So, Dr. Kashi,
what are we looking at here,
some kind
of psychotic break?
Oh, definitely.
He was very thorough.
Severed the optic nerve.
He was determined
to remove the eye.
And he used,
uh, what to cut with?
He doesn't look strong
enough, but he broke off
part of the bed frame
and used it as a knife.
Thank you.
Wow. They should put
warning labels on those beds.
Like I said --
determined.
I noticed that he had
two different-colored eyes.
Yes. Apparently,
he was in an accident
where much of one eye
was shattered.
His vision was saved
with a transplant.
When was this?
A year ago,
almost to the date.
And, interestingly,
it's the transplanted eye
he chose to cut out.
Really?
Hey, let me ask you something,
doc.
Is it possible to trace the
donor of a transplanted organ?
Difficult.
But possible?
Hmm.
- Hey.
Arthur Swenson had an eye
transplant a year ago, right?
Yeah.
Well, I remembered
that Paul Hayes
was talking about a health scare
he had a year ago
that changed his life,
so I pulled up his medical
records from Minneapolis.
You want me on board,
I'm on board.
Anyways, you want to guess
who else,
other than Arthur Swenson, had
a transplant in the last year?
Paul Hayes?
I gave it away, didn't I?
Okay,
so we've got two suspects
in two identical murders
in two different cities
that both had organ transplants
a year ago.
Yeah. Also...
I love
when there's an "also."
I got to thinking
about all that stuff
Arthur Swenson
was talking about.
Maybe your translation app
called it "language unknown"
because it's a dead language,
like ancient Greek or Manx.
Manx?
So I e-mailed an audio file
of Arthur's mumbling
to Dr. Morrison.
Who?
Dr. Morrison,
the anthropology Professor
who helped us out
with the Amazons.
Yes, okay. Okay.
Well, let's get our asses
on the road.
Headed to...?
Well, if we are in a repeat
of a cycle from six months ago,
then, after the murders
in Minneapolis and in Ames,
the next heart attack
was in Boulder, Colorado.
Randa?
Chick, right?
Loved your performance
tonight.
Must take, uh, must take
years of training.
Actually, uh...
I'm kind of a natural.
Um...
You know, I don't normally do
this kind of thing.
Mm-hmm.
Um, there's just --
just something about you.
All right,
case is coming together.
Things are coming together,
man.
You and me.
It is all good.
Hey.
What?
What are you thinking about,
organic tomatoes?
I'm not thinking
about anything.
I don't know about you,
but this last year has given me
a new perspective.
I hear you. Believe me.
But now I know
where I'm at my best,
and that is right here,
driving down crazy street
next to you.
Makes sense.
Yes, it does.
Or...
maybe you don't need me.
I mean,
maybe you're at your best
hacking and slicing
your way
through
all the world's crap alone,
not having to explain yourself
to anybody.
Yeah, that makes sense,
seeing as I have
so many other brothers
I can talk to
about this stuff.
Look, I'm not saying
I'm bailing on you.
I'm just saying make room
for the possibility
that we want
different things.
I mean, I want my time
to count for something.
So,
what we do doesn't count?
Yeah?
Hey, Dr. Kashi.
Okay.
Thank you.
Uh, could you run
one more name for me?
Yeah -- Hayes, Paul.
Uh-huh.
And the donor?
Seriously?
How many others?
Did anybody
from Boulder, Colorado,
receive
any of those organs?
Okay, thank you.
Well, this is gonna singe
your axons.
She says that both
Paul Hayes' kidney
and Arthur Swenson's new eye
came from --
you ready for this? --
Brick Holmes.
You don't mean
the Brick Holmes.
I do.
- The all-pro quarterback?
- Indeed.
Yeah, the guy played
at the top of his game
for like a million years,
didn't he?
Yeah, he -- he bought it
in a car crash last year.
Yeah.
Nose-dived off a bridge
or something.
He must've signed
a donor card.
Did the doctor say
how many organs he donated?
Including our two suspects?
Eight.
Eight?
Okay, um, and one of them's
in Boulder, am I right?
You would be wrong.
That's the bad news.
Good news is, Brick lived
just outside of Boulder.
Well, Brick's dead.
Yeah, but he's all we got,
so we are going to Boulder.
K'uhul ajaw, Cacao, shi-jiiy.
I just want to say
how sorry we are for your loss,
Mrs. Holmes.
Thank you.
You know, Brick Holmes was
my idol back in high school.
Amazing career.
18 pro seasons, 7 division
championships, 4 Super Bowls --
never slowed down a day.
Brick lived for competition
and athletic perfection.
I don't think it occurred
to his fans that he was human,
like the rest of us.
Do you know your son was
an organ donor?
Does that make this
a matter for the FBI?
Like we explained earlier,
we're mostly here to dot
some I's on a different matter.
There was a public-awareness
thing a few years ago.
A lot of star athletes
signed on.
I'm sure Brick
didn't think twice about it,
since he never thought
he was going to die.
A lot of jocks are like that,
I guess.
You know,
I-I can't help wonder
what happened that night
on that bridge.
There was light traffic, no
alcohol involved, no skid marks.
Big-time athlete,
reflexes like a cat,
how is it that he just drives
off the side of a bridge?
When things happen
that aren't supposed to happen,
they're called accidents,
I believe.
So, everybody knows about
Brick's football career, obviously,
but no one knows much
about his personal life.
Was he ever married?
Just to the game.
He gave it everything he had.
It's a difficult life.
Did you notice any changes
in Brick before he died --
you know, anyone,
anything new in his life?
No, no.
I don't think so.
So, no new interests?
Fly fishing, stamp collecting,
the occult?
The occult?
As a "for instance."
No.
Everything was
just as it had been.
I'm sorry,
but I'm afraid my time is up.
The university is naming a new
athletic building after Brick.
I can't be late.
Of course.
Just one more question.
There is always one more
question in life, isn't there?
That's what I find.
Right.
Oh, she didn't want to say much,
did she?
- Son of a bitch.
- What?
There it is.
It happened.
Come on, don't tell me someone
had their heart ripped out
here in Boulder.
All right, then I won't tell you.
What are you doing here,
Randa?
You know I like to stay close
to the mother ship.
I saw a car out front,
so I came in the back.
Cops?
I suppose Brick's death
continues to fascinate.
So we're clear...
You're still being very careful
about what you say?
I'm old, Randa,
not an idiot.
I'm just trying
to protect Brick.
And so am I.
Brick's heart beats
inside here now.
Brick gave me new life.
I can feel him.
It's why I moved
to Boulder...
to be near here.
And I'll watch out for you
like Brick did.
I don't need
your concern.
We need each other,
and Brick needs us.
You keep
our little secret safe,
and the three of us
will be just fine.
All right, Professor Morrison,
that does it.
The FBI thanks you.
Yes,
I am totally looking into
adding you
as a technical advisor.
Yeah, I-it comes
with a medical plan.
All right, goodbye.
He come through?
Yeah, he did.
All right, so, here's
what crazy Arthur Swenson
was babbling over and over.
Um, first,
it is a dead language --
ancient Mayan.
Doesn't get much deader
than that.
So, what Arthur was saying was
"The divine God Cacao is born."
Cacao?
Cacao. Yeah,
the Mayan God of maize --
corn, the big crop.
See, Cacao was
the most powerful God
because maize was the most
important thing to the Mayas.
Well, that and torturing
and killing everyone in sight.
So, this is
what we're looking for,
is a thousand-year-old
culture's God of corn?
Uh, I guess.
Well, whatever it is,
we better cap it quick,
or somebody in Phoenix
is next up
to get their heart yanked.
Someone in Phoenix
got a piece of Brick?
Yeah, I got a name.
Just e-mailed the cops.
Just heard back from them.
They haven't seen the guy
in days.
Uh, oh,
got another e-mail here, too.
This one is for you.
From a university.
Answering questions
about admissions.
Just something I'm looking into.
An option.
You're seriously talking about
hanging it up?
I'm not talking about anything,
Dean.
I'm just looking
at options.
So, what, should we just go
to Phoenix
and chase our tails
until this guy shows his face?
No. Uh, Brick Holmes
is the way into this.
Eleanor Holmes was doing her
damndest not to tell us a thing.
Nice job on changing
the subject, though.
All right,
naming ceremony's over at 10:00.
We got to get in and out.
Master bedroom.
Yeah.
Closets.
Brick's closet.
Looks like the stuff hasn't
been touched in a year.
Man, what this stuff
would go for on eBay.
Hey, Sammy,
would it totally crush you
to know that your boy Brick
wasn't a natural blond?
Dean, this is really weird.
What do you got?
I don't know.
Is this Eleanor's closet?
Why would his mother's closet
be in here? Are you sure?
Check this out.
This is what she was wearing
today when we talked to her.
Maybe she moved
into Brick's room after he died.
Or...
Oh.
Thanks, Dean.
Now that image is permanently
etched into my retinas.
That's
what I'm talking about.
Wow.
I knew he'd have something
like this in his house.
This is a lot of hardware.
Okay, the football trophies
I get,
but there's a lot
of other stuff here --
I mean, baseball, boxing,
race-car driving.
He was a fan.
Any kind of athlete --
he respected them.
I mean, look at all
the old stuff he's got --
a cricket mallet,
golf clubs,
a Kendo sword,
archery equipment.
Hey, look at this.
They're all the same.
"Dearest Betsy..."
Blah blah blah.
Who's Betsy?
I don't know.
Girlfriend?
Eleanor didn't mention
a Betsy.
This one looks old.
Uh, "Dearest Betsy,
third day of training camp.
"Roadwork improving.
Working on my left jab.
They say this kid Sugar Ray
is gonna be tough."
Sugar Ray?
As in Robinson?
Didn't he box in, like,
the '40s?
Is it signed the same?
Yeah. "Love, me."
Here. "Dearest Betsy,
on the road again.
"So hard to be away from you,
honey.
Will give the Red Sox hell
and get back to you."
"Dearest Betsy..."
"Dearest Betsy, Le Mans will be
a bitch this year with all the rain..."
"...the Phillies are tough,
but we're looking to be tougher..."
"...them Dodgers will wish
they never left Brooklyn..."
"...looking for my best gal
Friday night at the Garden..."
"...our o-line hung tough.
I had all day back there..."
"...Alain Prost is a monster
in the straightaway..."
"Dearest Betsy..."
"Love, me."
Wait,
this one looks recent.
"Dearest Betsy...
So tired of it all."
Hey.
I pulled up the names
on those trophies. Check it out.
All right, Brick Holmes --
football player.
Charlie Karnes --
race-car driver.
Davey Samuelson --
baseball player.
Kelly Duran -- boxer.
Four different guys, right?
Okay.
Check this out.
Same dark eyes, same cheekbones,
nose, mouth.
Wait, are you saying
that these four guys
who all look to be
in their mid-20s
and go back 70 years
could be the same guy?
Wow.
For a 95-year-old,
Brick Holmes could take a hit.
So, if all those athletes
were the same guy,
how'd he pull it off?
Appear, then go away
and come back with a new look?
Cacao, the, uh, the --
the maize God --
was Mayan, right?
Yeah.
The Maya were all about war
and torture and conquest...
and sports.
It says, "Their athletes
were treated like kings.
"The Mayan jocks made sacrifices
to Cacao by --"
ready for this? --
"killing a victim, pulling out
his heart, and eating it."
They believed the rituals
gave them super-charged power
over their opponents.
Yeah, but they didn't stay young
forever.
So, what?
Maybe Brick just made some kind
of deal with this Cacao?
Well,
we've seen it before --
people making deals
with demons, Gods.
I mean, maybe he stayed
young and strong
so long as his sacrifices
kept coming.
Remember all that antique
sports equipment he had?
This guy could go back
to the Mayan days.
Wow.
So, one of the greatest QBs
to ever play the game
was over 900 years old.
Well,
that explains Brick,
but what about the mooks
carrying his spare parts?
Maybe the spell
went along for the ride
and infected the people
who got his organs.
Remember how Paul Hayes said
he had a health scare
that changed his life?
I mean, maybe the spell
could compel him
to keep carrying out
the ritual.
Sort of like getting bit
by a werewolf.
I mean, once you're infected,
you do what you got to do,
especially if you like
the results.
Right, except old Arthur,
the dedicated cop,
couldn't handle it
and went nuts.
Brick Holmes, a heart eater.
Who knew?
Hey, sorry, buddy.
The mighty --
they fall hard, huh?
Well, at least he wasn't
sleeping with his mother.
Yeah, good, Sam.
Find the silver lining.
No, seriously. Look.
"Fighter Kelly Duran
is congratulated
on a second-round knockout
by wife Betsy."
"Dearest Betsy."
Hello, Eleanor.
Or would you rather us
call you Betsy?
Look, Eleanor,
innocent people are dying.
And they're gonna continue
to die until we stop it.
Did you know about the murders
over the past year?
No. I didn't.
I swear.
I thought when -- when
Brick died, it would be over.
Help us.
Betsy, this is not what you want
Brick's legacy to be.
His Mayan name was Inyo.
He was a proud young athlete
nearly 1,000 years ago.
He lived for sport
and never wanted
his days in the sun to end.
So he arranged a bargain
with the God Cacao
through a high priest.
Stay young forever.
As long as the sacrifices
continued, twice a year --
once for the planting,
once for harvest.
When did you find out
about this?
Not until I began to age
and -- and Brick --
Kelly, as he was
when I met him -- did not.
But by that time, Brick himself
had changed...inside.
He wasn't just the warrior
whose only reason for living
was combat.
He --
we were deeply,
deeply in love.
So in love, I'm ashamed to say,
that when I found out that --
how my husband stayed
young and strong,
I chose to ignore it.
You and Brick had to go
underground from time to time
to hide your secret, right?
Every 10 years or so,
he would re-emerge
with a new look, a new name.
And me, I was the wife,
and I was the woman
in hiding,
and then,
when I got into my 40s,
I became Brick's mother.
Eleanor.
I am so tired.
You can't imagine
the burden of it all.
I think even Brick
was through.
He could see the end of my days
were at hand, and...
He had lived centuries
all alone,
but I don't think
he could bear the thought
of life without me.
That's why he drove
off that bridge.
You must think
I'm a monster.
No.
No,
just that you married one.
Well, see,
here's the deal.
Now there are eight killers
out there
that we have to deal with,
not just one.
I don't think so.
What? Why not?
Brick used to say
the heart was key.
That was the focus
of the sacrifice.
Are you saying that if we stop
Brick's beating heart,
then we could stop
the whole thing?
Do you know where the person is
who has the heart?
Do you know?
Really?
Our king daddy monster
is a stripper?
We're pretty sure
this is gonna work, right?
Well, as long as Eleanor knows
what she's talking about.
You think Brick thought
maybe he'd burn to nothing
when he crashed that car?
Yeah, but he didn't,
which brings us here.
Smell that?
You're gross.
Eleanor sent you,
right?
I figured she'd probably break
and give me up.
This won't end well for her,
of course.
Not that it's gonna end well
for you.
Oh, now, you don't think we're
gonna let you do that, do you?
"We"?
I'm the guy from Phoenix
you were looking for.
Oh, you guys are stronger
than you look.
Comes with the package.
Plus, I work out a lot.
You can't imagine
who I was before.
This shy, awkward little thing
from Georgia
with a heart condition.
Then I had the surgery.
I became freaking
Xena: Warrior Princess.
I couldn't dissect a frog
in high school.
But sacrificing to Cacao?
Better than sex.
So, if I go real slow
and take my time and enjoy this,
I can actually show you
your own beating heart
before you die.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Well, we better get going, uh...
We just wanted you to know
that it really is over now.
Well, it had to be,
one way or the other.
I half thought you might fail
and Randa would come after me.
Either way,
I'd finally be at peace.
You take care of yourself,
Eleanor.
Wow. Back in business.
Got the win.
Admit it --
feels good, huh?
You know, I was thinking about
what Randa said about, uh,
you know, what it feels like
to be a warrior.
I get it, man, I do.
I know.
I know you do.
I don't.
Not anymore.
Hell, maybe I never did.
Come on, Sam, don't ruin
my buzz, would you?
Dean, listen,
when this is over --
when we close up shop
on Kevin and the tablet --
I'm done.
I mean that.
No, you don't.
Dean,
the year that I took off,
I had something
I've never had.
A normal life.
I mean, I got to see
what that felt like.
I want that.
I had that.
I think that's just how you feel
right now.
Amelia!
Amelia, this isn't funny.
Riot?
Riot!
Happy Birthday!
What is this?
You've never seen
a birthday cake before?
Sit.
Eat.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==