"Supernatural" by Carver Edlund.
Everything is in here --
I mean, everything,
from the racist truck
to me having sex.
Moondoor.
Wait, is that --
Defend the Queen of Moons.
I love you.
I know.
What's the second trial?
An innocent soul
has to be rescued from hell
and delivered unto heaven.
Aah!
Sam?
It's done.
Kevin tran. Thought you could
elude me forever.
He's gone.
The little geek
made a run for it.
What the hell?
What the hell is this?
"1951"?
? Supernatural 8x20 ?
Pac-Man Fever
Original Air Date on April 24, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Y--
Man,
I'm telling you,
give me five minutes
with some clippers, and --
Oh, shut up.
Uh, what time
did I lay down?
You took a siesta
around noon...
Yesterday.
I'm sorry. Uh...
That's why we don't have
nice things, Sam.
You okay?
Yeah,
I'm -- I'm fine.
Just, uh,
you know what?
I'm gonna get dressed.
We should go find Kevin.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey.
Easy, easy,
sleeping beauty.
Look, man.
I've hacked
into every security camera
around Garth's houseboat,
Kevin's hometown,
where Mrs. Tran lived.
And?
Well, nothing so far.
Dean,
we have to find him.
I know. I know.
Look, Garth is out
looking for him.
We've got a Hunter A.P.B.
out on Kevin.
We will do what we can
from here.
While you get better.
I'm fine.
Dean,
I can still go out there.
I can still hunt.
Really?
This is stupid.
All right.
You hit that target,
we'll talk about
you getting back out there.
No problem.
Look, man,
that second trial hit you
a lot harder than
that first one.
I don't know whether it was
just more intense or what.
It felt the same...
Till the next day.
So, we're gonna sit tight,
keep an eye out
until you, uh, get better.
It's from Charlie.
"In the neighborhood,
found you guys a case""
Found us a case?
"In the neighborhood"?
How the hell's she know
where we are?
Uh...Well, she doesn't.
Not exactly, at least.
It says she tracked our cells
to a 20-mile radius,
then the signal went out.
Huh.
This place must be
in some kind of,
like, Bermuda Triangle.
What, are you saying
that we can make and receive
phone calls from here
and nobody can track us?
Man, I love this place.
Your highness.
What's up, bitches?
You okay, Sam?
Yeah. No, I'm --
I'm good. Yeah.
What are you doing
in Kansas?
Uh, a comic convention,
in Topeka.
In the middle
of the week?
Girl's got to get
her collectibles.
So, you gonna invite me
into your dungeon,
or do I got to answer
your questions three first?
Follow us.
Let us introduce you
to the Men of Letters.
Holy awesome.
Too bad
they got wiped out,
though
that is what they get
for the sexist name.
Well, anyway,
that's our skinny.
How about you?
Um...
Made a deal with
the Yesteryear weirdos.
We're gonna team up
to stomp the Shadow Orcs.
You guys are still coming
to the midyear jubilee, right?
Wouldn't miss it.
So, what about
this case you brought us?
Oh.
When I was in Topeka,
I saw this pop up over the wire.
Tom Blake,
a checkout clerk in Salina
who went missing
on his way home from work --
he was found dead yesterday.
His insides?
Liquefied.
Locals have
no idea what happened.
They tried to bury the report
so people wouldn't freak,
but I flagged it.
I have eliminated
the following things
that go bump in the night.
Wait a second.
When did you become
such an expert?
Well, after you guys left,
I dug into all things monstrous.
I'm a wee bit obsessive...
If "a wee bit"
means completely.
I also found this series
of books by Carver Edlund.
Did those books
really happen?
Wow.
That is some meta-madness.
Thanks for saving the world
and stuff.
Sorry you have
zero luck with the ladies.
Wha--
we need to find every single
copy of those books
and burn them.
They're online now,
so good luck with that.
Awesome.
Well, you two crazy kids
deal with that.
I will go see
if there's anything to this,
uh, case of yours.
I'm coming with you.
Whoa. Are you sure
you're okay?
- Yes.
- No.
You're taking a knee
as long as you're off your game.
I'll go with you.
Look,
no disrespect, okay,
but there is
a big difference
between reading about hunting
and actually hunting.
I'm coming with.
For serious?
Okay.
Now, if you can hit
that target,
then we can
talk about you --
What?
All right, if you're gonna do
a ride-along, then, uh...
You got to lose
the novelty T-shirts.
Son of a pantsuit.
? Yeah, yeah
? I used to think
maybe you loved me ?
? now, baby, I'm sure
? and I just can't wait
? till the day
when you knock on my door ?
Montage.
Trials?
That's never good.
Yeah, and our Prophet's
in the wind.
What about, uh, Castiel?
He seems
helpful and dreamy.
He's M.I.A.,
with a tablet of his own
doing God knows what.
I mean, to be honest,
this whole thing is...
I mean, Sam's a tough
son of a bitch,
but Cass was saying
that these trials
are messing with him in ways
that even he can't heal.
If it's any consolation,
having read your history --
there is pretty much nothing
the Winchesters can't do
if they work together.
Thanks.
Must be nice,
having a brother,
someone to always
watch your back.
Yeah.
No brothers or sisters?
Actually, I have two.
Their names are
Xbox and PS3.
I'm not getting
any reception.
Can I use your phone?
Mm. Sure.
Yeah?
Hey. It's me.
You okay?
Yes, Dean,
I'm still fine.
Look, I can hunt.
Well, let the healing continue.
I'll check in with you
later.
Close enough.
Come in.
Hi.
Uh, Special Agent Hicks.
This is my partner,
Special Agent Ripley.
We're here about the body
with the creamy filling.
Ah, right.
I didn't think you guys
would have any interest in that.
FBI, ma'am.
We never leave a stone
unturned.
Mind if we take a peek?
Of course not.
I just need your signed
chain-of-custody request,
and it's all yours.
I'm sorry. The what?
Chain-of-custody request
from your supervisor to mine.
Right.
Uh, you know what?
You want to call
my supervisor?
I'm sure he can give you
the override or whatever.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Unless he can get me
the form,
I can't give you access
to the body.
But...FBI.
I understand, dear,
but paperwork is paperwork.
Of course.
Jennifer.
Uh, it is Jennifer?
Yeah.
Um, we have been
on the road all day,
and this
is strictly routine,
dot-the-"I," cross-the-"T"
kind of thing.
If you could do us
a solid...
Come back
with the signed form.
I'd be happy
to do you a solid.
Until then...
That never happened
in the books.
You want to tell me happened
back there, Boo Radley?
I'm sorry.
I-I froze.
I couldn't
control-alt-delete my way out.
Real-life role-playing
is hard.
It's okay.
We'll come back later
when, uh, Doris Do Right
isn't here anymore.
Oh, perfect.
Breaking and entering.
No different than hacking.
Beg to differ.
One I've been doing
since I was a teenager.
The other
I've done once
with you two idiots
walking me through it,
and I had my arm broken
in the process.
What did you hack
when you were a teenager?
Uh...NORAD.
Yeah. Whatever you say,
"Wargames."
Why don't we go grab some grub
while we wait?
Awesome.
I got three stars.
So?
I'm three levels
ahead of you, man.
Dude, stop.
I can't.
I'm just too good.
Dude!
Whoa. No, dude.
That's a bad idea.
Your face is a bad idea.
See?
Nothing to worry about.
Aaaaah! Aaaaah!
Maybe you should
go first this time.
Unh-unh.
Back on the horse, kiddo.
Come on.
Hey, there.
I am
Special Agent Ripley.
This is my partner.
Save it.
Your other agent's
over there.
What took you guys
so long?
What the hell
are you doing here?
Working the case.
Same as you.
Jake Hill. Librarian.
Went missing yesterday,
no relation to the other vic.
Coroner
already swooped in
and scooped up
what was left of him.
Yeah. Yeah, we met her.
Bit of a stickler.
Well, there's, uh, not a body,
nothing else to see here,
so why don't you
head on home?
Still haven't
talked to the witnesses.
Well,
we can handle that.
Charlie, why don't you
go talk to the witnesses?
But I don't want to miss
the "bro-ment."
Charlie!
Look, man,
I know you're frustrated,
but you're also sick.
I'm not leaving, Dean.
Hey, boys.
Special Agent Ripley,
FBI and...stuff.
What game
you guys playing?
"Super Eater."
"Underworld Adventures"
or "Dimension Travelers"?
"Underworld Adventures."
Nice.
So, about that childhood trauma
you experienced earlier.
I know you want to help.
I do, all right?
But --
Dean, you cannot take care
of the both of us.
I need to be out here.
"Play through the pain""
right?
Come on, man.
Don't quote me to me.
So, the boys said
they noticed something
on the body's arm
before it covered them
in years of future therapy.
Said it looked like
a blue handprint.
Sounds like something
you should read about.
In a book. At home.
I'm not leaving
until we find out
whatever's doing this.
Whatever.
You guys fight like
an old married couple.
Charlie.
Does this mean
we don't have to break into
the coroner's office anymore?
That's a great idea.
Is he leaving?
He's leaving.
That's all right.
I stole your car.
I think I know where he's going.
Come on.
Cool.
Wait, you stole my car?
What took you so long?
I stopped for gas.
Shut up.
The body's in here.
The hell?
Charlie!
It's the coroner.
I got this.
Hello.
Hey, there.
Front door was open.
Oh.
Uh, w-what are you
doing here?
I, uh, came back
to get a blank copy
of that form you asked for.
The FBI doesn't have
chain-of-custody forms?
The field office
had a power outage
after catching fire.
Figured I could just borrow
a copy or two.
Of course.
Just give me sec.
What the hell?
It's empty.
Uh...
They burned the bodies.
Already?
Yeah.
They think it's some kind
of, like, outbreak scenario.
Even got the CDC
to sign off on it.
These folks
run a tight ship.
Okay.
Here you go.
Great.
Perfect.
Thank you.
Well,
if you'll excuse me,
I have some work to do
in the morgue.
Uh, can I ask you
a personal question?
I am new
to the whole power-suit thing,
and yours...
is killer.
Where do you get them?
Does this mean we need
to take "Silkwood" showers now,
or is this
still a case?
Yeah. Something about that Mark
the kid saw rings a bell.
Probably have to check the lore --
or maybe dad's journal.
Hurry up.
All you need are three jackets,
three pairs of pants,
and you're all set.
So simple, so smart.
You should have a blog.
Okay.
I'll get right on that.
Um, so,
what about shoes?
I can never find
the right kind to go with --
Okay. I'm sorry,
but I'm not a stylist.
Uh, well...
Thanks for the forms
and the fashion advice.
You're the best.
Don't go changing.
'Kay, bye.
Leviathan?
Mm...
They consume their prey.
Well, maybe the vics
were Leviathan.
No black goo on either scene,
according to the reports.
Dragons. They, uh --
No signs of burns
on the vics.
I hate that thing.
I want one.
Wait a second.
Djinn.
Djinn vics
don't get liquefied.
No, no, no, no.
Not regular Djinn.
According to this,
there is a bastard offshoot.
Uh, their eyes
light up blue.
They pass as humans,
all that regular jazz.
Except these
"leave their victims
with jelly-like insides""
and supposedly,
when they poison their victims,
they leave behind
a blue handprint.
I hate that thing.
And I want one.
So, do these things
die like regular Djinn?
Silver blade dipped
in lamb's blood, yeah.
Now we just got to find
the asshat.
All right.
Well, breakthrough means
snack time to me.
And I want to just,
uh, stretch my legs.
I will pick us up
some grub,
and unlike you, Sam,
I will not forget the pie.
She seem
a little off to you?
Since the second
she got here.
Charlie...
it's Sam.
Uh...Again, call us.
Okay?
Hey.
Any word from Charlie?
Uh, no.
And there was
no comic convention in Topeka.
I don't know why.
I mean,
why would she lie to us?
One way to find out.
What are you doing?
When I called you
from her phone,
I turned on her GPS.
Charlie?
Hey, Charlie,
you in there?
Dean.
The hell?
What the hell
is this place?
Whatever it is,
it belongs to Charlie.
Or some variation of her.
Who the hell is she --
Jason Bourne?
All right, so,
we got no forced entry,
so either it was somebody
that she knew or --
Djinn.
Here's
all our missed calls.
You got anything
on her laptop?
Yeah.
Uh, she's been making donations
through her aliases
to Shawnee County General
here in Topeka.
Like, a charity?
A patient.
Gertrude Middleton.
We need answers.
Uh, I'll take Gertrude.
You keep Djinn-digging.
Gertrude's been in a persistent
vegetative state for 16 years.
About a year ago,
her condition got worse.
This ventilator's the only thing
keeping her alive.
How did this happen?
She and her husband
were hit by a drunk driver.
He didn't make it.
They were on their way
to pick up their daughter
from a sleepover.
Their daughter?
She was 12.
She got into trouble
after her parents' accident.
Nobody's
heard from her since.
Folks have been donating
to cover Gertrude's care
over the years.
It's a sweet gesture,
but the truth is, she's gone.
She ever get any visitors?
A couple nurses said
they thought
they saw someone
in here reading to her,
but nobody's ever officially
signed in to visit her.
She's all alone.
If you'll excuse me,
I have to make my rounds.
Thank you.
You got one hell of a daughter,
Mrs. Middleton.
I promise you I will find her.
You're not going anywhere.
Wilhelm scream.
Do you know
what I smell on you?
Deodorant?
A little pee, maybe?
Fear.
Djinn smell fear?
Well, well, well.
If you know about Djinn,
then you
and your little friend
are Hunters, not FBI.
No. I'm --
I'm more hunter-in-training.
Totally
not worth killing.
Oh, but you are worth killing,
sweetheart.
Yeah.
You see, my kind --
we prefer
a more bitter taste to blood
than
the run-of-the-mill Djinn.
We prefer
the taste of fear.
And when I got a whiff of you
at that morgue...
Oh, such delicious fear
inside of you.
I followed your scent.
I knew you'd make a meal
fit for two.
For two?
No.
So, no chance
of a recovery, huh?
No.
No, Gertrude seemed like
a cool mom, too --
kind, strong, taken from
her family way too young.
Remind you of anybody?
Did you find anything?
I think so.
A John Doe
from nine years ago.
The original coroner
wanted the body sent to the CDC,
but the coroner's
new assistant
"accidentally" ordered
the body to be burned.
New assistant?
Jennifer O'Brien.
Coroner's a hell of a cover
for hiding kills.
My manly man friend's
gonna come get you,
you creepy power-suit lady.
Oh, let him come.
He reeked of fear,
as well.
Look at this. CDC?
Never heard from Jennifer
this time, either.
She faked the reports,
burned the bodies
to cover her tracks.
Why'd she get sloppy again
after nine years,
start leaving the bodies
where they could be found?
Well, let's go ask her.
According to this,
she owns two pieces
of property in town --
one 2-bedroom house
about 10 minutes from here
and an abandoned
shipping warehouse.
Of course she does.
Charlie.
Hey.
Hey, Charlie.
You okay?
Where's Charlie?
What the hell's going on?
I don't know.
Uh, different Djinn.
Maybe she needs
a different antidote.
Charlie?
She's burning up, man.
We're not letting her
turn to jello.
Okay, okay.
Uh...Okay.
Djinn poison puts your brain
into something like
a feedback loop
while your blood boils, right?
Right.
Um, if the antidote
didn't break the loop,
then maybe we can find a way
to break from the inside.
I mean, Djinn take you
to your happy place.
Your happy place
is like a dream.
African dream root.
All right.
Let's do this.
Ugh.
Okay.
All right, I'm gonna need
to go to sleep fast,
so, uh, punch me.
Look, man,
I know you don't want to, okay?
Aah.
Wow, you're a little
off your game there
'cause that was, uh,
that was pretty --
Come with me
if you want to live.
I've always wanted
to say that.
What are you doing
in my dream?
You were attacked
by a Djinn.
The coroner,
Jennifer, remember?
Djinn usually send you to your,
uh, happy, your happy place.
No judgment,
but you got a really strange
sense of happy, kiddo.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Jennifer said that her kind
feeds off fear.
This isn't my happy place.
This is a recurring nightmare
of mine.
What is this?
It's a video game.
Wait a second.
You're telling me that this
whole thing is a video game?
It was called
"The Red Scare."
Uh, first-person shooter
against super-soldier vampires.
I copied it off of
a game company's server
before it was finished,
reprogrammed it to reflect
my flamingly liberal politics,
and then I released it
for free.
Then they tracked me down
and had me arrested.
I was 12.
And you've been on the run
ever since.
So, how do we
get out of here?
I don't know.
We gave you the Djinn antidote.
It didn't take.
And I killed the Djinn.
Both of them?
You killed my mom.
We got to get back
and help Sammy.
Tell me about this game.
Maybe if we can win --
Look, I don't know
how long I've been out,
but I've been through this level
a thousand times already.
What?
Every time I beat the level
and save the patients,
I get reset
back to the beginning,
only there's less weapons
and the vampires are faster.
It's an infinite loop.
Like Pac-Man
without level 256.
Level what?
Nothing.
Wait, what patients?
Charlie?
I know who this is.
What are you talking about?
When you went missing,
me and Sam found
your little crash pad.
We saw the payments
that you make for her.
So, I went and visited your mom,
looking for you.
She's why I'm in Kansas.
I sneak into the hospital
whenever I can,
and I just --
I read to her.
She used to read me to sleep
at night when I was a kid.
She'd read me
"The Hobbit."
She's the reason
I love the stuff I love.
I'm sorry for your loss.
She's not gone.
Sam?
Is this my nightmare
or yours?
So...
It wasn't your mama
who messed up.
It was you.
Shut up!
I just came of age.
I had to feed.
I screwed up.
M-mom knew
how to cover her tracks.
She always told me
not to play with my food.
Maybe you should have
listened to your mom.
This is it --
the boss battle.
Come on,
we got to save the patients.
Wait, wait.
You said that we're stuck
in a loop, right?
And out there in the real world,
you're dying.
And I might be, too.
We got to find a way
to break this loop.
Okay. How?
I think the only way
to stop this is to not play.
What?
No. No.
We've got to save them.
Nut up, Winchester.
See?
You can't stop, either.
Listen to me,
this poison --
it's designed to put your mind
into an endless cycle
while your insides
turn to mush, okay?
And its fuel is fear.
Now, call me crazy,
but I think
the only way
to break this cycle
is to let go of the fear
and stop playing the game.
You don't know that.
I know that your fear
is creating all of this.
But you're not afraid of those
super-soldier vamps out there,
you're not
afraid of this game,
and you're not afraid
of what it did to you.
Hey. Look at me.
You're afraid
of losing her.
Charlie,
she's already gone.
No. You don't understand.
You don't understand.
I was at a sleepover,
and I got scared, so...
I called my parents
to come and get me.
They should never have been
driving that night.
It wasn't your fault.
I just
want to tell her that I'm sorry
and I love her
and just have her
hear it again.
I just need her to hear that
one more time.
But she can't.
She can't.
I know.
Believe me, I know.
But you got to let her go.
Game over, kiddo.
Mom?
Dean.
Dean. Hey, hey!
Come here.
You okay?
What happened?
I'm okay.
Charlie?
I'm sorry.
I had to.
So, thanks
for saving our bacon.
Any time,
your highness.
You know you're gonna
be okay, right?
Those books portray you as,
like, one tough customer.
If anyone can get through
the trials, Sam, it's you.
Thanks.
You know,
you really should come back
and dig through
our archives.
You are definitely
a Woman of Letters.
I like the sound of that.
Well, thanks for
stopping by, Charlie.
Always wanted
to get "Tron"ed.
What's next for you?
Gonna go by the hospital.
Got to let go, right?
What about you?
You gonna let it go?
Never.
That's my boys.
I love you.
I know.
Okay, look,
you were right.
I-I should have laid low.
I-I know.
I should have hung back.
But I'm glad I was able --
What do you say
we find our Prophet?
Take all the time you need
with your mom, okay?
One last time, okay?
"In a hole in the ground,
there lived a hobbit.
"Not a nasty, dirty,
wet hole,
"filled with the ends of worms
and an oozy smell,
"nor yet a dry, bare,
sandy hole
"with nothing in it
to sit down on or to eat --
it was a hobbit-hole,
and that means comfort."
== sync, corrected by elderman ==