What do you think it is
that we're hunting?
Animal, vegetable, mineral.
I know you boys think
I'm a bag of loose screws.
Martin saved dad's ass
more times than we can count.
He's a great hunter.
No, I'm not.
I'm useless.
You asked me
if I lost someone.
I did -- my husband.
Amelia, you okay?
Amelia: It's Don.
He's alive.
I'm Benny.
I just might be
that hunter
that runs into Benny one day
and ices him.
I guess we'll cross that bridge
when we come to it, won't we?
Yeah.
Yeah,
you keep saying that.
[ Creedence Clearwater Revival's
"Born on the Bayou" plays ]
? Now, when I was
just a little boy ?
? standing to my daddy's knee
? my papa said,
"son, don't let the man get ya ?
? do what he done to me" ?
I sent Anthony home,
so the kitchen's all yours.
And be sure to lock up the door
and set the alarm,
turn off the A/C,
check the burners,
check the griddle...
And clear off
the cold table.
I got it.
Go on, now.
Thank you, Roy.
Oh, and don't forget
to "Z" out the register...
And batch out
the credit-card machines.
I know.
Darlin', it's not
my first rodeo, all right?
I'll see you tomorrow.
[ Door opens ]
Hell of a girl,
that Elizabeth.
Yeah.
Yeah, she really is.
Refill?
Sure.
You got designs?
Nah.
She's more like a little sister
to me, you know?
So you don't mind
if I take a shot?
[ Chuckles ]
She's all yours, chief.
Hey.
Please?
Thanks.
[ Frogs croaking,
insects chirping ]
[ Thud, rustling ]
[ Rustling ]
[ Man screams ]
[ Metal slices, thud ]
[ Grunts ]
? Supernatural 8x09 ?
Citizen Fang
Original Air Date on December 5, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Sam: Yeah.
And you're certain?
You sure?
Okay. Great.
Just, uh, just hang tight
till you hear from me, okay?
Who is it?
No, listen to me.
I said hang tight.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
We got to get.
Can I at least
finish my burger?
We got a vamp kill, Dean --
Carencro, Louisiana.
Huh.
It's been a while
since I've had some ?touff?e.
Who's the source?
Martin Creaser.
Sorry --
for a minute there,
I thought
you said Martin Creaser.
Crazy Martin
from the loony bin?
Glendale Springs
discharged him last month.
And?
Shouldn't he be assembling toys
in a padded room?
What's he doing
back on the job?
I asked him.
You what?
Look, he called me
when he got out, okay,
asked if I had
anything for him
that might help him
ease back into the game.
He seemed okay -- mostly --
so I said yes.
I've had him tracking Benny
for the past week.
You put "mostly okay" Martin
on Benny?
What is "mostly okay"
doing hunting at all?
Not hunting, Dean --
tracking.
Observe and report only.
I was crystal clear about that.
Wow.
I can't believe that.
Really, Dean?
You don't believe that?
Because Benny's a vampire.
And any hunter
worth his salt
isn't gonna let one
just walk around freely.
So I had Martin
keep tabs on him.
And right now, it's looking
like I made the right call.
So Martin's saying
Benny did this?
Yeah.
Okay.
"Okay"?
If Benny's in Louisiana
draining folks...
We should look into it.
[ Engine turns over ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Car door closes ]
[ Baby crying in distance ]
You said
"look for an eruption."
How's Mount Vesuvius?
[ Door closes ]
I got into town
about a week ago.
Up until last night, nothing.
He's been clean.
Doing what?
Just minding
his own business.
Working
at the gumbo shack.
Benny's working
at the gumbo shack?
Yeah.
Slinging hash, pouring coffee --
the whole bit.
And he may be Benny
to you.
Folks around here
call him Roy.
Martin, you sure you're running
on a full charge?
Y-yeah.
L-little s-shock therapy
in the morning,
and I-I'm good to go.
Tell us
what happened last night.
So, I followed him home,
just like every night.
He turned up a path.
I hear a scream.
I catch up.
Boom -- there he is.
The old coot that Roy was eyeballing
at the joint -- vamped.
Wait -- did you actually see
Benny kill the guy or not?
I saw enough.
Well, then, how can you be sure
it was Benny
if you didn't
actually see him do it?
B-b-because I saw Benny
turn up the path,
and then
two seconds later,
I trip over a body
with its throat ripped.
Look, man, you ever hear
of occam's razor?
"Keep it simple, stupid?"
It's not that complicated.
There's a lot of holes,
Martin.
Holes?!
The only holes
we should be looking at
are in
the vic's neck.
This sound like
the Benny you know?
I don't know Benny.
The Benny you know?
Say what?
Why am I getting
the distinct impression
that your brother
is vouching for a vampire?
Guys, let's not argue.
Nobody's arguing,
but if this is Benny --
and that's a big "if" --
Oh, it's him.
I got history with the guy,
okay?
I'm not signing up
for a witch hunt.
I owe him
more than that.
What in
God's great creation
could a Winchester
possibly owe a vampire?
Am I hearing this right?
Look,
until we get the facts,
we stow the bloodlust
and we work this case right,
or we work it
separately.
Doing it right would be separating
his head from his shoulders.
I just need some time,
Sammy.
Oh, yeah. Let the fang take
another life? I don't think so.
How much time do you need?
You're not actually
considering this?
Couple hours, tops.
And what if it turns out
to be Benny?
Then it's Benny,
and I'll deal with it!
Couple hours, Dean.
No more.
I'll be in touch.
H-hey.
Oh, look.
Hey, uh --
you're joking, right?
We're doing this
as soon as he pulls away.
No, we're not, Martin.
We're gonna give him
a little bit of time.
Hey, it's your brother.
It's your call.
[ Chair scrapes ]
How long are you gonna
let him go on like this?
It's staring him
right in the face.
[ Scoffs ]
Well, sometimes
it's not easy
to see things
for what they are.
Sam: Get the ball.
Come here!
Come here.
Good job.
[ Sighs ]
Thought about
what you're gonna say to him?
I've thought about it
and thought about it,
and I still don't know.
Look, I'm sure you have
a lot of people telling you
what the right thing to do is
here.
Sam...
He's your husband,
Amelia.
But I-I don't...
I don't want
to do the right thing.
I mean, this is the right thing,
you and me.
And maybe I'm going to hell
for saying this,
but I'm not ready
to give this up.
Neither am I.
Would it bother you
if I just took a few days
to clear my head?
Um...
Of course.
Uh, take whatever time
you need.
[ Rock music playing ]
[ Bells jingle ]
Actually,
I already know what I want.
[ Sighs ]
Let me guess -- gumbo?
[ Chuckles ]
Was gonna be the gumbo
till I saw [clicks tongue] pie.
Well,
the special's pecan.
'Course it is.
Let's do that.
[ Sighs ] Bad news.
You're out of pecan.
Story of my life.
Uh, that's all right.
Maybe you can make it up to me.
I'm actually looking
for an old friend of mine.
I heard he's kicking around
these parts.
His name's Roy.
Well, Roy works
the night shift here.
I mean, if we're talking
about the same Roy.
Uh, yeah, he, uh, putts around
in a beat-up camper.
Thing looks like
a rolling deathtrap.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, I thought
I was the only one
who gave him trouble
over that piece of junk.
[ Chuckles ]
You wouldn't happen to know
where he's parking that thing
these days, would you?
Well, he, uh,
was parking it out back,
but just called
to tell me
he's gone up the road
to Mill creek for a few days.
Okay.
Uh, did he say why?
Oh...
Fishing, I think.
He really deserves
a break.
He's been working doubles
for the last two weeks straight.
Um, listen,
I, uh, I tell you what.
If he pops up
before I can find him,
you do me a favor and just
have him give me a buzz.
Or...
could just drop a dime
yourself.
Sure thing...
Dean.
And, uh, you are...?
Elizabeth.
All right.
Take a rain check
on that pie.
Definitely.
[ Bells jingle ]
[ Ringing ]
Benny:
Leave a message at the beep.
[ Beep ]
Benny.
I got a body here in Carencro
with two holes in it,
and I just found out
you went fishing.
Do I need to tell you
what this looks like?
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Frogs croaking,
insects chirping ]
[ Grunting ]
It's not me, Dean.
Now, which "me"
are we talking about --
Benny...or Roy?
I'm just trying
to blend in.
"Blend in"?
Who'd you plant,
Benny?
Victim number two.
If you're concerned
about the missed calls,
I didn't want
to get you involved.
Now...
Want to safety that thing,
talk a little bit or what?
I'm all ears.
[ Sighs ]
Rogue vamp.
Came into the caf?
a couple nights ago --
youngster
goes by the name of Desmond.
He, uh, he remembers me
from the good old days.
The good old days?
I know
it's hard to believe,
but I haven't always been
this cute and cuddly.
He's chasing a memory,
Dean.
That's all.
He's crewing up
a new nest.
He's hoping
I can give him some cred.
I told him no.
All right.
So far, so good.
Let's get to the part
about the blood.
Didn't want to take no
for an answer.
He's trying
to roust me out,
leaving dead bodies in my wake
till I sign up.
Two bodies in two days.
No amateur is gonna kick me out
of my hometown, Dean.
Not this time.
"Hometown"?
You grew up here?
Born and bred.
With Andrea gone
and you hunting again,
seemed like the right time
for a homecoming,
you two being the only ones
who keep all my ducks in a row.
Went back to my old job
at the caf?, and...
I even found someone
I hold myself accountable to.
Best kind of someone,
Dean.
Family.
[ Chuckles softly ]
Elizabeth.
My great-granddaughter.
Really?
Now, hold it, now.
You didn't --
Uh, no.
[ Chuckling ] No.
Does she know?
No.
No, as far as she's concerned,
I was just another drifter.
I'd like
to keep it that way.
It's been tough
walking the line here
after all those years
in Purgatory
not having to deal
with the hunger.
But Elizabeth...
She keeps me honest.
I finally feel like
I got a handle on this thing.
Handle on things?
Benny, you've got
two stiffs on your hands
and two hunters
on your ass.
Oh, please. The half-wit
who found me at the caf??
I'll take my chances
with him.
That half-wit was sent
by my brother, and trust me --
my brother's not someone
you want to mess with.
I don't have time
to worry about them, Dean.
I didn't think Desmond had
an ounce of steel in his spine,
but I was wrong
about that.
So now I'm gonna do what
I should have done two days ago,
which is put him
back where he belongs.
You know there's only one way
to do that, right?
And that is for you
to sit on the sideline
while I convince Sam and Martin
to go after Desmond.
They see you out there,
they don't care
if you're gonna be collecting
for the March of Dimes.
They are gonna slice first
and ask questions later.
You know that.
You really think
they'll go for that?
Martin:
Let me get this straight.
I follow your boy...
...down a freaking path
and trip
over fresh vamp kill,
and then you practically
catch him in the act
of burying
a second body
and you're still
taking his side?
Vampires pick people off from
the outskirts of town, okay?
Pfffft!
Not in the caf?s
that they work in
with their great-grandkids.
In fact, killing any human --
it's not his style.
"Not his style"?
Listen, Dean,
we came here on a dead body.
You asked for some time, and now
there's another dead body.
Are we just
going on trust here?
Yes.
Okay.
Because we've killed
for a lot less,
and you know how these things
turn out for us.
Yes, I do --
too well.
In fact, every relationship
I have ever had
has gone to crap
at some point.
But the one thing
I can say about Benny --
he has never let me down.
[ Scoffs ]
Well, good on you, Dean.
Must feel great finally finding
someone you can trust
after all these years.
All I'm saying
is that Benny is innocent.
[ Clears throat ]
No.
You're too close to this.
You're not gonna find him.
And if you do,
I'm gonna tell you this.
You'll be lucky
to get out alive.
And you -- you go with him,
you're a dead man -- period.
These are innocent lives
we're talking about, Dean.
And you're willing to risk that
on Benny's word alone?
Damn right I am.
What...was that?
Dean made his choice.
Let's go do our job.
Glad your dad wasn't around
to hear that.
He'd have a mind to
take you both out the woodshed
and show you
what's what.
Half inclined
to do it myself.
You listen to me.
I brought you into this.
I can bring you out
just as easy.
So the only thing
you're gonna be inclined to do
is shut up
and follow my lead.
Okay. You say so.
Just saying -- brother chooses
a vampire over a brother?
I know how I'd feel.
[ Rock music plays ]
You are Sam, right?
Relax.
I ain't here to fight.
I heard about
what happened to you.
Rough deal.
Hmm.
Yeah, well,
I appreciate that.
We got ourselves a situation
here now, though, don't we?
Guess we do.
Truth is, I can't blame
either of you for what happened.
Hell, there were days there
I thought I was a dead man.
But when I do come back
and what I come back to is this,
well, it ain't no great mystery
if part of me is thinking,
"What's wrong
with this picture?"
Don --
Sam, let me finish.
I know
part of her loves me.
And now...
part of her loves you.
But the only one that knows
what's best for Amelia
is Amelia.
So when all of this
is said and done
and she's made
her decision,
I'll respect it.
And if you truly love her,
you'll do the same.
He could use another.
[ Sighs ]
Come on.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
What'd they say?
They didn't go for it.
They're on their way to you.
I'd get scarce.
No offense, Dean,
but your little brother
doesn't exactly
put chills up my spine.
Benny, listen to me.
Do not underestimate
my little brother, okay?
He can and will kill you
given the chance.
All right.
So, what now?
I go find Desmond.
You take me with.
Hey,
I just told you --
best thing you can do
is lay low.
That ain't gonna work
this time, bub.
You take me with,
or I don't tell you where he is.
You know where he is?
He said
he's not gonna stop the killing
till I join
his little nest.
Two bodies is enough.
I told him I'm in.
Benny.
Dean,
this is my fight.
Are you in
or are you out?
[ Owl hooting,
insects chirping ]
Something spooked him.
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
[ Engine turns over ]
Sam.
Sam!
Sam!!
Winchesters.
Man!
[ Engine shuts off ]
This the place, huh?
So, what's the plan?
I hang back while you guys
do some trust falls
and binge-drinking?
[ Chuckles ]
Man, if I didn't
know you better,
I'd say you have an extremely
low opinion of us vamps.
Pssh.
Call it
healthy skepticism.
Benny never told me
he was bringing a friend.
You're not gonna talk a lot,
are you?
I've been dealing
with crazy...
...all day.
[ Groans ]
Son of a...
It took you long enough.
[ Coughs ]
You've lost a step,
friend.
You need to lay off
the junk food.
[ Groans ]
Aah!
You okay?
I'm fine.
My life here is over,
isn't it?
Afraid so.
Once word gets out...
...the machete swingers
that'll come for you...
You can't take them all.
It's impossible.
And even if you could...
We'd have a problem.
Guys like us,
we don't get a home.
We don't get family.
You got Sam.
Yeah.
Benny, you got to go
deep underground,
where nobody knows
who you are.
Yeah.
I got one last thing
I got to do.
[ Speed-dialing, ringing ]
Female voice: The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Engine revs ]
What are you doing?
I'm, uh...
[ Clears throat ]
I'm leaving.
What?
[ Sighs ]
Don found you
at the bar.
Amelia --
He threatened you.
Amelia, no.
He didn't threaten me.
[ Sighs ]
Look, I'm just trying
to do the right thing here.
"The right thing"?
This morning, you and I
were the right thing, remember?
[ Sighs ]
I know that you and Don
deserve a chance, okay?
And...I think
you know that, too.
Just give him a chance --
like you gave me.
[ Sighs ]
I mean...
Amelia, you saved me.
Time to go, buddy.
Thanks for not giving up on me,
brother.
Don't give me
a reason to.
[ Pats back ]
[ Engine turns over ]
[ Vehicle departs ]
[ Ringing ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Hey, Dean.
Look, I'm just calling
to let you know
that the situation
is resolved.
Benny was not lying.
There was another vamp,
and we ganked him -- together.
Oh. That's good, Dean.
Yeah, shut up
and listen to me.
Benny's long gone, and he won't
be coming back ever.
So for your own sake,
do not follow him.
Are we clear?
You don't have to worry
about me, Dean.
I'm long gone, too.
Oh, and, Martin?
Yeah?
Find a new line of work.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Hey, Liz.
How's your shift going?
Mm.
I'd say she's covering for you
just fine...
Benny.
But us regulars --
we miss you.
Who is this?
I think you know
who this is.
How the hell
you get her phone?
You enjoy the cherry?
No!
Sorry.
Not quite done yet.
Oh.
Did you, uh,
reach your friend okay?
I did. Thanks.
I can't believe
I left my cell on the bus.
Wife says I'd lose my own head
if it wasn't screwed on.
I'll just be
another minute.
Well,
you take your time.
Thank you.
She's a nice girl.
Takes kindly to strangers.
You leave her alone --
now.
How far away are you?
An hour.
You got 45 minutes.
Miss?
Your cellphone.
[ Engine revs ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Bells jingle ]
Lay down your arms,
you unholy thing!
You got me here, now.
Why don't you just let her go
and walk away?
I don't think so.
You realize
I'm not asking.
I realize that
completely.
[ Whimpering ]
Roy, what's going on?
It's okay, Lizzie.
He ain't gonna hurt you.
Ain't that right?
Come on, now.
I got no beef with you.
You got no beef with me.
I got plenty of beef
with your kind.
All right.
That may be so,
but not for anything
that happened here.
I did not kill
those people.
I heard.
You and Dean had
a little Purgatory reunion.
Touching.
Roy...
Please just tell me
what's going on here.
Please.
I'm asking you --
do not do this.
The bad guy is gone,
okay?
She doesn't know...
Benny.
Roy?
Who's Benny?
"Who's Benny"?
Let's find out,
shall we?
[ Whimpers ]
Stay back!
[ Inhales sharply,
whimpering ]
Look.
See that?!
Dilated pupils!
Hair standing!
Signs of hunger!
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Whimpers ]
Don't worry.
He won't feed
off his own flesh and blood.
"Flesh and blood"?
Tell her, Benny.
Tell her how you're
her long-lost grandpappy.
Tell her about all the dead
you left behind.
Tell her about the monster
that you are!
[ Gasps ]
[ Whimpers ]
What do you want?
Isn't it obvious?
I want your head
on a stake.
[ Breathing shakily ]
Ohh...
[ Voice breaking ]
Roy, no.
[ Sniffles ]
I'm sorry.
Well, hope they're saving
a special place for you...
Wherever it is
you come from.
No!!
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Music playing on television ]
[ Laughter ]
[ Car door closes ]
[ Engine turns over ]
? ...just go away
? I feel all right
? I feel all right tonight
[ cellphone rings ]
? Feel all right
[ cellphone beeps ]
Yeah?
Woman: Dean?
H-hang on.
[ Music stops ]
Elizabeth?
Y-you told me to call you
if I saw...him.
What do you mean?
Roy?
Is --
is he there right now?
Elizabeth,
what's going on?
[ Voice breaking ]
Just come.
[ Tires screech ]
[ Engine revs ]
[ Engine shuts off,
car door opens ]
[ Door creaks ]
? Tears keep falling down
like rain ?
? here it comes,
that old familiar pain ?
? it's not like I'm trying
to account for every love... ?
[ Ringing ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Ringing continues ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Dean: Sammy?
[ Chuckles ]
"Sam, I need your help.
Come quick."
Nice one.
Swapping Amelia's phone out
with a burner,
sending
a distress signal...
[ Scoffs ]
You got me good.
When did you do that?
While back,
in case I needed it.
Looks like
I made the right call.
So, did you see her?
Yeah.
Yeah, I saw her.
[ Clears throat ]
And she's doing just fine.
But, 'course, you know that.
Actually, I didn't.
I did know it was the only way
to get you to lay off.
[ Scoffs ]
So?
Is it done?
Yeah, it's done.
Any casualties?
Martin.
Was it Benny?
He had it coming, Sam.
I'll tell you
what happened.
I-I know what happened,
Dean.
Okay, you want to listen to me
or not?
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Damn it.
? ...in my brain
? tears keep falling down
like rain ?
? here it comes...
[ Gasps ]
I knew that was you.
? Here it comes,
that old familiar pain ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==