Marc oh don...
...Ki?r tolic
einder bolic.
Freaking witches!
I figured out
how to close the Gates of Hell.
God built a series of tests,
and when you've done all three,
you can slam the gates.
All right. Where do we start?
You've got to kill a hound
of hell and bathe in its blood.
I need you to be safe.
So I'm gonna do
these trials.
Aah!
Sam,
I didn't pass the test.
But I did, and I'm doing
the rest of them.
My ass you are!
I can do this.
You were great, and I want to
give you a little something.
Here you go. Thanks.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Guess it's not my night.
Guess not.
? Supernatural 8x15 ?
Man's Best Friend With Benefits
Original Air Date on February 20, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Wow.
You know, of all the lame-ass
things you've ever said,
that's got to be
the lame-assiest.
I'm sorry,
but I happen to think
Shemp was a funnier stooge
than Curly.
Curly was
a freaking genius!
I always found Curly's work
a bit obvious.
It's supposed to be obvious,
man. Tre stooges.
So, we calling James
tonight?
No.
I'll just call him tomorrow.
That drive was a bitch.
I wonder what he wanted.
Well, his text said
that he needed help.
He's a cop. I figured
it was work-related.
Yeah, well,
we do owe him.
The guy saved our lives once,
Sammy.
I mean, it's not like the guy --
Saved our lives?
I'm gonna go for a beer run.
You need anything?
No, I'm good.
You sure?
Yeah.
'Cause you did just gank
a Hellhound,
which is no slice of pie,
and, uh, there is a mine field
of who knows what crap ahead.
Just want to make sure
that you are okay.
I'm good.
'Cause, you know, we could find
another devil dog.
You could tag out.
I could snuff
the son of a bitch.
Dean, Kevin doesn't even know
what the next trial is yet.
So whatever it is
you're worried about, stop.
I'll be ready.
Oh, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uh...No. Um...
Hey.
You friendly?
Friendly. Good.
All right.
You're a pretty dog.
Oh, really?
You want, uh -- you want
a little belly scratch, huh?
So, who do you belong to?
Uh...
Right. No tags.
Uh,
what are you doing here?
Oh, no.
Hey!
Hey.
Okay, okay, okay.
Before you get pissed off,
look,
I-I just want you to know
this isn't my fault.
She just showed up at the door,
okay?
Didn't track in any mud.
Just wanted her belly scratched.
I-I figured
maybe she could stay tonight,
and we'd try
and find her a home tomorrow.
She can stay the night.
Two seconds ago,
she was a dog.
All right,
who the hell are you?
Not a shapeshifter,
so you can stash the blade.
I'm a familiar.
A what?
Companion to a witch --
some witches.
Split their time
between human and animal form.
I get a more accurate read
on people in my other persona.
Approaching guys in a motel room
like this --
well, it gets complicated.
Hmm.
My name's Portia.
I belong to James Frampton.
No. No, no.
See, that --
that doesn't work for us,
'cause that would mean that
our buddy James is a witch.
Wow. You're quick.
James is a freaking witch?
He wasn't when you met him,
but that last case
you worked on with him --
Uh, lunatic alchemist.
It was nasty.
James wanted to learn more
about that world --
the black arts, witchcraft.
It became the center
of his life.
Wait,
so you're telling me
that James the cop
became a witch because of us?
Unh-unh.
You don't like dogs,
do you?
Wait. So James
isn't a cop anymore?
Sure he is.
Homicide detective.
His new powers make his work
even better.
Then what does he need
from us?
Well, something's been happening
to him.
It started
with excruciating headaches,
screaming sounds in his ears,
horrible nightmares.
Unable to sleep or think.
He can't work.
It -- it's like he's having
a breakdown.
Maybe you can find a way
to help him.
Well, here's the thing.
Uh, witches --
not real fans.
Really?
Well, James is a cop
with a spotless record.
He's used his skills
for nothing but good.
So why don't you lose
the ignorant bigotry
for maybe two seconds
and give him a shot?
That was incredibly hot.
It was pretty hot.
You might want to go easy
on that.
God, you look awful.
Not getting any better?
Worse.
I don't know
what's happening to me.
These dreams
they're like, um --
like torture.
You didn't mention dreams.
Dark, bloody.
Spencer, they, uh --
they scare the hell
out of me.
They're so real.
Just night after night.
Enough, James.
It's time to see someone.
Who?
Who do we see?
There's no medicine
for this.
Maybe you just need
time away.
It's way beyond that.
James, it's too much --
all that you've taken on.
Not just the workload,
but the nature of the work.
Look around.
See a lot of cops, do you?
Life in this realm
is life on the fringe.
We don't fit.
How do you reconcile
what you are with what you do?
I don't know
where Portia is.
What?
She's gone.
I think
I'm pushing her away.
So, these dreams
James is having --
he thinks
that they're real?
He thinks that he is
actually killing people?
I think so.
At least that's what I picked up
before he started blocking me.
What does that mean,
blocking you?
Familiars
and their masters --
we can communicate
telepathically.
I can get inside of James' head
anytime I want.
But he shut me out.
So, what, you think
maybe there's something in there
he doesn't want you to see?
Possibly, yeah --
something dark, you know,
that's destroying him.
He can't go to the police, and
he doesn't trust other witches.
But he trusts us?
You do know who we are,
right?
We're the last people
that somebody like James
needs to be telling
his troubles to.
This was my idea.
I was the one who sent you
the text under James' name.
He doesn't know you're here.
But...I think you're
maybe all he has.
Someone there?
You had no
right to do this.
I was afraid for your life!
My life is
none of their business!
Sam, Dean.
Witchcraft, James?
Really?
What the hell
are you thinking?
You come to help
or pile on?
I'm just saying,
you screw with that stuff,
you're gonna fry
your wiring.
All right.
Look, why don't you tell us
about these dreams?
She said people were dying
in them.
"Dying"?
They were torn to bits.
I, uh, I could feel my fingers
ripping into their flesh.
But they were dreams?
Well, I, uh,
woke up in my bed.
Okay, so...Dreams?
I'm not so sure.
Not helping, James.
Those people --
they died.
I checked
with the precinct.
All right, well,
maybe you heard it,
and it stuck in your head.
You're -- you don't think
I-I told myself all that?
You don't think I didn't say,
"that wasn't me.
I couldn't have done
such a thing"?
Is it yours?
James Martin Frampton.
What's happening to me?
Well, how about this?
Um, you pissed off
another witch,
and he or she hexed you
and forced you to...
It's possible, I suppose,
but I never heard of it.
How many of these dreams
have you had?
Four.
The most recent one
is last night.
Uh, it was a blind man.
I, uh...
I was choking him,
and, uh...
All right,
James, we're gonna --
we're gonna help you
figure this out,
but you're gonna have to
do your part.
Which is?
You're gonna have to
stay put.
House arrest, my friend.
Got the last of it.
All right.
Well, I have been looking
at the crime-scene reports,
and they are exactly the same
as James told us --
vics, dates, location.
The most recent one was
a blind man, just like he said.
That's not good.
Also, I looked into his record
on the force.
He went from rookie detective to
lieutenant basically overnight,
and in the last four years,
his solve rate's been
right at about 100%.
Of course.
He's got the booga-booga
on his side.
Man, you know that
we've never actually seen
this witch-killing spell
of Bobby's work, right?
I mean,
this is not a sure thing.
Is anything we ever do
a sure thing?
Well, no,
but I would just like
to have the odds in our favor
as much as possible.
Right.
Well, I'm concerned.
Concerned about the, uh --
the witch-killing spell...
...or that I'm gonna mess
these trials up?
Look, we get too far
down the road with this,
we can't go back,
And it'll be too late
for me to jump in.
Who says
that you're gonna have to?
You know, maybe I'll
actually pull this one off.
I'm just saying.
I know what you're saying,
Dean. You've said it.
You know, I've been going
over this and over this,
asking myself
"why doesn't he trust me?"
And it occurred to me,
finally.
It's not
that you don't trust me.
It's that you
can only trust you.
Are you done?
Yeah,
I'm done if you're done.
You know, once I get this
put together, we can't hesitate.
If we got to use it,
we use it.
You mean if we find the witch
that's doing this to James?
Or if there is
no other witch.
Or it wouldn't be the first
free pass we've given, Dean.
Look, I like James
as much as the next guy,
but people
are getting ganked here.
Besides, Benny, Kate --
they were forced to be
what they are.
James chose this.
Vics were all torn up
pretty bad.
Like someone shredded them
with their bare hands.
Like that could happen. Ed?
Ed Stoltz.
He's lead on the case.
Special Agent Keith.
Josh here tells me
you don't have a lot to go on.
Yeah.
Isolated parts of the city,
vics who meant nothing
to nobody, so...
Right.
Well, uh, my partner and I had
a look at the crime scenes.
Things really must be slow
at the Bureau.
Locations have already been
knocked down.
Well, we did manage to find
this piece of fabric.
Things get overlooked.
It happens.
Why don't you run
the blood?
It could be the vic.
It could be the doers.
Let's see
if we get a match.
A witness did mention seeing
a man in a suit
and a white shirt
leaving the area, so --
You didn't mention a witness
in your report.
Anything else?
No.
We'll get back to you
on the lab work.
So if that's all --
Sure, but this witness --
That's all that was said,
Agent Keith.
We really don't have a lot here,
okay?
We'll be in touch.
Am I getting the stink eye
in here or what?
They can tell
you're an outsider.
Are they all witches?
And stuff.
But if there's information
out here about James,
they'll know.
How did James
find you, anyway?
Not the way it works.
The familiar finds the master,
and they become inseparable.
Guess a lot of people feel
that way about their pets.
What?
I'm not James' pet.
Well, not all the time.
Not ever.
The master
and the familiar --
there's an unbreakable bond,
like a melding of souls.
We would die
for each other.
Portia.
Over here.
Dean,
meet Phillippe LeChat.
Dean's a wiccan
from Detroit.
Really?
Well...Sit, sit.
Spencer here?
Somewhere.
That's weird.
That only happens around cats.
Tell me about James.
Lot of buzz out there.
All gossip.
The community has
a little attitude going.
He brings it on himself.
The whole cop thing --
witch cop -- is he nuts?
I said
the exact same thing.
Then there's you, babe.
It isn't done, Portia,
and you know it.
I'm sorry. Uh, remind me,
what -- what isn't done?
Portia.
Uh,
I'm a -- I'm a wiccan.
I'm from Detroit.
Spencer's
the man to ask.
Oh, okay.
Uh...
You ever heard of a-a spell
where a witch can control
the actions of another witch?
No, I never heard
of a thing like that.
I don't think
it's possible.
How's James?
Better.
I'll tell him you asked.
Philippe,
it's time we were going.
Of course.
Good night.
So nice to meet you.
I knew it.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Where are you?
Some witch bar. Why?
Listen,
I just got the lab work
back from the blood
on James' shirt.
And?
Not good.
Blood's an exact match
to victim number three.
Well, that pretty much says
it all, doesn't it?
Yeah.
I hate doing this to you.
It's okay. Really.
We don't have to.
You know,
they won't find out.
Portia...
If I believe I'm innocent,
I have to do
the right thing.
And if I'm not innocent,
I have to do the right thing.
Tell me one day
this will be over.
I love you.
No!
No, Dean!
You have to listen to me,
please. It's not James.
Tonight,
James and I were close,
without psychological walls --
intimate.
I don't --
They had sex.
Wow.
I, uh -- I didn't expect that.
We have
an unusual relationship.
Familiars aren't supposed to be
sexually involved
with their witches.
Understandable, you know,
considering that you're a...
...well,
and that he's...
That's --
Little help here?
No?
James and I --
we hadn't made love in weeks.
His agony ate him up,
and he shut me out.
But tonight,
I saw his thoughts --
memories of the murders.
I'm sorry,
is this you trying
to talk us out of ganking James
or --
Dean, that's all I saw --
just the kills.
No preparation,
no thought process,
no anticipation, no motive.
Just the kills
without context.
No other awareness
of the crimes?
No.
Doesn't that at least suggest
he's under another's control?
Spencer said
that wasn't possible.
He said
he'd never heard of it.
James is chained.
He's confined.
At least take a shot.
Gentlemen.
Still investigating
this crappy little case?
I'm awed the Bureau
has so much time on its hands.
Right. Well, we have some,
uh, individual discretion
to pursue cases.
I'll catch up later, Ed.
Yeah, but at some point,
cases like this go cold,
as I'm sure you're aware.
Just not enough to keep them
floating -- that's all.
Sure.
No new leads, then?
No. And it's drifting towards
the back burner, really.
We just don't have
the manpower.
Then it must have been tough
to lose a valuable resource
like Lieutenant Frampton.
See,
he and I -- we, uh --
we caught a case together
a while back.
Well,
he's not lost to me.
He's -- he's on leave.
I remember he said he was
the youngest guy here
to ever make lieutenant.
Must have made a few waves.
Nah. This place is run
like a dogsled --
no stars. Just grunts.
One mutt goes lame,
another one pops up
and slogs through the slush.
Agent.
So this, uh, warlock
we're meeting --
he's --
he's a snitch?
Cops have snitches
all over town.
James uses Drexyl
when he suspects someone
in the community.
I got to ask.
I-I can't help
but wonder --
Which came first,
dog or girl?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean,
I'm just curious
as to which one
you consider yourself, mostly.
This have anything to do
with what I told you
about James and me last night?
How you're imagining it?
What?
No, that's...
Yes.
Drexyl, this is Dean.
Wiccan, Detroit.
I heard.
So, here's the deal --
absolutely no word on the street
about any witch
hexing another one.
You sure there's
not any kind of spell?
Look, Detroit, I pride myself
on reliable sourcing.
There is, however, a lot
of chatter about our James.
What kind of chatter?
That he's gone ripper.
As in Jack the --
Someone's circulating the rumor
that he's set at full kill.
"Someone"? One of us?
If the cops get wind of it,
arrest James,
find out what he really is,
that exposes the rest of us.
You know
that can't happen.
Meaning?
They're gonna give James
two choices --
leave
or the full hara-kiri.
Suicide?
Witches appreciate
a grand gesture.
I won't let him do that.
Well, the community might do it
for him.
Hey.
So, I have been going over
Bobby's data.
Anything?
Uh,
Portia might not be wrong.
Turns out there is
a spell for, uh --
for implanting images
into another person's brain.
Really?
Yeah.
Uh, "Creating false memories
into another witch's mind."
Wow.
So James could be convinced
he killed those other people
without ever touching them.
So, then,
maybe it is somebody else.
Yeah, who's going to a
hell of a lot of trouble
to make it look like James.
What'd the cops say?
Here's the thing.
Um, according to Ed Stoltz,
they got zip,
but they got something.
I saw the, uh, tech guy
who's working the case,
and he had a huge file folder
marked "James Frampton""
Ed didn't mention that.
No, he did not.
All right.
Oh, by the way,
got to hand it to you.
It's been 15 hours since Portia
mentioned her night with James,
and not one bestiality joke
out of you.
Portia tells me
my friends in the community
want me burned at the stake.
I'm not gonna lie.
It's, uh -- it's getting ugly.
Yeah, the cops may have more
on the case than they're saying,
including a thick dossier
on you.
Me?
Yeah.
I get the feeling whatever they
have is under lock and key
at the precinct,
uh, room C-110.
Then we need to break in.
Sure, yeah.
A locked room in a joint
crawling with cops 24/7 --
why didn't I think of that?
Dean, a witch can go to a place
without having to go to a place.
What, like phone sex?
Astral projection.
I can project my awareness
anywhere...
Ohh.
...from the comfort
of right here.
But these have got to go.
Not gonna happen.
Irons on, no magic.
No magic, no break-in.
Okay.
But only if we can go
with you.
James, are you sure you're
still even able to do this?
Oh, well,
that's a confidence builder.
Anything else I should know
before I become some disembodied
thing, completely at his mercy?
Just close your eyes.
Whatever I see,
I'll pass on to you, too.
Libera me occulta
cognoscere veritatem.
James, why don't you give us
a little warning
you're gonna snap us back
like that?
Stoltz --
he's building a case against me.
What?!
Ed -- he's always wanted
a breakthrough case.
Nailing a renegade cop --
that would qualify.
Yeah, especially one he holds
a grudge against.
My first case -- they dropped
him as lead detective.
They went with me.
So what is this, you think --
a payback?
He can't just arrest you.
He needs evidence.
He needs proof.
He's got it!
He's got everything.
From who?
Phil. The cat.
Philippe.
Hey, hey, hey.
Take it easy.
James, hey.
Talk this out, buddy.
James, don't!
We'll do this together.
No, we won't.
It's not safe for you.
Our time together is over.
Standing by you is my duty,
my choice!
Portia, the ceiling
is coming down on me.
You still have a life.
Please.
Portia, go.
James --
Go!
So, you don't think it's
too late for me to wear braces?
Won't even notice them.
We'll put in transparent.
James, what are you doing?
Why are you telling lies
about me?
I'm not. I wouldn't.
I saw the evidence room.
I saw the police sketch based
on an eyewitness account.
Get lost.
Please, don't.
Tell me why.
I had no choice.
What does that mean?
My master made me.
Liar.
You're a coward and a liar.
Spencer's my friend.
A direct command.
Please,
don't hurt my face.
I'm not interested --
He was always spineless.
Now literally.
It was you.
You were behind all this?
I humbly accept credit.
You made me think
I was a killer.
Ed Stoltz
put you up to it.
He found out you were a witch,
tried to blackmail you.
You're not using
your thinking cap, Jimmy.
It was actually crucial that he
didn't believe in the occult.
I'd say he's built
quite a solid case, don't you?
I don't understand.
Of course you don't.
Neither of you ever considered
my feelings.
Portia?
This is about her?
Can you imagine the insult
when she chose you?
I wanted her as my soul mate
the moment I saw her.
She was meant to be
my familiar.
Oh, she's way more
than familiar, isn't she?
When she picked you as master,
I endured it.
But when you two went
all Bella and Edward,
broke the code,
put your passions
before the community rules,
well, the arrogance,
the entitlement was too much.
Your total ruination
seemed appropriate.
The wiccan from Detroit.
So James didn't kill
those --
Seriously,
you want to take me on?
Hurry.
It's not only James' head
I can get inside.
Dean.
Sam!
Ego voco impetu delere...
...vos caelum et infernum.
Well, kids,
don't try this at home.
You sure you don't want to stay
and fight this?
Look,
we can help you.
Eh,
Spencer was right.
Ed Stoltz has built
enough of a case
against me
to make life hell
for a long time,
and the community here
wants no part of us.
We start over.
We're used to it.
It's the way it's always been,
for all of us.
I'll miss you.
Maybe even you.
I like dogs.
No. You really don't.
Well,
it's possible I was wrong.
What, about James?
Dude, we were both ready
to gank the guy.
No,
that's not what I meant.
Back there,
when Spencer had us.
He screwed with my head.
I saw mom...
When she died...
And then some other crap.
Yeah. Me, too.
You know, when I look back at
what our family's been through,
what everybody's
been through,
seeing all that pain...
I realize that the only way
we've made it through it all
is by hanging together.
I trust you, Sammy.
With this deal,
locking those sons of bitches up
in the furnace
once and for all,
it's too important not to.
So if you say you're good...
...then that's it.
I'm with you 100%.
I'm good.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==