You're freakin' alive.
What the hell happened?
Standing too close
to exploding dick
sends your ass
straight to Purgatory.
For the whole year?
Well, how'd you get out?
? I think
I'm going to Katmandu ?
? that's really,
really where I'm going to ?
? If I ever get out of here
? that's what I'm gonna do
? K-K-K-K-K-K-Katmandu
? I think it's really
where I'm going to ?
? If I ever get out of here
? I'm going to Katmandu
Hello, Dean.
How the hell
did you make it out?
Hello, Castiel. My name
is Naomi. We rescued you.
Hell Gates.
What about Hell Gates?
The tablet told me all the stuff
about closing the gates of Hell.
Forever.
Her name's Amelia Richardson.
She and I had a place together
in Kermit, Texas.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving.
What?
I'm just trying to do the right thing here.
You and Don
deserve a chance.
Dean Winchester?
You're an angel?
My name is Samandriel.
There are more tablets?
More than "Leviathan"
and "Demon"?
These are innocent lives
we're talking about.
And you're willing to risk that
on Benny's word alone?
Damn right I am.
Lay down your arms,
you unholy thing!
What do you want?
I want your head on a stake.
- No!!
- Is it done?
Yeah.
Any casualties?
Martin.
Was it Benny?
He had it coming, Sam.
? Katmandu
Naomi.
Naomi, Crowley has me.
Ah, ah, ah.
Been on angel radio,
have we?
No.
Don't lie to me,
Alfie.
I'm not lying.
Please,
I wouldn't lie to you.
Oh, Alfie,
after all these weeks together.
I mean, how --
how I wish that were so.
Now we're
going to have to...
Turn off that signal...
Again.
No.
No!
N-o-o-o-o-o-o!
? Supernatural 8x10 ?
Torn and Frayed
Original Air Date on January 16, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Who did you expect?
Long drive?
Well, I wouldn't have
had to make it
if you hadn't have hung up
on me.
Yeah, well,
I heard all I needed to hear.
No, you heard
what you wanted to hear.
I told you
Benny wasn't killing.
Hell, I watched him end
the fangbanger that was.
How about Martin?
How did he end that?
Stupid --
just like I said it would.
Crazy son of a bitch
didn't give Benny a choice.
It was self-defense.
Seriously, Dean?
That's the story
you're going with?
That the vampire
was the real victim here?
Hey, like it or not,
that's the truth, okay?
There was a time when that
actually meant something.
Yeah, yeah.
No kidding.
What does that mean?
You think this is
just about Benny?
What the hell
are you talking about?
What the hell do you think
I'm talking about?
Amelia?
Oh, come on, man.
I sent you that text
'cause I needed you to -- to --
You needed me to what?
To tear ass to Texas?
To be afraid that what happened
to Jessica,
what happened to...
everybody that we care about
might have happened
to her?
You were gonna kill Benny.
What was I supposed to do?
Is that what we are?
You save a vampire
by making me believe
that the woman I love
might be dead?
What do you
want to hear, Sam?
That I was wrong?
Fine. I was wrong.
Okay?
But if you'd have just
heard me out,
if you'd have trusted me,
all of this
could have been avoided.
You didn't want me
to trust you.
You wanted me to trust Benny,
and I can't do that.
Okay.
Okay, well, then,
what the hell do we do now?
That depends.
It depends on you.
On whether or not you're done
with him.
Well, honestly,
I don't know.
Glad I made the drive.
Shh.
He's been crying
for two days.
The doctors
missed something.
It's called an inguinal
hernia -- very hard to detect.
Castiel,
we have a situation.
Samandriel
has been captured.
I thought
Samandriel was dead.
He's been missing,
and now we know --
Crowley has him.
Where?
His distress call cut out
before I could pinpoint
his exact location,
but you will find him
and you will bring him home.
Crowley will have warded
against angels this time.
I'll need help getting in.
Take whatever you need.
But you will be certain,
Castiel,
it was your idea
to rescue Samandriel,
not mine,
not Heaven's.
Do you understand?
Aah.
Damn it, Cass!
How many times
I got to tell you...
...it's just creepy!
Dean, I need your help.
The angel Samandriel...
Sam--
...He's been taken.
You mean Alfie,
the wiener-on-a-stick kid?
Yes.
I -- I heard his
distress call this morning.
On what, angel radio?
I thought you shut that down.
Well, my penance,
it's going well,
and I thought it was time
to turn it back on.
I've, uh...been
helping people, Dean.
Well, good for you.
All right.
So, who snatched heaven's
most adorable angel?
Crowley.
I'm listening.
Samandriel is being held
in the general vicinity
of Hastings, Nebraska.
"The general vicinity"?
That's all you got?
Yes, which is why
I need your help.
It seems this is
gonna involve...
talking to people.
Come on, Cass, I thought
you were a hunter now.
Well...I thought so,
too, but...
It seems I --
I lack a certain --
Skill?
You saw nothing.
All right.
What am I looking for?
Well,
when you torture an angel,
it screams,
and that kind of pain,
it creates a ripple effect
of strange incidents.
Where's Sam?
Sam's gone.
It's all right.
We'll, uh, find Alfie ourselves.
This charming
little dung beetle
makes his living
upon the sands of Egypt.
Here,
billions of tiny particles,
the remnants of ancient seas,
are pushed ever higher
by the relentless winds
of the Sahara.
This is where the dung beetle
makes its living.
The ancient Egyptians...
Look,
last night at the bar,
I just wanted to make sure
it was you.
You know...
peeping in my window.
"Peeping."
You make it sound
so, uh...
Stalker-ish?
Um...
Anyway, I ran out
because he was leaving.
He travels a lot
since he's been back.
Right, n-no, I get it.
You had someplace...
I had to be, yeah.
Are we gonna have
a whole conversation
with me finishing
your sentences?
So, why are you here?
It's not
what it looks like.
I-I thought you were
in trouble -- that you had --
It doesn't matter.
You're okay.
I was okay.
You know,
settled in...content.
But here you are.
What am I supposed to do
with that?
Give me five seconds,
and I'll be gone.
I didn't come here to make
trouble for you.
I-I came because...
You cared?
See that?
I just did it again --
finished your sentence.
Yeah, I care.
I care, too.
I told you
it was an accident.
Yes, of course.
But now there shall be
no more accidents,
no more angel radio.
Stop this, please.
It's been...
...weeks, yes.
We're almost there,
though.
I'm certain of it.
I'm begging you!
When we demons
possess a human,
we invade all of them,
their muscles,
their...bones, their brains.
I can't help but wonder
if it isn't the same for angels.
No.
Vah-teh-kah-rah.
Sal-voch-tay.
Sal-voch-tay!
Mr. Hinckley?
Hi. Uh, we're from the,
uh, Geneva Gazette.
I wanted to ask you a few
questions about your ambush.
Yeah,
well...I'd laugh, too,
if it didn't feel like the sun
just ate my face.
It's a metaphor.
Sorry.
Uh, now,
in the police report,
it said that the, uh --
the bush talked to you, yeah?
Yeah, I know it sounds crazy,
but, yeah.
And what did it say?
No clue.
Sounded like Klingon to me.
Gonna need exact words.
Are you serious?
That's his serious face,
yes.
As much as you can remember,
Mr. Hinckley.
Sounded something like...
"Sol-voch."
Yeah.
"Sol-voch-tay."
Well, what do you think?
Mean anything to you?
Yes. It's Enochian.
It means "obey."
"Obey"? Obey what?
I don't know.
But the amount of pain
an angel must be in
not just to manifest through
shrubbery but to burn --
Dean...We have to find him
before it's too late.
Okay.
Okay, well, look,
a sign like that --
Alfie can't be too far,
right?
So we'll just start at the bush
and work our way out.
And look for what exactly?
Crowley could have him anywhere.
Well, if I know Crowley,
the place will be swarming
with demons,
so we'll just drive
till we see ugly.
It's official --
I hate motels.
Say something.
What would you
like me to say?
"That was great"?
"That was...a mistake"?
I don't know.
Both, I guess.
I understand.
Do you?
Do you understand
I have a life here?
A good man
that loves me --
a man
I don't want to hurt?
I know.
And do you know you're
the first thing I think about
when I wake up
in the morning
and the last thing
before I go to sleep?
It's tough to let
something like that go.
Yeah.
Especially if you keep
showing up here.
Are you saying
you want me to leave?
I'm telling you
that if you stay,
against everything I believe in,
I would be with you.
But if you leave...
Don't come back.
I can't have you with one foot
in my life
and one foot
out there doing...
Whatever it is you do.
That life of yours
I have no idea about.
You don't
want to know about it.
Believe me.
It's a big step.
For me or you?
Both.
I...need to think
about this.
You need to
think about this.
Words will never cover
what you mean to me --
what you'll always mean to me,
but we should...
Think about it.
Okay.
How about two days
from now...
around 7:30?
I'll be off work then.
One of us will be here,
and we'll know.
Neither of us
will be here...
and we'll know.
Or both of us
will be here...
and we'll know.
Wow,
will you look at that?
Our ninth
abandoned factory.
Ain't that America?
Hey, what do you say,
this doesn't pan out,
we head back to that
beer-and-bacon happy hour
about a mile back, huh?
Wait a minute, Dean.
Those derelicts,
they're demons.
I can see
their true faces.
Crowley's got that many
hell monkeys outside,
he's got to have
at least double inside.
And Angel Warding.
I can feel it.
Well, you, me, and a demon knife
ain't gonna cut it.
Okay. I'll get Sam.
No.
We don't need Sam.
But you just said --
Look, if Sam wanted in,
he'd be here, okay?
I got a better idea.
Slow read?
Slowest.
Where's Garth?
Supply run?
I don't know.
Sort of lost track
of when he comes and goes.
You guys need help
with something?
I'm working here.
You look horrible.
Yeah. Thanks.
He's right.
Are you okay, Kevin?
Fine.
I'm just...
in the middle of this.
And? Any luck?
Interpreting
half a Demon tablet?
No.
I got nothing.
All right,
well, buck up,
'cause, uh, we need some more
of that demon TNT ASAP.
You used it all?
Yeah, so let's whip up
another batch.
Sure.
West Bank witch hazel,
skull of Egyptian calf,
the tail of
some random-ass newt
that may or may not
be extinct --
All right, all right,
I get it --
ingredients are hard
to come by, huh?
That's just
the first three ingredients.
Give me the list.
I'll get what we need.
Well...
What on earth could you possibly
need now, Viggo?
I've given you every torture
instrument known to man --
short of
a Neil Diamond album.
I've found something, sir.
I need a translator.
You're looking at him.
Show me.
Zoh-bah-leh-ta.
What have we here?
I think it's Enochian.
Of course it's Enochian,
you pigeon.
The question is,
why is he speaking Enochian?
What have you drilled into here,
Viggo, huh?
Zoh-bah-leh-ta.
Sah-teh-voch-leh.
Bollocks.
What is it, sir?
Well, what our feathered friend
was uttering essentially was,
"You, celestial being,
have been created to be an angel
of the Lord."
You've got
into his operating system --
his factory settings.
From who? God?
Who the hell cares
where it comes from?
Let's find out what makes
this flying monkey tick.
Sah-teh-voch-leh.
I mean, come on.
How long's it take to get
a calf skull from Egypt?
Kevin.
Your mom's hot.
I'm serious,
your mom is one sexy --
Hey, I thought I told you
to go underground.
Hey.
I am so far underground,
I'm breathing
through a straw, brother.
Uh, look...
What happened with your friend
Martin back there,
it wasn't supposed
to go down that way.
I know.
Your granddaughter told me.
Dean, you did this old dog
a real solid,
and, uh...the way
you stood up for me --
Well, shoe on the other foot,
you would have done the same.
Yeah.
I hate to ask for much else,
but I don't suppose
there's any chance
you're anywhere near
the Catskills?
Working a case on the other side
of the country.
Why? What's up?
Yeah, just hitting a little
rough patch, I guess.
You know,
doing this whole solo thing.
Benny...
One day at a time, man.
You know what?
Uh...A cup of coffee
sure would do me good.
All right, as soon as I'm done
with this case,
I'll, uh...
I'll be there, okay?
Yeah.
All right, brother.
Thank you.
Hey.
Where is your mom?
Somewhere safe.
You kicked your mom
to the curb?
She was too distracting.
I couldn't focus.
The angels said
I had to go to the desert
to learn the word of God,
all right?
So...This is my desert.
Yeah,
but your mom's your mom.
I can't enjoy a world
I need to save, Dean.
I can enjoy it
when this is all over with.
For right now...
There's nothing more important
than this.
Watching humanity --
it never gets old, does it?
I got what we need.
Oh, it's about time.
What's he doing here?
Don't worry, Dean.
Once we save Alfie,
I'm out.
Oh, once "we" save Alfie.
Don't hurt yourself, Sam.
Cass and I can handle it.
Not according to Cass.
I told you
we didn't need him.
We need everything,
Dean.
And I need both of you,
as you say, to stow your crap.
Can you do that?
So, there are four
main points of warding --
north, south, east,
and west --
and four Enochian symbols,
like this,
that you need to destroy
before I can enter.
Okay, so, what?
We go in,
take care of the hell mooks,
and you extract
the angel?
Yes.
After killing so many,
I need to save
at least this one.
Sounds like a plan.
Okay. Let's do this.
Wait. Here.
This doesn't just work
on angels.
It kills demons, too.
Thanks, Cass.
Aah!
Well, not my most
original work, but...
Voh-meh-pah-rah-less.
What is it?
That was tablet talk.
Protecting the Word of God
seems to be hardwired
into these dingbats.
Thanks.
Come on.
Zod-leh-fah.
"Demon tablet."
Tell me one I don't know, huh?
Alfie.
M-m-Mr. Crowley,
not that this isn't important,
but perhaps we should be making
preparations to leave.
We -- we seem to be
under attack.
Did you say something?
All right,
anytime now, Cass.
Cass! Hey!
You okay?
It must be the sigils.
I'm not at full power.
Sam,
help me muss this crud.
No, wait!
There's no time.
Samandriel won't last
much longer.
Cass.
Here, take this.
Dean, hurry up.
Come on!
All right.
Plan "B."
We have a plan "B"?
As you were saying?
Bah-nah-sah-ee.
Cass? Anytime now.
Yes?
Ar-doh-zah-feh.
Spit it out,
you heavenly pile of filth!
Pah-deh-rah.
Holy mother of sin.
What? What is it?
There's an Angel tablet.
Hold still.
Wait!
I know -- I know things.
Cass! Go!
Good, good.
There's so much you don't know.
You need me.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think so.
It's okay.
You're safe now.
I'm taking you home.
No. You can't take me
back there, Castiel.
Why not?
You don't understand.
I told Crowley...
Things --
things
he shouldn't have known.
He got to our coding,
our secrets --
secrets I didn't even know
we had!
What secrets?
Heaven, Naomi.
No. W-who's Naomi?
Who is --
listen to me.
Listen to me closely.
I've been there.
I know!
They're controlling us,
Castiel!
What do you mean?
Kill him!
What does he mean,
"they're controlling us"?
Castiel!
Who is controlling us?
Why did I see your face?
Why was I so afraid?
What did you do to me?
This is a direct order!
Kill him!
What did I just do?
You killed a traitor.
Samandriel...was good.
And I was trying
to atone for --
Samandriel was broken.
He revealed the existence of
what I would die to protect --
what any of us
would die to protect.
The Angel tablet,
Castiel.
Crowley knows.
I just murdered one of our own
to protect a tablet?
If the Demon tablet
can seal demons in hell,
what do you think the Angel
tablet could do to us?
You're a hero, Castiel.
You've done Heaven
a great service.
And that's what I tell
Sam and Dean?
Cass!
What the hell happened?
You tell the Winchesters
that Samandriel
had been compromised.
He was compromised.
He came at you,
and you acted in self-defense.
He came at me.
I killed him
in self-defense.
Say you must return
his body to Heaven,
and then bring him to me.
Cass, you okay?
My vessel must have been damaged
in the melee.
I have to go.
Samandriel's remains
belong in Heaven.
I need to see just how far
Crowley dug into him.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Cass, wait.
Thank you both...
For everything
you've done.
Cass!
Okay.
That should do it.
Cass can't see or hear us now.
Okay, what the hell?
I know.
I told you something was off with him
since he got back from Purgatory.
So, what, you think someone's
messing with him or something?
Who?
Angels?
Why would the angels have him
kill another angel?
You know what, man?
I got this.
You go.
What?
Don't you have a girl
to get back to?
Yeah. I guess I do.
Um...
Since when are you
on the Amelia bandwagon?
I don't know.
I'm just tired
of all the fighting.
And, you know, maybe
I'm a...little bit jealous.
I could never separate myself
from the job like you could.
Hell, maybe it's time for at least one
of us to be happy.
What, you being
such a big hugger and all?
She does make me happy,
and she could be waiting for me
if I went back.
I'd be a...very lucky man
if she was.
But now...
with everything
staring down at us,
with all that's left
to be done...
I don't know.
Huh.
Yeah.
Well, I do know this --
whatever you decide...decide.
Both feet in
or both feet out.
Anything in between
is what gets you dead.
Yeah,
I keep hearing that.
I'm gonna...take a walk.
Clear my head.
Dean.
Thank you mightily, bud.
I'm in a hard way here.
How close are you?
I'm sorry, man.
I, um...I'm not gonna make it.
You mean now, or...?
Listen, Benny.
Everything you've done for me
I will never forget,
but, uh...
This is it.
End of the line?
End of the line.
Yeah, well, I never liked
these cellphones anyway.
You, uh...
You stay good,
all right?
You too, Dean.
And, uh...
Thanks for the ride.
Yeah, man.
Adios.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==