You have no one at all,
right?
My husband. He died
in Afghanistan eight months ago.
Cass.
Hello, Dean.
Getting me out of Purgatory
wasn't your responsibility.
I pulled away.
I needed to do penance.
For the things I did
on earth and in heaven.
How...the hell
did you make it out?
My name is Naomi.
We rescued you.
Consider these chats
your repayment.
You will report in
to me regularly,
and you will never remember
having done so.
Gary?
Olivia.
After last time, I-I didn't
think that you would come.
I wasn't going to,
but...
I'm glad you did.
So am I.
Do you hear that?
What?
The thumping noise?
Is -- is that you?
You can hear that?
Gary!
Ohh!
Gary, what is it?!
What --
Ohh!
Gary! Gary!
? Supernatural 8x08 ?
Hunteri Heroici
Original Air Date on November 28, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Right, yeah.
No, just, uh -- just call us
whenever you find something.
Yeah.
Yeah, course.
Right. No, I-I, uh...
Yeah, hey, you know what?
Uh, Dean's here.
He really wants to talk
to you.
Ms. Tran,
yeah, hi, uh...
Tunnel.
What's going on
in Tran-land?
Well, uh, Garth finally got them
to his houseboat,
but Kevin's having
a lot of trouble
reading their half
of the tablet.
So far, bits and pieces.
Nothing about boarding up hell.
Garth has a safe-houseboat?
Dude, I don't even
ask questions anymore.
What's the word, Cass?
It's a shortened version
of my name.
Yes, it is.
I meant what's the word
on the Word?
Any, uh, tablet chatter
on angel radio?
Oh, I couldn't say.
I turned that off.
You can do that?
Yeah, it's a simple matter
of blocking out
certain subsonic frequencies.
I could draw you a diagram
if you want.
No, that's -- we're good.
Why'd you flip the switch?
Because it's a direct link
to heaven.
And I don't want anything to do
with that place --
not anymore.
So what now?
Move to Vermont,
open up a charming B&B?
No.
I still want --
I still need to help people.
So...I'm gonna become
a hunter.
Really?
Yeah. I could be
your third wheel.
You know
that's not a good thing, right?
Of course it is. A third wheel
adds extra grip, greater stability.
I even found a case.
Oklahoma City -- a man's heart
jumped 10 feet out of his chest.
It sounds like
our kind of thing, right?
He's got a point.
Excellent.
I'll see you there.
Wait, Cass, Cass.
If you want to play cowboys
and bloodsuckers, that's fine.
But you're gonna stick with us,
okay?
None of this zapping around
crap. Capiche?
Yeah, I capiche.
All right, then.
Can I, uh, at least ride
in the front seat?
No. No.
Coroner said his heart
was ejected from his body.
Got some air, too.
Found it in a sandbox.
Any idea what happened,
Detective?
A lot of people are thinking
drugs, Agent Nash --
an assload of drugs.
There are no narcotics
in that man's system.
His molecules
are all wrong.
But you don't think that,
huh?
Never seen an eightball
do that.
Wow.
And who called this in?
Friend of his named
Olivia Kopple.
She saw the whole thing.
Oh.
Ah, crap.
I have -- I have to take this.
Here's everything we got.
Knock yourself out.
- Thanks.
- Listen, you see anything weird,
anything out of the box,
you just call me.
Whatever you say, Scully.
Detective Glass.
On my way.
I can't sense
any EMF or sulfur.
Mr. Frieling's arterial health
is, uh, excellent.
Mm.
He did recently suffer
from a...
...mild, uh...
What is that?
...bladder infection.
Cass, stop smelling
the dead guy.
Why? Now I know everything
about this man. So we can --
Do you know
he was having an affair?
What?
Strike one, Sherlock.
According to Olivia,
they would meet at the park
every Thursday at 12:45,
walk to the Moonlight diner,
where she always ordered
a caesar salad,
dressing on the side.
They would chat
about everything,
and she'd be back on the road
by 1:30.
You don't think
she's telling the truth.
Too much detail.
Sounds rehearsed.
Plus, we drove past
the Moonlight diner
on the way into town.
It's attached
to the Moonlight motel.
Okay, well, let's say that, uh,
Gary here's on the prowl,
but he's playing it safe
because...
...dude's married.
Doesn't want anyone
to see his ride
parked out in front
of a by-the-hour fleabag.
So he stashes his car
at the park across the street,
meets Olivia there.
His wife
probably found out about it,
and it broke her heart.
So she breaks his.
Sounds witchy.
Yes, it does.
Guy was living a lie,
and it came back
to bite him in the ticker.
But nice job
on the bladder infection.
He said
he'd be here by 5:00.
Uh, just deep breath.
It's gonna be okay.
I know.
It's just this house,
you --
he's gonna think
we're moving too fast.
Are we moving too fast?
We're making up
for lost time.
Don't talk politics.
Don't say anything bad
about the Cowboys.
And whatever you do,
don't --
do not use the words "moist"
or "irregardless."
There goes my opener.
Hi, Dad!
Ohh, munchkin!
Okay, embarrassing.
That is my job, kiddo.
So, who's this handsome fella?
Yeah, he's a good boy!
How you doing there?
You're beautiful.
That good boy belongs
to this good boy.
Stan Thompson,
this is Sam Winchester.
Hi.
I heard a lot about you.
Not all bad, I hope.
So, this is a nice place.
Lawn could use a mow.
Sam found it.
I've been so busy lately.
He's had to move us in
by himself, pretty much.
Huh.
Job almost well done.
Do you want a drink, Dad?
We have beer, iced tea --
Anything cold will be fantastic.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Okay.
Mr. Thompson, um, I just --
I know this must be weird.
Uh, you haven't seen Amelia
in months,
and now she's living with a guy
you've never met.
Ame said
you went to Stanford.
I did.
It's a good school.
It is.
So what do you do now?
I work at a motel
in town.
Ah. Balancing the books?
Uh, no.
Maintenance mostly.
Ah.
Well, that makes sense.
'Cause I got to say, Sam,
you look like
a real fixer-upper to me.
I-I don't understand.
Gary had a heart attack.
Why would the FBI --
The parks
are government property.
We just got a few questions
for you.
I'll, uh...
I'll handle this.
I've done research.
I can crack her.
Now, Ms. Frieling,
I don't want to bother you.
I-I really don't.
But I-I do have
just one question for you.
Why did you kill
your husband?!
Agent Stills.
A word, please.
What?
I was being bad cop.
No, you were being
bad everything.
Please,
forgive my partner.
He's, uh -- he's going
through some stuff.
Listen to Sam.
What he was trying to ask --
is -- is there any way
Gary might have had secrets --
something he was hiding?
Hiding? Like what?
Deb?
Olivia.
Hey.
Are you okay?
As in mistress Olivia?
This is awkward.
I'm sorry. W-what did you think
Gary was hiding?
That he was sleeping
with her.
I know.
You know?
Gary and I -- we...
had an arrangement.
He was seeing Olivia,
and I was spending some time
with our neighbor P.J.
I'll, uh -- I'll put this in the kitchen.
I'll help.
Yeah.
Okay.
Frigging suburbs, man.
So she's not a witch.
Just the best wife ever.
Then what killed her husband?
Who gives a...
It's a miracle!
God wants me to live!
Looks like suicide.
It was.
Guy left a note.
He invested everything
in Roman Industries
and lost it all when they
crashed and burned last year.
So why call us?
Because I have two witnesses
who swear
that Madoff here floated
in midair for a good 10 seconds,
then he looked down,
and splat.
Not sure I buy that,
but the way they're talking,
it sounds like something
straight out of a --
Cartoon.
Hey, Detective.
You said you wanted weird.
Thanks.
Yeah, what do you got?
She's right, you know.
I mean, the whole heart jumping
out of the guy's chest,
the -- the --
the delayed fall --
that's
straight-up Bugs Bunny.
So we're looking for some sort
of insect-rabbit hybrid?
How do we kill it?
No, we don't, Cass.
That's a character,
like, uh --
like Woody Woodpecker
or Daffy Duck.
They're
little animated movies.
You know, uh, the coyote chases
a roadrunner,
and then the -- the anvil
gets dropped on his head.
Is it
supposed to be funny?
No.
It's hilarious.
Stay tuned, kids!
We'll be right back!
I understand.
The bird represents God.
And coyote is man,
endlessly chasing the divine,
yet never able to catch him.
It's...
It's hilarious.
I got no idea
what we're hunting.
Maybe it's a Tulpa.
Maybe it's some --
some crazy God
who watched too much
"Robot Chicken."
I-I -- I mean,
is there a link
between "Heartbreak Hotel"
and "Free Fallin'"?
Not that I can find.
All right, well,
I'm gonna call it.
Cass, you gonna book a room
or what?
No, I'll stay here.
Oh, okay. Yeah.
We'll have a slumber party
and braid Sam's hair.
- Where are you gonna sleep?
- I don't sleep.
Okay, well, I need
my four hours, so...
I'll watch over you.
That's not gonna happen.
Something's coming across
the police band.
Wait, you can hear that?
It's all waves.
A bank has been robbed.
It sounds loony.
Define "loony."
That's loony, all right.
Agents. I was just about
to give you a ring.
Got to ask --
do you boys chase the crazy,
or does the crazy chase you?
Depends on the day.
Who's the pancake?
Security guard.
He called in
reporting a robbery,
but by the time we got here --
A robbery?
Looks like the black hole
was trying to jimmy open
a safe-deposit box
when Mr. Rent-A-Cop
found him.
And, well,
you know how that story ends.
Black hole?
It's our name for a burglar
that's been running us ragged.
He's a pro --
no fingerprints,
never any sign
of forced entry --
just a pair of those every time,
like he's signing his work.
Perp's never done anything like
this before, though...obviously.
You mind if I take a look
at your files
on those other break-ins?
No skin off my nose.
I'm headed to the station now
if you want a ride.
Perfect.
Hey.
Can you lift this?
"X" marks the spot.
Well, whoever's doing this is
playing by cartoon rules.
- Animation doesn't have rules.
- Sure it does.
In Toontown, a pretty girl
can make your heart
leap out of your chest,
anvils fall from the sky,
and if you draw a door
or a black hole on the wall,
you can stroll
right through it.
So this is
how the thief got in.
And out.
And cracked the vault.
Then why isn't it working
now?
I got no clue.
Your father...
Beautiful handwriting.
How you feeling, Cass?
I'm fine.
Well, I just --
I-I know that when...
I got puked
out of Purgatory,
it took me a few weeks to...
Find my sea legs.
I'm fine.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm happy you're back.
I'm freaking thrilled.
It's just this whole
mysterious-resurrection thing --
it always has
one mother of a downside.
So, what do you want me
to do?
Maybe take a trip
upstairs.
To heaven?
Yeah, poke around,
see if the God squad
can't tell us how you got out.
No.
Look, man, I-I hate
those flying-ass monkeys
just as much as you do,
but --
Dean! I said no!
Talk to me.
Dean, I...
When I was...bad...and I had
all those things --
the...the leviathans...
writhing inside me...
I caused a lot of suffering
on Earth,
but I devastated heaven.
I vaporized
thousands of my own kind,
and I-I-I can't go back.
'Cause if you do,
the angels will kill you.
Because if I see what heaven's
become -- what I...
...what I made of it...
I'm afraid I might kill myself.
Hey.
Got something.
Good.
Excellent. What?
So this black-hole guy --
before he tried the bank,
he robbed a house
across from the park
where Gary blew a gasket.
So, uh, you think
the house heist
and Gary's corpse
are connected?
According to the file,
they happened at pretty
much the exact same time.
Here.
Check this out. Okay.
Here's the house, and Gary died
across the street here.
And that building from
this morning -- right there.
The black hole hit that, too.
Let me guess --
where, uh, what's his name
took a swan dive.
All right. I'll bite.
What about the others?
Well, those are the places
that stuff got stolen.
But nobody got dead.
Take away the graffiti,
and these all look like
just normal smash-and-grabs.
But I made a few phone calls,
talked to some people
who are nearby --
neighbors and whatnot --
and they reported
a whole lot of crazy.
Like?
Like a jogger
bumping his head
and sprouting a four-inch lump
or a kid walking into a wall
and hearing birdies.
Basically, for 50 yards
around each robbery,
people were living
in a cartoon.
But it didn't last long --
I mean, 5, 10 minutes
at each place.
About the length of time
it would take a thief
to get in and out.
Exactly.
But whatever power he's using,
it's -- it's not targeted.
I mean, it's -- it's
kind of like an area of effect.
I mean, picture him
in a bubble of weird,
and anything that touches it
gets daffy.
So this animaniac
can step through walls,
can toss an anvil?
Yeah, but he's warping reality
to do it.
So if someone
happens to be nearby
meeting the girl
of his dreams...
His heart
makes a break for it.
Okay, so smashing the, uh --
the rent-a-cop --
that -- that was on purpose,
but the rest of them --
what, is that just collateral weird?
Maybe.
So we're looking
for a thief.
And the deposit box he was
after.
Now, the house, the office --
every place he's hit
belonged to someone
living at the Sunset Fields
retirement home.
So you think
our guy's there.
Worth a shot.
All right. Well, let's gear up.
It's wabbit season.
I don't think
you pronounced that correctly.
Come on. It's not that bad.
You can't tell me this joint
doesn't give you the heebs
and/or jeebs.
Hello. Can I help you?
Hi.
Yeah.
Agent Crosby. FBI.
Sorry,
I'm Dr. Dwight Mahoney.
I run Sunset Fields.
We need to question
your residents.
Well...why?
About what?
Grand larceny,
mostly.
Of course.
Um, by all means, ask away.
If there's anything I can do
to help, let me know.
Appreciate it.
Great.
All right, let's do this.
No flirting, you two.
You are so pretty,
Charles.
That's not my name.
Oh! You look
so much like my third husband.
We're here to talk
about the robbery, ma'am.
Robbery?
Mm-hmm.
The one the police talked to you
about a few days ago.
Someone broke
into your old house
and stole
a stack of bearer bonds
and, uh, some jewelry
that you stashed
under your floorboards.
Oh, my diamonds, yes.
I hid them there.
I'm sorry, Charles.
I didn't trust you.
You were quite
the bounder.
Did you tell anyone where
your valuables were, Mrs. Tate?
I don't think so.
But then I get a little fuzzy
sometimes.
Have you noticed
anything strange lately --
uh, cold spots, smells?
Well, there's the cat.
The cat?
He talks sometimes.
Really hates that mouse.
I'll interrogate the cat.
You all done here?
All right.
It's creepy, right?
A lot of these people --
they just tune out
and live in their own heads.
It's like maybe the real world
is too much for them,
and they just run and hide,
you know?
Hmm.
Soup's on...
and semi-edible.
You remembered.
Dad was in the army, so we moved
around a lot when I was a kid.
Having spaghetti and hot dogs
our first night in a new house
was sort of a tradition.
All right. Got it.
Uh, my father was
in the Marines.
Jarhead, huh?
That's right. Uh, 2nd battalion,
First Marines, Echo company.
I always thought they were
a little puffed up, myself.
But, hey.
What do I know?
I'm just an old grunt.
You're my old grunt.
So, Ame tells me
you never served.
No.
See, I find that
hard to believe
'cause I got to say, Sam,
you got the look.
The look?
The one a lot of guys get after
they've been through the meat grinder --
the one that let's you know
they've seen
a lot of crap
they can't forget.
The second
their feet hit solid ground,
they start running,
and they don't stop --
not till they find something
to hold on to.
You think
that's what I'm doing here?
Just holding on?
I think the two of you are
holding on to each other, yeah.
'Cause I know she's scared.
After what happened to Don, I
don't blame her for taking off.
Needing to run away and hide --
I know why she did it.
The question is --
what are you running from, Sam?
Hey, what do you got?
Hey, um, nothing.
Uh, no hex bags, no EMF. You?
Nada.
Half the folks I talked to don't
even remember being robbed.
Dean, um...
You remember a guy
named Fred Jones?
I think he was
a contact of dad's,
lived outside of Salt Lake.
Yeah, that guy gave me
my first beer.
I don't even think
I was double digits.
Right, yeah. Me, too.
Um, he was psychic, right?
Psychokinetic. Why?
'Cause he's in room 114.
Cass. Let's go.
I've almost cracked him.
Now.
Hey.
I'm not through with you.
Dumbass.
Mr. Jones?
Hey, it's, uh,
Sam Winchester.
Fred?
My nerves!
Get me a doctor!
Fred! Hey!
So,
you really think this one man
is causing all of these...
Shenanigans?
Well, if he is,
he'd be surrounded
by a circle of crazy, right?
Hang on.
Bingo.
But how?
Fred's got juice.
I mean, an average psychokinetic
can move things with his mind,
but a guy like Fred --
you get him worked up,
he can reshape reality.
All right, so where's his "off" switch?
I don't know.
I'm not even certain
if he knows we're here.
Do we...kill him?
Excuse me, Agents.
Did he just threaten to murder
one of my patients?
Real freaking smooth.
Well, we don't have to
leave him.
I could teleport him.
Fred's radioactive,
Cass.
Zap him -- no telling
what will happen.
Me and Sam
will circle back tonight,
get Fred nice and clean.
You go invisible girl and keep
an eye on him. You hear me?
Good.
Happy Birthday, Sheila.
Ha. Good.
Get ready. Big breath.
Oh, ready.
I'm just gonna wipe this off
your face, okay?
I'm just gonna
put this on.
Oh.
You got my message. Good.
What the hell happened?
There was
a pastry mishap.
Okay, and?
And the frosting reached
near-supersonic speeds.
I thought --
Hey. Fred's gone.
Hey.
What?
Oh, fan-freaking-tastic.
Way to take your eye
off the ball.
You're
not supposed to be here.
Well, trust me, sweetheart,
you got bigger fish.
Charles,
she's wearing my diamonds.
Wait.
What? What's wrong?
This is
Mrs. Tate's bracelet.
Where did you get it?
Answer the question.
My boyfriend
gave it to me.
Hey. Bearer bonds.
Maybe these belonged
to Sheila Tate.
So this man is our thief.
Yeah. Dean.
Cass.
Stay still.
Move your hands.
How did you...
Guy eats his Wheaties.
Sam, come on. What did you...
Get up.
Come on. Sit down.
Wait a second!
What did you just do to me?!
Hey, hey, hey! Listen to me.
Where is Fred Jones?
I -- he -- he took him.
Who?!
Dr. Mahoney.
That guy's evil, man, okay?
- He's using Mr. Jones.
- How?
Look, all Fred does is watch
cartoons, but he is magic, okay?
A few weeks ago,
I-I slammed my foot in his door.
I smashed it flat --
and I mean flat.
And then when I shook the thing,
it popped back up,
like something out of a cartoon
or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we know.
So I told Dr. Mahoney, and then
he started doing experiments.
Just -- we just wanted to see
what he could do.
What about the robberies?
Oh, Mahoney's been skimming off
Sunset Fields for years.
A lot of those folks --
they got stuff stashed away,
like, off the books.
So Mahoney would track down
the loot,
and then we would take Fred
for a drive.
Right, and use his bubble
of weird to rip people off.
How did you end up
gut-shot?
Mahoney -- after --
after he anviled that guard,
he started freaking out,
and then you showed up,
and then the cake blew in
the day room, and then he lost it.
What does that mean,
"he lost it"?
I mean he's on his way
back to the bank right now
for one last score.
Doc's blowing town.
I mean, he said
that Fred was a loose end.
He was gonna kill him.
And then I like Fred,
so I said that if he hurt
the guy, I'd go to the cops.
And I didn't know
that he had a gun.
Okay.
Do you think Mr. Jones knows
what's happening?
I don't know.
Seems to me like the dude's
living in a dream world.
Look, I am trying to help.
Boy, I'll tell you,
if don could see you...
Don't. Just don't.
You can't --
you need to come home.
Is that why you're here --
to drag me back?
This is my life.
This -- it won't last.
You are living
in a dream world.
I like it here.
I like this house.
I like Sam.
Sam is a mess.
I'm a mess.
But when I'm with Sam,
I'm happy, Dad.
And I haven't been happy
in a really long time.
So please, just...
let us be messes together.
Give us a chance.
I'll dry.
Is that your car outside --
the Impala?
Yeah, it was my dad's.
Guy had good taste...
...for a jarhead.
All right.
Jones has got to be close.
I'll hit the bank.
You see if you can find him.
Awesome.
Can you feel that, Sam?
The power.
Calamity Jane for you!
Fred, hey.
Fred, hey, buddy.
Hey. Hey, Fred?
Listen to me.
Can you hear me?
Fred!
If we could just talk
to him.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, wake up.
Wake up.
Cass?
Wait. Wait!
Aha!
Cass, uh,
where are we?
Inside
Mr. Jones' mind.
You said
you wanted to talk to him.
Who the hell are you?
Fred. Fred. Um, hey, it's --
it's -- it's me.
I'm, uh -- I'm Sam --
Sam Winchester.
John's boy?
That's right.
The scrawny one?
It's only been three,
four years since I've seen you.
You --
more like, uh, 20.
Uh, listen, Fred,
I'm gonna need you to focus.
How did you...
Why are you here, Sam?
What's up, Doc?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You're lying!
This is happening, Mr. Jones.
They're using you.
As what -- some kind
of a damn psychic coppertop?
You plug me in, and the whole
world goes wacky?
It doesn't work that way.
How would you know?
No offense,
but it seems to me
like you've been spending
more time in here
than you have...
Out there.
You want to know what's
the worst thing that can happen
to a guy who's got a mind
like I got?
Losing it.
You let me walk,
and half of this is yours.
I think I'm gonna pass.
I'm not really into stealing
from sweet old ladies.
I'm not stealing
from them.
I'm stealing
from their children.
Little bastards think they can
drop their folks off at a home
and visit twice a year,
maybe.
I took care
of all these old geezers.
I think I deserve--
I don't care!
Fine.
Have it your way.
Welcome to the fun house.
Cartoons -- yeah, yeah, I always
loved them when I was a kid.
They made me feel...
Happy -- safe.
They were...
Something
to hold on to.
Yeah.
Give up?
I've been dealing
with this crazy for months!
And you -- idiot --
bring a gun to a gag fight.
Yeah, well,
I did bring this.
And "X" marks the spot.
I need you to stop this --
take control.
It's too hard!
Look, it can be nice living
in a dream world.
It can be great.
I know that.
And you can hide,
and you can pretend all the crap
out there doesn't exist,
but you can't do it forever
because...eventually,
whatever it is you're running
from -- it'll find you.
It'll come along, and it'll
punch you in the gut.
And then...
Then you got to wake up,
because if you don't,
then trying to keep that dream
alive will destroy you!
It'll destroy everything!
Looks like somebody turned off
the boob tube.
- Good.
- Means I can use this.
No! You are never
going to hurt anyone again!
That's all, folks.
My God.
Fred. You good?
Now I'm good.
In a month, year...
Nobody gets sharper
with age.
I'm gonna lose control
again,
and somebody's gonna
get hurt...again.
You got to make it stop.
There might be a way.
The procedure will be painful,
and...when it's over,
I'm not sure how much of you
will be left.
Well,
what are you waiting for?
Is he, uh --
is he okay?
He's listening
to "Ode to Joy."
He's happy.
All right, well,
let's blow this termite terrace.
Cass, you get to ride shotgun.
You done good.
Thanks, but I, uh...
I can't come. I, uh...
Hello, Castiel.
And, no.
No?
I can see what you're thinking,
and I won't allow it.
You don't understand.
I have been trying
to pretend
that I can escape what I did
in heaven, but I can't.
All that pain
that I caused --
I-I have to come back,
to make things right.
And you are...
by doing what you're told.
Bottom line --
unless I ring my bell,
you stay out of heaven,
Castiel.
Well, then,
what should I do?
What do
you want to do?
You -- you what, Cass?
W-why can't you come with us?
I, um...
I want to stay
with Mr. Jones.
Someone should watch over him
for a few days just to be safe.
Okay, and then what?
Then I'm not sure.
But I know
I can't run anymore.
So, Ame is playing
the Sugarplum fairy, right?
Right?
Now, this is her big moment,
you understand,
and she waddles up onto the stage --
Waddles?
What? You were a chubby kid.
It was adorable.
Anyway, she waddles up
onto the stage,
and she is dragging two feet
of toilet paper behind her.
No.
You remember that?
Yeah.
Officially the end
of her career.
You want one of these?
Please, yeah.
Thanks.
My, uh --
my brother used to do that.
Yeah?
Yeah.
He a good guy?
Yeah, uh, he --
he was...the best.
Uh, I, uh...
I lost him, and, uh, I-I ran.
I'm sorry
to hear about that.
What?
A-are you sure?
Oh, God.
Amelia?
Baby? You okay?
It's Don.
He's alive.
Sam, you with me?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==