I think dad wants us
to pick up where he left off.
Saving people,
hunting things...
the family business.
There are things much older
than souls in purgatory.
? In the shuffling madness ?
Leviathan!
? Of the locomotive breath ?
Dick is coming.
? Runs the all-time loser ?
A shark's got to eat.
? Headlong to his death ?
Bobby!
? He picks up Gideon's Bible ?
? open at page one ?
When it's your time...
? Thank God ?
...go.
? And the train,
it won't stop going ?
? no way to slow down ?
What the hell are you?
He's a Prophet
of the Lord.
And that's the word of God?
Yes.
It's about Leviathan.
Does it say anything
about how to kill them?
When we freaks die,
where do we go?
It's like the backside
of your worst nightmares.
It's all blood and bone
and darkness.
Purgatory.
Cut off the head,
and the body will flounder.
Prophet's mine.
You are well and truly
on your own.
We're in Purgatory?
Cass, I think
we better g--
Cass?
Will, get up.
Something just happened.
Go.
Go do something.
W-what am I
supposed to...
Hello?
It was a deer.
I don't know. It was like --
it was a deer or some--
Oh!
Where am I?
What?
W-- hey, hey.
Where's the road?
12 miles that way.
[ Styx's "Man in the Wilderness"
plays ]
? Another year
has passed me by ?
? still I look at myself
and cry ?
? what kind of man
have I become? ?
? all of the years I've spent
in search of myself ?
? and I'm still in the dark ?
? 'cause I can't seem
to find the light alone ?
? sometimes I feel ?
? like a man
in the wilderness ?
? I'm a lonely soldier
off to war ?
? sent away to die ?
? never quite knowing why ?
? sometimes it makes
no sense at all ?
? it makes no sense at all ?
This better be you,
you son of a bitch.
Hold on, you bastard.
Hold on!
Anima corpori...
fuerit corpus...
totem resurgent.
Wow.
Wow. That was fast.
No thanks to you.
The hell took you
so long?
You're welcome.
Everything working?
Good enough.
So...
What now?
Like we talked about,
I guess.
Then this is goodbye.
Keep your nose clean, Benny.
You hear me?
We made it, brother.
I can't believe it.
You and me both.
? Supernatural 8x01 ?
We Need to Talk About Kevin
Original Air Date on October 3, 2012
== sync by elderman ==
Oh!
Dean?!
What the --
I'm not a demon.
Or a Leviathan. What --
Or a shifter.
Good.
My turn.
Come on. Let's go.
I don't need to.
I know it's you.
Damn it, Sammy!
Come on!
No!
Dean,
can I just say hello?
All right.
Well...
...let's do this.
I don't know whether to give you
a hug or take a shower.
Come here.
Dude...
You're...freakin' alive.
I mean,
what the hell happened?
Well, I guess standing too close
to exploding Dick
sends your ass
straight to Purgatory.
You were in Purgatory?
For the whole year?
Yeah, time flies when
you're running for your life.
Well,
how'd you get out?
I guess
whoever built that box
didn't want me in there
any more than I did.
What does that mean?
I'm here, okay?
What about Cass?
Was he there?
Yeah,
Cass didn't make it.
What exactly
does that mean?
Something happened to him
down there.
Things got pretty hairy
towards the end,
and he...just let go.
So Cass is dead?
You saw him die?
I saw enough.
So, then what,
you're not sure?
I said
I saw enough, Sam.
Right.
Dean, I'm sorry.
Me too.
So you -- I can't believe
you're actually here.
You know that half your numbers
are out of service?
Felt like I was
leaving messages in the wind.
Yeah, I-I-I didn't
get your messages.
How come?
Probably because
I ditched the phones.
Because...?
I guess, um...
I guess something happened
to me this year, too.
I don't hunt anymore.
Yeah.
And Sasha Grey's
gone legit.
What?
Nothing.
Um, she did
a Soderbergh movie.
What?
She did a Soderbergh --
No. You, Sam.
You quit?
Yeah. Yeah, I --
you were gone...Dean.
Cass was gone,
Bobby was dead.
I mean,
Crowley even shipped off
Kevin and Meg
to parts unknown.
So you turned tail
on the family business.
Nothing says "family" quite like
the whole family being dead.
I wasn't dead.
In fact, I was knee-deep
in God's armpit
killing monsters,
which, I thought,
is what we actually do.
Yes, Dean.
And far as I knew,
what we do is the thing
that got every single member
of my family killed.
I had no one --
no one.
And for the first time in
my life, I was completely alone.
And, honestly, I didn't
exactly have a roadmap.
So, yeah, I fixed up the Impala,
and I just...drove.
After you looked for me.
Did you look for me,
Sam?
Good. That's good.
Now, we -- we...always
told each other
not to look for
each other.
That's smart.
Good for you.
Of course,
we always ignored that
because of our deep, abiding
love for each another,
but not this time,
right, Sammy?
Look, I'm still the same guy,
Dean.
Well, bully for you.
I'm not.
Welcome back.
You want some dinner?
Pass.
Okay.
What?
Sam Winchester,
it's Kevin Tran.
Crowley had me
in this warehouse,
and I just escaped.
I don't know where I am.
And I don't know
if he or -- or any other demons
are still after me.
I need your help.
Call me back.
It's Kevin Tran.
When was that?
Sam Winchester.
It's Kevin Tran.
I called you a week ago.
Call me, please.
I don't know what the hell
I'm doing out here, man.
Okay.
I get it.
So, what,
you want to...
strategize or something?
Sam, it's Kevin.
I'm good.
Whoo! I'm so good.
Is he...drunk?
3 months
since you ditched my ass.
Haven't slept for more than
four hours a night.
It's all good
in the hood.
Uh, if you're still alive,
eat me.
Eat me.
Sam, it's been 6 months.
I can only assume
you're dead.
If not,
don't try and reach me.
You won't be able to.
I won't be calling this number
anymore.
He was
our responsibility.
And you couldn't answer
the damn phone.
All right,
listen to this --
Kevin's last message.
Listen
to the background.
If not,
don't try and reach me.
You won't be able to.
I won't be calling this number
anymore.
Hear that?
What is it?
I think
he was on a bus.
Listen again.
If not,
don't try and reach me.
Last stop -- Centreville.
...won't be calling
this number --
Centreville?
Centreville, where?
Michigan.
And why would Kevin be
in Centreville, Michigan?
Because...
his high-school girlfriend
goes to college there.
That's thin.
It's the best lead
we got.
"We"?
You were right.
He was
our responsibility.
So...let's find him,
okay?
Hey.
Well...
No visible signs of douchery --
I'll give you that.
Smell like dog
to you?
In the car?
You tell me.
Hmm.
Aah!
Take a breath.
Calm down.
Where's the angel?
You're him.
The human.
Where's the angel?
I don't know.
Aah!
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, hey,
what do you say
we blow this joint,
hit the road?
Now?
Yeah, Kevin's not getting
any more found.
The kid survived
a year without us.
He'll be okay for another
12 hours.
Besides, when's the last time
you slept?
Hmm.
What?
Nothing.
Is that, uh, that how you
rationalized taking a year off?
People will be okay?
People were okay, Dean.
You're okay.
Wow.
Look, I did
what we promised we'd do.
I moved on.
I lived my life.
Yeah, no,
I'm getting that.
Look, it wasn't like
I was...just oblivious.
I mean,
I read the paper every day.
I saw
the...weird stories,
the kind of stuff
we used to chase.
And you said what?
"Not my problem"?
Yes.
And you know what?
The world went on.
People died, Sam.
People will always die,
Dean.
Or maybe another hunter
took care of it.
I don't know,
but the point is,
for the first time,
I realized
that it wasn't only up to me
to stop it.
Hmm.
So what was it, hmm?
What could possibly
make you stop just like that?
A girl?
Was there a girl?
The girl had nothing
to do with it.
There was a girl.
Yeah. There was.
And then there wasn't.
Any more questions?
Listen, I know this is gonna
sound crazy to you.
I don't even necessarily
need you to understand.
But...you need to know.
I didn't just drop out,
Dean.
I found something.
Something I've...never had
all my life.
What was her name?
Amelia.
So, what, you, uh,
you dropped your peanut butter
in her chocolate?
How'd it happen?
I hit a dog.
I knew I smelled dog.
And I knew
you'd throw a bitch fit.
Hey,
the rules are simple, Sam.
You don't take a joint
from a guy named Don,
and there's no dogs
in the car!
All right,
what about you?
What about me?
Look at you.
You've still
got that look.
You're shaky.
You're on edge.
What was it like?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
Try me.
It was bloody.
Messy.
31 flavors
of bottom-dwelling nasties.
Hell, most days felt like
360-degree combat.
But there was something
about being there.
Felt pure.
What?
No thanks
for saving your hide?
Sure.
I won't shove this
up your ass.
Mm.
Awful strange way to punch
your meal ticket, friend.
I got something
you need.
Yeah, what's that?
A way out.
Even a dentaenapocalypse
like you
knows
there's no such thing.
There is
if you're human.
God has made it so.
At least,
that's the rumor.
Bull.
Suit yourself.
Maybe
you've gone native.
Maybe you like
being man meat
for every
Tom, Dick, and Harry.
Prove it.
Nah.
You're either in
or you're out.
So you just want to
guide me out of Purgatory
out of the goodness
of your undead heart?
More or less.
What's in it for you?
I'm hopping a ride.
What?
It's a human portal,
jackass.
Only humans
can pass through.
I show you the door,
you hump my soul
to the other side.
So you're looking
for a soul train.
Sure.
If that's
what you're into.
And how do I know
this isn't a set-up?
How do I know
I ain't gonna end up
like your friend
over there?
He was my friend.
Now you are.
First rule of Purgatory,
kid.
You can't trust nobody.
You just asked me
to trust you.
You see?
You're getting it now.
First
we find the angel.
Mm, three's a crowd,
chief.
Well, hey.
Either you're in
or you're out.
The last time I saw Kevin
was, like, a year ago.
When he disappeared?
Mm-hmm.
He stole his mother's car
because he thought
he was on a mission
from God or something?
It was crazy.
Shut up!
My friend Adam --
who got addicted to Adderall
but got a perfs on his S.A.T.s,
so it was totally worth it --
same thing.
Shut up!
Seerse.
Mission from God.
Look, Channing,
we know
Kevin was here.
No, he wasn't.
And we understand
if you're trying to protect him.
But nobody can protect Kevin
better than we can.
I hate Kevin.
I wouldn't protect him.
I thought
you two had a thing.
Yeah, when he
was going to Princeton.
Wow.
Just like that?
Mm-hmm.
So why would Kevin
come sniffing around here
if not to see her?
No idea.
Maybe
we should split up,
ask around,
see if anybody's seen him?
Yeah, Asian kid, yea high,
at a university.
That should be easy.
Okay.
Are you ready to forget
all about what's-his-name?
Okay, this guy's name is Kyle,
he's Jewish,
um, I'm pretty sure
he has an Asian thing.
Perfs, right?
Shut up, bitch.
Inferni clamavi ad te regem
sermonos meos.
The Prophet still has not yet
shown his face to me.
But you should know
Dean Winchester is back.
Help. I need help.
The dog needs help.
That way!
He just -- he just
came out of nowhere,
right
in front of my car.
We need a doctor.
Are you a doctor?
The doctor's coming, sir.
But I'm not sure --
You're not sure
what?
This is an animal hospital.
You save animals.
Sir.
Save this animal!
Roberta, can you escort
this gentleman out, please?
Yes.
I did this.
Come on.
Don't judge me.
I got bubkes.
Well...
And here you go.
Ah, thank you.
Sweet mother of God.
It's for me?
Seriously?
Check this out.
So, I went through
campus security archives
around the time Kevin
should have been here.
Anyone look familiar?
Dude.
It's a burger.
It's treasure.
All right, so, what, Kevin
comes all the way to campus
and doesn't see
his girlfriend?
I don't know...
but I went
to the computer lab
and found
the computer he was on.
And?
And I found the website
he was visiting,
found his account username,
hacked in to the website,
found when else
this username logged in,
and then I reverse-tracked
the I.P. address
back to the original user,
Kevin,
who has apparently been using
the same wireless router
for the past two months.
That is
spectacular work.
Any chance I can get that
in English?
Yeah.
I think he's in Iowa --
at a coffee shop.
A church?
You sure this is right?
Barista at the coffee shop
swears he's seen Kevin
ducking in here
for the past few months.
Kevin.
It's Sam and Dean Winchester.
Open up.
Stop! Stop!
Not Leviathans.
It's us.
What the hell
happened to you guys?
Cliff Notes?
I went to Purgatory.
Sam hit a dog.
For real?
You want some towels?
Who taught you
all this?
I guess...God.
God taught you
how to trap demons?
Technically, yeah.
Wait, wait,
hold on.
Crowley kidnapped you.
I saw that.
But then you left a message
saying you escaped.
How?
Well...
first, he took me
to a warehouse.
Look at you.
Haircut,
manicure, pedicure.
Like a new penny.
- Will there be torture now?
- Torture?
Heavens, no.
No. Quite the opposite,
my young prince.
Sky's the limit
for you and I.
There was
a tablet there,
like the last one.
There we go.
Now, remember --
feel like a winner,
be a winner.
Okay?
Interpret.
Wait,
there's another tablet?
So another
word of God.
Yes.
How many words of God
are there?
I just became a Prophet,
like, a year ago.
Well, did this tablet
have a name?
"Demons."
What about demons?
As far as
I could tell...
everything.
What are we looking at?
It's all
just fragments.
Bits and pieces.
This is hard.
Throw me a bone here,
Kev.
Wait...
Yes?
I'm sorry.
Is it just me,
or is it hot in here?
Is it?
Our mistake.
Okay.
I see something.
Hell Gates.
Talk to me.
What about
Hell Gates?
There's one
in Wisconsin.
The tablet told me
how to open it.
There were ingredients
for a spell.
Right away.
Mr. Crowley
would like you to proceed.
Where is Mr. Crowley?
Where do you think, dumbass?
Wisconsin.
Go.
You showed the king of Hell
how to open a Hell Gate?
So that all the demons in Hell
could come out
all at the same time?
What?
No.
Men?
Kevin?
I told Crowley
I was opening a Hell Gate,
but I was reading
from another chapter --
how to destroy demons.
You son of a bitch.
Wait. Kevin?
Where's
the tablet now?
Safe.
Safe where?
Hey. As long as
it's safe, okay?
Were you able to read
anything else off the tablet
before
you stashed it?
Only the stuff about
closing the gates of Hell.
Forever.
Come again?
Banish all demons
off the face of the Earth,
lock them away
forever.
That could be important,
right?
Closing
the gates of Hell forever?
Yeah. Yeah,
that could be important.
Okay, if this kid is right,
he's sitting on a bombshell.
Hell,
he is the bombshell.
What?
That.
I mean, there's no way that Kevin's
getting out of this intact, is there?
Well, I think he's doing
pretty well for himself so far.
Yeah, he got out.
And now he's in it...
whether
he likes it or not.
So...free will,
that's only for you?
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
Sam, we have an opportunity
to wipe the slate clean.
We take Kevin to the tablet,
he tells us the spell,
we send every demon
back to hell -- forever.
Every single bastard
that destroyed our lives,
killed our mother,
killed Jess.
And you're not sure?
Kevin, I, uh...
I owe you
an apology.
Um...
look, when you disappeared
and Dean disappeared,
I...needed
to clear my head,
and...I'm thinking maybe
you were one of the pieces
that I should have been there
to pick up.
You've been a hunter
since you were a kid, right?
Yeah, mostly.
Yeah.
Ever since I realized
I was a Prophet...
It's just hard to believe
this is actually my life.
Yeah.
It sucks right now.
I know that.
Um, it might suck
for a lot longer,
but...trust me on this --
it gets better.
You know I'm not gay,
right?
If we can do this,
get the tablet,
get you everything you need
to close the gates of Hell,
there's a world out there
where nobody --
not Crowley, no demon --
is chasing you anymore.
I guess I just don't see
how I get from here to there.
I used to not be able
to see it, either.
But there is a way.
Just give me
5 minutes.
He's sustained
some serious internal bleeding.
There's at least
two leg fractures
that
I can see right now.
But with some TLC,
he should pull through for you.
Thanks, Doctor.
You're gonna
take the dog?
Look, I-I would.
He's...not mine.
He's not anybody's.
I-I spend a lot of the time
on the road.
Don't you think
you're responsible?
Why do you think
I brought him here?
Roberta, could you hand
this man his trophy
on his way out,
please?
Well, maybe if you were
such an upstanding guy,
you wouldn't have hit him
in the first place?
Fine.
I'll take him.
There's my hero.
We got company.
Sam.
What the hell
is that?
It's Purgatory.
Dean Winchester.
Back from Purgatory.
Spanky the demon.
Yeah, I heard about you.
The one who uses
too much teeth, right?
Dean!
Hello, boys.
Dean.
You're looking...
well, let's just say Purgatory
didn't do you any favors.
Where's your angel?
Ask your mother.
There's
that grade-school zip.
Missed it.
I really did.
Moose.
Still
with the pork chops.
I admire that.
Let Channing go.
That's not Channing,
Kevin.
Not anymore.
What an awful thing
to say to the boy.
Of course
it's Channing.
Kev.
Last time we danced,
you stole my tablet
and killed my men.
Tell you what.
Come with me now,
bygones.
And I'll let the girl go back
to...What's-the-Point U.
He's lying.
You won't get Channing back.
She's probably dead already.
Will you please
stop saying that?
Let the girl
speak.
Kevin?
Channing?
What's
going on?
There's a demon in you,
and you're going
to your safety school.
What?!
But it's gonna be
okay.
I-I-I-I just --
I can't.
No, no, wait.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Kevin.
Myself for the girl.
But this ends.
All right?
No fighting, no nothing.
It ends.
Can't let you do that,
buddy.
Or what?
You'll kill me?
I'll grab my stuff.
Chin up, gentlemen.
I'm a professional.
This ain't over
by a long shot, Crowley.
Really, Dean, who writes
your stuff? A marshmallow?
Come on, Kevin.
Chop, chop.
Kevin?
Aah!
Really, boys?
Kevin!
Kevin.
Sam, Dean, run!
Find
another meatsuit.
Hello?
Wrong number.
Automated jackass.
All right,
anybody want anything?
I'm good.
Kevin?
How
you holding up?
Awesome.
The king of Hell just
snapped my girlfriend's neck.
How 'bout you?
All right,
listen to me.
I'm sorry about your girlfriend,
okay? I am.
But the sooner you get this,
the better.
You're in it now
whether you like it or not.
That means
you do what you got to do.
I'm hitting the head.
There he is.
How did you
get a phone?
Would you believe
they sell these things
in convenience stores
now?
A lot's changed
in 50 years.
Must be a hell of a lot
to take in.
Mostly it's the choices,
you know?
So many choices.
Yeah, I hear that.
Listen, Benny,
not to beat a dead horse.
What we did down there
is what we had to do.
Now, I don't regret it
for a second.
But...you know,
maybe until we both adjust,
it's best we don't talk
for a while.
There it is.
One day at a time, just like
we talked about, right?
I think you had it right,
bud.
What's that?
Purgatory was pure.
I'm kind of wishin'
I had appreciated it more.
You know?
Like you.
Listen, you got an emergency,
you call me, you understand?
I hear you.
You keep your nose clean, too,
brother.
Yeah.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==