Hey. You Dean?
Hey, Garth.
Garth.
Oh, Marmaduke, you're crazy!
He grows on you.
What'd I miss?
You're right.
He has grown on me.
That's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
I don't hunt anymore.
- You quit?
- Yeah.
What could possibly
make you stop just like that?
Was there a girl?
Yeah. Amelia.
- All right, what about you?
- What about me?
I'm Benny.
I can see you two have
a lot to talk about.
Hey, hon.
Just in time.
Grab me a cold one,
would ya?
Why don't you have Sara Alcott
get it for you?!
What?
Oh, my God!
Mary, help!
Mary, what are you doing?!
Mary! Mary, help me!
Get the...
Aah! Mary!
Mary! No!
Aaaaaaah!
* Supernatural 8x06 *
Southern Comfort
Original Air Date on November 7, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Heads up.
I caught wind of a case
on this police scanner.
Sounds like
our kind of thing.
I wasn't even gone
10 minutes.
Okay.
That matters why?
I don't know, Dean.
How about because you haven't
said a word to me
since Prentiss Island?
And now, what?
You want me to shut up
and ride shotgun
and act
like nothing happened?
You want to talk
about Benny?
- Fine. Let's talk.
- Okay.
How about he's a vampire?
He's also the reason
I'm topside
and not roasting on a spit
in Purgatory.
Anything else?
Don't pretend
I don't get it.
I know you had to do
what you had to down there.
I highly doubt you get anything
about Purgatory.
But you're out now,
and Benny's still breathing.
Why?
He's my friend, Sam.
And what about my friend, Amy?
She was what?
'Cause you sure as hell didn't
have a problem ganking her.
Well, I guess people change,
don't they?
We let that werewolf Kate go,
didn't we?
She was different.
She...
you think
Benny's different?
He tell you he's not
drinking live blood, or something.
And you believe him.
Wow.
Okay. You know, you're right.
People do change.
Yeah.
I got a vampire buddy,
and you turn your phone off
for a year.
Don't turn this on me.
Look, Benny slips up
and some other hunter
turns his lights out, so be it.
But it's not gonna be you,
right?
You coming or not?
So,
guy's old lady comes home
while he's working
underneath his ride,
puts the pedal to the metal,
and takes half his head off.
What, that's it?
Yeah, in a nutshell.
She says she blacked out,
doesn't remember a damn thing.
Well,
sounds like insanity.
Maybe.
So, how does that make this
our kind of thing?
Because, Sam,
Kevin's in the wind, okay,
you're sulking around
like a eunuch in a whorehouse,
and I can't help
but ask myself,
when is decapitation
not my thing?
Whoa, whoa.
FBI?
Yeah, happened to be
in the neighborhood.
First a Texas Ranger,
now you guys?
Texas Ranger?
Yes, sir.
Right over there.
Oh,
you got to be kidding me.
Hey, Chuck Norris.
Sam? Dean!
Forgot he was a hugger.
- Come here!
- All right. Okay.
We're still...
we're still working here.
Uh, you guys have no idea
how much I missed you.
Um,
excuse us, would you?
Yeah,
we'll be right back.
A Texas Ranger, Garth?
Seriously? We're in Missouri.
What? Come on.
I look like a funeral director
in one of those.
Wow.
I heard some chatter you two
were back in the batter's box,
but I didn't believe it
till now.
Oh, uh, one sec.
Um...
Yo, Earl.
What you got?
A revenant.
Okay, uh, you'll need a casket
and some silver spikes.
Oh, and don't get bit.
No, it won't turn you,
but it will hurt like hell.
Okay, so,
once you got all that,
nail that sucker in, bury him,
and throw away the key.
Okay?
All right. Hasta.
What are you doing?
My job, hombre.
- Your "job"?
- Yeah.
And since when is
giving advice your job?
Hold up.
Are you the new Bobby?
You shut your mouth.
Yes.
What?!
Bobby was gone.
You two were MIA.
It was a weird time.
Somebody had to step in
and take up the slack.
All right.
Let's just
get back to work,
and we'll talk about this later,
all right?
Did Garth just tell us
what to do?
Uh, Scott Lew.
These gentlemen here
are with the FBI.
Mr. Lew's parents were
the individuals involved
in this...
unfortunate situation.
Sorry for your loss.
Just a few questions,
Mr. Lew.
Um, by any chance
were your parents having...
marital problems?
No.
Uh, no more than anyone else.
What about
your mother's health?
Any chance this was
a seizure, a stroke,
anything that might
help explain this?
I don't think so.
Um, they're checking her out
at the, um, hospital right now.
What about
stranger behavior?
Stranger? How?
Hearing voices,
seeing things...
your mother mention anything
like that?
My parents were married
for 30 years...
high-school sweethearts.
There's no good explanation
for why this happened,
no matter
where you want to look.
Okay, well,
thank you, Scott.
We'll be in touch.
No EMF.
No traces of sulfur
anywhere.
Like I thought... bust.
Hold on there, Sam.
There's a lot of things
to factor in here.
Uh, it happened
last night,
so the readings
could be cold by now.
Good point.
And, uh,
even if there was any sulfur,
Barney Fife and his crew
probably contaminated
the whole crime scene
and any evidence
that was here with it.
Wow.
He's on a roll.
That's one word for it.
Uh, guys,
I think I found something.
Is that gum,
or is that ectoplasm?
Ectoplasm is usually black,
right?
Mm.
Definitely ectoplasm.
So, what are we thinking...
uh, some kind of ghost, right?
Uh,
Ranger McCrae here.
One of those things rings
Hammer, I'm throwing down.
Oh, great.
Okay.
Thanks, Doc.
Asked the coroner
to drop me a line
in case the autopsy turned up
anything... unusual.
And guess what.
Our dead guy had the word
"Alcott" carved into his chest.
With what?
Coroner's best guess?
His wife Mary's
fingernails.
Mrs. Lew, can you tell us
what happened?
I was at the store
getting groceries,
and the next thing I know,
my son Scott finds me
in the driveway.
And Chester was...
Do you remember anything at all
about what happened?
Um... Chester dying?
Not really.
Bits and pieces, I guess.
Such as?
I remember his screams...
the smell of burnt rubber,
and...
I remember feeling
so angry...
just uncontrollable rage,
like I wasn't myself.
And after it was over,
all that anger was...
it was gone.
Uh, ma'am, does the word
"Alcott" mean anything to you?
What does she have to do
with anything?
It's a she?
My husband, Chester, and I
were going steady in high school
for a few years already
when we had a big fight.
What about?
Something stupid,
I'm sure.
It was around prom,
and so he took Sara Alcott
as his date instead of me.
So, this Sara Alcott
was a rival
for your husband's
affections?
Sara had
one night with him,
whereas I was with Chester
for 37 years.
Of course, right.
Sure.
Um,
just one more question.
Um
Is... Ms. Alcott still alive?
As far as I know,
yes.
Thank you very much,
Mrs. Lew.
Let me get this straight.
This poor guy goes to prom with
some girl over 30 years ago,
and because of that,
he is now a pancake?
I mean,
if this is a ghost,
maybe it's some sort of possession?
What are you talking about?
You heard her.
Alcott's alive.
Well, we're definitely gonna
want to talk to her.
Yeah,
sounds like a plan.
Did we eat yet?
Mmm. Thanks.
Keep 'em coming.
All right.
So, Dean,
give me the skinny.
Where were you
this past year?
Why don't we save what I did
on my summer vacation
for another time?
Aw, come on.
All right.
I was in Purgatory.
Like
the Purgatory Purgatory?
No, the one in Miami.
Man, that's balls.
That's not how you say
"balls."
So how'd you get out?
What's up with all
the, uh, hillbilly hankies?
These people know
the civil war's over, right?
Mm.
That's a touchy subject
around these parts.
See, Missouri was
a border state.
So, half the men
were Confederate,
the other half
were the Union.
How do you know all this?
I went to college.
You went to college?
Yeah.
College,
and on to dental school.
What, you...
you were a dentist?
Yeah, just for, like,
a hot minute.
Where'd you think I got
my first case?
Let me guess...
Tooth Fairy.
Yeah.
Man, I felt terrible
when I ganked that S.O.B.
Uh,
you killed the Tooth Fairy?
Yeah, man.
I mean, not my proudest moment,
but  it happened.
Mmm.
Man, this is good.
Hey, hon.
Uh, just, uh, grabbing some joe
on the way to the hospital,
gonna bring mom her stuff.
Oh, crap.
Jeff's here.
Don't worry,
I'll be fine.
Okay.
Love you.
Hey, Scott, how's...
uh, look, I heard about
what happened with your folks.
I'm really sorry.
If there's...
there's anything...
I mean, anything...
that I can do,
just...
just ask, man. Please.
How about getting me
my money back, Jeff?!
Oh!
So, first the mom goes
"Natural Born Killer,"
and now the son?
Well, what do we got...
a ghost with an oedipus complex?
I don't know
what that means.
Check that out.
"Sussex."
What is that,
another name?
I don't know.
Hey,
what'd the cops say?
Aw, come on.
Not much.
Uh, Scott insisted he wasn't
in control of himself.
Says all he remembers
is a red-hot rage.
So, what is this, some...
some kind of family curse?
Is that Bobby's hat?
Oh, yeah. Sure is.
We worked a rugaru case together
a few years back.
He left it in my car,
so I kept it as a...
memento.
What are you doing?!
That's not how you wear it.
Gentlemen,
surveillance is up,
but something
is all screwy with it.
Must be the camera.
Yeah, thank you,
there, deputy.
You guys see the head?
Ever seen anything like that
before?
Like that? No way.
So?
So, I'm thinking we need to talk
to Sara Alcott.
I found her... although these
days, she goes by Sara Brown.
How about this?
I'll check her out, and you two
see what you can find out about Sussex.
Word.
Awesome.
Mmm.
Now, I know you didn't come
all this way
for my sweet tea, Agent.
No.
Um, actually, I'm...
I'm here about Chester Lew.
Oh, yes.
So sad.
It is.
Is it true you and Chester...
dated a ways back?
Well, that is an odd question
for the FBI, isn't it?
You wouldn't believe
the awkward questions
I've had to ask people.
Yeah.
Well yes.
Yes.
Me and that old tomcat, Chester,
we went to prom together.
That's about it.
And that's all?
Well, I wasn't exactly
a good girl,
if that's what you mean.
And after that,
I-I thought that Chester and I
were gonna be hot and heavy.
But it just wasn't
meant to be.
And, uh, a week later,
he eloped with Mary.
Did you speak much to Mary
or Chester again after that?
Well, I'd see them about,
you know... picnics and such.
But... Mary kept Chester
on a pretty short leash.
Honestly, I'd moved on,
but it seems she never did.
And why do you think
that is?
Well,
I guess in her mind,
I was a reminder
of Chester's betrayal.
Huh.
So, if that's all...
Yes, uh, thank you very much
for your help.
It's been a long time
since I let myself go like that.
Yeah,
I know what you mean.
You asked me
if I lost someone.
I did.
My husband.
He died in Afghanistan
eight months ago.
That must have been,
um...
I...
I can't imagine.
Yeah.
We were together forever.
Or at least it seemed
that way.
Then one day,
Don just enlists.
Didn't ask me,
just said something
about wanting to do
the right thing.
Next thing I know, he's
off overseas and I'm all alone.
I got a couple letters,
some phone calls,
and then a knock
at the door.
Just like that.
And everywhere I looked,
all I could see
was judgment and pity
and just this constant reminder
of Don everywhere.
So I moved here...
...and became even more of
a hot mess than I already was.
And you hit a dog.
Easy there, flyweight.
Last time
you drank a beer,
I had to pick you up
off the floor.
You're such an idjit.
Idjit's supposed to be used
angrily.
Okay? Not happy.
If you're gonna butcher it,
don't say it at all.
Whoa, then. Okay.
N-none of my business,
but... this have anything to do
with you and... Sam?
No, you had it right.
It's none of your business.
Okay.
It just seems that you guys
are a little tense
around each other.
We're fine.
Can we get back to work?
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Just, uh...
just letting you know
that I'm here for you,
for anything.
I know sometimes Bobby,
he would...
You're not Bobby!
Okay?
You're never gonna be Bobby,
so stop!
Bobby belonged to all of us,
Dean... not just you and Sam.
Now, I'm just taking
what he showed me
and trying do something
with it.
That's all!
Why don't you see
if you can find something
in that bourbon-drenched book
of his
so we can get the hell
out of Dixie, all right?
Yeah. I'm on it.
Hey.
"Sussex" is not a who,
it's a what.
It's a business that went
belly-up about a year ago.
Look at this.
So, the guy
that Scott brained?
His old business partner...
ran the company into the ground.
So,
Scott had a beef with Jeff.
Looks like.
Hey,
you're on speaker.
Sara Alcott's clean,
if you look past the fact
that she and Chester
knocked boots on prom night
back in the day.
Okay, so...
Mary has
a grudge against Sara,
and Scott has a grudge
against Jeff.
Besides the fact this is
making my head hurt,
how does this add up
to a ghost?
Guys!
Bobby has it right here.
Green goo equals a spectre.
Which equals ghost,
right?
Mm, yeah, kind of.
A spectre is
an avenging ghost.
It, uh...
it possesses you
and finds out whatever betrayals
you're feeling
and forces you
to act on them.
Bobby say anything in there
about how we hunt these things?
Uh, the last spectre
he encountered
rose shortly after someone
desecrated a nearby grave.
Which...
Uh, there was a grave desecrated
locally three days ago.
It says here...
Oh.
This could get awkward.
What?
The unknown soldier?
You're kidding me,
right?
Mary Lew steamrolled
her husband
the day after this place
was vandalized.
Do the math.
But I thought the unknown
soldier was buried in Arlington.
Yep, but this is the Confederate
tomb of the unknown soldier.
See, the idea was,
they took a faceless, nameless
soldier they couldn't identify,
and they buried him here
to commemorate
all the soldiers who died.
Did you learn that
in college?
Nope...
Civil War re-enactments.
Once a year, every year.
Don't hate.
Okay, uh,
what about the guard?
Uh, he's ceremonial.
Gone by dusk.
- So, then we do this tonight?
- Yeah.
Burn a Confederate soldier's bones
in a town full of rednecks?
Sure.
Place doesn't look disturbed
to me.
What's
the police report say?
Uh, they think it was
just some kids messing around.
They, uh... they found
some beer cans, some graffiti.
Oh, and the casket was open
when they got here,
but they closed that
back up.
Yeah, but not before Casper had
a chance to make a run for it.
So, what? If they never touched this,
none of this would be happening?
Yeah,
according to Bobby.
All right, well,
let's get this party started.
Sammy, you want to give me
a hand?
And... go.
Whoa.
Check out this hardware.
Do you guys know
how much this is worth?
Yeah, but why open it up if
you're not gonna take anything?
I don't know.
Maybe the cops showed up
and they had to split fast.
You sure this will work,
even on a spectre?
It's a ghost, isn't it?
You burn its bones,
the ghost disappears.
All right. All right.
Uh, I kind of feel like we
should say something, all right?
Don't you?
Just... a little...
Sure.
We won.
Write that up for me,
would you, Doug?
Help! Please!
Hey. You okay?
Need my... asthma... inhaler.
From evidence. Please.
Why don't you write
your own reports, Sheriff?!
10 bones says Deputy Doug had
an Axe to grind with his boss.
How can you be
so sure?
Ah, what the hell?
Maybe we torched
the wrong redneck.
Or maybe not.
Maybe an object was removed
from the grave,
something the spectre's
attaching itself to.
Like Bobby's flask?
Um,
I don't know, guys.
You saw what I saw.
Those kids didn't take anything.
Or they did.
And this spectre hitched a ride
with it.
And whoever has the object
gets possessed.
Okay. So, who's got the object,
and, more importantly,
who do they got
a grudge against?
All right.
We need you to focus, Deputy.
Other lives depend on it.
Tell me what happened
after you shot the sheriff.
I was on the ground.
I think Karl tackled me,
and I asked him what happened.
And?
He didn't answer me.
He just took my gun
and walked away.
Did he say
where he was going?
I guess...
I must have hurt him, too.
He said he was going
to the hospital.
You two find out what you can
about the unknown soldier.
I got the hospital.
Hey, uh, Sam.
If you ever need to talk,
I just want to let you know
that I'm here.
About anything...
you know, life, uh, Dean, you.
I'm okay. Thanks.
I mean, it just seems
like you and Dean are talking
but nobody's listening
to each other.
I had this cousin once...
well, he's gone now...
but his name was Frank.
Frank and I
used to build...
Hey.
Uh, just lock up
when you leave.
I'm late.
Wait, what?
I just think it's better
if neither of us get
the wrong idea here.
O-okay.
And I know I said
a lot of things last night,
and I know I can't ask you
to forget them.
But just... Do.
Why?
Because I don't need
your pity.
I don't need you looking at me
the way they all...
like that.
Wait, um
you think this is pity?
Amelia, I'm glad you told me
about Don.
It helps me understand.
How messed up I am?
You think I don't know that?
You don't have to feel sorry
for me, Sam.
I didn't mean it
like that.
Yeah, well, like I said,
I'm late. So...
Hey, you comin'?
You do know there is
a good reason
he's called the Unknown soldier,
right?
Right.
Uh, we were just hoping
maybe a theory or two
had been a floated around
over the years...
something local, maybe?
There is one.
Hey, ump.
You remember me?
I stole second!
Karl?
What the hell are you doing?
Why are you doing...
Why am I gonna make mustard
from your brain stem?!
I don't know.
Why did you call me out,
ump?
I'm sorry.
Please.
Looks like
you're shooting blanks.
Hey, that tickled.
Corporal Collins
of the Union
shot and killed
his brother, Vance,
who fought
for the Confederacy.
Local boys.
Wait,
so two brothers fought
on opposite sides
of the Civil War?
Legend has it that Vance
swore vengeance on his brother
with his dying breath.
Years later...
consumed by guilt, no doubt...
the corporal dug
his brother up
where he'd buried him
on the battlefield
and brought him home.
Are you suggesting this Vance
guy is the unknown soldier?
That's one theory,
anyway.
What's that?
Karl, listen,
I know the spectre's turning
the temperature up in there.
So just tell me
what the object is,
and we'll send this joker
home.
I don't think so.
There's unfinished business,
thanks to you.
Oh,
the spectre likes you.
Oh, yeah?
Why don't you tell him
to come on out here?
We'll make promise bracelets.
Most of the soldiers
were poor farmers,
so the families would give them
a penny on a string.
It was for good luck,
and in case they ever got lost,
they always had a penny
for food or drink.
A penny.
Here. Have a taste.
It's me. Do what you gotta.
Dean, hey.
There was a string on the floor
of the tomb.
It used to hold an old penny.
That's the object.
We're coming right now.
Dean?
What the hell, man?
We went to the hospital.
You're not answering your phone.
You should have looked for me
when I was in Purgatory.
Come on, Dean.
I know it's not you in there
pulling the strings.
Shut up!
Don't!
You never even wanted
this life.
Always blamed me
for pulling you back into it.
- That's not true.
- Really?
'Cause everything
you've ever done
since you climbed into my ride
has been to deceive me.
What do you want me
to say?
That I've made mistakes?
I've made mistakes,
Dean.
That's not Dean, Sam.
Shut up!
Mistakes?
Well, let's go through
some of Sammy's greatest hits.
Drinking demon blood,
check.
Being in cahoots with Ruby.
Not telling me
that you lost your soul.
Or how about running around
with Samuel for a whole year,
letting me think
that you were dead
while you're doing
all kinds of crazy.
Those aren't mistakes,
Sam.
Those are choices!
All right.
You said it.
We've both played
a little fast and loose.
Yeah, I might have lied,
but I never once betrayed you.
I never once left you
to die.
And for what, a girl?
You left me to die
for a girl?!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Garth, don't.
No, he won't kill me.
His beef isn't with me.
You're not gonna shoot me,
are you, Dean?
Move.
Come on, Dean.
You do not want to kill
your brother.
You... you've been protecting
him your whole life.
Don't stop now.
He left me to rot
in Purgatory!
All right. All right.
Maybe he did. I don't know.
I wasn't there.
But I'm sure he had his reasons.
Just like you had your reasons
for Benny.
Who?
Benny has been more of a brother
to me this past year
than you've ever been!
That's right.
Cass let me down.
You let me down.
The only person that
hasn't let me down is Benny.
I know you're angry.
But, man,
you got to fight this thing.
Do not do this!
Just let it go.
Come on, Dean.
Goodbye, Sam.
Ow! God!
Garth, don't!
It's cool.
It's all good.
I'm cool.
It took me forever to melt
that penny, but it's finally gone.
How come that penny didn't
jack you like everyone else?
I mean, I can understand
why it didn't affect
the kid who took it.
He's young and innocent.
But, uh, everyone
at some point in their life
feels like
they've been screwed.
Not me, man.
I let all that stuff go
with the help of my yogi,
my Sega Genesis.
And you should, too.
You can't change the past,
amigo.
Now, there's something
I want to say to you.
Stop being a idjit!
With Bobby dead, you and Sam
are all each other has.
And that's not so bad, man.
Now, you know
what's coming next, right?
Come on.
Oh...
Yeah, okay.
Hey, uh...
Keep on truckin', Garth.
Thanks.
Oh, got to go.
Yo, Lamar.
What do we got?
Wendigo?
You got a flare gun?
No?
What about
a flame thrower?
Then you'd better get
some sneakers, buddy,
'cause you're
gonna have to run.
All right.
Balls!
Sam, I can't.
I don't pity you.
Okay?
I don't.
You and I...
we're a lot of things,
but we're not to be pitied.
Look, I lost my brother, Dean,
a few months ago.
It felt like
my world imploded
and came raining down on me,
and...
I ran.
Just like you.
Is that supposed to be
a pep talk?
Yeah, uh, sort of.
Because...
See, now I pity you.
Oh, look, I mean,
that wasn't really my point.
Yeah, well, bell's rung
on that one, so...
So, uh...
So what now?
I don't know.
You want to talk about it?
Last night?
No. Dean, you pervert.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Do you want to
talk about Don?
Hey,
I'd like that, too.
Sammy!
For the record, the girl...
her name's Amelia.
Amelia Richardson.
She and I had a place together
in Kermit, Texas.
Look, man, I don't even remember
what I said, but, uh...
But what?
But you didn't mean it?
Oh, please.
You and I both know
you didn't need that penny
to say those things.
Come on, Sam.
Own up to your crap,
Dean.
I told you from the jump
where I was coming from,
why I didn't look
for you.
But you?
You had secrets.
You had Benny.
And you got
on your high and mighty,
and you've been kicking me
ever since you got back.
But that's over.
So move on, or I will.
Okay.
I hear you.
Good.
You know what?
Hear this, too.
I just might be
that hunter
that runs into Benny one day
and ices him.
I guess we'll cross that bridge
when we come to it, won't we?
Yeah.
You keep saying that.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==