She's uh...
Meg.
She's a demon, Sam.
Remember me?
I sure remember you, Clarence.
I learned that
from the pizza man.
She's running. Which means
you're running from Crowley.
My name is Naomi.
We rescued you.
They're controlling us,
Castiel!
Kill him!
This is a direct order!
What did I just do?
You tell the winchesters
that Samandriel had been...
Compromised.
You acted in...
Self-defense.
Cass, you okay?
There's another tablet?
So, another Word of God.
The Angel Tablet,
Castiel.
Crowley knows.
God built a series of tests.
When you've done all three,
you can slam the Gates of Hell.
Sam,
I didn't pass a test.
But I did. And I'm doing
the rest of them.
Cass,
you got your ears on?
You keep a lookout
for my little brother, okay?
No, Cass. No!
No, Cass, don't.
Please.
No hesitation.
Quick. Brutal.
Everything's
back in order.
Finally.
You're ready.
? Supernatural 8x17 ?
Goodbye Stranger
Original Air Date on March 20, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
What the hell is this?
Spear of Destiny?
What is this --
God's toothpick?
You know, would it have killed
these asshats
to label these boxes
in something
other than hieroglyphics?
It's ridiculous.
Hey.
You listening to me?
Yeah.
It's, uh...
Fascinating stuff.
You should probably, uh,
write it all down
in your journal
for the archives,
you know?
Yeah, thanks.
You're a lot of help.
Hey, Doc Holliday,
you all right over there?
Uh, yeah.
Um...
I'm fine.
Just, uh, wrong pipe.
Well, hello.
These Men of Letters
weren't so boring after all.
Konnichiwa.
Hey, check this out.
What is wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
You kidding me?
This is a first edition, dude.
You know what this would
go for on eBay?
No. Why? Do you?
No.
Maybe.
Shut up.
You find anything?
I did, yeah --
uh, dead bodies showing up
all over the Midwest last week.
Benton, Indiana;
Downers Grove, Illinois;
uh, Novi, Michigan;
and then again last night
in Lincoln Springs, Missouri.
And how is this us?
Because each of the victims
had severe burns
around their eyes, hands,
and feet,
puncture wounds through
the backs of their hands,
eyes and internal organs
liquefied.
That sounds like us.
Yeah.
Also, no link
between any of the victims.
Uh, one was
a real-estate agent.
Another was
a local historian.
Woman killed last night
was a teacher.
So, chupacabra.
What do we got?
Power tools gone rogue?
Wait -- are we talking
a-a "Maximum Overdrive"
situation here?
I don't know.
Worth a shot, though.
I'll grab my gear. We should
probably leave in five.
Mm-hmm.
'Less, of course, you need some
more time with Miss October.
What?
Oh.
Yeah.
Yeah, make it 10.
We just have a few
routine follow-up questions
about your wife, sir.
Did she have
any enemies?
Ann?
Honestly, I can't think of
a soul who'd want to hurt her,
even after
everything that happened.
Everything
that happened?
About a week ago,
something changed in Ann.
She was out of sorts,
not herself at all.
Out of sorts how?
It'd be better
if I show you.
She stopped sleeping.
She stopped eating.
She went out
in the middle of the night,
going God knows where.
I tried to talk to her,
but, uh...
She would just mutter
to herself.
About what?
Something...
about an orchard?
Finally, I just followed her
one night,
and she went
to the playground.
Over here --
the elementary school.
And she started digging.
She would leave with
these little bags full of dirt.
Hung them here.
All these bags represent holes
that she dug in the ground.
Were these holes, uh --
I don't know -- 6 feet deep?
No.
She dug for hours.
She never broke a sweat.
Straight down
10, maybe 15 feet.
Did you notice
anything else?
I didn't say anything
to the cops
'cause I didn't want them
to think I was crazy.
After Ann came home,
I came down here
to confront her,
and she was on the phone.
Any idea
who she was talking to?
No.
But I know what I saw.
And it wasn't my Annie.
After I called her out,
her eyes...
they turned black.
Now, I-I know
I must have imagined it.
I know I did.
But I-I left.
I went to the bar,
probably had too much to drink,
and by the time
I came back...
...my Annie was, uh...
I should have stayed.
I should have
protected her.
I'm moving into
my sister's place today.
I can't be here
anymore.
Sure.
Well, um, thank you very much
for your time.
We're both very sorry
for your loss.
So, somebody's killing demons.
Well, that is awesome.
I feel like we should send
a card or flowers.
What kind of flower says
"thanks for killing demons"?
Yeah, but who's killing demons?
And why?
And, by the way, since when does
a demon possess someone,
then go
all "Beautiful Mind"
and -- and start digging
in the dirt?
Does any of this
seem right to you?
I like the part about killing demons.
That sounds right.
Sure.
Of course.
Well, thank you very much
for all your help.
I really appreciate
the time.
All right. Bye.
So, real-estate guy's wife said
he was acting weird.
Uh, historian's hubby
said the same --
just got all obsessive
and then weird.
No one saw
any black eyes,
but still, where there's smoke,
you know...
I wonder what they're
all looking for.
Well, Wendy Rice here
was the last person
to speak with Ann,
so let's see if she can tell us.
Special Agent lynne.
This is my partner,
Special Agent Tandy.
We'd like to ask you a few
questions about Ann Morton.
Oh.
Uh, uh, uh, of course.
Please come in.
I had never met her
before she called
the other night.
Now,
why was she calling you?
She was looking to find
an original map of the city.
Did she say
what for?
Well, she -- she didn't,
but she did mention
an -- an old orchard
that had gone missing.
Missing?
This -- this town was wiped
from the earth
by one of the river's
100-year floods.
It was --
it was rebuilt.
But all the original records
were -- were lost.
I'm --
I'm a PhD candidate.
And this --
this is my research.
I, uh...
My dissertation is -- is
on the history of this town
and, uh, its connection
to the Underground Railroad
and -- and -- and whatnot.
I've been working
to re-create a map for years
as part of my research,
and this -- this is
the old Jakubiak orchard there.
I found out yesterday it's
where Downey meets Bond Street.
Now, did Ann say
why she was looking
for the site
of an old orchard?
No.
We -- we set a time to meet,
and she never showed.
Then I read about her
in the paper.
It's just tragic.
Ann's assistant called
this morning, though,
asking if I still
had the map.
Assistant?
Oh.
That's probably him.
Maybe he can help.
Oh. Are -- are you --
Put this on your shoulder.
I'm fine.
The other demon escaped.
I bound the one I caught
in a devil's trap.
I'm gonna
interrogate it now.
Wait a second. Cass.
How about you answer
some questions first?
Like, where the hell
have you been?
You heard me,
didn't you?
You prayed to him?
Yes, I heard you.
But that's
not why I'm here.
I've been hunting demons.
So this is you.
Why?
What should I tell them?
The truth.
Most of it, anyway.
Maybe they can
get us closer.
I've been searching for the
other half of the Demon Tablet.
Without us?
I've been trying to help,
Dean.
And in my search,
I uncovered
that Crowley has sent out demons
to find Lucifer's crypts.
Lucifer had crypts?
Dozens of them,
apparently.
But why
the storage wars?
I mean, what the hell
are they all looking for?
It would be more helpful
if they knew everything.
They cannot be trusted.
But --
Lie, Castiel.
Tell them
what we discussed.
They're looking for a parchment
that would allow them
to decipher Crowley's half
of the Demon Tablet
without a Prophet.
A demonic decoder ring?
In Crowley's hands?
Awesome.
The crypts were, uh,
lost over time.
Only those closest to Lucifer
knew their whereabouts.
Then how did Crowley
find them?
His demons
have been possessing locals
who may have
some special knowledge.
That would explain
the crazy room at Ann's house.
But how did they know where to
start looking in the first place?
I don't know.
I'm hoping the strange-haired
demon in the kitchen
is more knowledgeable
than the others I interrogated.
Well, he puts the "ass"
in "Cass," huh?
He's definitely off.
Off?
He hasn't been right since
he got back from Purgatory.
We still don't know
how he got out of there.
I don't know, Dean.
If he's so sketchy, then why
were you praying to him?
You know,
I can hear you both.
I am a celestial being.
Sam and Dean Winchester.
Oh, the thoughts she had
about you two.
Mostly you, Sam.
What can I say?
She has a thing
for smutton chops.
All right, you douchebag,
listen --
aah!
Who told you
about the crypts?
I thought angels were
supposed to be the good cops.
Aah!
Wait! Stop!
Stop!!
We have a hostage!
It's one of Crowley's pets.
She's at the Murray Hotel,
down by the interstate.
She knows the towns
where all the crypts are buried.
She saw them all
back in the day.
And she told you
about the parchment?
What parchment?!
Hey. Hey!
Think he's the only bad cop
in this room?
Stop lying!
We know
what you're really looking for.
No.
I am telling you,
we're looking...
Kill it!
...for -- aah!
Cass!
What the hell was that?!
It told us
what we needed.
No, she didn't!
You can't just --
I started this hunt
without you
because I didn't want anything
to slow me down.
We have to get
to the motel now.
Hold on a second --
Cass!
Cass? Cass?
Damn it. Go. Go. Go.
There. There.
Thanks for waiting.
The hostage is in there.
Aren't you a little short
for a Stormtrooper?
So, I got to ask.
Um...
What's up with the hair?
What?
Aww. Thanks for noticing,
Dean.
But this wasn't my idea.
It was Crowley's.
And it's just another reason
I want to stab him in the face.
Wait a second.
You've been telling Crowley the
location of Lucifer's crypts.
What can I say?
I needed a break
from the constant torture.
And I did visit them all
during my time with Yellow Eyes.
But don't worry.
I haven't exactly been giving
them the Glengarry leads.
You mean
you've been lying to them?
I just get them
in the ballpark.
Enough time's passed
and enough's changed
that they bought it.
Why lie?
Buy myself some time,
dummy.
Try to find a way
to get free.
Wait -- so...
A bunch of innocent people died
so you could...
buy yourself some time?
Hi. I'm Meg.
I'm a demon.
So, what have
they found?
Bupkis.
Every crypt's been
one Al Capone's vault
after another.
And on top of that, someone
kept picking up the trail
and icing demons.
I'm guessing
that was you, Castiel.
But Crowley
just keeps sending more.
He's hell-bent on...
She's gonna tell them
the truth.
Do I have to kill her?
She does know
the location of the crypts.
But working with a demon
is...unclean.
Well, we could use her --
as Crowley did.
Agreed.
...finding
that Angel Tablet.
Wait a second.
Did you just say
"Angel Tablet"?
You know, I get why
Crowley calls you "moose" now.
Yes -- "Angel Tablet."
Crowley found out
Lucifer had it,
figures it's stashed
in a crypt.
Well, this is news to me,
as well.
Demons I interrogated,
they must have been lying
about their true intentions.
Really?
'Cause I saw you
"Zero Dark Thirty" that demon.
You were
more than persuasive.
You're both missing
the point.
I lied to them,
which means they're digging
in the wrong place.
But not for long.
They'll be back here soon.
So,
who's up for fleeing?
She's right. We need to find
those crypts before they do.
Meg, you're the only one
who's been there.
We need your help.
Any of you dummies
got a map?
There. That's where
the crypt was.
What's there now?
Do I look like Google
to you?
None of these buildings
were here way back in the day.
Figure it out, genius.
Is there any booze
in this dump?
He lied to us.
Yeah, maybe.
I can kind of understand why.
I mean, an Angel Tablet?
If the Demon Tablet
can shut the Gates of Hell,
what can
the Angel Tablet do?
These wounds
have festered.
You really do know how to make
a girl's nethers quiver,
don't you?
I am aware
of how to do that.
Although it doesn't
usually involve cleaning wounds.
Why are you so sweet on me,
Clarence?
I don't know.
And I still don't know
who Clarence is.
Would it kill you
to watch a movie, read a book?
A movie, no.
But a book
with the proper spells --
yeah, it could,
theoretically, kill me.
You know, you're much cuter
when you're shutting up.
So, which Cass
are you now?
Original make and model
or crazy town?
I'm just me.
So, your noodle's
back in order?
Yeah, my...noodle
remembers everything.
I think
it's a pretty good noodle.
Really?
You remember everything?
If you're referring
to the pizza man...
Yes, I remember
the pizza man.
And it's a good memory.
Here goes.
All right.
According to this,
the crypt has to be
below an abandoned building.
Good times.
You really think we can trust,
uh, Meg-stiel?
No.
But what choice
do we have?
You ever miss
the Apocalypse?
No. Why would I miss
the end of times?
I miss the simplicity.
I was bad.
You were good.
Life was easier.
Now it's all so messy.
I'm kind of good,
which sucks.
And you're kind of bad --
which is actually
all manner of hot.
We survive this...
I'm gonna order
some pizza
and we're gonna
move some furniture around.
You understand?
No, I-I --
wait -- actually...
Yes, I --
All right.
Let's roll, campers.
Sir?
I, uh, searched the site
top to bottom.
It's empty.
No, there's no crypt there.
And, uh, that's not all.
It's just me now, sir.
I, um...
We may have lost Meg.
Sir?
Hello, sir?
Just to be clear...
...you can't find
a hole in the ground...
Your coworkers have met
with an untimely demise...
...and you've lost
my favorite chew toy.
Brilliant.
What's that old expression?
"If you want
something done right..."
...blah, blah, blah.
So, this is it.
Basement?
All right, Cass and I
will head in
and get
our Indiana Jones on.
Sam, you stay outside
with Meg.
What?
We got this.
What are you
talking about, Dean?
I'm not letting you
go in there alone.
He won't be alone.
That's not what I mean.
Meg can hang here,
watch our backs.
Oh, what?
Now you trust Meg?
Hey,
I got you this far.
Shut up.
Shut up, Meg.
Dean --
Sam, I saw your bloody rag
in the trash can, okay?
That wasn't --
Stop.
Just stop.
Sam, we don't know
what's in there, okay?
And you almost let a demon
get the best of you back there.
I'm fine.
No, you're not fine.
You haven't been fine
since the first trial.
That's why
I called Cass.
Trial?
Shut up, Meg. Shut up, Meg.
Dean, I'm telling you --
I'm okay.
No, you're not.
Sam...
You're damaged in ways
even I can't heal.
Dean's right.
You should stay here
and protect Meg.
Since when
do I need protecting?
Since you were held captive
and tortured for over a year.
Touch?.
All right,
we'll be back.
Hey, what did you mean
back there about Sam?
It's difficult to say.
It's something
on the subatomic level
and his
electromagnetic field --
Okay, bottom-line it for me,
Bill Nye.
Is it lethal?
I don't know.
Wait.
There's a draft.
There's something
behind there.
Stand back.
Wait -- so I took
how many bullets for you guys,
and you didn't even
look for me?
Like, once?
My hero.
What's with all the "trial"
and "being damaged" crap?
Look, no disrespect,
but you haven't exactly been
the most, uh, trustworthy person
in our lives, Meg.
You're not gonna tell me?
Seriously?
How am I not team Sam?
Fine.
Whatever it is,
you okay dying over it?
You don't want to say,
fine.
But remember, I spent time
in that walking corpse of yours.
I know your sad, little thoughts
and feelings.
That's creepy.
Here's what I remember.
Deep down, in parts you never
let see the light of day,
you want to live
a long, normal life
away from creepy old things
like me.
I do.
You know,
I spent last year with...
someone, and, um...
...now I know
that's actually possible.
Wait -- that's how you spent
your last year?
With a chick?
Lame.
You know,
how about we just wait quietly?
What was her name?
You don't even trust me
with a name?
Cut me,
do I not bleed, Sam?
So, some chick actually got you
off hunting, huh?
That's one rare creature.
Tell me --
how'd you meet
this unicorn?
I found it.
Tell the Winchester
the crypt is empty.
Then you can
come back --
It's warded
against angels.
Well,
you can come back --
Crowley's demons
are still in town,
and we're
running out of time.
What should I do?
Handle it.
Dean...
That's it.
How do you know?
It's the only thing in here
warded against angels.
Winner, winner,
chicken dinner.
Good.
Hand it to me,
and I'll take it to heaven.
No, we will take it to Kevin
so he can translate.
Right. Of course.
I'll take it to him
right away.
No time to waste.
Well, he's not that far.
I've been meaning to...
go check on him,
bring him some supplies.
If the demons get their hands
on the Angel Tablet,
they'll kill us all.
They'll destroy heaven.
I can reason with Dean.
He's a good man.
Kill him.
I can resupply the Prophet,
Dean.
You know, why don't, uh,
why don't Sam and I
take it over to him,
and you can get back
to your mission?
Finding the other half
of the Demon Tablet --
that is priority,
isn't it?
I can't let you take that,
Dean.
Can't or won't?
Both.
How did you get out
of Purgatory, Cass?
There has to be
another way.
You have done this
a thousand times, Castiel.
You're ready.
Kill him.
Then take the tablet
and bring it home,
where it belongs.
Just tell me
how you got out of Purgatory.
Be honest with me --
for the first time
since you've been back --
and this is yours.
Wait -- h-hold on.
There's one part
I don't understand.
You hit a dog
and stopped. Why?
That whole story,
and that's your takeaway?
Oh, I heard the rest.
You fell in love
with a unicorn.
It was beautiful, then sad,
then sadder.
I laughed, I cried,
I puked in my mouth a little.
And honestly,
I kind of get it.
Really?
We've got company.
Cass.
Cass, I don't know what the hell
is wrong with you,
but if you're in there
and you can hear me,
you don't
have to do this.
Cass!
This isn't right.
Do you realize
what that tablet can do for us?
I...
For heaven?
I won't hurt Dean.
Yes. You will.
You are.
Cass, fight this!
This is not you!
Fight it!
What have you done
to me?!
Just relax, Castiel.
Let your vessel do
what you know deep down
is the right thing.
What have you done to me,
Naomi?
Who's Naomi?!
What have I done to you?!
Do you have any idea
what it's like out there?
There's blood everywhere,
and it's on your hands.
After everything you did --
to us, to heaven.
I fixed you, Castiel.
I fixed you!
Cass!
I believe
they're playing my song.
You want it?
Take it!
But you're gonna
have to kill me first.
Come on, you coward.
Do it.
Do it!
Please.
End this, Castiel.
Cass...
This isn't you.
Bring me the tablet!
Ohh!
Cass.
I know you're in there.
I know you can hear me.
Cass...
It's me.
We're family.
We need you.
I need you.
You have to choose,
Castiel --
us or them.
Cass.
Aah!
Castiel!
Castiel!!
Cass?
No.
Cass. Cass!
I'm so sorry, Dean.
What the hell
just happened?
Love what you've done
with the place.
You really think all that
was gonna keep me out forever?
At least long enough
for Dean and Cass
to get the tablet
and get out.
Castiel.
So, that's who's been
poking my boys --
and not in a sexy way.
Got a bone to pick with you,
moose.
After what you did
to my poor dog.
You gonna talk us to death
or get down to it already?
There's my whore.
I'm not here
for my dearly departed, though.
I'm here for the stone
with the funny scribbles on it.
That's not gonna happen.
Love it
when you get all tough.
Touches me right where
my bathing suit goes.
Go.
Save your brother...
and my unicorn.
Timon and Pumbaa...
...tell you
their big plan?
Did they share
that little chestnut with you?
They mean to close
the Gates of Hell, sweetheart.
They mean to kill me
and all the demons --
you included.
You had me at "kill you,"
Crowley.
So, this "Naomi"
has been controlling you
since she got you
out of Purgatory?
Yeah.
Well, w-what broke
the connection?
I don't know.
I just know that I have to
protect this tablet now.
From Naomi?
Yes.
And from you.
From me?
What are you talking about?
Cass?
Cass!
Damn it.
Dean!
Dean.
Where's Cass?
He's gone.
Meg?
We got to go -- now.
I could beat on you
for eternity.
Take all the time
you want, you pig.
No Cass
in the back seat.
Your stone is long gone.
Aah!
Naomi.
Fancy meeting you here.
Haven't seen you
in a dark age.
Love the haircut.
How's the shoulder?
Just a flesh wound.
Now,
I don't have the tablet,
and if you're here,
neither do you.
Which means that your Castiel
is in the wind with our prize.
If I didn't know you better, I'd
say you're losing your touch.
Castiel isn't
in the wind.
He's doing exactly
what he's supposed to do --
protect the tablet.
Even from you?
Easy, love.
If you remember our time
in Mesopotamia the way I do,
you know I'm a lover,
not a fighter.
What do you want,
you cockroach?
Maybe we can make a deal
before this gets
truly bollocksed.
I mean, I must have something
that you want.
Tart stole my move.
So...what happened?
I mean,
Cass touched the tablet,
and it reset him to his
factory settings or something?
I don't know.
And I don't care.
All I know is that he is
off the reservation
with a-a heavenly WMD.
Listen, man, I can't take
any more lies -- from anyone.
Yeah.
Um...
I know.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you.
I-I...just wanted to believe
I was okay.
I don't know.
Well, you heard
what Cass said --
that that first trial hurt you in ways
that even he can't heal.
Sammy, I need you
to be honest with me
from here on out, man.
You're right.
And I will be.
Listen, I may not be able
to carry the burden
that comes along
with these trials...
But I can carry you.
You...realize
you kind of just quoted
"Lord of the Rings," right?
Come on, man. But it's
the Rudy Hobbit, all right?
Rudy Hobbit
always gets a pass.
Shut up.
? ...is the undisputed truth
? but I have to have things
my own way ?
? to keep me in my youth
? like a ship
without an anchor ?
? like a slave without a chain
? just the thought
of those sweet ladies ?
? sends a shiver
through my veins ?
? and I will go on shining
? shining like brand-new
? I'll never look behind me ?
? my troubles will be few
? goodbye, stranger,
it's been nice ?
? hope you find your paradise
? tried to see
your point of view ?
? hope your dreams
will all come true ?
? goodbye, Mary,
goodbye, Jane ?
? will we ever meet again?
? Feel no sorrow,
feel no shame ?
? come tomorrow,
feel no pain ?
? sweet devotion
? it's not for me ?
? just give me motion
? and set me free
? and land and the ocean
== sync, corrected by elderman ==