I'm about to close
the Gate of Hell forever.
? Carry on, my wayward son
? there'll be peace
when you are done ?
Ugh!
? Lay your weary head to rest
? Don't you cry no more
You were in Purgatory?
It felt pure.
I don't hunt anymore.
I found something.
Did you look for me?
Kevin Tran.
Thought you could
elude me forever?
God built a series of tests.
When you've done all three,
you can slam the Gates of Hell.
Where do we start?
Kill a hound of hell.
An innocent soul
has to be rescued from Hell
- and delivered unto heaven.
- And the final test?
To cure a Demon.
? Once, I rose above
the noise and confusion ?
Abaddon --
a knight of Hell.
She's gone.
My name is Naomi.
We rescued you.
? I was soaring ever higher
The Angel Tablet.
I won't hurt Dean.
Kill him.
We're family.
I have to protect
this tablet now.
These trials --
they're purifying me.
? I hear the voices
when I'm dreaming ?
Metatron?
I'm the scribe of God.
Heaven needs your help,
Castiel.
? Carry on, my wayward son
I'm killing everyone
you've ever saved.
Maybe we should just take
the deal.
The trials --
you'll give them up.
Kick it in the ass
like we always do.
Are you with me?
? ...no more
On the house, Sheriff.
Oh, thanks, Nance,
but I didn't order --
so...
Good luck.
...what are we drinking?
Roderick?
Wow, Jody.
Words cannot begin
to describe
the injustice that
that picture does to you.
Come on.
What?
Look at you.
The fancy career,
the suit.
I'm pretty much what I am --
small-town girl.
We do share something,
you and I.
What?
Loss.
My son and my husband.
How did you know?
I've lost someone, too.
It's not a date
till I've cried.
So now you've cried.
Oh, this is crazy.
This is crazy.
I'm crazy.
He's attractive, though,
right?
He's hot.
Manu mortis accesso,
spiritus vitae recedit.
You have less than one minute
before a very dear, attractive,
and slightly tipsy friend
of yours snuffs it.
Call it off, Crowley.
Because?
Because it's over,
you son of a bitch.
We want to deal.
30 seconds.
We stop the trials,
and you stop the killing.
I want the Demon Tablet --
the whole Demon Tablet.
Fine, but then the Angel Tablet
comes to us.
On what grounds?
On the grounds
that you're a douche bag
and no douche bag
should have that much power.
Deal or not?
First, I need to hear
two little words --
I surrender.
? Supernatural 8x23 ?
Sacrifice
Original Air Date on May 15, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
You hid the Demon Tablet
underneath the devil?
Seriously?
What? I was delirious.
You sure
this is gonna work?
What choice do we have?
All right, listen,
this is a secret lair.
You understand me?
No keggers.
I don't have any friends.
Yeah, well,
just lay low.
Who knows?
You'll be a mathlete again
before you know it.
You guys?
You're doing
the right thing.
What was he like?
Who?
Oh. God?
Mm, pretty much
like you'd expect.
Larger-than-life, gruff,
bit of a sexist.
But fair --
eminently fair.
The Nephilim was a monster,
Castiel.
And the next trial?
Across the street.
His name
is Dwight Charles.
I've been listening in
on the Angel radio.
Cupid frequency,
actually.
And he is the next
on their list.
Their list?
To do
the horizontal mambo.
Slap bellies.
To find love.
Oh. Yes.
Well, that.
He's slotted to be dinged by
Cupid's arrow within 24 hours,
which is good for us,
because the second trial
is retrieving
Cupid's bow.
No killing?
No killing.
Hello, boys.
What's
that old expression?
Success has many fathers.
Failure is a Winchester.
Where's the stone?
You show us yours,
and we'll show you ours.
Really, Dean?
I'm trying to conduct
a professional negotiation here,
and you want to talk
dangly bits?
The stone.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slowly.
There she is.
And the contract?
Yeah, I'm sure there's
no hidden agendas in there.
The highlights --
we swap tablets,
you stand down
from the trials forever.
You stop killing
everyone we've ever saved.
Agreed.
Unh-unh-unh.
Nice try, squirrel.
Moose is doing
these trials.
Moose signs.
No, no, no.
He's not signing anything
until I read the fine print.
I can read it.
Hey, you wanted me here.
I'm here.
But I'll be damned if I'm gonna
let him screw us even more.
What's this?
Trouble in paradise,
boys?
What is it, Nathaniel?
One of our freelancers
has reached out to us.
He's found Castiel.
Where?
A drinking establishment
in Houston, Texas.
And...
What?
He says
Castiel was not alone.
Who was he with?
By the description,
I-I think it was him --
the scribe.
You're gonna move
your lips
the whole way up here,
aren't you?
You know
why I always defeat you?
It's your humanity.
It's a built-in handicap.
You always put emotion
ahead of good, old-fashioned
common sense.
Let's have the big galoot
sign it now, shall we?
Is this a joke?
You realize
all I have to do is...
Unh-unh-unh.
Demonic handcuffs,
jackass.
No flicking, no teleporting,
no smoking out --
oh, and...
no deal.
Which pretty much means
that you're our bitch.
Fine.
You want to play chain gang?
Let's.
You saddled yourself
to the wrong bull, mate.
I can do this all day,
'cause you know what?
Damn, it feels good!
But sooner or later,
you're gonna have to face it --
you're ours.
Which means
that your demon ass
is going to be a mortal ass
pretty damn quick.
What's
he mouthing on about?
You're the third trial,
Crowley.
What are you reading?
Personal advertisements.
The faster that man finds love,
the faster the Cupid will come.
Trust me.
I'm friends with friends
who do this for a living.
Help you gents?
Yes.
Would you say
that you're looking for, uh,
a partner in crime...
...or, uh, someone
who's into nurse role-play
and light domination?
Brother,
it's 10:00 a.m. on a Tuesday.
Uh, we'll have two drafts,
please.
Coming up.
You're not the most subtle tool
in the shed, are you?
Kill him.
Next one won't wing you.
Take it someplace else.
Let him go.
Haven't you caused enough harm
already, Castiel?
Stop. Please, Castiel,
don't make this any worse.
Please.
You really think
this is gonna hold me,
that you're gonna cure me
or whatever it is?
He's primed.
How you feeling?
Honestly, for the first time
in a long time,
it feels like
we're gonna win.
I'm good.
All right, well,
no dancing in the end zone
until we're finished.
What's the good father's
playbook say now?
Well...
Now that we got
the consecrated ground,
I just, uh
I slip Crowley one dose of blood
every hour for eight hours
and seal the deal
with a bloody-fist sandwich.
That should do it.
Your blood's supposed to be
purified, isn't it?
You ever, uh -- you ever done
the "forgive me, father" before?
Well, once,
when we were kids.
Which is why I have no clue
what to say now.
Well, I mean, I could give you
suggestions if you want.
O-okay. Yeah, sure.
All right.
Well,
I'm just spit-balling here,
but if I were you, uh...
Ruby, killing Lilith,
letting Lucifer out,
losing your soul,
not looking for me when I went
to Purgatory,
Thanks.
for starters.
Or, hey, h-how about what
you did to, uh, Penny Markle
in the sixth grade?
Why don't you lead
with that?
Well, that was you.
Carry on.
Okay, um...
...if anybody's listening,
here goes.
Dean,
I need your help.
Little busy, Cass.
Take a number.
I'm afraid
this can't wait.
Naomi
has taken Metatron.
And you know Metatron how?
I've been working with him
on the Angel trials.
The what?
We're gonna shut it all down --
Heaven, Hell,
all of it.
I know you.
We've never
officially met.
Naomi.
Your reputation precedes you.
The Archangels --
wanted me to debrief you
after God left.
"Debrief" me.
Is that what you call it?
Well,
how would you know?
You ran
before I had the chance.
But...here we are.
I just have one question
before we begin.
You had to know that we would
leap at the chance
to extract all of God's secrets
from that head of yours,
which is why
I ask myself...Why?
Why did the scribe suddenly
come in from the shadows?
And what are you doing
with Castiel?
"Of the blessings
set before you,
make your choice
and be content."
Not a big reader,
are we?
Metatron, the guy
who was full-on crazy,
cat-lady-hoarder
angel yesterday --
now he wants
to save Heaven?
Yes, he wants to.
But I'm the only one
who can.
I can't fail, Dean,
not on this one.
I need your help.
Look, Cass,
that's all well and good, okay,
but you're asking me
to leave Sam,
and we've got Crowley in there
tied and tressed.
Now,
if anybody needs a chaperone
while doing
the heavy lifting, it's Sam.
You should go.
Seriously.
Oh, what, and leave you here
with the King of Hell?
Come on.
I got this.
And if you guys can lock
the angels up, too...
That's a good day.
Look, I...
I'm down with sending the angels
back to Heaven,
just 'cause they're dicks.
But the Demons?
This is on us.
Start the injections now.
If I'm not back in eight hours,
finish it,
no questions,
no hesitation.
Yeah.
You really think injecting me
with human blood
is gonna make me human?
Did you read that
on the back of a cereal box?
Aah!
You're miles out of your league,
moose.
See you in an hour.
Is this a joke?
No.
It's the word of God.
What?
It's a tablet.
All right, translate.
That's what you do.
Okay.
Um,
it's the Angel Tablet,
which I've never laid eyes on
in my life.
You want a translation
in like six hours
when it took me six months
and a dead mom
to translate
a piece of the Demon Tablet?
And according to your own words
this morning...
...this is not what I do.
It's what I did.
You told me I was out,
Dean.
Yeah, well --
and if this is gonna be
the "guys like us are never out"
speech, save it.
Dean's right.
Cass!
There is no out.
Only duty.
Get the hell off me.
You are a Prophet of the Lord,
always and forever...
...until the day
you cease to exist,
and then another Prophet
takes your place.
Now, are you clear
as to the task before you?
Then do it, and let's go.
Aah!
What the hell,
Crowley?
Biting?! Seriously?!
Inferni sectatores,
nunc audite regem.
For the love of everything,
whoever is hearing this --
if anyone is hearing this --
this is your king.
Send help immediately.
Anything?
You've been gone long enough.
No.
There was one female,
but...
What?
...I don't think
she was female.
Anything here?
Free drinks.
Your, uh, buddy over there
thinks you saved his life.
Do you really think it's wise
to be drinking on the job?
What show
you been watching?
Talk to me.
Are you sure about this?
I mean, it's one thing
me and Sammy
slamming the gates to the pit,
but you -- you're --
you're boarding up Heaven,
and you're locking
the door behind you.
Yeah. I know.
You did a lot of damage
up there, man.
You think they're just gonna
let that slide?
Do you mean
do I think they'll kill me?
Yeah, they might.
So this is it?
E.T. goes home.
Hey, there.
Where's Ed?
Flu. I'm Gail.
Well, okay, then.
Showtime.
Let me give you
a hand.
Oh, thanks.
Ah.
You're a real gentleman.
Hey.
Holy crud, this is like
the first five minutes
of every porno
I've ever seen.
Thanks.
Gail, Rod.
Ma'am.
Rod rides a stool here
most days.
I'll be seeing you both.
Thanks for the help.
No problem.
Damn, that's sweet.
? Oh,
it's so nice to be with you ?
? I love all the things
you say and do ?
How about
the next one's on me?
? And it's so nice
to hear you say ?
? you're gonna please me
in every way ?
How we doing, Moose?
Ain't it about time
for the next love injection?
? Ch-ch-ch-ch-changes
? turn and face the strange
? ch-ch-changes
? just gonna have to be
a different man ?
? time may change me,
but I can't trace -- ?
Did you really think you could
kidnap the King of Hell
and no one was gonna notice,
dumb nuts?!
Hello, boys.
That's my line.
Abaddon?
They told me
you were dead.
So not.
And the rest
of the cavalry?
Oh, no, it's just
little, old, unkillable me.
Brilliant.
Why send in a few grunts
when you can send in a knight?
Say your prayers,
Moose.
That'll do.
Undo these.
I'll kill him myself.
That was an order,
was it?
I am your King.
About that...
Hello, brother.
Give us your bow.
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
Talk first, stab later.
Do you know what I find
the most shocking
about time-traveling
through a closet
and landing
in the year 2013?
Aah!
Somebody thought
it was a good idea
to make you
the King of Hell.
You know what that boy's
trying to do, right?
He's trying
to shut the Gates of Hell.
Right now you and I are gonna
talk about regime change.
You little whore.
I am your k--
I love the suit.
Aah! Aah!
Aaaah!!
I've been afraid to go home
for some time now.
Orders used to come once a day,
and now it's chaos.
It all seems to be
breaking down.
And you think
you can fix that?
With time, yes.
Take it, then.
You've been digging.
Why are you doing this --
this?
Do you have any idea
what it would be like
to be plucked from obscurity,
to sit at God's feet,
to be asked
to write down his word?
The ache I felt
when he was gone,
telling myself,
"Father's left,
but look what he's left us --
paradise."
But you and your Archangels
couldn't leave well enough
alone.
You ran me from my home.
Did you really think
you could do all of that to me
and there'd be
no payback?
Ahh.
You did good back there,
Moose.
I'll deny it if you ever
quote me, but I'm a proud man.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks.
Hold on.
Uh, w-what's that?
It's what it looks like.
Are you joking?
I just saved your life.
Seriously?
Me, seriously?
We just shared a foxhole,
you and I.
We beat back
the Tet offensive,
outrun the --
the rape of Nanking together!
And still you're gonna do me
like this?!
Aah!
"Band of Brothers"?
"The Pacific"?
None of this
means anything to you?
All those motels, you never once
watched HBO, not once?
"Girls"?
You're my Marnie, Moose.
A-and Hannah -- she just --
she needs to be loved.
She deserves it.
Don't we all -- you, me --
we deserve to be loved.
I deserve to be loved!
I just want to be loved.
What?
Would it be possible,
Moose...
...I'd like...
to ask you
a-a favor, Sam.
Earlier, when you
were confessing back there...
...what did you say?
I only ask because,
given my history...
...it raises the question...
Where do I start...
...to even look for forgiveness?
I mean...
How about we start
with this?
I think I found
the Angel trials,
but I don't see anything
about a Nephilim
or a Cupid's bow
or anything like that.
Oh, come on, Kev!
We're
on the one-yard line here.
Okay, a-and I should have
mentioned this six months ago,
but the sports metaphors --
y-you want to motivate me,
"Magic" cards,
"Skyrim," Aziz Ansari.
I'm not here to fight you,
Castiel.
Dean?
Not anymore.
Where is Metatron?
He told you he was going to fix
Heaven, didn't he?
Murdering a Nephilim,
cutting off a Cupid's bow --
it's a lie, all of it.
I've been in his head.
You've been
in all our heads.
That's the problem.
No, Castiel, you're wrong.
This is what you do.
You twist things.
I'm trying to fix Heaven.
Metatron is trying
to fix Heaven.
Metatron isn't trying
to fix anything.
He's trying to break it --
an act of revenge
for driving him away.
Break it how?
Dean.
Expel all Angels from Heaven,
just as God cast out Lucifer.
Cast you out to where?
Hell?
Here.
Thousands of us,
walking the Earth.
Lies.
Wait!
Our mission was to protect
what God created.
I don't know
when we forgot that.
I want nothing more than to see
you shut the Gates of Hell,
but I told you
that you could trust me.
If Sam completes those trials,
he is going to die.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I saw it
in Metatron's head.
It was always God's intention --
the ultimate sacrifice.
As for you, Castiel,
I beg of you, stop this path.
Metatron
has been neutralized.
If you want back in,
truly, I will listen.
Hey, right now, talk to me.
Is she lying?
I don't know.
Well, find out!
She's lying.
Take me to him.
Dean --
take me to him now!
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus,
hanc animam redintegra,
lustra.
Dean, I'm not wrong.
I'm going to fix my home.
Cass!
Sammy, stop!
She told you I lied,
didn't she?
You should've listened
to the bitch.
Easy there. Okay.
Just take it easy.
We got a slight change of plan.
What?
What's going on?
Where's Cass?!
Metatron lied.
You finish this trial,
you're dead, Sam.
So?
You promised.
Shh!
Castiel, I want you to stop
thinking about master plans,
Heaven and Angels,
and all this.
That doesn't concern you
anymore.
These were never trials,
Castiel.
This is a spell.
And what I'm taking
from you now --
your essence, your Grace --
is the last piece.
And now something wonderful
is going to happen,
for me and for you.
I want you to live this new life
to the fullest.
Find a wife.
Make babies.
And when you die
and your soul comes to Heaven,
find me.
Tell me your story.
Hmm?
Now go.
Look at him.
Look at him!
Look how close we are!
Other people will die
if I don't finish this!
Think about it.
Think about
what we know, huh?
Pulling souls from hell,
curing demons,
hell,
ganking a Hellhound!
We have enough knowledge on
our side to turn the tide here.
But I can't do it
without you.
You can barely do it
with me.
I mean, you think I screw up
everything I try.
You think I need a chaperone,
remember?
Come on, man.
That's not what I meant.
No, it's exactly
what you meant.
You want to know
what I confessed in there?
What my greatest sin was?
It was how many times
I let you down.
I can't do that again.
Sam --
What happens when you've decided
I can't be trusted again?
I mean, who are you gonna
turn to next time instead of me?
Another angel, another --
another vampire?
Do you have any idea
what it feels like
to watch your brother just --
Hold on, hold on!
You seriously think that?
Because none of it --
none of it -- is true.
Listen, man, I know we've had
our disagreements, okay?
Hell, I know I've said some junk
that set you back on your heels.
But, Sammy...come on.
I killed Benny
to save you.
I'm willing
to let this bastard
and all the sons of bitches that
killed mom walk because of you.
Don't you dare think that there
is anything, past or present,
that I would put
in front of you!
It has never been like that,
ever!
I need you to see that.
I'm begging you.
How do I stop?
Just let it go.
I can't.
It's in me, Dean.
You don't know
what this feels like.
Hey, listen,
we will figure it out, okay,
just like we always do.
Come on.
Come on. Let it go, okay?
Let it go, brother.
Hey, Dean.
See?
Aah!
Sam?
I got you, little brother.
You're gonna be just fine.
Sam, Sam?
Cass?!
Castiel?!
Where the hell are you?
Sammy!
No, Cass.
What's happening?
Angels.
They're falling.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==