OLDER TED: This is the story
of two blind dates. One in 2009,
and one seven years earlier.
In all that time, my dating routine
remained more or less the same.
Until the fall of 2009,
when I finally had a date that was different
because it was exactly the same.
I was on a blind date
with the same woman
I went on a blind date with
seven years earlier.
- Ted?
- Jen?
It's nice to meet you.
OLDER TED: And she didn't remember it.
But then again...
It's nice to meet you, too.
OLDER TED: ... neither did I.
- Do you want to?
- Yeah.
Guess who just got four tickets to the
Origins of Chewbacca Star Wars exhibit?
- Why?
- No, I said, "Guess who?"
I heard you.
Yeah, isn't it a little early
in our relationship
to do something
that would end our relationship?
What? No, what are you talking about?
It can be our first double date as couples!
And plus, it sounds awesome!
Is the original Chewbacca
going to be there?
Peter Mayhew, in the fur. Who's with me?
Hey, do you think they'll have
Wookiee-to-English dictionaries there?
I mean, even just an everyday phrase book
would be helpful.
We're not going to the
Origins of Chewbacca exhibit, Marshall.
It's in Houston this year.
Everyone knows that.
I just wanted to get rid of the girls.
Where are you taking me, Barney?
OLDER TED: This wasn't the first time your
Uncle Barney had kidnapped one of us.
Wait a second. The Origins of Chewbacca
exhibit's in Montreal this year.
Everyone knows that.
Where are you taking me?
My guy in the DA's office scored us
front row seats to a lethal injection.
But we're still stopping
for chili dogs first.
Stop the cab.
Where are you taking me?
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Barney, why are we here?
Marshall, now that Robin
and I are together,
I've learned a lot about relationships
by watching you and Lily.
- Thanks, man.
- You're a terrible couple.
Lily has taken all the man out of you.
I used to think
that's just every relationship.
But what I've got with Robin proves
that you can have a girlfriend
and fully functioning male genitalia
all at the same time.
Okay, right.
So, if Robin knew that you were here,
she would be completely fine with it?
Are you kidding? She'd sprint down here
with a purse full of singles
and a poncho for the 10:30 Jell-O show.
B t dub, I called ahead, it's lime.
OLDER TED: Meanwhile, Jen and I were in
my favorite first date restaurant
for the second time.
- So, Jen, what do you do?
- I'm between jobs. Banking crisis.
I'm between jobs. Internet bubble burst.
Makes me realize I should go into
something more stable, like banking.
- So, what about you?
- I'm an architect.
Hopefully, one day,
I can use my own humble brush
on the masterpiece that is
Manhattan's skyline.
I teach architecture.
Get 50% off at the bookstore,
so that's pretty sweet.
Married!
What is wrong with you?
You're just looking.
It's like fantasizing about other women.
It's harmless. Wait.
Don't tell me you don't fantasize
about other women.
I do!
- It's just not that easy.
- False.
I once fantasized about that silhouette
chick you see on a truck's mud flaps.
Took me less than a mile.
Not everyone is you, okay, Barney?
Even when I do start to have
a dirty thought like that,
it seems so much like cheating on Lily,
that I feel guilty.
So, first,
I need to have a different fantasy.
(HICCUPS)
Bad news.
Lily has a rare and fatal hiccup disorder
that's apparently medically legitimate.
What? How could this be?
Beats me, but it says it right here
on this doctor clipboard that doctors have.
(HICCUPS)
(CRYING SOFTLY)
It's time, baby.
(CRYING) I will never love again.
No, Marshall, you must.
And after an appropriate number of years,
you should find someone else,
someone like that busty delivery girl
from that one time,
and plow her like a cornfield.
(HICCUPS RAPIDLY)
(MARSHALL MOANING)
And so, Marshall,
to honor Lily, you must find
that busty delivery girl from that one time
and plow her like a cornfield.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
(CLEARING THROAT)
Delivery for Marshall Eriksen.
This one's for you, Lil.
Where do I sign?
And then watch out, because it is on!
That is the saddest thing I've ever heard.
Dude, Lily gets you in real life.
- She has no business in your fantasies.
- It's all I know, okay?
- I can't help it.
- I accept your invitation. Marshall Eriksen,
from this day forward,
I will be the wingman of your mind.
Now, focus on the next dancer.
Put Lily completely out of your mind.
ANNOUNCER: Gentlemen,
say hello to (STAMMERING) Jasmine.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Barney?
Is it just me or does that stripper
look exactly like...
Ted, we found a stripper who looks
exactly like Lily!
- Uh, yeah, I can't talk right now.
- I'm speechless, too.
Everything's as perky
as we've always imagined!
Stop looking at her.
Look, I gotta go.
(WHISPERING) Take a picture.
Oh, I will.
But first, I'm going to make Marshall
watch as I wedge Ulysses S. Grant
- between his wife's tatas.
- I'll kill you!
(BARNEY YELLING)
- Sorry about that.
- So, any thoughts on food?
Yeah, do you wanna share the oysters?
I would love to share the oysters.
Good. 'Cause if you didn't,
that would be mighty shellfish.
Wow, that's bad.
That's why it's funny!
- We've been on this date before.
We've been
on this exact blind date before.
In this exact same restaurant.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but I
don't remember that date going that well.
Me, neither.
I remember thinking
that you were a little snobby.
Wait, you dress your cats up
in weird costumes.
They're not weird.
See, you're being snobby again.
Oh, my God.
Do you realize what this means?
Since our first date,
we've done a complete lap
of all the single people in New York
only to end up back here, with each other.
Whoa.
We're going to die alone, aren't we?
Well, you've got your cats.
This is insane.
Wait, I gotta ask.
Why did you think I was snobby?
Wait, okay, yeah,
we were sitting over there.
(TED LAUGHING)
"Main Lobster."
They spelled Maine without the "e."
Good to know we're not getting
the crappy understudy lobsters, right?
Tonight, the role of pound-and-a-half
lobster will be played by...
I get it, Ted.
Pointing out spelling errors in a menu
makes you seem kind of snooty.
Huh.
I had no idea.
Okay, well, what about me?
Aside from the cats,
how did I come across?
That's right, the check.
The check came and, of course,
I was going to pay,
but you didn't do the check dance.
Guys want to wave the girl off
and, you know, look like a big shot.
Huh.
I had no idea.
This is good. We're learning stuff.
You know what we should do?
We should retrace the rest of that night
and figure out what else
we do wrong on first dates.
'Cause let's be honest.
We are scaring people off, Jen.
- We really are. Okay, I'm in.
- Great.
Where'd we go next?
- I think we went to MacLaren's.
- Okay.
Hey, I didn't really talk about
my cats that much, did I?
And then, there's Tabby-Gail Adams,
the jester of the group.
Tone down the kitty talk. Check.
You will not believe who we saw tonight.
- Dude...
- We saw the third doppelganger!
(GASPING)
OLDER TED: I should explain. Over
the years, we had spotted two strangers
who looked exactly
like members of our group.
(ALL CHATTERING)
Hey, hey, hey!
OLDER TED: Lesbian Robin.
(SPITTING)
(LILY LAUGHING)
OLDER TED: And Mustache Marshall.
By the following summer, we would find
the remaining two doppelgangers,
but I'll get to that.
Ladies, meet Stripper Lily.
Oh!
- Okay.
- Yeah, I couldn't get her face in it,
but she looks just like you.
- So you went to a strip club?
- (CHUCKLING) Busted.
And there was a stripper
who looked exactly like me?
Okay, babe, look, before you get mad,
let me...
Awesome!
I bet the guys were going crazy.
I bet they wanted to touch her so bad,
but all you can do is look,
unless you go into the back room,
but, honey, you gotta pay for that.
So, strip club.
(VOICE SHAKING) Marshall made me go.
All right, so what did I do wrong next?
Let me have it. I'm here to learn.
Well, I kept dropping hints that I was cold,
but you didn't offer me your jacket.
- It's a little brisk out tonight, huh?
- Not really.
Really? I can't feel my fingers.
I'm pretty impervious to stuff like that.
I couldn't admit I was cold.
I didn't want to seem like a wimp
compared to your action hero ex-boyfriend
who you wouldn't stop talking about.
After a day of fighting fires,
Jim would love to come home
and unwind working on his '68 Camaro.
That or bare-knuckle boxing,
which he learned in the Marine Corps.
I had an aunt in the Coast Guard.
Okay, so no talking about the ex.
Not even about his shockingly
small wiener?
See? Why didn't you lead off with that?
(JEN LAUGHING)
Was there a shower on stage?
Sometimes there's a shower on stage.
I bet stripper me would get in there
with another girl and just go bananas.
See, Marshall?
We got to have a bros' night at a strip club
and both of our ladies
are totally cool with it.
I'm not cool with it.
Because they understand that it's healthy
for us to do that from time to time.
- It's disgusting.
- Because it's harmless.
Did one of your whores tell you that?
And, Lil, Marshall shouldn't have
to go to so much trouble
just to have an innocent fantasy.
- Trouble? What trouble?
- It's... No, it's nothing.
- Marshall, tell her. We're all friends here.
- (LAUGHING) No, we're not.
Lily, sometimes I think
about other women. Okay, it happens.
But even when I do, I feel so guilty
that I...
I have to imagine you passing away first
because even in a fantasy world,
I could never cheat on you.
You're just my life, baby, and I love you.
You kill me off?
I mean,
fantasize about other girls all you want,
but could you maybe not murder me?
Murder? No! I... Baby, no.
You develop a chronic illness!
I spare no expense for your care!
I even set up a foundation in your name.
We're, like, this close to a cure.
- Remember?
- Oh, yeah! I do remember.
We went in here for a drink
with your friends, who I loved.
Or hated, depending on whether
you're still friends with them.
- You love them.
- They're family, Ted.
Let's go in and see what they remember.
And they are my best friends,
so don't be surprised if they suddenly
can't think of anything I do wrong.
Did he juggle? Bad puns?
Expect a standing ovation
for picking up a $19 check?
Let's not forget the menu typo gold mine.
Keep panning that river, buddy.
Well, it is a lot cheaper
than buying a condom.
(EX CLAIMS)
Actually, you know what it was?
I remember him coming across
as kind of a player.
- Me?
- ALL: Ted?
Yeah. We were all sitting over there.
And here's a picture of my cats
dressed up like Batman villains.
You got the Joker, the Riddler,
Mr. Freeze...
Well, what about Catwoman?
Yeah, that would've been good.
Psst. Ted.
Nice.
Wait, wait, wait, no, no, no!
I remember that.
I was not checking out a girl.
Psst. Ted.
(MAN CHATTERING)
Nice.
We were checking out
Mustache Marshall.
ALL: Oh!
Gosh, I thought you were such a jerk.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, well, it's nice to know "past me"
wasn't a total jackass, huh?
"Present you" isn't so bad, either.
- Thank you very much. Yes.
- You got it?
Oh, yeah! I remember this.
And there's the Chrysler Building.
And the Empire State Building.
And at twelve o' clock, a rotund couple
going at it against the glass.
Oh!
That's kind of sweet.
Oh, look, snack break.
Good for them.
Letting a guy eat pizza off your back,
that's love.
(JEN GIGGLING)
So, I know this wasn't
the best first date of all time,
but I'm glad we stuck it out.
Me, too.
That was really great. What went wrong?
I remember now.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
So, would you maybe
want to go out again?
Yeah, I... I would.
- Will you call me?
- Absolutely.
- Promise?
- Promise.
I have been so busy.
Good night, Ted.
(CAT MEOWING OPERA)
- Hello?
- Jen, I'm sorry.
Look, I know I'm seven years late
with this call,
but I was an idiot back then.
You saw the goatee.
The truth is, I had a great time tonight,
and I'd love to see you again.
Ted, there are two kinds of guys.
The guys that you want to call you,
who don't,
and the guys you don't want to call you,
who always do.
And somehow, right now, you're both.
Baby, you should be able to fantasize
about another woman
without feeling guilty, or, you know,
killing me off.
I wish that I could,
but I've been doing this for so long,
I'm all confused about death and sex.
It's gotten to the point
where every time I drive past a cemetery,
I'm sporting a partial.
All right, we gotta fix this.
Okay, when Stripper Lily gets out here,
you have my permission
to fantasize about her.
And since she's basically me,
maybe you won't feel guilty.
Thanks, baby. I'm so lucky to have you.
And stripper you.
Bring out Stripper Lily!
You know, I don't come here that much.
Hey, Barney. Here's the usual
and I'll send over the other usual
as soon as she's done stretching.
Thank you, kindly stranger.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen...
Oh! Hey, Barney. I didn't see you come in.
I'll load up some AC/DC for you, buddy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please put your hands together
for (STAMMERING) Jasmine.
(CROWD CHEERING)
- I am hot!
- Yeah.
Crawl for it, stripper me.
This is awesome, baby.
- Can I get another $100?
- That was $100?
Wow, she crawls fast.
Look, Jen, I wish I could go back
and talk some sense into 2002 Ted,
but that guy's a lost cause.
He's 24. He thinks a little facial hair
makes him look like Johnny Depp.
And he has no idea what a great girl
he's missing out on.
But I've learned a lot since then.
I've learned a lot tonight.
The only thing that we've learned is that
seven years ago,
it was a mistake for us to go out.
And I guess it was a mistake
for us to go out tonight.
No, it wasn't.
I had a great time tonight.
And seven years ago,
if you think about it,
we didn't miss by that much.
I mean, if a couple of things
had gone a little bit differently,
who knows what would have happened?
(REWIND PLAYING)
(SINGING) Asking you to stay
The words are finally here
Let's rewind and rewind
You see, you're the only star
in the film I never made
Would you rewind it all the time
Rewind it all the time
- Wow.
You are the best, you are the best.
My girlfriend is at a strip club with me
and she couldn't care less.
I do care, Barney.
Look, we're dating now, okay?
That changes things.
We need to have a serious talk about this.
- Just the best.
- Hey, girlfriend trouble?
I wish I could help,
but my unbelievably cool wife
just bought us a private dance
with her stripper body double.
So, if you need me, I'll be getting grinded
like some pepper in the champagne room.
Just the best.
(SIGHS)
Now what?
I just remembered why I didn't call you.
Why?
(SIGHING) I can't believe
I'm gonna screw this up again.
- But I like finding typos in menus.
- What?
And I know my shellfish pun is stupid,
but the truth is,
I'm not suddenly gonna stop
making stupid jokes.
Now that you mention it,
I'm never going to stop talking
about my cats.
They're funny and adorable and totally
worth having to take six Benadryl a day.
(TED LAUGHS)
Shouldn't we hold out for the person
who doesn't just tolerate our little quirks,
but actually kind of likes them?
Even if it means finding ourselves
on another blind date with each other
- seven years from now?
- Oh, dear God, I hope that doesn't happen.
Well, good luck out there, Jen.
You, too, Ted.
You'll find your shellfish lady.
OLDER TED: And kids, when I told
your mother that shellfish joke,
she did laugh.
And I swear, it was only, like, 30% pity.
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, Lil. Looks like Jasmine's having
a hard time getting out of those boots.
(IN FOREIGN ACCENT)
What did you say, buddy?
- Lily?
- Who?
Oh, yes, I am this Lily.
We married long time.
May I have monies for shopping?
(LILY SCREAMING)
Lily!
ENGLISH - US - SDH