Previously on "Dexter"...
You still don't remember
anything from before?
You know, before we took you in?
- No.
What are you doing?
I'd like to talk you through
a deep relaxation technique.
It might bring some
things to the surface.
Mama!
It was a match.
Joe Driscoll was your bio-dad.
And this is Rudy.
- Dexter.
- Hey.
I have waited a long
time to meet you.
Why the different
nail polishes?
What the hell's
this guy thinking?
And the real king
is still out there.
Hungry.
Ready.
He'll kill again.
It's just a matter of time.
Dex, Rudy's different.
I feel safe with him.
I think --
I'm falling for him.
Divorce papers.
Sign them now,
and I'll agree to supervised
visits twice a week.
You think you can really
make me back down?
Are you fucking my wife?
The kids are already
settled at Colleen's.
You can have your
visit when we get back.
I just wish he'd go away.
I mean, why can't he just go
away and disappear forever?
No!
Fucking whore!
Come on, buckaroos.
It's Monday.
Can't be late Monday.
Throws the whole week off.
What about breakfast?
Made and eaten.
- And the kids' lunches?
- Packed and ready to go.
Did you tell the locksmith?
Yeah, new locks
on every door,
reinforced strike plates,
seven-pin keyways.
Here you go, buddy.
Why don't you kids
go wait in my car?
I want to talk to
your mom for a sec.
Are you gonna make out?
None of your business.
- Are you?
- Astor.
Rita, you don't have
to do this, you know.
Getting attacked by your
ex-husband merits a day off.
I'm fine.
I'm not gonna let Paul
control my life anymore.
Those days are over.
It's gonna be okay.
The police have been notified.
They'll find him.
What if they don't?
I got you some
pepper spray.
Just aim for the eyes.
Hey, you want some?
It's Kirk Bliloc's cake.
I had some at
Kirk's birthday,
10 days ago.
See, you have lunch every
day with your boyfriend,
you miss a thing or
two around here.
Cake's still good.
It's mocha, I think.
It started out vanilla.
Guys, you should look at this.
Put that thing down,
for God's sake.
It was addressed to Homicide.
Put it down!
Jesus, is that blood?
Morgan, get your
ass over here.
Ass en route.
You're the blood expert.
What is this shit?
It's a little watery for jam.
Maybe you should open it.
What if there's an airborne toxin
in here waiting to be released?
I got to wash my hands.
So gullible.
What is it?
Well, it's definitely blood.
Wait, there's
something in here.
Marina View hotel.
It's a key.
May be some sort of
promotional gag.
You know, stay the weekend,
you get a jar of blood.
Show-and-tell's over.
Let's try and find
out who sent this.
Grab Batista and get
over to that hotel.
Batista's still working on the
explosion at the smack lab.
Morgan, put the cake down.
You're with me.
A jar of blood --
Dramatic, cryptic, playful.
Could it be him?
Got an extra key
from the manager.
Said the same thing as
the front-desk clerk.
The guy who checked into 103
was white and normal looking.
I haven't seen a single security
camera since we've been here.
It's likely this
guy scouted hotels
and chose one
with lax security.
Better be ready to
cancel your lunch.
Police. Open up.
Oh, my God. Jesus.
Get back in your room.
Metro dispatch, this is 3-Henry-8-8
out at the Marina View hotel.
I need uniformed
backup, forensics.
Fuck it.
Just send everybody out.
It's been a while since
we went prophylactic.
Not me.
Last night, I met this chick --
I'll stop you
right there, Vince.
So, they tell you anything
about what's inside?
No one's been inside.
Too much blood.
Dexter.
Just a heads-up --
It's bad in there.
Okay.
- I'm serious.
- Okay.
She's not kidding.
It's your wet dream in there.
Okay.
You're going in first alone.
Get a sense of what
we're dealing with
and give me a report.
Don't fuck up.
Now I'm really curious.
He's been
gone so long,
he had to be planning
a splashy return,
but a crime scene just for me?
Mommy!
Tell me you found
something, Morgan.
I talked to the
guests in room 105.
They didn't see
anyone go in or out.
What about across the hall?
German tourists.
They got their head up their lederhosen.
They said they heard
a whirring sound
but thought someone
was mixing margaritas
or vacuuming.
Oh, my god!
Hey.
Hey, you okay?
I'm just a little queasy.
I fell down in there.
Never should have
skipped breakfast.
Bullshit. You're shaking.
What the hell happened up there?
No, I'm okay.
I just need a little air.
Something finally got to you.
I guess you're
human after all.
Cut him some slack, all right?
I hate to disappoint you,
I think it's just low blood sugar.
Tell us what you saw, Dex.
How many dead?
A lot.
But no bodies,
just blood --
50, 60 liters.
Maybe half a dozen dead.
I don't know.
You're saying there was
a mass murder in there,
- but they took the bodies?
- How is that possible?
There's one elevator,
emergency stairs with alarms.
Someone would have seen
corpses coming out.
I don't fucking know.
Hey, Dexter,
you all right?
- I can't go back in there.
- You don't have to.
Fine.
Just get yourself
cleaned up and --
I don't know --
Work from the hallway or something.
You're in room 422.
Elevators are
to your right,
and Bobby will
see to your bags.
Dade county
sheriff's department.
I'm looking for
Rita Bennett.
That's me.
Did you find Paul?
- I'm sorry?
- Paul Bennett.
My ex-husband attacked
me last night.
My boyfriend filed
a police report.
The only report we have is the
one that Mr. Bennett filed.
What?
Wait.
Paul filed a police report?
For what?
Assault. Your ex-husband
was just released
from Baptist
Memorial hospital.
He's pressing
charges against you.
He attacked me!
Not according to him.
All right. Can we talk
about this later?
We need a formal statement.
You're gonna have to come with
us right now to the station.
Fine.
Hey, make sure you label
the section of the grid
each blood sample
came from. All right?
Sweet.
You should really
get in here, Dex.
I never seen
anything like this.
Wait till you've seen a few
more Columbian drug busts.
Dude, I got misting
up the walls,
across the ceiling,
but no tissue.
Come see.
Photos, Vince.
Hey, and how come the
blood's not clotting?
The blood's not clotting?
No.
Genuine medical mystery.
Just keep getting samples.
I'll test it at the lab.
Hello?
Don't hang up.
Dexter, I'm at the
sheriff's station.
Paul's pressing assault
charges against me.
How's it even possible?
I was defending myself.
Just stay calm.
I know a lawyer.
I'll straighten it out.
I am calm.
They're the hysterical ones.
They're charging me
with a class-2 felony.
Hello, Dexter?
Are you there?
Yeah, I'm right here.
This is ridiculous.
I could lose my job.
I could lose my kids.
I won't let that happen.
Well, I'm glad
you're so confident.
Rita, just trust me.
I know how the
system works.
Look, I'm at a crime scene right now,
and I have to go,
but I'll talk to my
lawyer friend right away.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm okay.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, bye.
Is there a wall socket in there?
Check it out.
- What? A wall socket?
- Yeah.
Of course there's a wall socket.
There's lots of wall --
Hey, you're right.
There was something
plugged in here --
probably a power
tool to cut them up.
Come take a look.
Photos, Vince.
Lots and lots of photos.
Open Sesame.
Blood samples for the fridge.
And you better make room.
There's a lot more coming.
Shooters at the Bel Canto
tonight. You in?
I'm not in the mood.
Angel,
you're on the market,
and the Bel Canto
is hottie central.
Look at this.
They were for
Nina's birthday --
backstage passes
to Neil Diamond.
You're in worse
shape than I thought.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
Oh, Masuka was looking for you.
Something about drinks
at the Bel Canto.
Yeah, I told him I
had a yeast infection.
A bit of an overshare.
You want to talk about
what happened today?
Already did.
Dexter, the last time
I saw you like that
was when dad died.
Can talk to me, you know?
Just got to open your
mouth and move it.
I'll call Rudy.
I'll tell him I'll be late.
Deb, seriously.
I puked.
I'm fine.
I know you want to help,
but unless you have breath mints,
there's nothing to do.
Why do you always do this?
- Do what?
- You shut me out!
Like your birth father
that lived up the highway
your whole life and never
tried to contact you.
I still don't know how
that makes you feel.
I'll tell you what,
if some random emotion strikes me
in the middle of the night,
you'll be the first one I call.
Fine.
Whatever.
Did Paul force his
way into the house?
N o.
Did you ask him to leave?
Yes, and he refused.
But in your statement,
it says
you invited your ex-husband
into your bedroom.
He was drunk,
and the kids were asleep,
and I knew exactly where
this was heading --
Cracked ribs and a broken jaw.
And you didn't want it to escalate.
I understand that,
but we can't prove intent.
Your ex-husband has
the injuries here, not you.
Paul has a record
of spousal abuse.
Spousal abuse can be mutual.
It was never mutual.
Okay.
But the man is
a model parolee.
His drug tests are clean.
He's got glowing reports from
the court-appointed supervisor.
Corrections will want to
see this guy transition.
I don't care!
He's not going near my
children. Do you understand?
Rita,
if you deny him visitation,
you could lose your children.
Now, you have
deposition in two days.
Do not give this man any more
ammunition than he already has.
Okay.
Damn.
Just blood?
What happened to the bodies?
Hell if I know.
I don't want to know.
Blood was bad enough.
No wonder you
seem so amped.
Your brother must
have loved it.
- Fuck no. He freaked.
- Really?
I thought, you know,
blood was his thing.
What happened?
I don' know. It was like usual.
He shut me out.
- Did he say anything?
- Let's not talk about Dex right now.
Was it like a panic attack?
I don't know.
He's not really big into
sharing his feelings,
in case you hadn't noticed.
Kiss me.
What's the matter?
You don't even have wood.
Well, you're the one that
said you wanted to talk.
Yeah, but not now.
I'm horny.
Maybe I should call him.
Are you fucking kidding me?
What? We --
We bonded last weekend.
Isn't that what boyfriends
are supposed to do,
show some interest
in the family?
Yeah, but not when his girlfriend's
trying to get into his pants.
Deb, that's not fair.
You take me out on a --
couples' weekend to get
to know your brother,
and then you punish
me for giving a damn?
I mean,
your issues don't have to be mine.
You know what?
Forget it.
Let's just go to sleep.
Okay.
I'm gonna go watch TV.
She loved him
so goddamn much.
She took every one of his
CDs in the separation.
She wouldn't even give
me his Greatest Hits.
Nina loved Neil Diamond.
"Song Sung Blue."
"September Morn."
Oh, my god --
"Kentucky Woman."
You got to
love that shit.
That's like the fourth
chick you've driven off.
Waitress!
Is there a waitress?
I need a drink.
Waitress!
Bro, you're a train wreck.
Look, you got to stop
talking about the divorce.
I ain't ashamed.
Yeah, I think that's clear,
but it's pathetic.
Look...
Don't talk about the
divorce unless they ask.
Comprendo?
- Eighty-six the ring.
- I have to take a squirt.
She's gonna fuck me silly.
My sister's right.
I don't share my problems with her...
Or with anybody.
Harry taught me that --
Secrecy, self-reliance,
and a well-stocked
cupboard of hefty bags.
Fortunately, I've never met
a problem I can't manage...
Until that boy in the blood.
He scares me.
I want him to go away.
You awake?
What?
Are you sure you
locked the door?
Yeah, I'm positive --
Bolt and chain.
What am I gonna do?
Don't worry.
I'll figure it out.
And I will.
I can always see
other people's problems
more clearly than my own.
Fortunately, Rita's has a name.
Everyone who set foot
on the bloody carpet
in room 103
left a footprint,
and since we do shoe molds
of everyone on personnel,
that leaves only one set of
footprints unaccounted for --
The killer's.
This shows everywhere
he went in the room.
- The question is why.
- Hold on.
Aren't we missing something?
Where are the victims' footprints?
Give that lady a lollipop.
Are you suggesting there were
never any bodies in room 103?
Why would a guy stage a massacre
and not have any bodies?
And where'd he get the blood?
I've just got a
preliminary blood report.
The blood in that room came from
at least 5 different bodies,
possibly more.
My fellow traveler
had five victims.
Ice-truck killer had 5 victims.
5 bloodless victims.
I always wondered what
he did with the blood.
Wait, wait.
The ice-truck killer did
not horde his victims' blood
just to have a party at the
motherfucking Marina View hotel.
Why would he do that?
To chase me down
the rabbit hole.
What was that, Morgan?
I didn't say anything.
I'll remind you people --
We arrested
the ice-truck killer.
His name is Neil Perry,
and he's awaiting trial in county.
Bullshit.
Neil Perry recanted his
confession. He's a fraud.
- Try telling that to the capital.
- I did.
Do we have any more evidence
to support this theory?
When Masuka noticed
the blood wasn't clotting,
I ran some tests,
and it was loaded with
Coumadin and heparin.
One's an anticoagulant.
The other's a preservative.
It means the blood's old.
Plus the blood spatters'
all impact and castoff.
There are no hand transfers or
swipe patterns to indicate the
presence of any actual victims.
Masuka, run the DNA
on all five vics
and see if it matches
the ice-truck killer's victims.
You two get out to
the Marina View hotel.
Retrace his steps.
Maybe it'll tell
us something.
And not a word to anyone
about the ice-truck killer.
All right, Astor,
just stand up straight.
Now, do you have the
emergency phone number list?
It's in my backpack.
Do I have to show it to you again?
Just promise me you won't let
your brother out of your sight.
Rita?
You're scaring them.
Yeah, well, they should be.
I didn't tell them what
Paul did the other night.
What'd you say when you
dragged them to the neighbors'?
I smelled gas.
I should have just
thrown them in the car
and headed out of state,
gone back to Michigan.
Remember what
the lawyer said.
You don't want to
do anything rash.
Just relax. The court supervisor
will be there the whole time.
Hey, buddy. Come on.
Where's the love? Come on.
Daddy, what happened?
Oh, nothing, buddy. Just a little
bump on the head. That's it.
Hey, we're going
to the circus.
We're going to the circus, 'cause daddy
always keeps his promises, remember?
Good.
All right. Ready?
Got your stuff?
Let's go.
You okay?
I prefer the enchanting
Rita over the worried one.
If I can figure out a way to
make her ex-husband my problem,
I can help her sleep
much easier tonight.
All I need is a little
proof of his inner monster.
Harry would have
insisted on that.
Harry didn't believe
in preemptive killing,
but maybe I can bend the
rules just this once.
After all, Harry
wasn't perfect.
He lied about
my birth father.
The trifecta --
Weapon, ammo, and impaired judgment.
Throw in a little
domestic violence,
and you have the perfect
recipe for a family slaughter.
Mommy!
Hide your head, Dexter.
Close your eyes.
No!
So, after he soaked
the room in blood,
he crossed to the desk...
And then over to
the bedside table.
There's a clock radio
and some smeared blood.
Maybe he turned it on.
No, we're missing something.
Let's go over it again.
We've been over it three times!
Well, maybe
the map's wrong.
Call your brother.
What?
Why is everybody's first
move to call Dexter?
You don't even like him.
What'd the freak do this time,
boil your goldfish?
No, it's just...
It's Rudy.
We had our first fight.
Tiff. I don't know.
Whatever you want to call it.
I thought we were talking
about your brother.
We were.
And we'll be back with Billy Joel,
the Eurythmics,
and Devo on 103 fm,
- hits from the '80s.
- Turn that off.
No, wait.
I want to hear it.
It's Devo.
Turn that shit off.
He said 103 fm.
This is room 103.
Leviticus 10:3.
- 10:3 -- 103.
- Son of a bitch.
You think he's trying
to tell us something?
"I will be sanctified in
them that come nigh me,
"and before all people,
"I will be glorified."
Hey.
Deb's pissed at me.
I need advice.
So you came here?
You know you know her
better than anyone.
Come on.
I got two porterhouses
and a sixer of microbrew.
Well, one minute we're
talking about her day,
you know,
the whole bloodbath thing.
Right.
And the next,
she wants to...
jump my bones.
I mean, Deb's hot and all, but
sprinkle in a little conversation
once in a while, you know?
She's my sister.
I don't know.
Can I help you
find something?
You wouldn't happen to
have a good meat knife.
Thanks.
Anyway,
the other half of the argument
was about you.
Me?
Yeah. It was already
tense enough, but
when I brought your name,
she lost it.
So, what do I do?
Tell her it's all your fault.
- Seriously?
- You will eventually.
Deb has a way of
wearing you down.
Just start from there.
It's easier.
I got to take this.
You mind if I...?
Hey. Where are you?
Still at work, chasing a lead.
Let me guess --
The bloodbath case.
I don't want to talk
shop right now.
Baby, I am so sorry.
You were totally right.
I was mad at Dexter,
and I took it out on you.
My shift's almost done.
You want to come over and talk?
I'd love to, babe, but
I'm about to eat
dinner with Dexter.
Well, after.
Yeah, but here's the thing.
I think I'm gonna sleep
at my place tonight.
I mean, it's closer, and
I'm drinking,
you know.
You understand, right?
Yeah.
I'll call you tomorrow.
- Care to dance?
- You dance to this?
A bit.
What about your wife?
Tan line on your ring finger.
Well, um...
I'm not gonna talk
about that tonight.
Divorced?
I get it.
Mine was just finalized.
Let's go.
Will you excuse me?
Excuse me.
Police.
I need to talk to you.
I'm not a hooker anymore.
I work for a legitimate
escort service now.
I'm not here to bust anyone.
I just need to know why you
paint your nails the way you do.
He was a real good client.
You want to spend
the night in a cell?
All right. About a year ago,
there was this guy.
- Guy or client?
- A john, okay?
That's when I
worked Calle Ocho.
Anyway, he started getting all
rough with me until he saw this.
Then what?
Then he changed his tune,
got all turned on.
Told me to take
my fake hand off.
He started doing some kinky,
weird stuff,
like he was worshipping it.
To cap it off,
he takes all my nail polish
and paints each nail
a different color.
I liked it, so I kept doing it.
You know that guy on the news
they arrested for the
ice-truck killings?
Yeah, the one
who stuffs roadkill?
- Is that the guy?
- No way.
My trick, he's sexy.
- A freak, but sexy.
- Okay.
From the beginning
and with more detail.
Well, thanks for
the hospitality.
Hey, thanks for the steaks.
You know,
I didn't get a chance to ask.
Deb mentioned that
you had a little --
incident at
the crime scene.
Did she?
Well, most of my
prosthetic clients
are pretty traumatized by
the time they get to me.
Anyway, I'm a good listener
if you ever want to talk.
Thanks, but unless
you know an expert in --
repressed memories...
For real?
You know something about it?
More than I ever wanted to.
When I was in high school,
I started having these dreams
of a woman hit by a truck.
Who was she?
I didn't know.
Then one day
I stopped by a mailbox,
and it all came
crashing back...
My mom
getting out to mail a letter,
me still in the car.
I watched her die.
How old were you?
4.
I didn't remember
anything till I --
went and mailed a letter.
Walked right into the belly of
the beast without knowing it.
What kind of memories
are you having?
They're still a little vague.
Right.
Well, you're gonna have
to face it eventually.
Maybe next time.
When you see Deb,
go with white roses.
They're her favorite.
That's a good tip.
It's funny how life brings
people together, huh?
Rudy misunderstands
my problem.
I want the boy and
blood to go away,
not come crashing back.
Fortunately, I have other people's
problems to focus on right now.
Like forgotten cellphones.
What do you got?
Well, so far we're
chasing a ghost.
Couple of employees
helped with the sketch, but
it's pretty generic.
Only real lead we have
is a couple of numbers
he set at the crime scene.
Screw the numbers.
Who was killed?
Where are the bodies?
I heard some pretty wild
theories out there.
Just theories.
We're still waiting
for full blood results.
Damn it, Maria,
you're stalling.
I'm just trying to
avoid speculation.
Well, you got to give
me something and soon.
This department can't afford
another public relations disaster.
Well...
Maybe you should tell the
D.A. to let Neil Perry go.
He's not the ice-truck killer.
Are you still hung up --
I can't believe this.
Jesus, Maria,
that's not gonna happen.
The D.A.
takes his cues from us.
If you just tell him
you made a mistake...
Not going to happen.
Now let it go.
First break in this case,
you come straight to me.
This may be a shot in the dark,
but I met this hooker last night.
Going with a pro --
Now, that's how you get over the ex.
No, that's not what I mean.
So you didn't fuck her.
But she blew you, right?
Would you shut up?
It was a lead.
On what?
I'll let you know
if it pans out, but
what do you know about
amputee fetishes?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know,
it's... it's called acrotomophilia.
But don't let them
hear you call it that.
It sounds like a disease.
No, they prefer to be
known as "devotees."
I knew you were the man to ask.
Not really.
I prefer a girl
with a kung fu grip.
You know who you
should talk to?
It's... What's his face --
Deb's boyfriend.
Prosthetics guys deal with
devotees all the time.
Thanks.
No memory flashes here.
No little lost boy in blood.
Maybe he went back to hiding
in the dormant reaches
of my cerebral cortex.
Here's to hoping.
- Yo, Dex.
- Hey.
So, this is what
you do for a living?
I'm trying to match castoff
patterns from a crime scene.
A power tool was used.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks.
Circular saw.
Seems like there'd be an easier
way to make a mess like this.
Yeah, trust me. I know.
I've been in here for hours.
You know, in my line of work,
you hear all sorts
of horror stories --
boat propellers,
garbage disposals.
It seems like something
you'd see with a chainsaw.
Yeah, I hear that.
But this power tool was
plugged into a socket.
Guess you haven't heard
of an electric chainsaw.
Come on, people.
We're coming up empty.
Those numbers mean
something. 1-0-3.
We need to find the connection,
and until we do,
you need to go over every
page of every police report
you wrote in the
last six months.
Think.
1-0-3. 103.
Bus station locker,
piece of a
bank account,
area code,
partial license plate.
What is it?
I want answers.
What are you doing here?
How do you always do it?
Do what?
Make me feel like I'm 6
years old all the time.
If this is about Rudy,
he was just picking up his cellphone.
Where'd he leave it?
My apartment.
What was he doing there?
- Uh... eating steaks.
- And?
Uh... I don't know.
Drinking beer.
And?
- Debra.
- And?
- Talking?
- Talking.
You talked.
You opened your mouth,
and sounds came out.
On the same night that I wanted to
talk to you, but you shut me out.
- Oh.
- Yeah, "oh."
You don't talk to me, Dex.
You've spent our entire lives
keeping me at a distance.
But my boyfriend shows
up on your doorstep
- with a couple of T-bones --
- They were porterhouses.
Porterhouses,
and you end up tossing beers back
into the middle of the night.
Dex, you are all the
family that I have,
and I barely know you.
So, if you're gonna eat steaks
with somebody after a rough day,
if somebody's gonna break
through your fucking walls,
I think it should be me.
I think I have earned it.
I'm late for Rita's deposition.
Deb, it's hard for me.
You know that.
You Rudy Cooper?
Angel Batista.
I work with your
girlfriend, Debra.
Oh, hi. Nice to meet you.
I'd like to ask you a few questions,
if you don't mind.
Sure.
Let me just
grab the door.
So,
does this have
to do with a case?
You could say that.
Well, fire away.
Well, I ran into this lady
with a prosthetic hand --
Call girl, actually.
Said she had a
very unique client,
an amputee devotee.
You have a lead on this client?
That's the bitch of it.
I don't have
a goddamned clue,
except for the
freaky sex stuff.
I was hoping that you could
steer me toward some
of those weirdos.
I'm afraid I got into this business
to help people get better,
not help people get off.
Yeah, I'm sure Debra will be
happy to hear that.
But I can talk to some
of my colleagues,
see if I can draw up a
list of contacts for you.
That'd be great.
How often does someone get a chance
to help catch a bad guy, huh?
You in a rush for
this information?
No, no, I'm good.
I'm chasing a long shot, really.
Well, just...
give me a call at the station
when you got something.
Will do.
Good to meet you.
Last question.
According to
your ex-husband,
you left town with your
boyfriend last weekend.
That's right.
His father died.
Did your ex-husband have
a scheduled visitation
with his children
during that time?
I told Paul I'd
make it up to him.
So, then he gave
you permission?
No.
I'm the one that gave him
visitation in the first place.
I'm the custodial parent.
I didn't have to do that.
- Could you give us a second?
- Yes, of course.
Why didn't you tell me you
broke your visitation agreement?
I didn't know it
was a big deal.
I think she's answered
that last question,
so unless there's
something else...
No, that's fine.
If I missed anything,
we'll get to it at the psychiatric
evaluation next Wednesday.
Nobody told me about any
psychiatric evaluation.
It's mandatory in these cases.
The psych test determines if
there's a competency hearing.
For me?
But he's the ex-con.
It's standard.
Rita, you should be fine.
Should be?
You mean she could
actually lose this?
Guys...
I'm handcuffed here.
You violated a
custody agreement.
You struck your ex-husband
in your bedroom.
He has a case.
Mama,
look at my henna tattoo.
- So, how much candy have you had?
- Lots.
Thanks.
- Now she'll never get to sleep.
- She'll calm down soon.
This one's
already crashed.
Mom, can my dad
read me a story?
I don't think so, honey.
Please?
Okay.
But just one.
Put your duds on, buddy --
Spider-man ones I bought you.
I'll get him ready.
You've got 20 minutes left.
Thanks, Betty.
Thank you.
Hey, Rita.
It doesn't have
to be this way.
I mean, we can make this
easier on each other, right?
I could drop the charges
if you agree to
unsupervised visitation.
Fuck you.
Hey, Dexy.
You know,
I don't think your girlfriend
appreciates the gravity
of the situation.
If she loses that case,
she could lose the kids.
- That won't happen.
- Never say "won't."
We live in a world of wills --
Wills and wonders.
That's what I'm trying
to teach my children.
And they are my children, too,
something she seems to forget.
Okay, so I made some mistakes,
but I learned from it, right?
Hey, I'm sober.
Look.
No needle marks.
I got the fucking Alaskan pipeline
running through these veins,
and all because of those --
two little s of
love in the next room.
My heart beats for
those two kids,
so if you or
that skinny bitch
try to screw
with what's mine,
I swear to God, I don't
care who I have to hurt --
Harry's first rule was don't
get emotionally involved.
I think this is why.
Astor, go brush your teeth.
Someone once said
it's easier dealing
with other people's
problems than your own.
They were wrong.
Paul?
Dexter?
Where were you?
Taking out the trash.
Did you see Paul?
When I was in the side yard,
I heard the
front door open.
Hey, my dad's car is gone.
Let's face it, Paul.
You've been a problem.
It's time for you to go away.
The ice-truck killer
case has been reopened.
Officially.
We have new forensic
evidence that shows
that the DNA from the blood
at the Marina View hotel
matches the DNA
from his victims.
What about Neil Perry?
Isn't he supposed to be
the ice-truck killer?
All those questions should be
directed to captain Matthews.
He's been personally
handling the Perry case.
Oh, shit.
I hope she told
the Captain.
Who knew?
Who knew about this?
This is the first we're
hearing about it, Captain.
The ice-truck killer
is still at large.
Sure.
I'll call you back.
You overplayed
your hand, Maria.
I gave you a chance
to make it right.
- I told you --
- You don't tell me shit!
This is my department.
I made you lieutenant.
Me.
You were just another
spik detective.
Nice, Tom.
Real nice.
Your true colors
finally come out.
Oh, no.
No, you haven't seen
my true colors, Maria.
But you're about to.
Enjoy this office
while it's still yours.
Thank you.
Dexter.
What happened?
What's wrong?
It's Paul.
I don't know all the details,
but he --
violated Florida's
three strikes law.
He's back in jail.
It is truly amazing
the things you can do
when you put your mind to it.
- What's so funny, mom?
- Yeah, why are you laughing?
No problem is insurmountable.
Not when you have the most
accessible evidence locker in Miami.
Paul did need to go away.
This is the police.
- Sir, you're going to have to
turn down the television.
- But death wasn't the answer.
Police.
Open up.
- We're coming in, Mr. Bennett.
- Life in prison will do just fine.
For now, at least, the
code of Harry remains...
unbroken.
Hey, get over here.
You're part of
this family, too.
I need an ambulance
at 1228 Caldon Street.
A guy's been stabbed.
Stay with us.
Hang in there, okay?
Keep looking at us.
Heard they're dropping ice-truck
murder charges on Neil Perry.
Yeah, I'm sure he'll be filing
a lawsuit any minute now.
More shit for us to deal with.
Speaking of which,
watch out for reporters out there.
They're still waiting on a
comment from the Captain.
So, things still rocky at home?
Oh, with Rudy?
Yeah.
I'm not calling
until he apologizes.
I'm done being
second choice.
Good for you, Morgan.
If you're not
doing anything tonight,
Masuka's invited us
to the Bel Canto.
For you.
It's too late.
You blew it.
I did blow it. This is the first
chance I've had to talk.
I'm too tired to talk.
Well...
let's go home,
fall into bed.
Why, Rudy?
I mean, fucking why?
You didn't want to fall
into bed the other night
when I laid my heart
out on the phone.
You wanted to
talk to my brother.
I was confused.
Well, I'm not confused. That's
the problem, I know what I want.
I was confused
because I love you.
What I want is very
simple and uncomplicated.
What did you say?
I love you.
Don't try to...
Fuck.
What?
I love you, too.
What happened to your lip?
I'm just, uh... incident with
a tool at the workshop.
Well, let's get you home
and take care of it.
So, this is doom.
I've been the architect
of so much of it.
It's only fair I should know
what all the fuss is all about.
He left me this
room for a reason.
Five women gave
their blood, their lives
for this moment.
There's only one
way to find out why.
Close your eyes, Dexter.
I want mama.
No!
Not in front of my baby!
Oh, god.
Please don't cry.
It's gonna be okay.
Don't you dare!
Not in front of my baby!
No!
Close your eyes, Dexter.
Don't look.
Dexter.
Close your eyes.
I want mama!
Mommy loves you, Dexter.