Previously on "dexter"...
dexter: No blood.
What a beautiful idea.
Refrigerated truck.
He wants a cold environment...
to slow the flow of blood.
I suppose I should be upset,
but I'm not.
In fact, I think this is a friendly message,
kind of like,"hey, want to play?"
Kara, it's me.It's james.
You just opened a dangerous door.
No, man.You did...
when you murdered a cop and an innocent lady.
Was kara sleeping with someone other than ricky?
Was it you?
What the fuck were you thinking?
-- Going out tonight with the guys, blow off steam. You in?
-- Hey, man.Sounds good.
I thought you said you wanted to go get shit-faced.
I am shit-faced.
I showed my face to guerrero, his whole church.
They're gonna think I'm behind this shit.
You fucked my sister.
You fucked a cop's wife.
Now you're just fucked, buddy.
He's escalating the thrill,
posing his victim in the middle of a 20,000-seat arena for all miami to see,
to show us what he's capable of doing.
What did I miss?
Fingertips.
Fuckin'-a, that's my girl.
This body belongs to the frozen fingertips in the truck.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you tony tucci,
the ice-truck killer.
Bullshit.
Of course I agree with my sister,
but unlike her, I'm not upset.
He's still out there, and I'm waiting...
breathless.
I find people around me are always making some kind of connection,
like friendship or romance,
but human bonds always lead to messy complications --
commitment, sharing,
driving people to the airport.
Besides, if I let someone get that close, they'd see who I really am...
and I can't let that happen.
So... time to put on my mask.
I need your expertise.
I live to serve.
Excuse us, fellas.
Interesting hand job.
That's funny.
It is?
So, how long you think it's been there?
This feels familiar.
Okay.
So, how long's it been there?
Blood stopped pooling,
still wet... couple hours at the most.
What time was it found?
A jogger called it in this morning about 7:30.
No prints.Wiped clean.
Real creep show, huh?
Any sign of the rest of the body?
Just mr. Hand.
Do you think this is our guy's work?
The ice-truck killer?
It's hard to say.There's blood.That's different.
Plus, it's a male victim --haven't seen that before.
The cut appears to be almost delicate.
You see between the first and second row of carpals --
very surgical.
Check out what else he left behind.
A little postcard
to remember him by.
How far is rand beach from here?
This is rand beach.
It was renamed petrie beach a few years ago.
Okay, everybody.
Everybody say "stinky feet."
Stinky feet!
Wait. Nobody move.
Dexter, were you smiling?
No.
Okay, we'll do another one.
This time, everybody smiles.You, too, dex.
Yeah, pretend you're burning ants.
Shut your damn face, deb.
Hey, language, please.
What? She always talks like that.
Enough, you two.
Dexter, come here.
What's your problem?
I hate the beach.
It's sandy and gross and nasty, and I want to go home.
Too bad.
You're part of a family.
And being part of a family means smiling for photos.
Why should I pretend I'm happy?
Because it'll make your mom happy,
and because it's how you fit in.
Remember we talked about that?
Yeah.
This is how you do it.
When somebody takes your picture, you smile.
It doesn't matter if you're happy or not.
You just do it to fit in.
-- Okay?
-- Okay.
All right.
Come here, handsome.
Okay.
Everybody ready?
One more time.
Stinky feet!
Yeah, I just need to stop by my apartment to pick up a few labs.
Straight to the station after, yeah. Thanks, lieutenant.
Dexter morgan,
this is your life.
It is my new friend --the ice-truck killer.
When he broke into my apartment, he took some time to get to know me --
my life..
my secrets.
...Have even brought in manpower from other counties
in an effort to expedite the search.
Officially, mr. Tucci has not been charged with any crime...
then tell the fucking governor to free up funds for overtime.
I mean The more guys I got out there, the sooner we find tucci.
Uh, kelly,I'll get back to you.
...Is still the department's top priority.
What's wrong?
Fingerprint I.D. Came back on that hand from the beach.
It belongs to tony tucci,
your ice-truck killer suspect.
What?
Wait a minute.
No. No, no, no.No way.
No way.
I mean, this --
this has to be a mistake.
The mistake was unleashing a high-profile manhunt before you had all the facts.
Okay.
This doesn't mean that tucci is not the killer.
Don'T.
Just -- just don'T.
You wanted to be on tv --well, get ready...
'cause the press will annihilate us for this.
We'll be lucky if tucci's mother doesn't file a lawsuit.
All right.
You go talk to that woman.
Do your mea culpas.
If we handle this right,
maybe we can mitigate the fallout.
Tom...
I'm the last person she wants to see.
I called her son a killer.
And now's your chance to make it right.
*************
I'm taking point.
You can help by getting all nonessentials off the beach.
Secure and separate any witnesses, all right?
Will do.
What did the captain say?
Did he make her cry?
Just control the fucking beach, angel.
I knew tucci wasn't the killer.I knew it.
Laguerta whipped up a manhunt r a rent-a-cop.
Oh, man, I wish I could have been there to see the captain rip her a new one.
Morgan, calm down.
Laguerta insulted the real killer's intelligence,
and now he's getting back at us for chasing after the wrong guy.
You see all these people over here?
Yeah.
What are they?
Uh, potential witnesses.
And what do we do with potential witnesses, morgan?
We --we interview them.
Got it.
Where is he...
the rest of him?
We're --we're still looking.
The entire force is looking.
We're making every effort.
Are you sure it's tony?
Because...
yes.
I'm afraid so.
Mrs. Tucci...
I said some very harsh things about your son.
Thank you.
"Thank you"? For what?
For coming to tell me in person.
For god's sake, please.
There's nothing more important than this.
Can you find my son's body?
If it's the last thing I do.
-- I made a grave --
-- bring him home, please.
I just want to bury my son.
I do love halloween.
What's inside of a pumpkin?
See for yourself.
You don't like this stuff? I do.
Come on.Get in there.
I'll finish cleaning this out.You can carve it tomorrow.
There he is again, mom.
My god.It's every night now.
That dog? Where's it coming from?
Next door --my neighbor'S.
Leaves the poor thing in the yard all day and night.
It's been getting worse.
I mean, I would talk to her, but I don't want to start something.
Listen to him, mom.He's so sad.
I just wish he would shut up so I could sleep.
Do you want me to talk to her?
No, you don't have to do that.
I insist.
Hello.
I don't think we've meet
boyfriend of the blonde next door.
I've seen you around.
Look, I'm just getting in.I'm tired.
That's precisely why I'm here.
We can't help but notice your dog, uh, cries...
-- a lot.
-- I know.
My ex moved out and left his dog.
Oh.
Trust me, I wish there was something I could do.
You could, uh, take him inside.
Walter's an outside dog.
You put walter inside, walter's an inside dog.
He doesn't like being inside.
Did he tell you that?
We'd appreciate it if you could find a way to keep him quiet.
The kids are upset.
Maybe that's 'cause they think their crackhead father is gonna come back and beat their asses again.
You know what works for me?
Earplugs.
I could make things so much easier for rita...
but that would be wrong.
I love halloween --
the one time of year when everyone wears a mask...
not just me.
People think it's fun to pretend you're a monster.
Me, I spend my life pretending I'm not.
Brother, friend, boyfriend --all part of my costume collection.
Some people might call me a fraud.
Let's see if it will fit.
You stabbed me in the back!
I prefer to think of myself as a master of disguise.
They're so excited.
Sure they are. They get to binge on sugar for an entire day.
Who wouldn't love that?
What about a costume for you?
Maybe this one?
no. No. I think I'll be snow white again.
It's kind of tradition.
Oh.
Dexter, look.I'm a princess, too.
Just like your mom --two perfect princesses.
Let me guess.You're gonna be a dwarf.
No way. I want to be joe from "blue's clues."
I keep telling him that a rugby shirt is not a costume.
Another photo from my family album.
He's re-creating my past with tony tucci's body parts.
He's forcing me to see this.
Nobody paying you to stand around and goddamn stare.
I thought angel was working this case, sergeant.
Sergeant?
Friends of yours?
Don't worry about it.
Worry about this.
The foot was severed between the tarsus and the metatarsus.
The wound is circular --again, almost surgical.
And there's blood.
Guy gives us body after body with no blood.
Why he's making a switch now?
He's trying to send a message --
one that's more important than his ritual need to drain the blood and wrap the parts.
Okay, so what's the message?
I'm not sure.
Well, who's he sending it to?
I can't tell you that, either.
What fucking good are you?
No fucking good at all, apparently.
You okay?
he's mocking me.
Don't take it personal.
Doakes hates all you lab geeks.
Who? Oh.
-- Relax, bro.
-- Sorry.
I need to bag this photo
under the ball. Do you mind?
He knows.
He's not corrupting the happy hallmark images of my youth.
He's revealing the ugly truth behind them.
Come on, simon.
You want it?
It's right there.
-- Over there.
-- Oh, yeah.
Guys, give it back! Pass it over here.
You guys, give it back.Come on, simon.
What you gonna do?
All right.Enough.
Get out of here.
What the hell is going on?
We're just having fun.
It didn't look like simon was having too much fun.
You're always telling me to fit in, and I'm just trying to be part of the team.
You can't be a bully, dexter.
First of all it's wrong.
Secondly, people remember bullies.
People like me --cops.
A bully is a felony waiting to happen.
So...
blend in.
Go on.
Officer morgan, I have an assignment for you.
I heard we found a foot this morning.
You want me to head out to the crime scene?
No.
Look, we pulled these from security cameras around the beach --
stores, hotels, atms.
I want you to check every frame.
Oh, you are shitting me.
If we're lucky, we can see the ice-truck killer coming and going.
We have techs who can do this.
Not all techs have the skill to spot suspicious activity.
I'm taking a huge leap of faith that you do.
Keep your eye out for another box of surveillance tapes.
It's on its way from the new crime scene.
Hey, doakes, what's up?
Fuck anyone's wife lately?
Thanks to your little chickenshit stunt,
guerrero's guys are tailing me everywhere I go.
Did you know that?
That's not good, james.
You should alert the police...
unless, of course, for some reason the officers of miami metro wouldn't want to help you --
like, you know, you fucked one of their wives.
You think this is a joke.
I'm gonna end up dead.It's just a matter of when.
You should have thought of that before you stuck your dick in my sister.
You're right.
I should have waited until the divorce came through.
Bullshit.
What? She didn't tell you?
She filed the papers, jackass.
You don't believe me, ask the captain.
He tried to pull ricky out of his assignment, but ricky didn't want to come out.
Of course not. His job was to bring down guerrero.
It was his job to protect his wife.
Ricky's the motherfucker who got her killed.
You backed the wrong cop, asshole.
Let's go, guys.Time for school.
Guys? Come on.
You don't want to be in the halloween parade?
Shut up!
Shut up! Just --
I need to talk to you about your dog.
I talked to your boyfriend.
My kids are exhausted.
All right, when it comes to my kids, I stop being nice.
So I need you to bring him in at night, feed him on a schedule,
and take him for some exercise every now and --
I'm sorry.
Is this funny?
No, no, no.
It's -- it's sad.
But you're funny.
Look at you, all tough.
I-I'm gonna call the police.I can do that.
There's nothing you can do.
The cops will tell meto keep him quiet,
and I'll say I will, and then they'll leave, and he'll go back to doing what he does.
But you're funny.
Unlike harry, my new friend doesn't place much value in blending in.
He wants me to see who he is and what he does.
Everything about him is brazen, authentic.
What does that make me?
Crap.
You okay, man?
No.
Hey, don't let this bastard get to you.
You're the best blood expert in the state,
and we need you to stay with this, my friend.
I'll be all right.
Wait.Before you get back to work,
check this out.
What is that, a butterfly?
No, socio,
it's a diamond-studded four-leaf clover.
I'm, uh,
I'm giving it to nina for our anniversary tomorrow night.
Oh, congratulations.
How many years?
10 years she's been my lucky charm now.
Tin is the traditional gift, but I didn't think she'd want a tin clover.
No.It's probably a good plan.
Are you sure that's not a butterfly?
Well, it does kind of look like a bug.
This can't be right.
What's up?
You see that? You see it?
I don't know.What do I see?
The blood flow in the hand suggested the heart was still pumping when it was severed.
Mean son of a bitch, no doubt.
But look at the foot.It's the same blood flow, plus the lividity.
Look, it's the same bruising, same ashen color, same level of decomposition
as the hand the day we found it.
But...
we found them a day apart.
I know.
Los santos.
Hollywood, fl--
L.T.,You got to listen to him.
It's the guard, tucci --
I think he's alive.
What are you talking about?
The ice-truck killer is keeping him alive to perform amputations.
Tucci's alive?
Both limbs were taken from a live body,
and we found them 24 hours apart.
That's not all.
Tell them, dexter.
If the hand came off yesterday at 7:00 A.M.And the foot this morning at 7:00...
we get another body part first thing tomorrow.
But he's alive.
Put together a task force.I want all available personnel on this,
and put a priority status on all forensics related to this case.
Captain matthews, please.
Have him call me back immediately.
Mrs. Tucci?
Maria laguerta.
I have some amazing news for you.
We believe your son is alive.
No. No. We haven't, but I promise we will.
No, thank you.
Yes. Yes.
Okay, we'll be in touch.Bye.
Doakes: We've got a live body now, people.
We want to find tucci while he's still breathing.
That means trying to figure out where tomorrow's drop is
so we catch our man in the act.
Any ideas?
Don't forget the photos.They're new.
Thank you, officer morgan.We're doing just fine out here.
Why do we think he's taking photos?
He wants to be remembered.
You use photos to record memories.
I almost feel sorry for them,
trying to put together a puzzle when they don't know pieces are missing from the box --
pieces he gave me.
He wants me to play the game his way.
Okay, what else could it be?
Change.
You got something to say, speak up.
The beach changed names.The office park used to be a soccer field.
He's dumping the body parts in places that used to be something else.
Okay.Places that have changed.
Let's make a list,
assign surveillance to each location for the morning.
South beach used to be a mangrove swamp.
Homestead park was originally an air force base, right?
They turned versace's mansion into a hotel.
Thank you, officer morgan.
The whole city of miami reinvents itself every 5 years.
Then we'll stay up all night until our list is complete.
I once was lost
but now I'm found was blind
but now I see
lieutenant.
Anything?
Well, I am so glad you could make it.
Well, I just came by to show my support.
It's been a long time since I've been to church.
Excuse me, everyone.Excuse me.
Um, I would like to introduce you to someone very special.
This is maria laguerta.
She's the policewoman looking for tony.
Not just me.
Actually, there's a lot of us looking.
You brought us all here together by giving us hope.
May the lord bless you
and guide you, maria.
This is saint anthony,
-- patron saint of
-- the lost.
Find him.
Okay.
I tried to apologize, but i couldn't get a word in edgewise.
And you wanted to apologize why?
You don't think I should, the way I went after her son?
Yeah, you did fuck that up.
Yeah.I crucified him without having all the facts.
I need to tell her that I'm sorry.
I need to let her know that I'm sorry.I need to tell her.
Who is that gonna make feel better, you or her?
Leave that woman alone with her candles and "kumbaya."
So, ere we at?
I added additional patrols at dolphin stadium,
bayside marketplace, and casa casuarina.
That's everybody we have out in the field --
homicide, robbery, off-duty patrol.
So what's next?
What's next is you should go home.
You've had the shit kicked out of you all day.
I like it here with you.You're the only person people hate more than me.
Come on.Let's both get out of here.
Nothing left but the waiting now, anyway.
Officer morgan.
Call me on my cellphone if you find anything.
What? Huh?
Want a piece of me?
Fucking asshole!
Debra: I will pay you $1 million
if you help me figure out where the next piece of tucci's gonna show up.
I'm afraid I'm lost on this one, deb.
It's like it's staring me right in the face, but --
$1 million.
You don't have $1 million.
I'll steal it from evidence.
I've been stuck in a goddamn fishbowl all day.
I want to be part of the hunt.
I'm almost off duty.
Sorry, sister.
$2 million.
I know you made a list of locations.
Just pick your favorite spot.We'll stake it out together.
My favorite spot.
Of course.
Come on.I want to play.
Deb, I got to go.We'll compare notes tomorrow, okay?
I used to love this place --
the bulldozers pressing garbage, layer after layer, right into the earth itself,
burying it, hiding it.
I found it soothing.
But it wasn't condos back then.
This has to be the right place.
So what am I missing?
Sorry about that.
Go back to sleep.
Hello.
Woman: Mr. Morgan? Dispatch.You've been called to the mccaffrey pumpkin patch.
Do you need the address?
No, I know exactly where it is.
-- Are you okay?
-- Are you kidding? That was awesome.
You've got some hay in your hair.
Where?
Right there!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Enough. Enough, you two.Come on.
Let me take a picture of you and the kids.
You'll miss these moments when they're older.
Thanks.
It's great to see you having such a good time, dex.
Are you kidding me? This hay's giving me a total allergy attack,
and we're going around in circles on a pumpkin patch.
I don't get it.
Ready?
Smile!
What do we have?
Ankle to knee.He's moving up the leg.
You think tucci's still alive?
If he is, he won't be for long.
Unless you're toting a portable dvd player,
you better be finished watching that security footage.
I am on break.I'm on my own time.
So you are, but your shift starts in two hours.
So if I were you,I'd head back to the station
Traffic at this hour's a bitch.
Speaking of bitch...
didn't dad bring us here once when we were kids?
I don't remember.
Hey, dexter, come here.Take a look at this.
Excuse us.
She's right, you know, about the traffic.
It's interesting.There's no sign of infection where the foot was cut off,
like he gave tucci prophylactic antibiotics before amputating.
At least he's looking after his patient.
Hey, check this out.
Is this appropriate?
It's our anniversary... and it's the big one.
Nina deserves the best.
"Ox"?
No. Fuck!
What's the matter with you? It's x's and o'S.
Like tic-tac-toe?
No, like hugs and kisses.
Diamond-filled hugs and kisses in a white-gold setting.
Well, that's good, 'cause you wouldn't want it to look like someone's playing tic-tac-toe on her head.
God da it.
Where's mom?
She had to run a few errands before she takes you two trick-or-treating.
But I'm too tired to go trick-or-treating.
I heard you two were up a lot last night.
It was that damn dog.
Hey, code, grown-up language is for grown-ups.
I don't think that dog will be bothering you anymore.
How do you know?
My mystic powers told me.
Heard lindsay lohan say "damn."
All right, tell you what --I'll make you a deal.
When you become a rock star, you can swear, too.
Walter! Walter!
You're right.He's gone.
Where's my dog?!What did you do with it?!
All right.Here he is.
Just remember to walk him, feed him, and love him, okay?
My nieces are shy sometimes.Girls, say thank you to rita.
Thank you.Thank you.
They already made a doggy bed --sweaters, towels.
It actually looks more comfortable than my bed.
I knew this would be a perfect fit.
You did a good thing, rita.Thank you.
Harry was the only one who saw me --
really saw me --
so he taught me to hide.
That's what's kept me safe.
But sometimes, I'm not sure where harry's vision of me ends and the real me starts.
If I'm just a collection of learned behaviors --bits and pieces of harry --
maybe my new friend is right.
Maybe I am a fraud.
Hi.
Hey.
Where's astor and cody?
They're passed out in a sugar coma at colleen'S.
Um, can I come in?
Oh, yeah, sure.Sorry.
I should warn you, I haven't really been myself lately.
maybe I can cheer you up.
Trick or treat.
You look great.
Who are you?
Lara croft.
"Tomb raider."
Oh.
You raid tombs dssed like that?
That's impressive.
What happened to snow white?
Well, I'm --I'm sick of her.
You know, I never did
get to thank you for picking the kids up for me.
Uh, you took care of your "errand"?
Yes.
The beagle has landed happily in the arms of two loving girls.
You are a superhero.
It was such an incredible feeling rescuing that dog.
You upset your neighbor.
Fuck her.
Well, I guess you're used to dealing with people like her, right?
Considerably worse.
Is that why you haven't been yourself lately?
There's a case I just can't seem to get out of my mind.
maybe I can help.
No. I'm afraid there's nothing you can do.
Oh, I don't know.
I'm a dognapper now... and a tomb raider.
There's all sorts of things I can do.
What --what are you doing?
Whatever I want.
I've come to appreciate the comfortable moments with rita --
the easy, quiet moments--
This...
might be better.
Look, there's mr. Tub-of-lardi bringing mrs. Tub-of-lardi another bucket of fried chicken.
Where's your brother?
I'm not his keeper.
W-what do you think of this?
It's an anniversary present for nina.
See, it's -- it's a diamond key to my heart.
It's -- it's a key, but, you s, it's shaped like a heart.
You can't tell me that it looks like anything else,'cause that's what it is.
That's it.That's what I like.
And I'm not gonna take it back.
It's perfect, angel.
She'll love it.
Really?
I would.
How -- how do I look?
Like the tie?
Angel.
Happy anniversary, baby.
You know you can't just walk in here anymore.
I just thought...
our anniversary...
maybe tonight we could put all that behind us.
It doesn't matter what night it is.
I told you I need time.
It's been three months, baby.
How much time do you need?
Don't turn this around on me, angel --
not after what you did.
I need as much time as I need.
Angel...
as long as you're here, you want to see aury?
Lo siento, princesa.
Lo siento, lo siento, lo siento.
Thank you.
That was...
...unexpected.
Yeah. For me, too.
I have no problem with...
unexpected.
No, you... certainly don'T.
I have to get back to the kids.
what are these?
I've been, uh, reorganizing my photos a little.
Oh.
Look how cute you are.
And your dad --such a nice face, just like you.
I was adopted.
I know.
But you're both good men.
I can tell.
Very poetic.
Poetic? It's a water fountain.
Well, yeah, but look at the way your dad took the photo.
His shadow's on the wall right next to you.
It's like he's always with you.
I'd frame this one.
All this time the answer was right here.
Harry -- photographer and foster father extraordinaire.
He is always with me,
and he's the common denominator.
Rita...
you're a genius.
All those years of smiling for the camera --
it was empty and fake,
the pictures meaningless, until now.
Pictures of harry.
So this is it.
It's cool.
Cool.
Dexter, this is the place where my father,
your grandfather, worked for 30 years.
He started out as the janitor,
worked his way up to chief of maintenance.
This place put food on our table.
In two weeks, it'll all be shut down.
I know.
Excuse me, miss! Miss?
-- Would you mind?
-- Oh, come on, dad.
I don't want to...
hey, you all right?
It's nothing. Bad medianoches for lunch. I'm okay.
I'm sorry, miss.It's okay. Thanks.
We're not gonna be needing a picture, after all.
Yeah, we are.
Dex, I really don't feel like doing this now.
Don't be a baby --
being part of a family means smiling for family photos, right?
My friend left this.
He's showing me where to go.
But I wonder... am I going because it's what he wants
or because that's what harry would want?
What do i want?
The hospital's shut down now,
abandoned for years,
but tonight it's visiting hours again.
Well, james...
why did you have to be such a pain in the ass, huh?
Ugh! Fuck.
I didn't tell you you could get up.
Please, please
Now you get up.
You traumatize my little girl in church...
break the knees of my best turner.
You're a wild dog, sergeant.
The only thing to do with a wild dog --
police! Hands in the air!
Thought you could use backup.
You could have filled me in, man. Shit.
Got you going after a goddamn cop, motherfucker.
We own your ass now.
So this was the plan all along --to use me as bait to bring down guerrero?
Yeah, and now my sister can rest in peace.
We're done now, doakes.We're even.
I'll call this in, bring the paramedics.
Get this piece of shit out of here.
Please.
Just do it.
Kill me.
I'm ready.
Just don't cut me anymore.
Please don't cut me anymore.
Gift-wrapped, begging for death.Tools at the ready.
Just kill me.It's okay.
He was left here so I would kill him,
but my new friend doesn't see me as clearly as he thinks.
I can't kill this man.
Harry wouldn't want it.
And neither would I.
Are you moan?
Message came through dispatch for you.
Who left this?
Who left it?!
jesus, stop that.I'm getting bruises.
I'm sorry.I'm so excited.
Try a hug once in a while.
I don't know who your contacts are, morgan,
but you are my up-and-comer.
You saved a man's life tonight.
I'm just the one who got the call, sir.
But you followed it up.
Right place at the right time, sir.
Where we at?
Morgan's tip was good.They're taking tucci over to county.
Alive?
Alive.
So, I suppose this gets deb off of surveillance-tape duty.
Really?
Is that what you suppose?
I got your page, lieutenant.
Doakes is caught up in the guerrero bust.
You're taking point here.
-- You got it.
-- I'm tired of chasing this guy's shadow.
I want forensic evidence if you have to tear apart this building brick by brick.
-- Entiende?
-- s?
Use morgan here.
How did your wife like that necklace, angel?
Oh, you were right.She loved it.
You nailed that one.
Everyone hides who they are... at lea some of the time.
Sometimes you bury that part of yourself so deeply that you have to be reminded
it's there at all.
Good work, man.I told you we'd get that piss-poor...
and sometimes you just want to forget who you are altogether.
And what about me?
Maybe I'll never be the human harry wanted me to be.
But I couldn't kill tony tucci.
That's not me, either.
My new friend thought I wouldn't be able to resist the kill he left for me,
but I did.
I'm not the monster he wants me to be.
So I'm neither man nor beast.
I'm something new entirely,
with my own set of rules.
I'm dexter.