Previously on "Dexter"...
Open up, Perry, it's the police.
Open up.
Hey, Angel, I got him!
They really found
the ice-truck killer?
I saw him, Dex. I chased him.
The fun part was
hanging them like cattle
right before I
cut their throats.
Son of a bitch.
I have so many
questions for him.
What was his message to me?
Now I need to know him.
Hi.
The fuck are you?
Paul Bennett, father on parole.
Dexter Morgan.
I can't think of anything clever to say.
Divorce papers --
sign them now,
and I'll agree to supervised
visits twice a week.
You think you can really
make me back down?
Are you fucking my wife?
I just wish he'd go away.
I mean, why can't he just go
away and disappear forever?
All along,
I thought this was a game
my alter ego and
I were playing.
But relationships
change, evolve,
and this one's getting deep.
I realize now my
days are numbered.
So I'd better make
the most of them.
Your instincts were dead-on.
They're always dead-on when it
comes to killers. Why is that?
I'm watchin' you.
What are we looking at here?
I'm thinking two circus
clowns dancing. You?
No, it looks like a lobster.
See the claws?
Why do bloodstains always
look like crustaceans to you?
I like seafood.
Rorschach would say you have a
hard time relating to others.
- Not as hard as her.
- It does look like a suicide.
Can I get some light
in here, please?
- Damn power outages.
- I don't know, Angel.
Most firearm suicides
are committed by men.
Women slash their wrists,
take pills, something more ladylike.
Not in Miami.
We closed a couple of suicide cases
just like this last year, remember?
- WOOH
- Look at this mess.
That's a fancy bathtub.
Rich husband?
House husband and
aspiring artist.
Ooh. Promising.
So, she supported him?
It looks like that.
She was some kind of
big-time prosecutor.
Those other suicides we closed -- those
were high-powered women too, right?
I don't know. I think so.
Note to self.
I don't care what it looks like.
Somebody killed her.
We're checking out
all the possibilities.?
Was your wife dealing with
any emotional problem?
You know, job stress,
the usual,
but she was working
through it in therapy.
She have any other problems
that you're aware of?
-?
- Are you listening to me?
Vanessa didn't kill herself.
Criminals stage
suicides all the time.
?
We'll check into it.
We need to collect your
clothes for evidence --
standard procedure.
Come on. I got to go.
There's a dead body in that house.
- There's a hot body in here.
- I so want to maul you right now.
I so want you to.
Call me when you're done, okay?
I'll bring handcuffs.
Morgan, what took you so long?
Playing "hide the salami"
with Mr. Prosthetics?
- I don't fuck and tell.
- Since when?
Can we go inside?
I'm kind of wet. Don't.
No, I need you to?
find out about the
victim's relationship with her husband.
It's always the husband, right?
Looks like a suicide, but you never
know -- younger guy, unemployed.
Maybe he was a boy toy and
killed her for her money.
I'm on it.
Doakes is sending you away
from a crime scene in rain
and you're not
putting up a fight?
- I'm a team player.
- You are?
Fuck you!
Oh, hey, Dex, come on in.
- Where's Rita?
- Uh, she's stuck in traffic.
Power's out in half the city.
Of course,
I love the extra kid time, but, uh,
court supervisor --
not so much.
Hey, you know, I feel really bad
about the last time I was here.
I didn't mean to get
all alpha male on you.
?
What are you supposed
to say to the guy
who's f'ing your wife
while you're in jail?
Sorry. Sorry I'm late.
Thanks for holding
down the fort.
Do you mind if I get going?
I got kids of my own
at home to look after.
No, no, no. It's okay.
Dexter and I are here now.
Great. Thank you. Bye, kids.
Mom, Dexter,
the lights are out.
They are?
Hey, I brought hot chocolate.
- Dad already made us some.
- With extra marshmallows.
- Tag -- you're it!
- I'd love some hot chocolate.
Take two. Looks like he's got extra.
Come here, buddy.
Mom, can dad stay and
put us to bed, please?
I think that's why
Dexter's here, sweetie.
- Dexter doesn't mind.
- Yay!
Only a song, no story --
it's way past your bedtime.
All right, bedbugs,
let's leave these two alone.
It's not like they
need a chaperone.
Meghan Dowd, Carolyn Jillian,
and now Vanessa Gayle --
all three powerful women,
all three shot themselves
in the past two years.
They've got to have
more in common
than career ambition and
a fondness of firearms.
Why the sudden
interest in suicides?
Morbid curiosity.
What can I do for you?
So many things.
I need the blood-spatter
report on Vanessa Gayle.
Blood spatter's inconclusive.
All I can tell is
she was shot at close range.
I wish I had more for you.
Me too.
Maria, the D.A. needs the work
sheet for the ice-truck-killer case.
I'm working on it.
When'd you talk to the D.A.?
We had dinner last night.
Mayor Allen took us out to
celebrate Neil Perry's arrest --
Hell of a good time.
Hmm. Iro de puta.
I'm the one who gets
Perry to confess and
- he's got the mayor kissing his ass.
- I wouldn't be too upset.
Matthews will be the one with
the egg on his face soon enough.
You still believe we
got the wrong guy?
Perry's the pretender
to the throne.
The real king is still out there,
and he'll kill again.
It's just a matter of time.
Or the ice-truck killer will use
Perry as a get-out-of-jail-free card.
You really think
that might happen?
If Perry's the wrong guy
and I let him take the fall,
definitely. Thanks, Dexter.
What if Laguerta's right?
What if the ice-truck
killer does disappear?
No. He's got unfinished
business with me.
Still, I can't just sit on my hands
waiting for something to happen.
I need a distraction.
Nothing like some
little debbies
and a worthy new adversary
to clear my head.
Talk to me, ladies.
What do you have in common?
Same sorority?
Pilates instructor?
Dr. Emmett Meridian.
The three suicide sisters
shared the same therapist --
Dr. Emmett Meridian.
He must be terrible at his job.
So far,
he comes up squeaky clean --
no malpractice suit,
no disgruntled patients.
And I thought I was a
master at damage control.
Perhaps I should schedule a
session with the good doctor
and try out a little
reverse psychology.
Come on in, Sean. Have a seat.
Thanks for seeing me
on such short notice.
Hey, I expect the police to
show up when I call, right?
The least I can do is clear my
lunch hour for a cop in need.
So, what brought you here?
A friend of mine died.
She killed herself.
- I need to understand why.
- How come?
She had everything going for her.
It doesn't make sense.
To some people,
death makes perfect sense.
Life -- now, that's the puzzle,
like you, Sean.
What really brought you here?
I just told you I came --
To talk about your friend's suicide,
I know.
I think you're using this suicide
deal as an excuse to come see me.
You're absolutely right.
How could you tell?
I'm sensing you do it a lot to
keep the world at arm's length.
And what are my
real intentions?
As soon as I pay for my lunch,
you're gonna tell me that.
Excuse me a second.
Judging from what I've seen so far,
I probably will.
This guy's good.
So why do his
patients keep dying?
Vanessa's estimated time of
death was Monday at 7:00 p.m.
Meridian was in session
with Scott Solomon.
I wonder if Mr.
Solomon kept his appointment that night.
So, we got almond chicken
pork fried rice.
So, Sean, let's start with the basics.
You married?
No.
Girlfriend?
Yes.
Sex life?
It's personal.
And this is therapy,
where we share personal things.
You know, it might help me open up
if you shared something about yourself.
Why did you become a psychiatrist?
See what you just did?
Trying to take
control like that?
You probably get away with it
most of the time, too, right?
That's a way of preventing other
people from getting close to you.
Let me ask you something, Sean.
Have you ever been
close to anybody?
My foster father.
He's the only one who
ever really knew me.
You're adopted?
Harry took me in when I was 3.
So tell me about Harry.
What kind of stuff did
you guys do together?
You know,
normal father-son stuff.
All right. Stop. Enough.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
Nice ambush.
That was the perfect
point of attack.
I can't believe I
finally got you.
I won.
- This isn't a game, Dexter.
- No, I know.
- It's not supposed to be fun.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, it's just --
You think I want to
teach you these things?
This is the only way I know how to
keep you out of an electric chair.
This is about survival,
Dex, nothing else.
Got it?
You've got a visitor, Perry.
- Miss me?
- Don't flatter yourself.
I have to comb through your
case before the trial,
make sure I have
my facts straight
on the notorious
ice-truck killer.
Um, I confessed.
What more do you need?
The evidence to line up.
We haven't been able to match
your prints against the partial
on the lozenge wrapper we found
at the abandoned hospital.
Liquid nitrogen --
I use it to freeze the body parts.
It's extremely effective,
but it burns like a bitch.
Oh.
Or you knew your
prints wouldn't match,
so you purposely burned
your fingertips to hide it.
Are you suggesting
that I'm a liar?
Just covering my bases, Neil.
We both want the same thing.
Uh... 10 minutes
alone with Angelina?
To see you convicted.
What's in it for me if
I help you do your job?
Hmm...
How about immortality?
We found your mother's
body under your house.
Now, you can go down as a
pathetic loser who killed mom
or the most heinous killer
in Florida's history --
your choice.
If I'm going to become a legend,
I need to be memorialized.
I want a reporter here to
interview me -- front page.
You're not allowed to talk to
the press before the trial.
If you want me to cooperate,
I'm sure you'll find a way.
Meridian had one thing right.
I do crave control.
The longer the ice-truck killer
maintains radio silence,
the less control I have.
Craigslist --
it's desperate, I know,
but apropos.
Personal ads are filled
with desperation.
"Tyler from Key West,"
"speedos tanning on the beach,"
"touched your tits
on Friday night" --
At least these folks
aren't just standing by
waiting for something to happen,
and neither am I.
"Dear Ken, I'm in pieces.
Why the cold shoulder?
Love, Barbie."
Hey, I got it.
Thanks.
Hey, I know you --
Monday night at Meridian's.
You're always leaving your 7:00
when I'm arriving for my 8:00.
- You missed last week, right?
- No, I was there.
I don't remember ever
seeing you, though.
- How do you like him?
- Meridian?
Best thing that's ever
happened to me...
so far.
How about you?
You finding him helpful?
I'm a sociopath.
There's not much he can do for me.
Cute and funny.
Let me guess -- taken.
- Girlfriend.
- Lucky girl.
Well, thanks for the help,
but I can handle it from here.
All right.
So Meridian has an alibi
for the time of death.
My sexual hang-ups and
control issues aside,
I need a follow-up appointment
to dig a little deeper.
Isn't that what
therapy's all about?
Oh, my god.
I love your body.
I love your legs.
I love your arms.
I couldn't have made
them better myself.
Hey.
Are you crying?
I'm fine.
Then what?
I don't know.
I'm sure this is really hot,
crying after sex.
Everything about you is hot.
Tell me what you're feeling.
It's...
It's just...
Every time I've ever been
naked with someone...
..we just fuck.
But not this time?
This is different.
It feels like...
I hate saying this.
It sounds so fucking cheesy.
It feels like making love.
Ew.
Yes.
But, ew,
promise me you'll never say that again.
What if I do?
Are you gonna cry about it?
You're so fucked up.
What's up, rock star?
Look at you.
What you doing? Hey.
Where's the supervisor?
Oh, she called on my
cell and canceled.
Who wants to play monster tag?
- I do.
- Yeah?
I'm coming after you.
You better run.
Paul, you know you're not
allowed unsupervised visits.
I know.
Big bad Paul needs a babysitter.
It's your day off, right?
Now, would it really be so terrible
if we spent time with
our kids together?
- I have a lunch date with Dexter.
- Come on. It'll be fun.
Mom, dad, come on.
I guess I could call Dexter.
It's official --
I'm nominating you for mom of the year.
Here comes the monster.
Contrary to what Dr.
Meridian thinks,
I don't always keep
others at a distance.
Things are looking up already.
Hey Barbie how would you
like to suck my cock?
Or not.
Clearly nobody here is my
missing partner in crime.
Hey, what's up?
You were looking for me?
What did forensics come
back with on Vanessa Gayle?
Gunpowder on her hand,
none on her husband's,
high-angle trajectory,
no drugs in the tox screen.
It all points to suicide.
- No chance it was murder?
- Too bad, huh?
I had the husband pegged, too.
Was hoping he could help me
score my own sugar mama.
- Try Craigslist.
- I already did --
Nothing but cat ladies
and saggy tits.
Miami Metro can close
this case as a suicide,
but I'm still not convinced.
Maybe my new therapist can
shed some light on my doubts.
You seem on edge today.
I'm not getting what
I came here for.
What'd you come here for?
We established in our last visit that
it wasn't to talk about suicide.
- Or feelings.
- Heaven forbid.
So, what do you
want to talk about?
Fakes --
people who pass themselves
off as something they're not.
- Like a pre-owned-car salesman?
- A brave politician.
- A jew for Jesus.
- A wolf in sheep's clothing.
Is that how you feel, Sean?
Like you're hiding
a dark secret?
- No, I wasn't talking about me.
- Who were you talking about?
You.
That's a common first-time
reaction to therapy.
You think I can't
care about you,
that I'm only pretending to care
because I have another motive.
- Bingo.
- You got me.
I do have another motive.
It's called a paycheck.
But that doesn't mean that
I can't care for my patients
or enjoy my job.
How are things at your job?
Frustrating, to
tell you the truth.
- What kind of forensics do you do?
- Blood spatter.
Most people can't stand blood.
I hate it.
Categorizing and analyzing
must be very soothing for you.
Yeah, it is, actually.
So, okay,
how are things with your girlfriend?
She canceled lunch with me
to be with her ex-husband.
Ouch.
Sounds like things are out
of your control right now.
No wonder you cut yourself
off from your emotions.
That way you never have
to feel powerless.
So, then, what should I do?
Accept that certain things
are out of your hands.
Let go.
Hey, Morgan -- I can't believe,
out of two million sperm,
you were the fastest swimmer.
What are you gonna do about it?
I wanted to kill him, dad.
It must have been tough
for you to walk away, son.
I'm proud that you did that.
Don't be,
because I still want to kill him.
When's that gonna go away?
I think I have everything I need,
Mr. Perry.
When's the story gonna run?
Well, they're saving space for tomorrow,
front page.
I just got to get
back and write.
Thanks so much for your time.
- How was your interview?
- It was fine.
You ready to talk
about the case?
Sure, as soon as I get
to talk to a reporter.
- You just did.
- Oh, give me a break.
That poser was one
of your cop buddies,
but nice try.
In case you forgot, Neil,
you're the one in jail.
I call the shots.
I could invoke my Miranda rights
at any time and lawyer up.
If you wanted a lawyer
you'd have one by now.
I know your game, lieutenant.
You think I'm a fraud and
you're trying to prove it,
but the truth is
you're the fraud.
You know what, Neil?
I'm really not in the
mood for your shit today.
I found out how
you got promoted.
Back when you and sergeant
Doakes were still partners,
Doakes got the drop on
a major coke dealer,
- brought you along for the ride.
- How did you get --
when the perp bailed from
a third-story apartment,
Doakes took the fire escape,
sent you to cover the
stairs just in case.
Only you got lucky
and you made the headline grab,
and so the legend began.
I wonder if Doakes would
have made a good lieutenant.
- I deserved that promotion.
- I'm sure you did.
It was a big bust.
Not as big as
catching me, of course, but, uh,
let's be honest.
You didn't catch me.
Your captain did.
At least that's what
they're saying on the news.
My therapist wants me to accept the
things that are out of my hands.
Tragically for him,
he's not out of my hands,
not if I can find proof
that the death of at least
three women under his care
was not a coincidence.
Where are you? Rita.
Breaking and entering.
I hope he got my good side.
Now, what's he recording
for posterity's sake?
Goodbye, Dexter.
Hello, ladies.
I need another prescription.
I'm sorry, Vanessa.
I can't do that.
Just one more, please.
We talked about this.
The antidepressants
were a temporary crutch
so that you could start
taking steps on your own.
But you don't understand.
I can't do this on my own.
I can't even get
out of fucking bed.
I just -- I want to die.
Look at me.
I understand the
appeal of death, okay?
No more pain.
All the career pressure,
the hopelessness, gone.
In many cultures,
there's no stigma attached
to taking one's life.
Suicide's respected,
even revered as a matter
of personal conscience.
How do most people do it?
Well, painkillers
are the most common.U KNOW
But they're
entirely unreliable.
The truly courageous
of heart...
use guns.
You took women who trusted you at
their weakest possible moment,
and rather than help them,
you suggested they end it all.
God, you even gave them
permission to use a gun.
You're a mean one, Mr. Shrink.
Create their drug addiction,
pull them off,
then fill their addled heads
with noble thoughts of suicide.
I think I've had a
breakthrough in therapy.
Come over. I Need you. Rita.
Hey, I got your texts.
Is everything...
- ..okay?
- It is now.
Okay, just,
I wanted to see you.
I felt bad about missing lunch
to be with Paul and the kids.
I hope you didn't
get the wrong idea.
No, of course not.
How'd it go?
Really good and
incredibly scary.
For the first time
in a long while, I
saw how easy it would be for me
to fall back into my old life.
- Why is that scary?
- Because...
I like my new life.
And I finally feel
like I'm in control.
I never felt that
way with Paul.
I do with you.
This is a disaster.
I chose Rita because she was damaged.
If she gets better,
I'll lose her for sure.
I'm ready, Dexter.
Oh.
I don't know what I've
been so afraid of.
You're the perfect boyfriend.
I want you to spend the night,
for real.
I'm so sorry.
I came over here because I
thought something was wrong.
But tonight's really
not a good night.
I'm right in the middle of a case.
I'm way too distracted.
Now? It's so late.
That's all the more reason
to get back to work.
The clock's ticking. Here.
But I'll call you
tomorrow. Okay?
Okay.
Shit.
I can't have sex with Rita.
Every time I sleep with a woman,
she sees me for what I really am --
empty --
and then she's gone.
But I don't want Rita to go,
which means I have
to deal with this.
I can't kill Meridian yet.
I need another therapy session.
Stay where you are. I'm armed.
With bad puns?
You said you needed a favor.
What's up?
Take off your pants.
Oh, I should have known it
was that kind of favor.
You never ask me to
come by before work.
No, but I like
the way you think.
I have a patient
who lost both her legs
in a car accident,
- really brutal.
- Like your mom?
Which is why I want to do
something special for her.
I want to give her a new
smokin' pair of legs --
- yours.
- No.
- Let me just take a cast.
- No way. no.
It'll take 20 minutes, tops.
Come on, please?
Stop being such a chick.
Sit down.
Feels good.
Can I make one of your cock?
That'd be a hell of a story
to tell the bullpen, huh?
Not likely.
I haven't told anyone about us.
Embarrassed about
banging Captain Hook?
- Not even a little.
- Then why?
I guess this matters to me.
So if I talk about
it and it goes away,
I'm actually losing something.
That retarded?
No.
But I got to tell you,
I'm not going anywhere.
Seriously?
And neither are you,
'cause I got your leg.
- Where the hell you been?
- With my boyfriend.
- Boyfriend?
- Yep.
We just fucked in his office.
And we're having
dinner tomorrow night.
- You looking for me?
- Yeah. Shut the door.
Did you tell anyone
about our bust,
the one that got me promoted?
No.
Nobody in the press?
Maria, we talked about
this when it happened.
It would fuck up your rep and
make me look like a whiny bitch.
It's bad for both of us.
So then the only way to
access that information
would be to read to
police report, right?
I guess.
We have to have our
firewall checked.
She was sitting on top of me,
basically naked...
..asking me to spend the night,
and I didn't know what to do.
It's okay, Sean.
Don't beat yourself up.
Your girlfriend really means
something to you. I know that.
If she means something,
why do I run away from her?
The same reason you work so hard
to shut everybody else out.
You're afraid they won't
like what they see.
Yeah, I think you're right.
How can I change that?
Well, for starters,
you accept the fact
that we all have a big,
bad wolf hiding inside of us,
a darkness we don't want
anyone else to see.
- Do you?
- Of course I do.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
And how do you deal
with your wolf?
Well, first of all,
I accepted that it was there.
I made friends with it.
And now I just let it out for
a big meal once in a while.
At least three times
that we know about.
- Can we get back to the sex thing?
- This is all about sex.
The reason you avoid
sexual intimacy
is because you don't want
to surrender control.
No, I've surrendered control.
It's not like my
girlfriend hasn't been,
you know, south of the border.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Intimacy --
really letting go
face-to-face --
there's nothing more
difficult than that.
The minute you start
to accept who you are,
you just might feel free enough
to share that intimacy together.
What are you doing?
I'd like to talk you through
a deep-relaxation technique.
It might bring some
things to the surface.
What kinds of things?
There must have been
a time in your life
when you felt powerless, right?
Foster child,
no control over your destiny.
If we can bring some of those
memories to the surface,
we might find the root
of your control issues.
First, I want you
to close your eyes
and focus on your breathing.
I want you to count
each breath, okay?
In, 1,
and out, 2. Just give it a try.
This is ridiculous.
I could be killing him right now.
Now I want you to
think of a time
When you felt completely
and totally powerless.
Hey, Morgan.
You still fucking your sister?
Leave me alone, Josh.
I told you to walk away.
God damn it, Dexter.
There are consequences to
everything you do in life.
Lose control, become powerless,
and it's over.
- I found the grave, son.
- I'll be like this forever?
Mommy!
I have to get out of here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Whoa.
whoa. whoa. Sean, come here.
Sean, Sean. Sean!
Oh, my god.
Are you okay?
Stay.
Stay with me.
You're sweet.
I am?
Next time,
we'll figure out what to tell the kids
so you don't have to
sneak out like this.
You want there to
be a next time?
And a time after that.
Don't you?
No. I mean, yeah.
I just...
I didn't freak you out?
Why would you think that?
Dexter, there's nothing you could
ever do that would scare me away.
I really hope you
came to apologize.
Nope. I came for a consult.
And you brought beverages?
I got this on loan
from the morgue.
Now, I could use
an expert opinion,
specifically your
expert opinion.
See, we can't figure out
exactly how the killer
cut off this head.
- Can you?
- Nope.
Really?
I think you can.
I mean, you chop people up,
don't you?
- Maybe you need a closer look.
- No. Keep it away.
I talked to the
medical examiner.
He couldn't confirm
how your mom died.
Said it might have
been a heart attack.
- I killed her.
- You don't have the balls.
I mean, you had to wait till
she died to chop her up.
And even then you were too
squeamish to cut off her head.
Not exactly the same as
stuffing roadkill, is it?
Oh, fuck you.
?
Especially the ice-truck killer.
You know,
you're not the first groupie to take
credit for someone else's work.
Oh, bullshit.
?
things that weren't
published in the newspapers.
That's because you hacked
into our computer system.
? I had the I.T.
guys check our firewall.
The DMZ was breached.
You read all our police reports.
You even got yourself a nice
paneled car last month.
- Nice touch, by the way.
- Why are you doing this?
Because you're not a killer.
You're a coward and a fake,
aren't you?
- Maybe you need another look.
- No, take it away.
All right, I lied, okay?
Just, I need you to
take it away from me...
Please.
So, what's on your
mind, lieutenant?
We got a lot to get done
before Perry's trial.
Yeah, about that trial --
I've got some bad news.
Perry recanted his
confession this morning.
What are you talking about?
I was going over some
details with him at county,
and he admitted that he
gave us a false confession.
He's a wannabe, Tom.
Just wanted his 15 minutes,
that's all.
How do you know which
time he was lying?
All due respect, Maria,
if we dropped charges
every time someone
recanted his confession,
our jails would be empty.
We're going to trial.
All due respect, Captain,
that's really not up to you.
It's up to the D.A.
I understand your
frustration, Maria,
but I reviewed the D.A.
work sheets.
The evidence is compelling.
We'll move forward with
the trial as planned.
Fair enough.
If that's what you two want,
I'm fully behind it.
I was really worried about you.
You sure you're all right?
I kept calling your house,
but I think the number
you gave me didn't work.
You wouldn't have
reached me anyway,
'cause I was at
my girlfriend's.
I spent the
night,
face-to-face.
- Sean, that's very good.
It's all good, doctor.
I even stopped worrying about that
friend of mine who's been out of touch.
You can't control other people,
you know?
This is a real breakthrough.
You should be proud of yourself.
I am proud.
Truth be told, I never expected
to make progress in therapy.
That's not true.
If that were true,
you never would have come
in here in the first place.
What do you want
to focus on today?
Glad you asked that.
I'm gonna tell you something
- that I've never told anyone before.
- Okay.
I'm a serial killer.
Oh, god.
Oh, that feels
so amazing to say out loud.
Well, you must be letting go,
because I've never heard
you make a joke before.
I'm not joking. I kill people.
Whew! There it is again.
You should try it.
I know.
Your big, bad wolf has racked
up a tidy little death toll.
I'm just kidding.
I disabled the cameras,
and I copied the files.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Then focus on your breathing,
maybe you'll remember --
- Meghan, Carolyn, Vanessa.
- Those sessions are confidential.
I'm a control freak, I know.
But I watched your home movies.
It's amazing stuff --
drugs, guns,
and a crazy psychiatrist.
No wonder you're so well
versed in control issues.
You got quite the God complex.
This session's over.
Not so fast, doc.
You're awake.
Shall we analyze your dreams?
No. That's right.
You've already told me
everything I need to know,
except why powerful women?
You took powerful women
and made them powerless.
They left behind
families, children.
I have to confess,
I'm a little conflicted.
You've helped me make
a major self-discovery.
The fact that I'm a killer...
..that's something
I can't control.
You helped me to accept
what I really am.
I'm grateful for that. But...
I was raised with a
certain set of principles.
I'm sorry, doc. Actions have
consequences, and this is yours.
I'm gonna have to let you go.
* Jennifer's got daddy's car *
* she's playin' "uptown"
on the stereo *
* we go cruisin' so close *
* the way they did long ago *
* my darlin' *
* turn the radio up
for that sweet sound *
* hold me close,
never let me go *
* keep this feelin' alive,
make me lose control *
- Hello?
- Is that Eric Carmen?
No. What's up?
I'm running late.
I'm in the middle of some housework.
If I don't get it done,
it's gonna drive me crazy.
- I never knew you were so anal.
- And I'm a neat freak.
You're just full
of surprises, huh?
Oh, you have no idea.
I'll be there as
soon as I can, okay?
Okay.
Barbie, be patient.
One day we'll share a cold one. Ken.