Previously on Dexter.
It is my new friend.
When he broke into my apartment,
he took some time to get to know me --
my life, my secrets.
Same as the others -- no blood.
Somebody who was here
last night saw something.
They got a night watchman,
but we can't find him.
It's the guard -- Tucci.
I think he's alive.
Taking Tucci over to County.
Rudy here is gonna put
me back together again.
Yo, pretty boy,
you're stealing my thunder.
I don't know. I just might have
to fight you for this one.
How about you focus on
whether or not he was the man
you saw at the old hospital that night,
Mr. Perry?
It was difficult to tell.
It was dark.
Florida prisons kick free
25,000 inmates a year.
I search for the ones who
think they beat the system,
like Jeremy Downs.
Jeremy got off easy.
To the coroner,
the knife strokes looked random,
but I saw the work
of a young virtuoso.
Are you gonna fuck me, faggot?
'Cause I killed the
last guy who raped me.
I understand now.
Jeremy didn't murder
that boy four years ago.
He was taking out the garbage.
Wait, is that all?
The FBI estimates that there
are less than 50 serial killers
active in the United
States today.
We don't get together at conventions,
share trade secrets,
or exchange christmas cards...
But sometimes I wonder what
it's like for the others.
The only sound I hear,
the only sound in
the entire world...
...is my heart beating.
I swear to Christ,
Morgan, after this case,
I'm submitting your ass
for psychiatric evaluation.
I'm just retracing
castoff patterns,
directionality angles.
Can you tell us what
happened here or not?
- It's an execution.
- Unlikely victim.
The kid's an honor student,
editor of his school yearbook.
It's all in the knife work.
It's skillful, no wasted motion.
The killer had experience.
Every stroke hit a major artery...
Or at least came close.
Are you getting a goddamn
hard-on there, Morgan?
It's trully horrific.
He was yearbook committee, you said?
I want your report
on this tomorrow.
I wish I could say
Sergeant Doakes
is my biggest problem right now,
but he's not.
I've seen these wounds before.
You're drooling on
Laguerta's couch.
- You pulling a midnight shift?
- Lopez has the trots.
- Why are you still here?
- Why not?
Nothing at home except an
empty fridge and an empty bed.
If I wasn't married
and 10 years younger...
I'd still be in high school.
Keep dreaming.
Wiseass.
I've been chasing leads
on the ice-truck killer.
- Pathetic long shots, mostly.
- Yeah? What kind of leads?
I looked at the research.
With mass murderers,
it's dumb shit that
trips them up.
Son of sam got a parking ticket
outside his own crime scene.
So you ran parking violations at
the crime scenes of our guy? Smart.
Yeah, but none of the registered
owners had criminal records.
Try "moving violations."
Timothy McVeigh drove way too
fast on the way out of town.
Neil Perry -- I know that name.
Yeah, he came forward as
a witness two weeks ago
when pieces of Tony Tucci
were showing up around town.
He rode through a
stop sign two blocks
from the third crime scene
at the Seven Seas motel.
Why would a voluntary witness be
at two separate crime scenes?
I don't know.
Maybe he was chopping up hookers.
- Holy mother of fuck, is this him?
- Let's find out.
Are you sure this is
the right address?
According to DMV,
this is where Perry lives.
With his seven inbred cousins,
by the look of it.
Something has got to be wrong with
somebody that can live in a steel box.
Aluminum, actually.
Nina and I had a
deluxe multisectional.
- For real?
- It was our starter home.
This is our car.
One of the victims was seen getting in
a wood-paneled station wagon
on the night of her death.
Let's take one step at a time.
Let's find our guy.
According to his files, he works as
a computer analyst for Miami Lake.
Now maybe...
Look up... slowly.
All right, take the front door.
Cover all the exits.
I'm going to the back.
Open up, Perry!
It's the police!
Open up, Perry! Police!
Open up, Perry!
Open the door!
Hey, Angel, I got him!
Police! Stop running, Perry!
Get the fuck down!
Fuck!
I knew I recognized the knife
work of the killer.
Jeremy Downs.
I had him. He was mine...
Until I found out the boy
Jeremy killed raped him...
He fucked me and I killed him.
So I let Jeremy go.
It seemed fair.
But my random act of
kindness was misguided.
If I had followed my instincts,
this boy's high-school yearbook
would still have an editor.
Captain Matthews is coordinating the
FDLE to launch a statewide manhunt...
The task force will tear apart
the house for any evidence
that links Neil Perry to
the ice-truck murders.
We need proof this time, people --
tangible proof.
What is it?
They really found
the ice-truck killer?
I did.
Yes, yes.
We will financially guarantee
extradition from anywhere. James?
Yeah, I'm on it, lieutenant.
I'll run the task force.
Actually I need you and Pullman to stay with
the knife victim in the alley.
- His parents are high-profile.
- Whatever you need.
Angel... You found Perry.
You run the task force.
Contact the fugitive's friends,
family, co-workers, coke dealer --
anybody who might
try to hide him.
- You want us to circulate his photo?
- In neighborhoods only.
Keep it away from the media.
This case stays low-profile.
The last thing I need is
another tony Tucci on my hands.
- Anything else, lieutenant?
- Yes --
choose task-force members who can
put their regular duties aside
and bust ass until Neil
Perry's apprehended.
- Dominic.
- Okay, that's all. Thank you.
- Do you really think this is the guy?
- It's all lining up.
I saw him, Dex. I chased him.
Debra Morgan. Get over here.
You're on the team.
Do you hear that?
I'm on the team.
Do you think we get hats?
Hardly looks a guy capable
of terrorizing Miami.
A science camp, maybe.
I'm off.
I'll keep you in the loop.
- Where's my blood report, Sparky?
- I'm on it, sergeant.
- How you doing, Mrs. Bennett?
- Hey, Charlie.
Where are the kids?
Your husband swung by a few minutes ago.
He didn't tell you?
I never seen Cody light
up like that before.
Big treat --
the old man coming down.
Wait, wait. Wait. Paul?
Yeah. He just picked up the kids.
You gave my children to Paul?
Are you stupid?
I told the
administrative office
that Cody and Astor are not to
be released into his custody!
- Well, nobody told me.
- He just got out of fucking jail!
Everyone, follow strict,
sterile protocol.
There will be no contamination
of my crime scene.
Bag anything that could be used to
murder or dispose of a human body.
That's pretty much
everything in here, boss.
Except this.
Can you say "sick fuck"?
Some might say that.
To others,
crypto-taxidermy is a fine art.
I got a mummified
chupacabra at home.
Can I have permission to run Masuka's
prints as the ice-truck killer?
I'll give you some
warm DNA right now.
God, you're gross.
I didn't hear that.
Detective, I found something.
An archive of hidden files.
A lot of how-to documents --
draining blood from cattle,
wartime amputation techniques.
"Butchering the human carcass"?
There's even an article about countries
that don't extradite to the U.S.
- We got this fucker.
- We got jack shit, Morgan.
Everything in here
is circumstantial.
We need some hard evidence.
HEY I'm not done looking yet. Are you?
The school had no right to
release my children to Paul.
- No, they didn't.
- He lost his custody rights
right around the time my head
hit the living room wall.
I would think so.
I should be out
looking for my kids.
Rita, the best thing you
could do for the kids
- is stay here in case he calls.
- What if he doesn't?
What if he kidnapped them to get
back at me for putting him in jail?
Dexter, I --
- Hi.
- I got you.
Astor!
Mom, look -- it's dad.
He came home.
Yeah. What,
you think I was gonna move to the moon?
Stop it. Just stop.
Do you know I called the police?
Why? I told you I was
taking tm to the carnival.
- No, you didn't.
- Rita, I called you at the hotel.
They said you were on a break,
so I left a message with
the info and my cell number.
Uh, hi. How are you?
I'm Paul Bennett,
father on parole.
Uh, Dexter Morgan.
Uh, I can't think of
anything clever to say.
Paul, this is unacceptable.
I have custody.
You can't just take them
without my permission.
I came to see my babies.
I missed them, Rita.
I missed a lot of things.
I should phone the station,
call off the dogs.
- Dexter, look -- my dad's home.
- Yeah, I see that, buddy.
Hey, Angel.
You're the expert on
manufactured living.
This closet look a
little small to you?
A little.
Sweet.
I've got newspaper articles.
"Dismembered body
found in a pool."
"Ice-truck killer
appalls Miami."
This is a record of
everything he's ever done.
I got photos.
?
Did we release those
photos to the press?
- No.
- Did he take them himself?
He had to.
- Did we just hit the mother lode?
- No.
We hit the motherfucking
mother lode.
The evidence just keeps
piling up at the mobile home.
I just authorized an
excavation of the back patio.
I think there's
something buried there.
What are we doing
to find Neil Perry?
I put his name in the automated
system and notified the FBI.
Airports on alert?
Airports, train stations,
bus lines.
We should track
his credit cards.
Already done,
along with A.T.M.s and bank accounts.
I also put a tap
on his home phone.
- Seems you thought of everything.
- It seems that way.
- Look, Maria --
- No need to apologize.
I don't require your
approval to do my job.
I know that.
I've been kicking your ass 'cause
I knew you had this in you.
Well, thank you for making
me the woman I am today.
I love you to everything.
I love you to everything, too.
He's not gonna hit you anymore.
He told me at the carnival.
I made him promise.
Thank you, baby.
I haven't had time to
process as much as the kids.
Paul was supposed to be
locked up for another year.
Cody seems to be
processing okay.
Cody's too young.
A dad's just a concept to him,
not a person.
But Astor --
she remembers what
he put us through.
Well, at least you're
not married anymore.
That's just it.
Technically, we are.
When Paul went to prison,
I started divorce proceedings,
but he refused to
sign the paperwork.
As a power play?
I don't think so.
I think for all the
darkness that haunts him,
Paul loves having a family.
I think he's just
afraid to let go.
When did you first notice it?
This darkness inside
the guy you fell for.
I always knew it was there.
I guess I just didn't
think I deserved better...
Till I met you.
I have a dark side, too.
What? I do.
Somehow I doubt that.
You have a good heart, Dexter.
You're not like Paul.
You don't hurt people.
Innocent people.
I don't hurt innocent people.
Hey, dude,
the bowling alley's around the corner.
Hey, I'm looking
for Jeremy Downs.
Jeremy? He vacated
the premises.
Focus. I'm trying
to find Jeremy.
Oh, I get it.
Look, man,
I'm not really into
that homo shit,
but I'm kind of short
on money for weed,
so I guess I'll do it for
less than Jeremy's charging.
- Wait. What does Jeremy charge?
- Jeremy's selling himself?
He's always hanging out with the
brokeback boys down at Flamingo Park.
Comes back with
fistfuls of cash.
It's me.
Get your ass over to Neil Perry's place.
- You're gonna want to see this.
- Deb, it's my day off.
Just get your ass over here.
We're about to bust open the
goods on the ice-truck killer.
Not what I expected.
So lifelike.
Hey, Dex.
I thought you'd want to be here.
Something's buried down there.
Masuka's been digging all night.
I hate to break
this to you, Deb,
but you know you've got
the wrong guy here, right?
The ice-truck killer drains
the blood from his victims,
freezes their bodies,
and only then severs their limbs.
It's clean and efficient --
his psychological signature.
Neil Perry, on the other hand,
stuffs roadkill.
Yeah, and turns it into
fucked-up fantasy shit.
But the fantasies are all wrong.
The guy we're looking for
wouldn't turn dead,
dirty things into living cartoons.
- He'd find that pathetic.
- How do you know?
Because it is pathetic.
Deb, trust me.
Neil Perry is not a killer.
He's a dabbler.
He's a waste of time.
If the guy we're looking for took
his early fantasies out on animals,
he'd bury them,
not display them.
And want about an early human kill?
Would he bury that, too?
- Sure. Probably.
- Then turn around.
You were saying?
It looks like an adult female.
Any idea how long the
body's been down there?
Based on decomposition,
she's been tits up for two,
maybe three years.
We'll know more
after the autopsy.
What happened to the limbs?
Did they rot off?
No. They're clean cuts.
But he didn't chop
up the whole body.
This could be
Perry's first kill,
like he was experimenting.
You're the expert, Dex.
What do you think?
Sure. Sounds good.
Actually, it sounds
perfectly awful.
For weeks, I've felt like a
student in a master class.
Is it really possible that
the master's on the run?
And even more tragic,
does he live in a double-wide?
The gravitron goes
so fast, mom.
My dad took me on
it three times.
Wow. Is that so?
All right,
let me cut you guys up some fruit.
Astor wouldn't go.
She was afraid.
So what?
I don't like fast rides.
Shh!
Hello?
- Who wants doughnuts?
- I do.
Paul, you can't just walk
in here whenever you want.
You don't live here anymore.
Oh. Sorry about that.
Old habits.
I'll ring the
doorbell next time.
I got these for you.
All right.
I'll just put them in, uh, something.
Dad, can I have a doughnut?
You got it, buddy. Coming up.
What, now you're making
me out to be the bad guy?
They haven't had breakfast yet.
You know what? Kidlet, my bad.
Sorry about that.
These doughnuts are
for after school.
But I could whip up
some eggs and pancakes.
- Paul!
- Very little syrup, I promise.
And meat
You into neat?
- Uh-huh.
I like meat
I like meat on my feet.
It's real squishy.
Paul. You can't do
this anymore, Paul.
What?! What?!
Help raise my kids?!
Yes, I can. That's my job.
All right, look.
I can't even begin to understand
how difficult this has been for you,
Rita, being a single mom, okay?
And for that,
I'm eternally sorry.
I let you down.
I let everybody down.
But if I could just
find that frying pan.
Astor... want to help
me find the frying pan?
We got a profile of Neil Perry.
He's a computer expert.
I.Q. off the chart.
He's a loner, no pryors.
His father split when he was 6.
His mother was an alcoholic, abusive,
and possibly his first victim.
Roberta Perry.
Dental records say she was
the one under the patio.
Now, Neil kept her death quiet
by cashing her social-security
checks for the last two years,
but he did not kill her
for the money.
Morgan?
We think he wanted release.
Roberta Perry ran
her son's life,
controlled him,
beat him as a kid.
We think he dreamt about
killing her for years.
I just spoke with Perry's
cellphone provider.
Can they track his location?
No signal --
he probably turned off his phone.
But, according to records,
he used it
on some of the nights the ice-truck
killer victims were taken.
Who did he call?
Voice mail, mostly,
checking messages.
Verizon triangulated
the location.
All the calls came
from the same place --
a six-block area on
southwest 8th street.
The Tamiami trail.
That strip's full of no-tell motels.
It's like a happy hunting
ground for hookers.
There's a good chance that's
where he's killing his victims.
Let's recanvass
the area for leads.
Now that we've got
a photo of this guy,
maybe we can find somebody
who actually saw him.
Let's go.
You're starting
to look like her.
Want to stop by your house,
check in with your family?
I'd rather check in
with your brother.
His instincts are usually
pretty good on this stuff.
Yeah, not today.
He'd just piss on our parade.
He needs his day off.
The first time I saw his work,
I felt like a spanish explorer landing
of the shores of the new world.
No blood in the victims,
no spatter, no stain.
Deb is wrong about him.
It's okay.
Hell, I've made mistakes.
In fact, I'm about to
correct a big one right now.
Jeremy Downs.
Hey, you want company?
Just keep walking
and looking ahead.
There's some mangroves over by the lake.
We can go in there.
It's too public.
My car's in the parking lot.
- Are your windows tinted?
- I said, "eyes front."
What's wrong?
Shit. Shit.
Get the fuck out of my way!
Take it easy, Jeremy!
Stay right there!
Take him down! Take him down!
Hands behind your back.
Stand up! Stand up!
Miami Metro P.D.
Can we have a minute?
Yeah.
- This guy look familiar?
- I don't know.
They come. They go.
You get it? They "come."
Look, my feet are aching
from pounding the pavement.
You think you
could help us out?
- What's your name?
Laline Consuelo Garci? G?mez.
Laline...
O?ste del hombre que
le dicen el ice-truck killer?
- S?.
- Puede ser el.
So let's try this again.
Have you seen this man?
He's a regular.
Rents a room by the month -- cash.
When was the last
time he was here?
He's here now. He brought a
girl to his room this morning.
A working girl? A hooker?
- What's the room number?
- 20. Here's the master.
Call for backup.
Let's hope this girl is still alive.
- Do we wait for tactical?
- Not with a possible victim in there.
Clear.
It's okay. We're here now.
You're safe.
Please get me out -- hurry --
before he comes back!
- Where is he?
- Please, I want to get out!
Where was he going?
The liquor store.
He said he's coming right back.
What?
Hey, where's Doakes?
He paged me.
We need your report from
that kid in the alley.
But it's my day off.
I was just at Don Shula's
famous golf course.
- Did you finish your report or not?
- Yeah, it's in my lab.
Wait. I'm on to you.
Excuse me?
Your crazy-ass,
knife-slashing two-step in the alley.
You were right.
You said the killer had
previous experience. He did.
Oh. Really?
Masuka lifted a print from the
alley that matched a kid from juvie.
Cut up a victim five years ago.
Same knife technique.
We just grabbed him
at Flamingo Park.
Great work, sergeant.
Yeah. Your instincts
were dead-on.
They're always dead-on when it
comes to killers. Why is that?
I'll just go get that report.
I'm watching you.
Miss me?
Police. On the ground.
Get down slowly.
Now the day is over
Night is drawing nigh
Get down!
The shadows of the evening
steal across the sky
- I said get the fuck down!
- Now the darkness gathers
- Facedown -- let's go!
- Stars begin to peep
birds and beasts and
flowers
soon will be asleep
What else do you want to
put in the concoction?
Gummi bears.
How do you two plan to eat that,
spread it on toast?
It already has toast in it.
So it does.
Keep mashing.
I'll get the door.
Oh. Hey, there, big guy.
Uh, Dexter, right?
Paul, hi. Rita's not here.
Oh, that's okay.
I'm actually here for the kids.
I came to dazzle
them with my booty.
This booty.
This is awkward.
I'm afraid I'm not comfortable
letting you inside the
house without Rita here.
Who are you, anyway,
like, the babysitter?
I'm watching the
kids right now,
so I suppose that makes
me the babysitter.
Are you fucking my wife?
I'll let Rita know
you stopped by.
Or I could just walk in.
It's my house.
I own this place.
I bet she didn't tell you that, did she?
Homeowner issues are
way over my head.
I should probably just call the police,
let them sort this out.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Yeah, why don't you...
give those presents
to my little buckets of sunshine,
tell Rita she can reach
me at the Motor Court?
Okay.
He might be a crack-addled,
wife-abusing yahoo,
but he refuses to
abandon his kids.
I'm not sure that's
a good thing.
Take him on in.
I'll be right there.
You got it.
Congratulations. You
just brought down
the most notorious serial
killer in Florida history.
Fucking "a." He's in
booking right now.
It sucks you weren't
a part of this.
I mean, you and me --
we paved the way for this, right?
I'm cool.
I've got my own bad guy.
Listen, I just picked up
a message from Tony Tucci.
Our favorite fun-loving amputee's
getting out of the hospital.
- There's a party tonight.
- No, thanks.
I don't want to go, either.
But the guy lost body parts, and we
get to tell him we caught the guy.
- What else you got going on?
- Wouldn't you like to know?
There will be hookers there.
All right. Fine, Mr.
grumpy head. Have it your way.
Did he threaten you?
No. Nothing like that.
He was just marking his territory.
Fucking bastard.
Only you could make
those words cute.
Stop it.
Paul said he owns this house.
Is that true?
Yeah. Yeah.
I think he got it
in a drug trade.
- Dex, what am I gonna do?
- I'd start by getting a divorce.
God, this is such a mess,
and I've dragged you into it.
There, there.
I just wish --
I just wish he'd go away.
Why can't he just go away
and disappear forever?
He can do that --
very easily.
Oh, shit. Fuck.
- We -- we need to talk.
- Yeah.
Just let me grab my heart
up off the fucking floor.
Holy fuck, Rita. Whew.
Come on in.
Uh, no.
No, I'm good right here.
Aw, come on.
Don't be that way. Come on in.
I got a six-pack
chilling in the cooler.
No. No more.
What?
No more surprise
visits to the house,
no more intimidating my friends,
and especially
no more Disney dad.
You lost your right to be a father when
you beat your children's mother.
If you want to get to
know Astor and Cody,
you're gonna have to
work for that privilege.
Whoa, whoa, babe,
can I get a word in here?
No. Divorce papers.
They're the ones you
refused to sign in prison.
Sign them now, and I'll agree to
supervised visits twice a week.
Show me you can do that for six months,
and then maybe --
maybe -- I'll think about
a nonsupervised schedule.
Is this some kind
of joke, Rita?
You think you can really
make me back down?
No, I don't.
But what else am I gonna do, Paul?
A judge put me in control.
I'm in control now,
and I have the power to make sure
you never see your children again
unless you do exactly
as I tell you.
Goddamn, you are fine
when you're mad.
I love the new you.
I do. My ass is yours to kick.
I deserve it. Here -- look.
Rita, I'm a changed man,
and I swear to God --
I am going to prove it to you.
All right. There she is.
Anybody bring any popcorn?
You got him.
Both of them.
- Where's Perry's lawyer?
- He waived the right.
I can't hear a thing.
Who's got the remote?
There they are --
my two colleagues...
...technically speaking.
Thankfully, one of
them's a fraud.
..because you assume that.
So you can assume I killed them.
You can assume anything that you want.
The doer
is merely a fiction that's
added to the deed -- the deed.
The deed is everything.
At least I hope he's a fraud.
Whoa! Here's to my new hand.
Some say bravery
is being the only one
who knows you're afraid.
But I've worked with a lot of amputees,
and I got to say --
I don't think tony
knew he was afraid.
Here's to one crazy bastard.
Kiss my atrophied ass.
- Now for the main event.
- Medical marijuana?
You wish.
Can you, uh, help me out here, Rudy?
Whoo!
Look at that shit.
Half human, half machine.
But all man, baby.
I got it.
Yeah.
May I have this dance?
Hey, buddy, you might have
a chance with me, after all.
Oh, don't worry. There's still
plenty enough of me to go around.
So, you made that
hand and foot?
Mm-hmm.
You did a good thing.
Tony lost a piece of himself,
and I helped him find it.
I mean, how often in life do
you get to make someone whole?
I wouldn't know.
It's like living art -- what you do.
It's funny you should
say that, because
before I turned to prosthetics,
I, uh,
studied the human form at the
university of Paris -- Sorbonne.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Have you had dinner yet?
- I would love to.
Uh, I thought I'd come
and show my support.
- Bad timing?
- No. No.
Um, have some
champagne, sergeant.
See, we got blogs.
We got podcasts.
You know,
the information won't stop.
It comes into your head
and bleeds out your eyes,
and it's all crap, you know?
See, you got to
dare for greatness
these days to get
people's attention.
Hmm.
Mm-hmm. Did I get yours?
Ohh. This is worse
than foreplay.
Why doesn't she ask
him any questions?
I have no idea what she's doing,
but my patience is wearing thin.
I gave Jeremy a chance,
and he blew it.
Is this one going to
disappoint me, too?
That's an interesting
interview technique.
I'm tired of asking questions.
You're getting off on
this too fucking much.
- Getting off on what?
- The game.
I'm guessing that's why you
didn't request a lawyer --
so you can sit here and say
whatever shit comes into your head.
Meanwhile, my ass is
spreading like cheez whiz,
waiting for you to figure
out this isn't the fun part.
What are you talking about?
We got you dead to rights.
But the good times won't start
rolling till you're in a courtroom
with your own
personal judge Ito
and Court TV carrying your scary-ass
scowls and crazy-shit live.
Fascination with serial
killers is an american pastime.
You've got groupie housewives,
magazine profiles,
maybe even a summer
blockbuster movie...
All waiting for you.
But the feeding frenzy won't
start till you throw out the chum.
Until then,
I'm just gonna chill.
You're right.
Yeah. This isn't the fun part.
The fun part...
was hanging them like cattle.
Hanging who?
The hookers...
Right before I cut their throats.
Son of a bitch.
I used gravity roots to
hang them upside down
to drain the blood. Then...
That shit is privileged.
The press never got ahold of that.
..I'd pour in liquid
nitrogen to freeze the blood
before I cut them into nice,
clean pieces.
Yes.
See, you got to understand --
I hate blood.
And there it is --
all the expectations I had,
all the promises of
greatness wiped out.
My circle of friends
is down to one.
How -- what are you doing here?
Are you a cop?
The cameras are off.
I have one minute.
Tell me why. I need to know.
- Why what?
- Don't!
You killed again.
I told you -- I warned you --
don't kill anyone who
doesn't deserve to die.
Why did you do it?
- To feel something different.
- Different than what?
What do you normally feel?
Nothing. Fucking
nothing at all.
I te every fucking
goddamn second of it.
I can't stand it --
living my life in my head.
Does killing make it better?
No.
Worse.
Fucking worse than ever.
Put your hands on the table.
Do it.
I'm a lot like you, you know?
Yeah, right. You're a killer?
I'm empty...
..but I found a way to make
it feel less bottomless.
- How?
- Pretend.
You pretend the feelings
are there for the world
and for the people around you.
Who knows?
Maybe one day they will be.
What the hell are
you doing, Morgan?
I'm scraping under the nails for blood.
Almost done.
Get out.
I want 10 more minutes with this
piece of shit before his lawyer shows.
Stand up!
Living my life in my head --
I know exactly
what Jeremy means.
At least I had
someone to talk to --
Harry, my foster father.
He spent endless hours
teaching me how to survive.
Excuse me,
are you Jeremy Downs' lawyer?
Yes, I am.
I'm just heading over to see him.
Sooner would be better.
- Seriously.
- Thank you.
My mom died when I was 16 --
cancer --
and then it was just me,
my brother, my dad.
- You have a brother?
- Yeah. Dexter.
He and my dad were
really tight.
They were always
spending time together.
I guess I was jealous.
What, you mean you weren't
daddy's little girl?
No, I was, kind of.
He just took a special interest in Dex,
you know?
I think that's why I became a cop.
That's what he was.
I thought maybe he would give
me more attention or something.
- And did he?
- Not really...
But we had our moments.
What about you?
How'd you become...
Captain hook?
Well, when I was little,
my mom got in a car accident,
and she lost both her legs.
That's terrible.
I remember when it happened,
I just wanted to put
her back together...
You know, like humpty-dumpty,
just the pieces weren't around.
I'm going to miss my playmate.
Sure, there's Rita and the kids,
but they don't know the real me.
They can never
know the real me.
And now the father is back.
Things have changed.
Everything has changed.
I always prided myself on
being an outsider, but now...
I feel the need to
connect with someone.
I saw myself in Jeremy...
But instead of helping
him like Harry helped me,
I gave him a piece of fortune-cookie
advice that he never even heard.
I failed him.
He deserves better...
And he'll get it from now on.
I guess I was wrong.
Jeremy did hear my advice.
He killed someone
who deserved to die.
What's the status on Perry?
I'm having him
transferred right now.
The D.A. wants to keep him at county,
pending arraignment.
Maria,
it was your decision making that
led to his capture and arrest,
and you made all our lives easier
by getting the bastard to confess.
I'm just doing my job.
It feels good to be
praising your police work
instead of your
politics for a change.
We need to make an
official comment.
Don't worry.
I'll keep it short.
I'm just heading downstairs
now for the press conference.
The press conference is over.
Oh, and, uh, don't worry.
I kept it short.
You got to be
fucking kidding me.
- That was my bust.
- This is my department.
Did you at least
give me credit?
Yes. I just gave it to you.
Haven't you been listening?
Ever since Harry's death,
I've been alone...
...but now,
for the first time...
I feel alone.
How long you need
with the prisoner?
As long as I can get.
Jeremy is gone,
and Neil Perry will soon vanish
into the catacombs
of the system.
I have so many
questions for him.
How did he discover my secrets?
What was his message to me?
He's been in my home,
my photos...
my life.
He knows me.
Now I need to know him...
...to connect face-to-face
before he's beyond
my reach forever.
Hi.
Who the fuck are you?