PREVIOUSLY ON "DEXTER"...
Dexter:
TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT.
AND IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
AGAIN AND AGAIN --
HAS TO HAPPEN.
THERE HE IS.
HE'S THE ONE.
[ CHOKING ]
YOU'RE MINE NOW,
SO DO EXACTLY AS I SAY.
YOU BETTER BE A COP.
NO -- FORENSICS.
THERE IS NO BLOOD
NEAR THE BODY AT ALL.
IT'S THE WEIRDEST THING
YOU EVER SAW.
I'VE NEVER SEEN SUCH CLEAN,
DRY, NEAT-LOOKING DEAD FLESH.
HOW DOES THE KILLER
GET RID OF THE BLOOD?
ONE OF THESE DAYS,
YOU'RE GONNA TELL ME.
I TOLD YOU BLOOD SPATTER
DOESN'T TAKE UP ALL MY TIME.
HOW THE HELL WAS YOUR DATE
WITH RITA LAST NIGHT?
GREAT.
SHE'S PERFECT BECAUSE RITA IS,
IN HER OWN WAY,
AS DAMAGED AS ME.
OPEN YOUR EYES
AND LOOK AT WHAT YOU DID!
Man: PLEASE,
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
TRUST ME.
I DEFINITELY UNDERSTAND.
[ WHIRRING ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAMS ]
HELLO?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?
JUST FINISHING UP A LITTLE
PROJECT, BUT I'LL COME BY LATER.
THEY FOUND
ANOTHER HOOKER.
THAT'S THE THIRD ONE
IN FIVE MONTHS.
THIRD?
YOU MEAN THERE'S A...
SERIAL KILLER,
THAT'S RIGHT.
There are people out there
who do really bad things.
You have to learn how to spot
them, but I can teach you.
THE KILLER FLAYED THE SKIN,
THE FLESH, COMPLETELY OFF.
NOW,
WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
HE'S EXPERIMENTING.
HE TRYING TO FIND THE RIGHT WAY.
HE'S CERTAINLY RAISING THE BAR.
DAMN, THIS GUY IS GOOD.
THE KILLER IS AN ARTIST.
YOU GIVE ME
THE FUCKING CREEPS.
YEAH, I KNOW.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
BUT NOW WE HAVE A FOURTH BODY,
AND THE CUTS WERE DIFFERENT.
AND THAT'S TELLING US A STORY.
THE RITUAL IS CHANGING.
I'D LIKE TO CHECK AND SEE
IF ANY REFRIGERATED TRUCKS
HAVE BEEN STOLEN
IN THE LAST WEEK OR SO.
[ GASPS ]
IT JUST SEEMS ODD.
YOUR SISTER HAS
THIS ICE-TRUCK THEORY,
AND THEN HERE YOU ARE
TO BACK IT UP.
SHE'S GOOD, LIEUTENANT.
YOU SHOULD GIVE HER A CHANCE.
I THINK
THIS IS A FRIENDLY MESSAGE.
"HEY, WANT TO PLAY?"
AND, YES, I WANT TO PLAY.
I REALLY, REALLY DO.
[ SIZZLING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ LEATHER CRUNCHING ]
[ FROGS CROAKING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
I DREAM.
I DREAM I'M FLOATING
ON THE SURFACE OF MY OWN LIFE,
WATCHING IT UNFOLD,
OBSERVING IT.
I'M THE OUTSIDER, LOOKING IN.
Man: HO HO!
HA HA!
[ LAUGHTER ]
YEAH!
OH, YOU WANT TO PLAY, MAN?!
COME ON!
IN THE WATER!
AAH!
WHOA!
LOOK AT THEM.
THEY CAN LAUGH AND PLAY.
IT COMES SO EASILY FOR THEM.
EVEN THOUGH
I'M NOT ONE OF THEM,
EVEN THOUGH SOMETIMES
I CAN REALLY BE A MONSTER...
TODAY, I'M JUST...
A SEA MONSTER.
SOON ENOUGH, I'LL HAVE TO GO
BACK TO DOING WHAT I DO...
SO I MAKE A POINT OF ENJOYING
DAYS LIKE THIS
WHEN I HAVE THEM.
[ AIR-CONDITIONER WHIRRING ]
JUST A SECOND.
THE ICE-TRUCK KILLER LEFT ME
A GRUESOME SOUVENIR.
EXPLAINING IT
COULD BE KIND OF...
AWKWARD.
HEY.
BAGELS, BROTHER --
LET ME IN.
COULD IT BE MORE DEPRESSING
IN HERE?
GOT ANYTHING TO DRINK?
IT'S HOT AS HELL OUT THERE.
O.J.?
WITH ICE.
SO, HOW YOU DOING?
I'M FINE.
YEAH, THINGS ARE FINE.
BREAKFAST, WHICH I ALREADY HAD,
WAS FINE,
BUT YOU KNOW ME --
I'M ALWAYS HUNGRY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
MMM.
SO, WHAT'S UP, HOTSHOT?
ALL RIGHT, GET THIS --
LIEUTENANT'S LOOKING
FOR THAT REFRIGERATED TRUCK
IN EVERY SWAMP, GLADE,
AND CHOP SHOP
FROM HERE TO THE KEYS.
BUT THE WAY I SEE IT,
THAT WHACKJOB TRUCK DRIVER
THREW A SEVERED HEAD
AT YOUR CAR.
IT'S NOT AS IF HE'S SHY.
YOU THINK HE'S HIDING THE TRUCK
IN PLAIN SIGHT,
WANTING IT TO BE FOUND?
I COULD ANSWER THAT
IF LaGUERTA DIDN'T HAVE ME
BACK WITH MY HOOKERS.
FINDING THAT TRUCK IS YOUR
GOLDEN TICKET INTO HOMICIDE.
JUST BECAUSE LaGUERTA HAS YOU
LOOKING FOR HOOKERS ON HER TIME
DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN'T LOOK
FOR THE TRUCK --
ON MY TIME.
HMM.
WHAT'S WITH THESE?
I'VE GOT COURT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
WHY IS IT WE NEVER TALK
BROTHER-SISTER STUFF?
OUR DAD WAS A COP.
YOU'RE A COP.
I WORK FOR THE COPS.
FOR US, THIS IS
BROTHER-SISTER STUFF.
BRINGS OUT YOUR EYES.
FIRST HE THROWS
A SEVERED HEAD AT ME,
THEN HE LEAVES ME
THESE DOLL PARTS,
LIKE PIECES OF A PUZZLE.
I LIKE PUZZLES.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
MORE FRUSTRATING
THAN PUTTING A PUZZLE TOGETHER
AND FINDING THAT IT STILL
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
Man: PLEASE STATE
YOUR NAME AND OCCUPATION.
MY NAME IS DEXTER MORGAN,
AND I'M A FORENSICS SPECIALIST
IN BLOOD-SPATTER ANALYSIS
FOR THE MIAMI METRO
POLICE DEPARTMENT.
AND HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
DOING BLOOD-SPATTER ANALYSIS?
ALMOST 12 YEARS.
YOU'VE BEEN INVOLVED
IN QUITE A FEW CASES, THEN.
2,103.
GIVE OR TAKE.
NO, 2,103.
THEN IT'S SAFE TO SAY
BLOOD IS YOUR LIFE.
SAFE TO SAY.
UNLIKE THE OTHER GUYS
DOWN AT THE STATION,
I LOVE COMING TO COURT
TO RUB SHOULDERS
WITH THE GOOD PEOPLE
OF THE SUNSHINE STATE...
AND SASQUATCH.
IN A COURTHOUSE, EVERYONE'S
ON THEIR BEST BEHAVIOR...
...LIKE THEY'RE BEING WATCHED.
AND THEY ARE.
SOME PEOPLE WOULD LOOK
AT THIS FAMILY
AND SEE ONLY TRAGEDY
AND HEARTBREAK.
BUT I SEE SO MUCH MORE
THAN THAT.
I'LL DO THIS, OKAY?
[ SIGHS ]
I SEE OPPORTUNITY.
ALEXANDER PRYCE FINISHED
HIS HOMEWORK, KISSED HIS MOM,
WENT OUT FOR A JOG.
HE TOLD HER HE'D BE BACK IN TIME
TO TAKE OUT THE TRASH CANS.
JUST ANOTHER NIGHT, UNTIL...
UNTIL THE DEFENDANT
NOT ONLY STRUCK HIM WITH HIS CAR
BUT FLED THE SCENE,
LEAVING ALEXANDER PRYCE
ALONE AND DYING FOR HOURS
BEFORE HIS BODY WAS FOUND
THE NEXT MORNING --
FROM HEINOUS TO UNSPEAKABLE.
THE PEOPLE WILL PROVE
THAT NOT ONLY DID MR. CHAMBERS
STRIKE AND KILL ALEXANDER PRYCE
BUT DID SO WHILE ONCE AGAIN
UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF ALCOHOL.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, ALEX!
THANK YOU.
RIP RIGHT INTO IT.
WHAT?
YEAH.
HOPE IT'S MONEY.
YEAH, YOU WISH.
OH!
THANKS, GUYS.
IT'S LIKE 80 DEGREES OUT.
BUT NEXT YEAR
AT THIS TIME,
WE'RE COMING TO VISIT YOU
AT HARVARD.
IT'S EVERYTHING I'VE EVER
WANTED FOR YOU, ALEXANDER.
THANKS, DAD.
ALL RIGHT,
ENOUGH CORNINESS.
Dexter:
I SEE THEIR PAIN.
ON SOME LEVEL,
I EVEN UNDERSTAND THEIR PAIN.
I JUST CAN'T FEEL THEIR PAIN.
IT JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE WE SEE HOW FAR
MATT CHAMBERS'S CROCODILE TEARS
WILL GET HIM.
BUT UNTIL THEN,
A LITTLE OF
MY FAVORITE TROPICAL FRUIT...
THE PERFECT DRIVING FOOD
NEXT TO A PULLED-PORK SANDWICH.
ALSO, I CAN KEEP MY ENERGY UP
FOR THE DAY JOB.
*VEN CONMIGO... *
*JUNTO A MI CORAZ?N *
*Y ME QUITE LA VIDA
SI NO TENGO TU AMOR *
Woman: DETECTIVE!
BUENA.
DID WE GET AN I.D.?
FIRST ON SCENE
PULLED THE WALLET.
WE'RE STILL WAITING.
HELLO, DEX.
HER BOSS --
LIEUTENANT LaGUERTA.
IN KEEPING WITH HER TOTAL SENSE
OF ENTITLEMENT,
SHE HAS THIS ATTRACTION TO ME.
AND I THOUGHT I WAS CREEPY.
GIVEN THE SKIN RUPTURE
AND THE SECONDARY SPATTER,
DISTANCE HAD TO BE
A 50-, 60-FOOT DROP.
THE EASTBOUND'S
ONLY 40 FEET.
IT'S NOT HIGH ENOUGH
FOR THIS KIND OF DAMAGE.
SO, BEST GUESS, ORIGINATING
POINT IS THE WESTBOUND CAUSEWAY.
HEY! GET ME A TEAM
ON THE WESTBOUND CAUSEWAY!
OH, SHE'S GOOD.
ANGEL, LOOK AT THIS.
I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING
IN HIS MOUTH.
MEDIC!
Ohh.
AH, IT'S JUST A DEATH RATTLE.
HE'S GONZO.
YOU BETTER CHECK
OUT MY FRIEND, TOO.
NO TELLING WHAT THIS GUY
MIGHT HAVE HAD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THIS IS WHAT HE HAD.
CALL ME CRAZY, ANGEL,
BUT I THINK THIS IS HUMAN FLESH.
[ SIGHS ]
HOOKED UP
WITH SEAN LAST NIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
THE CABLE-GUY SEAN?
[ Chuckling ]
OH, GOD, NO.
HE SMELLED LIKE CHEESE.
SO THE MECHANIC SEAN?
YEP.
HE CAME OVER.
WE OPENED A BOTTLE
OF PINOT GRIS.
WE FINISHED A BOTTLE
BEFORE I KNEW IT,
WE WERE --
STOP THAT.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO HEAR THIS, DO YOU?
NO.
BUT IF YOU TWO ARE GETTING
SERIOUS, I'D LOVE TO MEET HIM.
WHY DON'T YOU
AND SEAN THE MECHANIC
JOIN ME AND RITA THE GIRLFRIEND
FOR DINNER TOMORROW NIGHT?
WHY?
SO YOU CAN TELL ME LATER
HE'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH
FOR YOUR LITTLE SISTER?
DON'T.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WAS GOING ON
ABOUT BROTHER-AND-SISTER STUFF.
THAT BECOMES BROTHER-AND-SISTER
DOUBLE-DATING?
COME ON.
IT'LL BE FUN.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL GO, BUT I'M NOT
PROMISING WE'LL HAVE ANY FUN.
NOT NOW.
WHAT CRAWLED UP HIS ASS?
He hates lab rats.
WELL, HERE'S A HEADLINE --
IT'S LAB RATS
THAT MAKE US COPS LOOK GOOD.
OKAY, LISTEN UP.
WE JUST GOT AN I.D. ON THE BODY
FROM UNDER THE CAUSEWAY.
HIS NAME IS RICKY SIMMONS.
HE WAS A COP.
LET ME
ASK YOU SOMETHING.
YEAH.
WHEN WE WERE PARTNERS, YOU USED
TO USE EVERY EXCUSE IN THE BOOK
TO GET OUT OF MAKING
A NEXT-OF-KIN NOTIFICATION.
I KNEW RICKY FROM
THE DEPARTMENT SOFTBALL TEAM.
HE WAS A GOOD GUY, A GOOD COP.
IT'S THE LEAST I COULD DO.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
MOTHERFUCKER!
[ WOMAN SOBBING ]
CALL IT IN!
3H-77 TO DISPATCH.
WE NEED E.M.T.
AND POLICE BACKUP NOW.
I'LL CHECK THE HOUSE.
KARA, IT'S ME.
IT'S JAMES.
YOU'RE OKAY.
[ WOMAN SOBBING ]
HEY, IT'S ME.
IT'S OKAY.
THIS IS SO FUCKED-UP, MAN.
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
GOING AFTER
A COP'S FAMILY...
WHO WOULD DO SUCH A THING?
THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE.
BUT IT'S STILL FUCKED-UP.
THEY'RE TELLING ME RICKY SIMMONS
WAS UNDER DEEP COVER
IN CARLOS GUERRERO'S FAMILY.
ALL RIGHT. THANKS.
HE'D BEEN WORKING THE GIG FOR 10
MONTHS, AND EVERYTHING WAS GOOD.
BUT THIS,
GOING AFTER HIS WIFE...
GUERRERO'S CROSSING
A WHOLE NEW LINE.
NOW HE'S GONE AND PISSED OFF
THE ENTIRE
MIAMI POLICE DEPARTMENT.
IS THERE ANY WORD
ON THE WIFE?
SHE SHOULD BE
IN SURGERY BY NOW.
?QU? PAS??
UH, THERE'S AN INCONSISTENCY
SOMEWHERE.
AND THAT WOULD BE?
I'M NOT SURE, BUT IT'S
THE ANSWER TO A QUESTION
WE HAVEN'T THOUGHT OF YET.
LOOK.
[ BEEPING ]
WHOSE IS IT?
PROBABLY HERS.
RICKY SIMMONS, HER HUSBAND --
LAST NUMBER DIALED.
I GOT IT.
GOOD WORK, ANGEL.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
IT WAS DEXTER.
UH, SERGEANT?
[ SCOFFS ]
98, 99, 100!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WE HAVE A NEW WORLD RECORD!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ Laughing ]
STOP IT!
CAN'T STOP!
MUST TICKLE!
GOT TO HEAR
THE MAGIC WORD!
I HAVE YOUR MAGIC WORD
RIGHT HERE -- CHOCOLATE CHIP.
COOKIES!
OOH.
HOMEMADE.
OKAY, YOU GUYS,
TAKE YOUR COOKIES
INTO THE BEDROOM.
TWO EACH.
BUT YOU NEVER LET US EAT
IN OUR BEDROOM.
WELL, I WANT SOME ALONE TIME
WITH DEXTER.
ARE YOU GONNA KISS HIM?
ACTUALLY, YES.
COOL.
GROSS!
COOKIE?
I WUV COOKIES.
[ LAUGHS ]
WELL, YOU'RE SNARFING THEM DOWN
LIKE THE COOKIE MONSTER.
THIS ISN'T SNARFING.
THIS IS EATING WITH ENTHUSIASM.
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR DAY.
MMM, I HAD COURT --
YOU KNOW, THE BLOOD THING.
AND THEN A CRIME SCENE
AND MORE BLOOD.
MMM, I DON'T KNOW
HOW YOU DO IT.
WELL, BLOOD IS...
MY LIFE.
...MY JOB.
LATELY, THE THING THAT
SURPRISES ME MOST ABOUT RITA
IS HOW MUCH I LIKE
BEING WITH HER.
BUT WHENEVER THAT HAPPENS
WITH A WOMAN,
WHEN I FEEL COMFORTABLE
WITH HER, IT ALL GOES WRONG.
THAT'S WHY I THINK IT'S BEST
TO TAKE IT ONE STEP AT A TIME.
HEY, YOU KNOW,
DEB HAS BEEN ALL OVER ME
FOR US TO GET TOGETHER
WITH HER NEW BOYFRIEND.
YOU THINK YOU CAN GET
A BABYSITTER SOME NIGHT?
YOU MEAN AN ACTUAL
GROWN-UP MEAL?
I'D LOVE THAT.
MAKE A DATE.
I PICK YOU.
AND I PICK MY SISTER
TO CHAPERON.
[ CELLPHONE RINGING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ BEEP ]
SISTER.
Deb:
So, Miami's the haystack,
and the ice truck's
the needle, right?
OKAY.
And, brother, I just found
the fucking needle.
HOW DID YOU FIND IT?
I PUT THE WORD OUT
WITH PATROL --
YOU KNOW, THE WHOLE
HIDE-IN-PLAIN-SIGHT THING.
JUAN PIERRE FLAGGED THIS ONE
AND CALLED ME.
THIS IS A BUSY STREET.
ANYONE SEE THE DRIVER?
THE RESTAURANT MANAGER SAID
IT WAS HERE WHEN HE OPENED UP.
IS THIS THE ONE YOU SAW?
I FEEL LIKE A KID
AT HIS OWN SURPRISE PARTY.
THIS IS THE SAME TRUCK.
IT'S HARD TO SAY.
IT ALL HAPPENED SO FAST.
LET'S GO ON A NONFORENSIC-GEEK
LIMB HERE AND SAY THAT IT IS.
WHY IS IT STILL RUNNING?
IT KEEPS THE BACK COMPARTMENT
REFRIGERATED.
DIOS M?O.
HOLY SHIT,
THEY'RE FUCKING FINGERTIPS.
CLEAN SLICES,
NO BLOOD.
MY GUESS IS HE DRAINED
THE BODY ENTIRELY
BEFORE THESE CUTS
WERE MADE.
HOW'D HE DO THAT --
SOME KIND OF PUMP?
NO.
I HAD FORENSICS DO A WORKUP
ON OUR LAST VICTIM.
OUR GUY'S OLD SCHOOL.
YEAH, HE HOISTS THE BODY UP,
SEVERS THE JUGULAR.
THE HEART
DOES ALL THE WORK.
IT'S THE MOST EFFECTIVE METHOD,
REALLY.
FUCKING BUTCHER.
THERE ARE 206 BONES
IN THE HUMAN BODY.
HE COULD HAVE LEFT
ANY ONE OF THEM.
BUT HE GAVE US EXACTLY WHAT
WE NEED TO IDENTIFY THE VICTIM,
LIKE HE'S LEAVING A TRAIL
OF BREAD CRUMBS.
WHO MADE THE FIND?
OFFICER MORGAN.
HARRY'S DAUGHTER, HUH?
MUST BE IN THE GENES,
HER AND HER BROTHER.
THIS TRUCK'S A GOOD GET.
IT'S THEIR FIRST
SOLID LEAD.
I ENCOURAGE ALL MY OFFICERS
TO THINK OUTSIDE THE BOX.
WELL, NICE WORK,
LIEUTENANT.
I GOT
THE DEPUTY MAYOR.
CONGRATULATE MORGAN
FOR ME.
MM-HMM.
[ INDISTINCT TALKING
ON POLICE RADIO ]
ANOTHER BEAUTIFUL MIAMI DAY --
MUTILATED CORPSES WITH THE
CHANCE OF AFTERNOON SHOWERS.
CHALK ONE UP
FOR MIAMI METRO, EH, MA'AM?
LAST TIME I CHECKED, MORGAN,
I'M THE LIEUTENANT,
WHICH MEANS MY OFFICERS
KEEP ME APPRISED
AT ALL TIMES
ON ALL THINGS.
YOU PULL A STUNT
LIKE THAT AGAIN,
IT WON'T MATTER
WHO YOUR FATHER WAS.
OKAY?
[ SCREWGUN WHIRRING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
DUDE, IS THIS BLOOD?
IT'S CHOCOLATE.
IT'S ON YOUR SHIRT, TOO.
OH.
IT'S A NEW SHIRT.
[ WHIRRING ]
WHAT IS TAKING SO LONG?
IT'S A BIG TRUCK.
THEY WON'T FIND ANYTHING,
NOT EVEN A TIC TAC.
HE'S THOUGHT ALL THIS THROUGH.
I KNOW I WOULD.
YOUR FAMOUS HUNCHES
TELLING YOU ANYTHING?
ICE COLD.
YOU'RE A GODDAMN RIOT.
THIS FUCKING GUY'S
TOYING WITH US.
DEB'S RIGHT.
THIS TRUCK'S NOT ANOTHER PIECE
OF THE PUZZLE...
[ HAND TRUCK RATTLES ]
...THEY ARE.
[ TELEPHONE RINGS IN DISTANCE ]
WATCHING ICE MELT --
THIS IS FUN.
STAND A LITTLE CLOSER, MORGAN,
AND I'LL MELT YOUR HEART.
I THINK HE'S GOT A CRUSH
ON YOU, DEX.
HUH?
YO, I WAS TALKING TO MORGAN
THE SISTER.
VINCE MASUKA
ONLY SWINGS ONE WAY.
YEAH,
FROM VINE TO VINE.
ENOUGH.
I'M GLAD TO SEE
THE SEXUAL-HARASSMENT SEMINAR
REALLY PAID OFF.
[ ICE CRACKLING ]
OH, THIS IS SERIOUSLY
FUCKED-UP, MY FRIENDS.
WHY GO TO ALL THIS TROUBLE?
WHAT'S THIS SICK SON OF A BITCH
TRYING TO TELL US?
NOT "US" -- ME.
MY FREEZER, THE PAINTED DOLL'S
FINGERNAILS...
I THINK HE'S TRYING
TO IMPRESS ME...
AND IT'S WORKING.
WHAT, A MAN CAN'T CALL HIS WIFE
THREE TIMES IN ONE DAY?
S?, CLARO.
BUENO.
KISS MY BABY AND TELL HER,
"DADDY BE HOMEPARA LA CENA."
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
I'M GETTING ANOTHER CALL.
YEAH,TE AMO.
[ BEEP ]
BATISTA.
?DE VERAS?
I'LL BE THERE IN TWO MINUTES.
[ CELLPHONE CLICKS ]
SHE'S STILL IN SURGERY.
THE DOCTORS ARE HOPEFUL.
ICE-TRUCK KILLER RETURNS,
DEAD UNDERCOVER COP --
IT'S A TYPICAL DAY
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU GOT TO HEAR THIS.
Kara:[ Sobbing ]
RICKY, WHERE THE FUCK ARE YOU?
I'M GONNA TRY
FOR THE BACK DOOR.
OHH!
OH, FUCK, HE SAW ME!
OH, PLEASE DON'T HURT ME!
[GUNSHOT ]
Batista: LIEUTENANT!
NATIONAL DATABASE
KICKED BACK THE DNA MATCH.
NORBERTO CERVANTES.
LET ME SEE THAT.
[ UP-TEMPO SPANISH MUSIC PLAYS ]
DAME. AHORA.
ES TU D?A
DE MALA SUERTE.
ESTOY AGRADECIDO
POR TU LEALDAD.
EL GUSTO
ES M?O, PATR?N.
GET DOWN!
POLICE!
PUT YOUR HANDS UP!
GET THEM DOWN!
PUT YOUR FUCKING HANDS UP!
PUT YOUR HANDS UP!
HEY!
IS THAT NECESSARY?
IT'S A DANGEROUS WORLD,
GUERRERO.
YES, AND ONE CAN'T BE
TOO CAREFUL, DETECTIVE.
YES, I-I'VE HAD ALC--
PROBLEMS WITH ALCOHOL
IN THE PAST.
I NEVER TRIED TO HIDE THAT.
BUT, UH, YOU HEARD
FROM MY A.A. SPONSOR.
I-I'VE BEEN SOBER
FOR OVER A YEAR NOW, SO...
LOOK, I-I'M NOT DISPUTING
THAT -- THAT IT WAS MY CAR...
THAT HIT MR. PRYCE.
BUT...
I REPORTED IT STOLEN
HOURS BEFORE THE ACCIDENT.
[ SIGHS ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
Dexter:
MEN LIKE MATT CHAMBERS
KNOW HOW TO PULL ON
THE INVISIBLE MASK OF SYMPATHY,
EVEN EMPATHY,
AND OTHERWISE RIGHT-THINKING
PEOPLE DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
[ ELEVATOR DINGS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
I KNEW IT.
"NOT GUILTY."
MATT CHAMBERS MAY HAVE FOUND
A WAY TO BEAT THE SYSTEM...
BUT SO HAVE I.
Kara:[ Sobbing ]
RICKY, WHERE THE FUCK ARE YOU?
OHH!
OH, FUCK, HE SAW ME!
OH, PLEASE DON'T HURT ME!
[GUNSHOT ]
[ RECORDER CLICKS OFF ]
THE WAY WE SEE IT,
YOU'RE IN ON THE KILL
OF RICKY SIMMONS,
BUT THAT'S NOT ENOUGH FOR YOU
OR FOR GUERRERO.
RICKY IS DEAD?
THAT SADDENS ME.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
SHUT THE FUCK UP!
WAIT, YOU'RE NOT IMPLYING
THAT RICKY SIMMONS WAS A COP,
ARE YOU?
I'M TRULY DISAPPOINTED.
NOT ONLY DO I HAVE
A DEAD COP,
SOMEONE BROKE IN HIS HOUSE
AND SHOT HIS WIFE.
WORD OUT IN THE WORLD,
SERGEANT --
SIMMONS'S WIFE
WAS FUCKING AROUND.
MAYBE HE TRIED
TO KILL THE BITCH HIMSELF
AND FELT SO BAD ABOUT IT,
HE COMMITTED SUICIDE.
A COP MURDER-SUICIDE --
IT'S A HEALTH CRISIS
FOR YOU GUYS, AIN'T IT?
WHOA, WHOA!
YOU THINK
IT'S A FUCKING COINCIDENCE
YOUR ASS IS IN HERE?!
WE GOT YOU ON THE CAUSEWAY
THE MORNING RICKY SIMMONS DIED!
BULLSHIT.
WE DON'T DEAL IN BULLSHIT.
WE DEAL
IN GOOD POLICE WORK...
AND GOOD SCIENCE.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN A
MOTHERFUCKER AT CAT'S CRADLE.
I NEVER PLAYED IT.
OKAY, KARA SIMMONS WAS SHOT
WHILE SHE WAS RUNNING.
HER PHONE CALL
TELLS US THAT, RIGHT?
SHE WAS RUNNING TOWARDS
THE BACK DOOR -- THERE.
SHE TURNS.
THE SHOOTER SEES HER.
SHE'S SHOT HIGH ON THE CHEST.
IT SPINS HER AROUND,
SPRAYING BLOOD ON THE WALLS
THERE AND THERE.
SHE LOSES HER CELLPHONE.
SHE STRUGGLES
WITH THE COFFEE TABLE,
THE COUCH, AND THEN
SHE FINALLY FALLS BACK,
"POP" -- THERE.
[ SIGHS ]
SHE NEVER GOT THIS FAR.
IT'S NOT HER BLOOD.
[ KNIFE CLICKS ]
[ TILE RIPS ]
ANGEL, MEET OUR SHOOTER.
Batista: DNA OF CERVANTES' FLESH
IN RICKY SIMMONS' MOUTH.
DNA FROM A ROGUE DROP OF BLOOD
WE FOUND AT THE SIMMONS' HOUSE.
[ KEYS CLACKING ]
[ BEEPING ]
TELL ME
YOU'RE SURE ABOUT THIS.
100%.
THAT PUTS CERVANTES
AT BOTH CRIME SCENES.
LET'S NAIL HIS COFFIN
AND SHIP IT.
WHOA.
HANG ON, SERGEANT.
WE GET HIM TO ROLL OVER ON
GUERRERO, AND WE OWN THEM BOTH.
YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT THROWING HIM A DEAL?
AND THEN, WHAT, HE WALKS?
IF HE DOES, WE PICK HIM UP
ON OTHER CHARGES.
IF HE GETS US GUERRERO,
IT'S WIN-WIN.
GETS US GUERRERO?!
WE CAN'T CATCH THE GUY!
HE'S UN-FUCKING-TOUCHABLE!
[ SIGHS ]
COME ON, LIEUTENANT.
WE ALREADY GOT A WIN.
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOUR WIN.
IT'S ABOUT THE BIG PICTURE.
Dexter:
I'VE SEEN THIS BEFORE.
WHENEVER A COP IS KILLED,
IT'S LIKE EVERYONE'S LIFE HAS
BEEN STOPPED IN MID-SENTENCE.
DAVEY SANCHEZ WAS
A FEARLESS AND DEDICATED COP.
DAVEY SANCHEZ WAS A SON,
A HUSBAND, AND A FATHER.
DAVEY SANCHEZ WAS MY PARTNER.
DAVEY SANCHEZ WAS MY HERO.
THAT WAS GREAT.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT, DAD?
EVER SINCE DAVEY WAS KILLED,
MY WORLD FEELS OUT OF CONTROL.
HOW DO YOU FIX IT?
TWO WAYS, I GUESS...
HONOR DAVEY'S MEMORY...
...AND CATCH THE BASTARD
WHO DID THIS TO HIM.
IT'S NOT ABOUT VENGEANCE.
IT'S NOT
ABOUT RETALIATION...
OR BALANCING THE BOOKS.
IT'S ABOUT SOMETHING
DEEP INSIDE.
MY FATHER HAD MORE
THAN HIS SHARE OF PAIN.
BUT HE DIDN'T DEAL WITH IT
THE WAY MOST PEOPLE DO.
HAPPY HOUR --
NOW, THERE'S A MISNOMER.
I'LL HAVE WHAT HE'S HAVING.
WISE CHOICE.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU CELEBRATING?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
HEY, HAVE WE MET?
I DOUBT IT.
I JUST MOVED DOWN HERE.
I NEEDED A NEW START.
GIRLFRIEND OR BOYFRIEND?
EX-WIFE.
SHE SAID I DRANK TOO MUCH.
HENCE THE "EX" PART.
FUCK HER.
MAN, SHE WAS ALL OVER ME
TO CHANGE,
LIKE SHE NEVER DONE ANYTHING
WRONG IN HER LIFE...
BESIDES MARRYING ME.
WE ALL MAKE MISTAKES.
UNFORTUNATELY,
MINE USUALLY INVOLVE LAWYERS.
GOD!
DAMN IT!
I THOUGHT I WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO HATED THE HURRICANES.
I TAKE IT YOU DIDN'T GROW UP
IN MIAMI.
NO, I'VE HAD TO MOVE
AROUND SOME.
SAY NO MORE.
BUT HOME
IS WHERE MY ASS IS.
I'M GETTING MINE
OUT OF TOWN.
ENJOY MIAMI.
REMEMBER, THERE'S NOTHING
A NEW CITY CAN'T CURE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
HEY, THANKS, BUDDY.
NEXT ONE'S ON ME.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU SURE YOU'RE GOOD
TO DRIVE?
BEEN A LOT WORSE.
[ CAR ALARM BEEPS ]
[ CAR DOOR CLOSES,
ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
I SURE HOPE HE DOESN'T GO OUT
THERE AND KILL HIMSELF.
THAT WOULD BE...TRAGIC.
MATT CHAMBERS IS ACCUSED OF
COMMITTING A CRIME IN FLORIDA.
HE WAS ARRESTED IN FLORIDA,
AND HE'S BEING TRIED
IN FLORIDA.
SO THE GOOD PEOPLE OF FLORIDA
ONLY WENT AS FAR AS VALIDATING
THEIR OWN ASSUMPTIONS
THAT MATT CHAMBERS
IS A FLORIDA BAD GUY.
[ PRINTER WHIRS ]
"NOTHING A NEW CITY
CAN'T CURE."
MY FATHER TAUGHT ME ONE THING
ABOVE ALL OTHERS -- TO BE SURE.
AND I AM.
MATT CHAMBERS,
MIAMI IS YOUR LAST STOP.
IF GOD IS IN THE DETAILS,
AND IF I BELIEVED IN GOD,
THEN HE'S IN THIS ROOM WITH ME.
I JUST WISH HE'D BROUGHT
AN EXTENSION CORD.
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ON P.A. ]
HEY.
IT'S JAMES.
WE'RE GONNA GET THE BASTARD
WHO DID THIS TO YOU.
[ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
Deb: THIS GUY
IS JUST TOYING WITH US,
AND LaGUERTA'S
TOO FUCKING DUMB TO SEE IT.
DEB WAS SAYING
THAT THIS PSYCHO GUY
CUT OFF THAT CHICK'S
FINGERTIPS?
MAN, THAT'S GOT TO
SUCK, RIGHT?
GUERRERO TAKING HOME LOBSTERS
TO BOIL ALIVE --
THAT'S NOT HIS STYLE.
HE USUALLY LEAVES THE KILLING
TO SOMEONE ELSE.
SO, HOW LONG HAVE YOU TWO
BEEN GOING OUT?
A COUPLE WEEKS, I GUESS.
UH, DEB NEVER MENTIONED
HOW YOU MET.
WELL, SHE BROUGHT HER CAR
INTO MY SHOP, AND...
YOU HAVE YOUR OWN PLACE?
NO, BUT I WISH I DID.
SOMEDAY, HUH?
DEX, ENOUGH
WITH THE INQUISITION.
NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IF I HAD A SISTER
WITH LEGS LIKE YOURS,
I'D BE CHECKING OUT THE DUDE
SHE WAS SEEING, TOO.
IS THIS GUY A KEEPER
OR WHAT?
COME ON.
I'LL GET YOU ANOTHER DRINK.
ARE YOU GUYS GOOD?
YEP.
SEEMS LIKE A NICE GUY.
MM-HMM.
THEY COULD BARELY KEEP
THEIR HANDS OFF EACH OTHER.
I CAN KILL A MAN,
DISMEMBER HIS BODY,
AND BE HOME IN TIME
FOR "LETTERMAN."
BUT KNOWING WHAT TO SAY
WHEN MY GIRLFRIEND'S
FEELING INSECURE...
I'M TOTALLY LOST.
Man: OFF YOUR ASS, CERVANTES.
HANDS BEHIND YOUR BACK.
WALK BACKWARDS
AND ASSUME THE POSITION.
[ KEYS RATTLE ]
STEP AWAY.
[ LOCK CLICKS ]
EXIT THE CELL.
WHERE ARE WE GOING?
THE CALL CAME DOWN.
THEY WANT YOU MOVED
TO A MORE SECURE BLOCK.
YOU THINK THE CALL TO TAKE CARE
OF ME CAME DOWN FROM THE WARDEN?
WHO THE FUCK DO YOU THINK
THE WARDEN LISTENS TO?
GET USED TO IT.
[ GRUNTING ]
THAT'S
FROM MR. GUERRERO.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
Dexter:
* ARE YOU SLEEPING? *
* BROTHER JOHN *
* MORNING BELLS ARE RINGING *
* DING DING DONG *
Man:NEW CLAIMS
FOR U.S. UNEMPLOYMENT BENEFITS
FELL UNEXPECTEDLY TO 273,000
LAST WEEK,
PUSHING THE 4-WEEK
AVERAGE CLAIM
TO THE LOWEST LEVEL
IN NEARLY 6 YEARS.
INITIAL CLAIMS
FOR STATE JOBLESS AID
FELL 11,000
IN THE WEEK JUST ENDED.
[ TELEVISION MUTES ]
Dexter:EVERY TIME A WOMAN
TRIES TO DO THIS TO ME, IT...
TICKLES.
STILL, IT'S NOT ENTIRELY
UNPLEASANT.
WHAT?
THE KIDS.
OH, THEY SLEEP
THROUGH THUNDERSTORMS.
[ GRUNTS ]
I'M SORRY.
[ SIGHS ]
TELL ME.
I-I CAN'T DO THIS.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M OKAY.
[ SIGHS ]
WE HAVE AN ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM,
AND ITS NAME IS "SEX."
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
HEY, AS FAR
AS I'M CONCERNED,
IT CAN JUST STAY
IN THE CORNER
AND MIND
ITS OWN DAMN BUSINESS.
IT'S EASIER SAID
THAN DONE.
YEAH.
BUT IT NEEDS TO BE RIGHT...
FOR BOTH OF US.
OR IT WON'T BE RIGHT
FOR EITHER OF US.
I DON'T WANT THAT.
DO YOU?
NO.
YOU KNOW...
[ CHUCKLES ]
WOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I FOUND
THE ONE GOOD, TRULY DECENT MAN
LEFT ON THE PLANET.
...WAS FOUND DEAD
IN A BASEMENT HALLWAY
OF THE MIAMI METRO JAIL.
NORBERTO CERVANTES
WAS A KNOWN ASSOCIATE
OF REPUTED DRUG LORD
CARLOS GUERRERO.
SPECULATION IS
THAT ANOTHER INMATE
IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE MAYHEM HERE TONIGHT.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
NOTICE HOW THE SKIN IS GLOVING
AROUND THE JOINTS?
AND THAT IS IMPORTANT
BECAUSE?
A SURE SIGN
OF POSTMORTEM SEVERANCE,
MEANING THE VICTIM WAS ALREADY
DEAD WHEN SHE WAS [WHISTLES]
RELIEVED OF HER FINGERTIPS.
WHY THE DIFFERENT
NAIL POLISHES?
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS GUY
THINKING?
Dexter:HE'S THINKING,
"TAG, DEXTER, YOU'RE IT."
I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU HAVE AN I.D.?
SHARI TAYLOR --
ANOTHER HOOKER.
AT LEAST HE'S CONSISTENT.
YEAH.
KILLING YOUNG WOMEN
THAT HAVE TO SELL THEIR BODIES
JUST TO SURVIVE...
OR FEED THEIR KIDS.
MY SISTER PUTS UP A FRONT
SO THE WORLD WON'T SEE
HOW VULNERABLE SHE IS.
ME, I PUT UP A FRONT
SO THE WORLD WON'T SEE
HOW VULNERABLE I'M NOT.
I DON'T CARE WHO
THESE FINGERTIPS BELONG TO,
ONLY WHAT MY NEW FRIEND
OUT THERE IS TRYING TO SAY.
MORGAN?
THE CAPTAIN WANTS YOU.
HER.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
YOU WANTED
TO SEE ME, SIR?
LIEUTENANT LaGUERTA HAS
SOMETHING SHE WANTS TO TELL YOU.
OFFICER MORGAN, YOU'VE SHOWN
TREMENDOUS INITIATIVE
THESE LAST FEW DAYS.
BECAUSE OF YOU, WE WERE ABLE TO
TRACK DOWN THAT ICE TRUCK,
AND WE NOW HAVE AN I.D.
ON THE LATEST VICTIM.
THE CAPTAIN BELIEVES
YOU SHOULD BE REASSIGNED
FROM VICE TO HOMICIDE.
AND I CONCUR.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU'RE A GOOD COP,
LIKE YOUR OLD MAN.
[ Laughing ]
THANK YOU, SIR!
[ SNIFFLES ]
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I SEE A DETECTIVE SHIELD
IN YOUR FUTURE.
I WON'T LET YOU DOWN,
SIR.
[ LAUGHS ]
I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
I PROMOTEDYOU,
DIDN'T I?
NOW FIND ME
THIS ICE-TRUCK SON OF A BITCH.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
OKAY?
OKAY.
[ SIGHS ]
Y NINA Y TU HIJA,
?C?MO EST?N?
EST?N MARAVILLOSAS.
T? SABES QUE ELLAS TAMBI?N
TE NECESITAN, ?EH?
ANGEL,
VETE A TU CASA.
Okay.
LaGuerta:
BURNING THE OIL?
I CLOCKED OUT.
WHY ARE YOU GOING AT THIS
SO HARD?
WHEN SOMEONE COMES
AFTER ONE OF US,
HE COMES AFTER ALL OF US.
I KNOW THAT LOOK, MARIA.
YOU GOT SOMETHING TO SAY,
JUST SAY IT.
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH THE HOSPITAL.
KARA SIMMONS SUFFERED MASSIVE
HEART FAILURE 30 MINUTES AGO.
I GOT TO BE THERE.
JAMES, SHE DIED.
WAS CERVANTES RIGHT?
WAS KARA SLEEPING WITH SOMEONE
OTHER THAN RICKY?
WAS IT YOU?
[ SIGHS ] WHAT THE FUCK
WERE YOU THINKING?!
WHAT THE FUCK BUSINESS
IS IT OF YOURS?!
MY COPS, MY PRECINCT --
MY BUSINESS!
KARA WAS GONNA ASK RICKY
FOR A DIVORCE
AS SOON AS HE CAME OFF
UNDERCOVER.
SHE DIDN'T WANT TO...
SHE DIDN'T WANT TO HURT HIM
WHEN HE WAS ON THE CASE.
IF I GO BY THE BOOK,
I TAKE YOU OFF THE CASE.
FUCK THE BOOK.
THERE'S NOBODY
MORE MOTIVATED TO GET --
REVENGE?
JUSTICE.
TAKE POINT
ON GUERRERO.
THANKS.
IN SLAUGHTERHOUSES,
THEY STUN THE ANIMALS
BEFORE BUTCHERING THEM.
IT'S THE HUMANE THING TO DO.
THOSE ANIMALS...
THEY'RE THE LUCKY ONES.
[ ENGINE TURNS OFF ]
[ BEEPING ]
"BROTHER, MEET ME
AT LOCO'S CRAB SHACK.
TOTALLY IMPORTANT.
DO NOT LET ME DOWN. DEB."
GONE TO REST HIS WEARY HEAD.
THE GOOD NEWS IS,
HE'LL STILL BE HERE
WHEN I COME BACK FOR
OUR OWN PERSONAL HAPPY HOUR.
[ UP-TEMPO SPANISH MUSIC PLAYS ]
MMM,
GOD, THESE ARE SO GOOD.
NOT AS GOOD
AS YOUR GOOD NEWS.
MY LITTLE SISTER'S ALL GROWED-UP
AND TRANSFERRED TO HOMICIDE.
MMM.
AND THE BEST PART --
LaGUERTA HAD TO SAY
THE ACTUAL WORDS.
I THOUGHT HER HEAD
WOULD EXPLODE.
I'M REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
YOU HAD MY BACK THE WHOLE WAY,
AND I APPRECIATE IT.
I MEAN THAT.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
AND THAT'S WHY I WANTED
TO SHARE THIS MOMENT WITH YOU.
SO, SEAN WAS BUSY?
AH, IT TURNS OUT
THERE'S ANOTHER WOMAN.
WHO?
ME.
SEAN THE MECHANIC
IS MARRIED?
IMAGINE ME PICKING
THE WRONG GUY, HUH?
AND YOU AND HE ARE...
SO OVER.
I DUMPED HIS MARRIED ASS.
I JUST WISH I COULD GET
INTO A HEALTHY RELATIONSHIP,
LIKE YOU AND RITA,
WITHOUT THE DRAMA
AND THE TENSION
AND THE UNCERTAINTY.
YEAH, I'M A LUCKY GUY.
[ SPANISH MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
JESUS, DAD,
IT'S CALLED BEING ON TIME!
DID YOU EVER HEAR OF IT?
I WAS HAVING A BAD DAY.
THE CAPTAIN AND I
HAD A DISCUSSION.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SH--
WAIT.
W-WHAT KIND OF BAD DAY?
IT'S ABOUT THE GUY
WHO KILLED DAVEY, ISN'T IT?
THE JUDGE SAID THE BUST WASN'T
RIGHTEOUS AND LET HIM WALK.
THAT GUY KILLS A COP,
AND NOTHING HAPPENS?
[ SCOFFS ]
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
LIFE'S NOT FAIR, DEXTER.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
CAN'T ANYONE DO ANYTHING?
CAN'T YOU DO SOMETHING?
NO, NOT NOW.
SO WHAT, THEN?
THE WORLD JUST KEEPS
SPINNING OUT OF CONTROL?
NO.
THE WORLD CAN ALWAYS
BE SET RIGHT AGAIN.
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
THAT GUY KILLS A COP,
AND NOTHING HAPPENS?
NOT ANYMORE.
BE BACK IN A SEC.
I'M KIND OF RUNNING THE GAMUT
HERE EMOTION-WISE.
NATURE CALLS.
ALL THE PLANNING,
THE MAKING SURE...
DOES IT GO AWAY
BECAUSE I HAVE A CHANCE
TO RID THE WORLD OF A COP
KILLER AND BALANCE THE BOOKS?
DO I JUST IGNORE
EVERYTHING MY FATHER TAUGHT ME
ABOUT HOW TO DO THIS RIGHT,
ABOUT HOW TO STAY SAFE
SO I CAN DO IT AGAIN?
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
YEP.
I DON'T GIVE A SHIT
ABOUT YOUR GODDAMN PROBLEMS.
I GAVE YOU A JOB.
YOU TAKE CARE OF IT.
[ CELLPHONE CLICKS ]
WHAT THE FUCK
YOU LOOKING AT?
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, ALEX!
[INDISTINCT VOICES ]
BUT NEXT YEAR
AT THIS TIME...
IT'S YOU.
AND YOU.
Alex:
THANKS, DAD.
[ SIGHS ]
ALL RIGHT,
ENOUGH CORNINESS.
WE MEET AGAIN...
AAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPING ]
...FOR THE LAST TIME.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTH--
ANYTHING.
SOME PEOPLE BELIEVE THAT.
THE PROBLEM IS, I DON'T.
BUT IT'S TRUE.
I WAS -- I WAS SET UP.
BY WHOM?
THAT -- THAT FAMILY.
THEY NEEDED SOMEONE
TO BLAME.
IT'S A NATURAL THING TO DO
WHEN YOU'RE GRIEVING.
SO THEN NONE OF THIS
IS YOUR FAULT?
I SWEAR.
[ DRILL WHIRRING ]
Okay! Okay! Okay!
No!
Okay. Okay. Stop.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, OKAY.
IT -- IT WAS ME,
ONLY IT WASN'T ME.
IT WAS THE BOOZE.
IT TAKES ME OVER.
THAT'S A POINT OF VIEW
TO WHICH I'M NOT ENTIRELY
UNSYMPATHETIC.
NEITHER YOU NOR I
IS IN COMPLETE CONTROL
OF OUR DESTINIES.
ALTHOUGH, AT THE MOMENT,
[ WHIRRING ]
IT WOULD SEEM
I HAVE THE UPPER HAND.
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ Voice breaking ]
REALLY, I'M SO SORRY.
YOU'VE DONE THIS
TOO MANY TIMES TO BE SORRY.
[ GASPING ]
[ UP-TEMPO SPANISH MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ DRILL WHIRRING ]
CARLOS GUERRERO HAS CHOSEN
TO LIVE IN A DANGEROUS WORLD.
THAT'S HIS TRUTH.
MY TRUTH IS,
THAT WORLD DOESN'T NEED ME
TO BALANCE ITS BOOKS.
[ SINGING IN SPANISH ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
MATT CHAMBERS, WELCOME TO
YOUR LAST CHANGE OF ADDRESS.
YOU'LL LIKE IT HERE.
YOU AND YOUR NEIGHBORS
HAVE SO MUCH IN COMMON.
[ SWITCH CLICKS ]
[ AIR-CONDITIONER WHIRRING ]
THE WORST THING ABOUT FINALLY
PUTTING TOGETHER A PUZZLE
IS FINDING
THERE ARE MISSING PIECES.
HE CAME BACK AND LEFT NOTHING
BEHIND BUT A MESSAGE --
COME FIND ME.
AND I WILL.
THERE ARE NO SECRETS IN LIFE,
JUST HIDDEN TRUTHS
THAT LIE BENEATH THE SURFACE.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com