Previously on "Dexter"...
No blood --
What a beautiful idea.
Brother, I just found
the fucking ice-truck.
It is my new friend.
When he broke into my apartment,
he took some time to get to know me --
My life, my secrets.
Paul doesn't live here anymore.
No shit.
He's in jail. But...
See, he still owes me
for two ounces of blow,
which means you owe me.
The coyote wanted more money,
and I didn't have it.
Poor bastards --
Spend their life savings,
get stuffed into a fishhold.
- They can't pay...
- They disappear.
Jorge Castillo --
The only suspect even remotely
close to the park
where Yelina was supposed
to drop the money.
Excuse me.
Private yard.
Sorry, I just assumed
you were Cuban.
American, pal,
just like you.
Just like me.
Co?o.
Come on.
Get back in there,
you Cuban piece of shit.
They're even better-matched
than I thought.
Fucking animals.
God bless America.
Taking the extra time to kill Valerie
may have been ill-advised.
My life has always been a sequence
of carefully planned moments.
But sometimes you just have
to take a risk.
Life is so fleeting,
so fragile.
Every breath the potential
to be our last.
You ready?
Can I have
my cereal now?
We all grieve in our own way.
Sure.
I prefer the 6-year-old
approach.
Yet another I've sent
to a watery grave.
Well, not quite.
Hey, what about this one?
I want angel cake.
It's angel food, stupid,
and you don't get a vote.
- It's my birthday.
- Guys.
So how'd it go?
Bob the goldfish --
May he rest in peace.
Thanks for coming over and
taking care of this for me.
Dead stuff...
I know.
Well, go have a seat.
Your treat for coming over early
is on its way.
I don't get birthdays --
The party, the song.
Celebrating another year
just being alive feels... forced.
That one!
That's the one I want.
- Coconut it is.
- I hate coconut.
You've never had coconut.
It's dispatch.
I might have to
settle for toast to go.
Morgan.
Sure, what's the location?
I'll be right there.
The crime scene.
My crime scene.
I shouldn't have killed them both.
I didn't have enough time.
A footprint, a microscopic
drop of blood --
What did I leave behind?
Impossible.
Nice place setting, huh?
We're running her prints now.
It had to be him.
He's watching me.
Dex?
Good.
I.D. the victim.
You find anything else?
That ain't enough?
Any eyewitnesses?
Just do your job.
Worry about the blood.
You gonna answer that?
This tin can smells like ass.
The sooner you get busy,
the sooner we can finger
who did this.
You heard the man.
He dove 100 feet
to bring up the body.
He's getting back at me for
not killing that security guard.
Please tell me this wasn't
the ice-truck killer.
I've got the press sniffing
outside already.
- No, it's not his M.O.
- We got an I.D. -- Valerie Castillo.
And guess this. Her husband,
Jorge, owns the salvage yard.
Then, try and
track him down.
Sir, we found something.
You got anything?
No bruising.
Nothing under her nails.
She didn't put up a fight.
If she was killed here,
which I doubt,
whoever did it was a real pro.
Under normal circumstances,
I'd take that as a compliment.
- Prints?
- She's clean.
This trailer --
That's another matter.
I don't even want to know
what some of those stains are.
Yo, Dex, I think
I found something.
Zoom in on this, will you?
- I'm kind of low on batteries here.
- Dude, it'll take, like, two seconds.
Yo, what's up with you today?
You're throwing off my Chi.
- You're not Chinese.
- I'm not?
Look, right here.
Does that look like
a needle mark to you?
It's more like a bug bite,
blemish maybe.
Yeah...
I guess.
I'll let the
coroner bag her.
I'm hungry.
This ain't no auto garage.
Oh! Oh, god.
Oh, I didn't need to see that.
You never seen
a latrine before, Morgan?
Yeah, just not indoors.
Well, the army taught me
a lot of things.
I feel a Desert Storm story
coming on.
Digging holes for people to take
a dump? That was most important.
I'm not really getting that.
It doesn't matter how many bars
you got on your collar, Morgan.
- Everybody's shit stinks.
- Here we go.
- We were partners a long time.
- From the looks of things,
Valerie Castillo's better half
was knee-deep.
- You like the husband for this?
- It's always the husband.
What have you got?
It looks like a phone number
and a name -- Mariel.
Call it in to Batista.
He can run it down for us.
Sergeant Doakes!
We heard movement
in the trunk.
I got it.
Padre nuestro
que est? en los cielos.
Santificado sea tu nombre.
Venga tu reino.
H?gase tu voluntad
en la tierra...
You all right, kid?
Come on, man.
No!
Subtle.
Maybe you should cuff him.
Mi hijito, todo est? bien.
Te vamos a ayudar.
The noose is tightening.
This is how it ends -- In the
hands of a 7-year-old?
Hey, Deb.
I usually like kids.
Who's the boy?
All we got so far
is that he's Cuban
and he seems to
like Laguerta.
Spend enough time
in a hot trunk,
I guess she'd look
good to anybody.
Did he... you know?
see anything?
I'm not sure.
He's pretty out of it.
Social services is on the way.
You okay? You got a whole
brow thing going on.
Morgan, bring some water!
I love her.
Maybe I should spend some time
in a hot trunk, too.
My neat little world of lies is
crumbling all around me,
and I can't tell a soul,
especially not Deb.
- Deb, we've been through this.
- But I have my books. I mean,
I could just stay
in the car...
...or I can walk
with you guys.
I promise I'll be quiet.
You won't even know I'm there.
The pheasants will know
you're there.
- But Dexter was my age when --
- Deb, that's enough.
The Logans are waiting.
Did you pack your swimsuit?
- Yes.
- Good girl.
I want to see that backflip
when we come home.
All right. Go on out to the car.
We'll be there in a sec.
She does kind of
have a point, dad.
What we do on these weekends your
sister can never know about.
Keeping the truth from the people
closest to you is how you'll survive...
...and how you'll protect them
if anything ever goes wrong.
Guys, hurry up. You're gonna
be late for school.
I'm headed to the store. Is there
anything else you want for your party?
Balloons aren't much of a list.
It's okay. It don't need that
other stuff. It's too expensive.
How about you let me worry
about that stuff, okay?
It's your party. You can have
whatever you want.
- Hello?
- Hey, babe, it's me.
Go wait in the car.
What's wrong with mom?
She only gets that way when
she's talking to dad.
Hi.
I was able to track down that name Mariel
with the number that you called in.
She's a
Cuban refugee.
She's staying with cousins.
I had a cop bring her in.
Why scratch the number
in the floor?
Next of kin, in case something
happened to her.
Guys like Castillo are ruthless.
They prey on families.
He was holding Mariel and six
others captive at a salvage yard.
That explains the garage.
And if the relatives don't
pay the release fee,
the coyote would dump
their ass overboard.
Cocksuckers make me sick.
Come on.
Mariel, estos son mis amigos
que yo te dije.
Sargento Doakes y la detective
Morgan. Puede sentar.
Mariel, when was the last time
you saw Jorge Castillo?
?Cu?ndo fue la ultima vez que
t? viste a Jorge Castillo?
Cuando me encerr? con los otros
despu?s de bajarnos del barco.
When he locked her and the other refugees up
after pulling them
from the boat.
No ten?amos comida ni agua.
Un hombre trat? de escapar.
Jorge lo agarr? y lo golpe?.
They went without
food and water.
Some guy tried to escape, but
he was beaten by Jorge.
- How'd she get free?
- ?C?mo escap??
Alguien abri? la puerta al garaje.
Y nos escapamos.
Somebody opened the door
to the garage.
Cuando los agarren, espero
que los hagan sufrir mucho,
especialmente esa concha
que nos trat? como perro.
She said, "when we find them,
to make them suffer
for what they did,
especially that concha
that treated her like a dog.
Concha?
Ah, got you.
Fuck me.
The wife was in on it.
Ask if she knows the little boy
social services picked up.
?Y qui?n era el ni?o peque?o
que estaba con usted?
?Qu? ni?o?
Yo nunca vi un ni?o.
She never saw a boy.
No hair, no fibers, C.O.D.
exsanguination -- So far, so good.
- You're hovering.
- Keep reading.
- What am I looking for?
- Wait for it.
This is a prelim.
I don't have time --
"M" fucking 99.
Etorphine hydrochloride?
An animal tranquilizer more
powerful than morphine.
It causes total paralysis.
That mark on her neck
kept bugging me,
so I ordered up
a tox screen.
That's it. No more doughnuts
for Masuka.
Dude, this stuff is
strictly controlled.
The only way to get it is
with a D.E.A. license.
I put a request in
for the list.
I should have it for Doakes
in the morning.
Nice.
Yeah, baby.
I'm on that list,
and eventually the alias I used
will lead them back to me.
Ticktock.
- Hey, you.
- Thank god you're there.
I really need to talk
with someone.
Everything okay?
- Paul called after you left.
- Paul? Who's Paul?
My soon-to-be ex.
He's already out of jail --
Overcrowding.
Can you believe it?
Every time something goes
just a little bit right,
something like this happens.
He wants to come to Astor's party.
- What did you tell him?
- I'd have to think about it.
But even if I say "no", he won't
listen. He never does.
Can you --
Can you come over tonight?
I don't know, I'm kind of
under the gun here, big case.
I shouldn't be dumping all this
on you. I'm sorry.
No, don't be. Tell you what, I'll
stop by if I can. I promise.
Okay. I'll keep a plate warm
just in case.
Thanks.
Bye.
Check the marinas.
Find Jorge Castillo's boat.
We'll search the house.
Where's Laguerta?
Trying to bring that kid in
for a sketch.
Sketch?
He told social services that some
guy saved him from the bad lady.
Valerie Castillo?
It sounds like she got exactly
what she had coming to her.
Personally, I'd shake
this guy's hand.
Yeah, you say that now.
Found his passport.
God...
I feel like I need a shower
just looking at this douche bag.
Well, keep searching.
Phone records, bank
accounts, credit cards.
Maybe the wife got greedy,
and that's why he killed her.
Maybe.
This morning at the salvage yard,
what was that thing by the car?
What thing?
Before you opened the trunk,
you tried to cockblock me.
I was just looking out
for my team.
I didn't see you looking out
for Laguerta.
- I would if she'd asked.
- I didn't ask.
Fine.
Next time,
just get your ass shot.
- It's possible our guy left town.
- If he even did it.
- What if we have a copycat killer?
- That's a bit of a stretch, don't you think?
Just hear me out.
What if the person who killed
Valerie Castillo was trying
to bleed her out like
the ice-truck killer
but didn't know how?
She wasn't a hooker.
But she was killed
someplace else,
dumped and laid out in a ritualistic
manner, just like all the others.
Except she wasn't in pieces.
But she had cuts
on her neck.
I'm just saying, with all the media
coverage on the ice-truck killer,
it's possible.
What do you suggest, Morgan?
Let me work up a profile, just
in case Jorge doesn't pan out.
Fine.
Whatever.
That's the second time you've made
that face. Who are you avoiding?
We got one more stop to make.
Nothing lasts forever.
Just ask a Ford Pinto.
Eventually, most serial killers
get caught.
There's really not much
of a retirement plan.
But it can't end like this.
It's too soon.
I'm not ready.
He saw me.
What's this?
You've been asking who's been
calling. My mom lives here.
Did you forget your laundry?
She's been on me to stop
by for dinner. So I'm stoppin' by.
And here's the plan.
We go in.
We eat. We out before
the cheesecake. You got it?
I'm, what, your
exit strategy?
Look, you can stay
out here if you want.
That gives me a better excuse
to leave earlier or...
...you can come in and have
some free food. It's your call.
Shit!
My sisters are here, too.
Fucking family reunion!
So this john comes out of nowhere.
He's got me by the throat.
I can't reach around
and get my gun
and I see he has
a nipple ring.
I rip that fucker out
like it's a grenade pin.
Morgan!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Cop mouth.
We're used to it.
When James graces his family
with this presence.
Some of us don't work at a bank.
Please, first words out of
my baby brother's mouth were,
"Got milk, motherfucker".
Oh, okay, now, that's enough,
all of you.
That security guard on the news
is gonna be all right?
If someone did a hatchet job
on me like that, I'd cash it all in.
Yeah, Tony's doing okay.
The hospital's setting him up
with some prosthetics.
I don't know, he's just got
this spirit about him.
The guy's missing body parts
because of this
ice-truck killer asshole,
and he's still hitting on me.
That's because men only
think with one body part,
and that one was not cut off.
Ma!
Well, it's the damn truth.
Morgan, come on.
We got a case to solve.
Oh, are you sure, honey? I got
some cheesecake in the fridge.
Yeah.
We're sure.
You know...
I would love
some cheesecake bit.
You can wait in the car.
That's your call.
He'll wait.
- I'll do the dishes.
- I'll help you.
Ooh, I'm sorry.
I wonder, in time,
if they'll even remember me,
other than the man who broke
their mother's heart.
I'll be breaking
their hearts, too.
He is their father.
They have a right to know
he's been released, right?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah. Even if I tell Paul not to come,
he'll show up here eventually.
I know him.
Everything's been going
so good at work...
With you.
I don't know what to do.
He's really got a hold on you,
doesn't he?
Paul always had a temper,
but when he was using...
He said if I...
...left, he would find
us and hurt the kids.
Somehow, I thought that by staying,
I was protecting them.
Cody doesn't remember
the worst of it, but...
Astor...
She was the one who called
the police the last time.
She was protecting me.
You're not that
woman anymore.
You're stronger
than that now.
If their dad shows up,
we'll deal with it together.
Dad's coming home?
Can he sleep in my room, mom?
Can he, mom?
I shouldn't even be here.
Rita will be devastated
if I'm arrested.
Her husband was a crackhead,
her boyfriend's a serial killer.
It's kind of hard not
to take that personally.
Better get inside, son.
Storm's on its way.
Why didn't you tell me
what you are, Dex?
Any last words?
Figures.
I don't have
bad dreams.
When I sleep,
all of me sleeps.
Nothing ever goes bump
in Dexter's night.
I've never felt a
moment of remorse,
doubt,
regret.
What's happening to me?
If my back wasn't against
the wall, I'd almost feel guilty
for hacking into
Masuka's e-mail.
Once I got past all the porn,
it was easy.
And there I am.
Dr. Patrick Bateman --
So wholesome, so inconspicuous.
Harry would frown upon
destroying evidence,
but he never wanted me
to get caught, either.
What are you doing in here?
My computer went down.
I was just checking some e-mail.
Can you take a look
at this for me?
Copycat killer?
I worked all night
on that profile.
I'd like to give it to Laguerta, but
I want to make sure it's good enough.
I'm honored.
"The similar manner in which the victim's
body was displayed suggests this killer
"feels a connection
to the ice-truck killer,
"excited by what he's doing.
"The cut on the victim's cheek,
while not fatal,
"appears to be
a signature of sorts.
"Because of the lack of evidence
collected from the crime scene,
"the suspect may be familiar
"with law enforcement
or forensics procedure."
Why'd you quit? You're getting
to the good stuff.
Let me guess --
Single white male, mid-30s,
lives alone,
disconnected
from his emotions.
It's a little textbook,
don't you think?
But it totally fits this case.
You're trying to make it fit.
My advice?
Keep this to yourself.
Really?
Deb, you're new to Homicide.
This blows up in your face,
you've given
Laguerta the excuse
she's been looking for
to send you back to Vice.
No.
I'm on to something here.
I feel it.
Like one of your hunches.
Way to have my back.
Where's your sister?
Debra! What the hell
do you think you're doing?
How did you get into my cabinet?
You hide the
key in the pantry...
...on the top shelf.
You and your brother know
never
to touch my guns unless
it's under my direct supervision.
But I was being really careful!
I mean,
I was only shooting at
the cans and the bottles.
And I'm really good,
like Dexter,
and now we can all
go hunting together.
I'm disappointed in you, Debra.
Grab your things.
Thanks a lot.
Starting this morning, we have
cadets from the academy
going over every inch
of the salvage yard.
Those days I don't miss.
The kid we found yesterday
saw someone abduct Valerie
Castillo from that yard.
Because he didn't recognize
a photo of Jorge Castillo,
Lieutenant Laguerta is bringing
him in to attempt a sketch.
Come on, sweetheart.
Let's take the seatbelt off.
There you go.
Come on.
Come on, sweetheart.
You want to go inside
to see the nice lady?
Come on, sweetie.
Let's go.
Thanks for bringing him by.
Hola, Oscar.
?T? quieres venir conmigo?
Normally, I wouldn't approve
of something like this,
but you've made
quite an impression.
You have kids?
No.
I was like him once --
A stranger in a strange place,
left to grow up
with strangers,
all for a better life.
Well, police lieutenant --
I'd say you've done okay.
- Any luck with the family?
- No. He talks about an Uncle Roberto.
He just uses the first name.
Maybe we'll have
some luck on our end.
I hope so.
I hate to send another one
of these kids into foster care.
Thank you.
Bye, sweetheart.
Meanwhile, we'll follow
up on the D.E.A. list
of M-99 buyers.
That would include
vets, doctors,
animal control, even circuses.
Be thorough.
Check everyone.
Masuka, what do we have on
the home and the boat?
Still processing, sir.
If it turns up the husband
is a dead end,
then we're looking at
a new suspect, folks.
Morgan.
Any ideas?
Don't do it, Deb.
The last thing
I need right now
is to be profiled for
all of Miami metro.
We could be looking at
someone who's inspired
by the ice-truck killer.
A copycat.
If so, the suspect is probably
familiar with forensic procedures.
I have a profile. I'd be happy
to show it to you.
I'll be in my lab.
Hello, Dex.
Oscar...
?El hombre que viste era
como yo o m?s delgado?
Mi hijito, est? bien.
Cu?ntanos.
Cu?ntanos lo que
t? viste esa noche.
- I'll be right back.
- No!
Est? bien,
me quedo aqu?.
I forgot how much I loved
pastelitos growing up.
He just needed
a little reminder of home.
I was barely his age when I came
over with my family.
I threw up
the whole damn way.
?Quieres m?s?
?Cinco?
Go get the artist. I think
somebody's ready.
Save me some.
No, dice que no.
Cinco no puede.
Pero tres, s?.
- No es 5, es 10.
- ?10?
Te digo que t? hablas con el se?or
cuando el venga, y entonces,
s?, yo te doy 10,
lo que t? quieras. 20.
30.
- 50?
- 50.
Did you thank Mrs. Carrol
for picking you up
from school for me?
Yes.
So, what do you think?
Everything okay?
You want to talk out it?
Holly, Blake, and Ashley said
they can't come to my party.
Honey, that's not true.
I spoke with their moms last week.
It's all Cody's fault.
He couldn't keep his mouth shut
about dad getting out of jail.
- Did not!
- You told everyone!
I have to know.
Dexter...
Thank god.
My arm's asleep.
How long have you
two been like this?
Half an hour.
I was afraid I'd wake him
if I moved.
At that age, when they're out,
they're out.
You could brush his teeth,
and he wouldn't wake up.
Here. Lift up his head.
I'll slide this underneath.
Oh, thanks.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting on some lab work.
I had some time to kill.
Go ahead. We didn't get very far.
He's so tired.
We're gonna pick it up
again tomorrow.
It's only a matter of time
before we know what
this little guy saw.
If you, um... here.
You want help or not?
I have a hair or something
stuck on my lens.
Luckily, you're in good hands.
I traded my glasses in for
contacts in high school.
Boys?
Yeah. What I really
needed was tits.
I had Winnie the Poohs on my bras
until I was 16. As you can see,
- not a whole lot's changed since then.
- Morgan.
Try not to blink, okay?
Okay, okay.
I'll do it.
Let me ask you something.
Your brother's adopted,
right?
Yeah, my dad found him
at a crime scene.
How did the department
feel about Harry getting...
personally involved in a case?
It didn't seem to be a problem.
My parents never talked about it much.
Oh, but still, raising a boy,
it's a lot of work, no?
Dex?
God, no.
I got in more trouble than he did.
He was the perfect one.
Here, I think I see it.
There's the bastard.
Thanks.
Let me ask you a question.
Why do you have it in for me?
You're loud,
you're impulsive, and
you constantly
question authority.
Fair enough.
I hear you have an
interesting theory on --
Honey, what is it?
Sweetie.
I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
It's all right.
These things happen.
Go get changed,
and I'll fix the bed.
Mommy?
Is it okay if
I didn't have my party?
It's only a matter of time
before that boy finishes telling
the police who he saw that
night at the salvage yard --
Me.
Once the sketch is finished,
there will be no place left to hide.
If I want any chance of survival,
I have to get rid of it all.
I have to let go.
Alex Timmons --
Sniper.
Yes, I did it. Is that
what you want to hear?
Gene Marshall --
Arsonist.
Have you ever watched
someone burned alive?
Cindy Landon --
Black widow.
I'll fuck you
if you let me go.
Such fond memories of them all.
They all accepted their fate
in their own way.
Now it's time for me
to do the same.
Valerie Castillo --
My last victim.
He's not angry. That's not
what this is about.
He's testing me.
I was wrong
the whole time.
My playmate saw an opportunity
to paint me into a corner
to see if I'd find my way out,
if I'd fight to survive.
If you have a
well-preserved sample,
transferring a dry drop of blood
is relatively easy,
almost as easy as it was lifting
Jorge Castillo's fingerprints
from his boat and
putting them on this knife.
Just got off the phone
with the FBI.
Now for the hard part.
I wanted to see what their
computers would spit out.
I cross-referenced my profile
with the ice-truck killer list.
11 new hits.
How about we hold off till
we get a sketch,
take it from there.
I know, I know. I want to get
a head start on this.
We could look these over
at lunch -- My treat.
You never give up,
do you?
Thank your mom for dinner
the other night.
Can't remember
the last time
I met a guy's family
and they actually liked me.
You held your own.
Most people don't get
a dirty word in edgewise
with my sisters around the table.
In our house, every Thursday
night was pancake night --
A Morgan tradition.
I miss that kind
of stuff, you know?
I found something.
The wife's blood?
You're sure?
This was found in the Castillo's
bedroom hamper.
We check all the clothing items
that come in.
Sometimes because of sheer
volume, that takes time.
It doesn't prove anything.
Not by itself but
I've been re-examining the video
footage I took from that morning.
Notice the cuts along
the carotid arteries.
They're long, deep.
Valerie Castillo bled to death
in minutes.
No shit.
The person who did this
wasn't trying to emulate
the ice-truck killer. He was...
in a hurry.
He was probably afraid
of getting caught.
Most killers are.
Except if this was a copycat,
he wouldn't be in a rush.
He would savor his first kill.
He would control the precise moment
Valerie Castillo died instead of
just letting
her bleed out.
This is all too...
passive.
Have you completely ruled out
the husband?
Why are you doing this?
The boy said he didn't recognize
Jorge Castillo in any of the photos.
Well, he was a dehydrated and
traumatized 7-year-old
left to fend for himself
for days in a salvage yard.
You really think it's the husband?
He's a deep-sea fisherman.
Most know how to use a knife.
Plus, he's still missing.
Have you finished your search
of the salvage yard?
I'll have them send
the cadets out again.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I know how hard you worked
on that profile.
No, Dex, I really
don't think you do.
How long are you grounded for?
Two months.
Deb, I had to tell him.
No, Dex, you didn't.
You could have kept
your fucking mouth shut.
Dad was worried about you,
and so was I.
Well, now you can spend
more time together.
I'm not stupid, Dexter.
That's always what you wanted.
No, it's not.
Deb, you're my sister.
No, I am not.
And he is my father!
There are so many times,
I swear, Dexter,
I wish he wouldn't
have brought you home!
Dexter, I am...
so sorry.
I really... really didn't
mean it like that.
Here.
I thought you might want that.
You're a better shot
than me anyway.
- Hello?
- Paul, hey, it's me.
- Look, we need to talk.
- Sure thing.
I know you want to see Astor, but, I mean,
the kids are doing so well now.
Maybe -- Maybe it would be
a good idea if you...
...don't come to the party.
- I just want...
- She is my daughter, too, Rita.
I have every
right to be there.
You know what?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but I have
full custody now,
and you can't just drop in
on us like this anymore.
Now, I checked and the restraining
order is still in effect.
So if you step one foot
on this property,
the first call I'm gonna
make is to the police.
The second call is
to your parole officer.
I need the sergeant.
Morgan.
I'll be right there.
Est? listo.
Ya lo tir?.
Oscarsito.
It?o Roberto!
The uncle called our office
this morning. He lives in Tampa.
That's great.
He should be with family.
Can I take him home?
We're good.
Thank you.
Thank you for
finding him, huh?
He's a very special boy.
I know.
Cu?date?
L.T., you need to see this.
- You okay?
- These contacts.
Dios m?o.
Wrecks like this are usually
sold for scrap.
The husband stashes
a knife inside
and lets a demo crew
shred the truck
before we find it.
No more murder weapon.
There's blood.
Want to bet it's the wife's?
It's always the husband.
You were right all along.
Shake it off, Morgan.
Homicide takes time.
Deb will forgive me...
eventually.
That's who she is --
Bighearted, kind.
Nothing like me.
- Laguerta thought you should see this.
- What you got?
That kid Oscar swears
this is who he saw.
- Son of a bitch.
- Dex.
Okay, I gave them Jorge's sock,
a knife with his prints,
and a drop of his wife's blood.
Forensics trifecta like that
should trump a child's drawing...
I hope.
- Too fucking weird.
- Jesus Christ saved this kid?
On his own for
as long as Oscar was,
who's to say he didn't?
When did lighting candles become
more fun than blowing them out?
Nice turnout.
I called all the moms
to assure them
that Paul would not be
making an appearance.
Do Astor and Cody know that
you told their dad not to come?
After presents.
Ready?
Make a wish, baby.
Just don't tell anybody,
or it won't come true.
It already came true.
Dad's not here.
- I want the middle piece.
- Okay.
I was wrong about birthdays.
Maybe the reason to celebrate
them is what they offer --
The hope of living
to see another one.
The thing about
Deb forgiving me --
I better give her
a few more days.
I barely escaped getting
caught this time.
I realize now my days
are numbered.
So I better make
the most of them.
All along, I thought
this was a game
my alter ego and
I were playing.
But relationships change,
evolve,
and this one's getting deep.
Like Harry said in my dream...
...the storm's on its way.