Previously on "Dexter"...
I got here as fast as I could.
What are we looking at?
Female victim,
cut up into pieces.
The ice-truck killer?
So soon?
This is what he wanted
me to find all along.
Dexter...
Laura Moser...
My mother.
Laura Moser and 3 others found
chopped up with a chain saw.
Your father was a decent
man and an honest cop,
but what he saw in that
cargo container changed him.
Angel was stabbed
from behind.
You think
it's the attacker's blood?
We know Batista fought back.
The samples you gave
me were a match.
They're from the same person.
So if you or that skinny bitch
try to screw with what's mine,
I swear to God,
I don't care who I have to hurt.
Let's face it, Paul.
You've been a problem.
I need you to explain to
them why you're in this place.
I have no fucking idea
why I'm in this place.
You really don't
want to do this.
Effective immediately, you will
no longer serve as my lieutenant.
This isn't fucking over, Tom!
Debra Morgan...
Will you marry me?
Yes, yes, yes.
Where's my sister?
Took her code 12.
Left about an hour ago.
She went to dinner?
She wasn't supposed to go anywhere.
You made it easy.
So desperate to fall in love.
Where the fuck are you?
I'm here at work, and you're not.
I need to talk to you.
Do not see Rudy
until you find me.
I've lived in
darkness a long time.
Over the years,
my eyes adjusted
until the dark became my
world and I could see.
But then Rudy turned
on the light.
He flooded my memory,
and now I'm blind.
I don't have much time --
or, to be more accurate,
my sister doesn't have much time.
He wants me to find him,
but where do I look?
I can't think.
It's too bright.
Let me know if the
tape's too tight.
You know, there's no need
for you to be uncomfortable.
Why are you doing this?
Wouldn't want to
spoil the surprise.
Oh, God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Shh, I'm just checking
the supplies, okay?
Things are moving a little
faster than I had planned.
This isn't you.
Pretty sure it is.
No!
I know there's more --
I've seen it.
I never wanted to hurt you.
I know. I know.
Does this make it easier for you?
Because I can keep going.
Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
There's nothing to be
ashamed of, Deb. I mean,
you're not the only one
who bought it, okay?
Your name isn't even
fucking Rudy Cooper, is it?
Nope...
But he died
for a good cause.
Yeah, so will you.
You kidnapped a cop this time,
you know?
Not some invisible hooker --
you kidnapped a cop!
It's all part of the plan.
Oh, Jesus.
It's hard to believe it's
almost come to fruition.
I mean, this is a lot of years
in the making.
We're only hours away.
He wouldn't have taken
Deb unless he left me
everything a clever monster
would need in order to find them.
* Born free, *
* As free as the wind blows *
* As free as the grass grows *
* Born free to
follow your heart *
Seems I have a
new screen saver.
I knew he wouldn't
leave me stranded,
but "Born free"?
Of course.
Thanks to Rudy, now I know where
dearly disturbed Dexter was born.
Born free
of all that's human --
That's where I'll find him.
She knows.
All fucking night with that.
Listen, Angel,
we need your help.
Masuka says you were
following up a lead
on the ice-truck killer
when you were attacked.
A hooker with a
prosthetic hand.
John painted her nails
different colors,
but it didn't go nowhere.
Except she was just cut up
by the ice-truck killer.
Holy shit.
Monique was a victim?
Now, we're operating
on the theory
that he found out you
were on his trail.
And if we're right,
that means you got stabbed
for a reason.
It wasn't no carjacking.
How did he know it was me?
No one knew what I was
doing except Masuka.
Someone else had
to know. Think.
I consulted with Rudy,
Debra's boyfriend,
the prosthetics guy.
But that's crazy, right?
No, she's been AWOL since going
out last night to meet him.
She was supposed to come
back and help me canvass,
- but she never made it.
- That's not like her.
- Angel, we got to go.
- Go, just go.
There are roughly 5,000 cargo
containers in the port of Miami.
Finding the one where my mother
was butchered took a bit of magic.
Busted.
Shit.
Just a second!
I told you he was here.
There some reason you're not
answering your damn phone?
Ambien.
What happened here, Dexter?
I couldn't find the remote.
Where's your sister?
She didn't come back to work,
and she's not at her apartment.
I honestly don't
know, sergeant.
Dexter...
We think her boyfriend Rudy's
connected to the ice-truck killer.
We're working on getting
a search warrant right now
to search his home.
No.
Wow...
Cut the crap.
You know something.
What?
James!
I saw him last night,
skulking in the lab,
ordering secret blood tests.
What kind of tests?
I was looking for a type match on
the blood on Batista's collar.
And whose was it?
Rudy's.
- Motherfucker.
- Knock it off!
- He knew all along!
- Rudy lied about a cut on his lip.
Angel headbutted his
attacker in the face.
- It was just a wild hunch.
- Why didn't you tell us?
I couldn't destroy Deb's
love life on a hunch.
- I had to get the facts.
- Here are the facts:
if he kills her, it's your fault.
Now, what else do you know?
That's it.
He's lying.
Give him a break, James.
It's his sister, all right?
Well, if he knows what's good for her,
he'll sit his ass at home
and answer the fucking
phone when it rings.
Call if you hear anything.
Hello?
Please don't hang up.
Paul?
The kids don't want
to talk to you, all right?
You got to give them
more time.
This isn't about them.
It's about how
I was arrested.
Yeah, with a needle in your arm --
I know all about it.
Well, I don't.
Listen, I take responsibility
for all the shit I pulled,
but, Rita,
I was in the program.
I kicked the hard stuff.
Well, apparently not.
I was clean.
I swear on my kids' lives.
It's been driving
me nuts how I got --
from your house one minute
to the motel room the next,
completely out of
my mind on junk.
Yeah, it's called
a blackout, Paul.
- It's called a setup.
- Well done.
The last thing I remember
was standing in the
kitchen, talking to Dexter.
Now, he could have smacked
me over the head and
dragged me out of the house
probably through the backyard.
You really are a piece of work.
I'm telling you --
Dexter is not who
you think he is.
Hello?
This one, I've got to make sure we
got about seven copies of these.
I want to make sure it's
distributed to everyone, okay?
Okay, his name is Rudy Cooper.
Some of you may
have met him.
He was dating
officer Morgan.
Now, she was last
seen 16 hours ago,
driving to meet him at
the Miami Beach marina.
So we need to canvass
the entire area.
Check boat rentals.
You guys know the drill.
I've already sent a team over to
his prosthetics lab at the hospital.
The judge just signed off on the
warrant for Cooper's apartment.
Well, let's tear
that place apart.
Jake, Sergio, Kim,
you guys are with me.
Your attention, please.
I want to introduce you to our
new lieutenant, Esmee Pascal.
She agreed to put her vacation
on hold, come in early,
to provide us with
some much-needed leadership
at this critical time.
Lieutenant, you're on.
I understand we
have a new suspect
in the ice-truck killer case.
We're on our way over
now to search his place.
And you are...
Maria Laguerta.
And we have an officer missing,
so we need to move fast.
I thought that sergeant Doakes
was running that investigation.
- He's out following a lead.
- What lead?
He said he'd let me know if it came
to anything. Now if you excuse me --
I'll take it over from here.
Thank you, Maria.
Who here can get me up to
speed on the way over?
I can, I guess.
You're driving.
And feel free to join us when
you locate your partner.
Would you like to come
with us, captain?
You seem to have
everything under control.
Let's go, people.
It's in there somewhere --
My birthplace.
Now what?
No cameras,
no patrols, no dogs.
With billions spent
on Homeland Security,
it can't be as easy
as a couple of snips.
So much for the war on terror.
Finding a needle in a haystack isn't hard
isn't hard when every
straw is computerized.
Reefer yard, plug 4-3-6.
I don't like this place.
Something nameless
was born here...
Something that lives
in the deepest, darkest hole
of the thing called "Dexter."
Get in there!
Somebody else --
Get in there now!
It's all right, little guy.
You're safe now.
Nothing will hurt you --
I promise.
Okay, Deb...
don't be dead.
Shit.
Surprise, motherfucker.
Are you following me now?
You better have a hell of
a reason for being here.
I'm looking for my sister.
In a cargo box?
Yeah, I'm kind of
working on a theory.
You forget you work
for the fucking cops?
We love theories.
Spin me a story, asshole.
What I do on my time is
my business, sergeant.
Yeah, me too,
and I'm on my time now.
There's no lieutenant
here to save your ass,
so don't fuck with me,
Morgan!
All right, you got me.
I ordered some
furniture from Thailand.
I was waiting for
it to be delivered.
Lab geek --
My ass.
Hey, what the hell's
going on over here?!
Security, I need to get
somebody down here right now.
Miami metro P.D.
Yeah
Is this guy under arrest?
That's a good question.
You're connected to this.
I don't know how,
but I'm gonna find out,
and some of what I find is
gonna stick to your ass.
Let me out of
here, motherfucker!
Let me out of here!
Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out, you piece of shit!
Let me out of here,
you fucking piece -- Aah!
Fuck! Let me out!
Sorry, but you were
drowning out Fred's radio,
and he was kind enough
to lend us his wheels.
Bye!
His happy place,
where he kills more than time --
This is where he'd
leave me a clue.
- Hey, Dexter, better bundle up.
- I like the cold.
You know, hypothermia can
easily sneak up on you.
Yeah, and so can hypochondria.
And a home setup like this would
take years to put together.
He must have hated
leaving it behind.
What are you looking for?
A clue, signature
or calling card --
Anything that might give us
a sense of where he went.
Well, I don't think he was exactly
thinking about us when he did this.
I mean, look at this place.
Hey, you were right about the
victim at Santa's cottage.
He rushed his work.
He killed that girl to keep
us busy so he could escape,
but he wouldn't go without
leaving us a message.
We just need to find it.
Check this out.
This is where he
played with his meat.
Pretty whacked out, huh?
I can think of 101
uses for this table.
Know what I mean?
He has my sister, Vince.
Right.
I mean -- I didn't
mean -- I'm sorry.
Shit.
You're Karen, right?
That's right.
You're in charge of evidence --
this entire room -- evidence.
Take photos of every item
in its original position:
work-kit, packages...
Show me the inventory
list when you're done.
Is he in charge?
Guess he is now.
Rita?
Hi. I'm Bob Hicks.
Can I help you?
I guess Paul never
mentioned me.
I'm his Narcotics
Anonymous sponsor.
Right.
So, having your sponsor
do your dirty work --
Which step is that?
See, he's --
he's just concerned for the kids.
No, he's concerned for himself.
If you'll excuse me...
I thought he was lying,
too, until I saw the proof.
What proof?
Well, the X-rays the prison
doctor took of Paul's head --
They showed a
skull fracture.
Yeah, which I
deservedly gave him.
No.
You didn't.
See,
after you struck him,
the hospital took X-rays --
No fracture.
- But in prison, a fracture.
- If you know Paul,
you'd know he'd bash his
own head against the wall
to get what he wants.
Well, I do know Paul.
I think I know him pretty well.
No, listen,
if Paul was attacked,
the way that it happened --
that takes expertise, skill.
No first-timer is gonna
be able to pull that off.
Yeah, which is why his
accusations are ludicrous.
Dexter spends all his time in
a laboratory, for God's sake.
So you've been there?
Bob...
You seem like a nice man,
but this is none of
your goddamn business.
Okay.
Got it.
We traced the name and
social of Rudy Cooper
to a New Jersey plumber who
mysteriously died in '98.
You got to be kidding me.
After all this,
we still don't have an I.D.
on this guy?
Rudy isn't his real name?
- You trying to be smart?
- Not trying, no.
If you fucking know his name,
you better --
Whatever it is going on
between you two, it ends now.
What did you find in there?
Other than the obvious,
a lot of trace bloodstains.
It's probably where
he killed them all,
but I'd like to look at the rest
of the apartment before I go.
Yeah, okay.
- You mind if I...
- Be my guest.
It's perfect --
Right out in the open.
At least he's consistent.
Was there anything else
near this record player?
Yeah, a fucking doll
sitting on top.
"Home sweet home."
Is he taking me back
before the blood,
to a place where
a boy was born?
"Home sweet home",
but which "home"?
Down on the floor, please.
It's kind of foolish, Deb.
I don't usually work this way.
Call it
an homage to a fellow
traveler I greatly admire.
Laura Moser --
addict, dealer --
My mother.
Arrested in '69,
again in '71.
Same address
listed both times.
1235 Mangrove Drive.
They say home is
where the heart is.
Maybe this is
where I left mine.
Surprise.
What are you doing here?
White-chocolate mocha --
Your favorite.
I'm gonna have to
drink it on the road.
You know, I've never even been here
before. I'd love a tour sometime.
Yeah, sometime that's not now.
Dexter, what's going on?
It's Deb, okay?
She's in trouble.
Oh, God.
Is it serious?
Yeah, actually,
it's very serious,
but I just can't worry about you,
too, right now.
She knows. She knows.
She knows.
...been leaving a
trail of dead bodies.
Authorities say
their big break came
when they found a video
of his latest victim.
If she knows, you yapping about it
ain't gonna change it. Shut the fuck up!
The suspect is operating under
an alias -- "Rudy Cooper."
We didn't have his fingerprints
in our criminal database,
so his identity is
still unclear to us.
- She knows. She knows.
- So sorry, Mr. Batista.
We had to take the psych
overflow from County,
- but this one's harmless.
- Yeah, don't be so sure.
We never take
the violent ones.
They have the arsonists,
the rapists,
the psycho killers over there.
I tell you --
Those people belong in prison.
Do they fingerprint
psych patients at County?
Yes, of course.
Half of them don't
know their own names.
Got to I.D. them somehow.
That should take care of him.
Enjoy the peace and quiet.
I.D. tech.
Hey, it's, uh, Batista.
Can you do me a favor?
I need you to run
Rudy Cooper's prints
against psych, mental,
and institution records.
* Ring around the rosie *
* A pocket full of posies *
* Ashes, ashes *
* We all fall down! *
Dexter!
Where are you,
you silly little bear?
I'm gonna find you!
Where can you be?
You silly little goose.
I'm gonna find you!
You silly bear.
Where is my baby?
Where is my Dexter?
Where are you?
- Here!
- Oh, my goodness!
Oh my goodness!
You surprised me,
you stinky little bear.
Hey, where could your
brother be hiding?
Bynie's right there!
- Hey, Bynie.
- You weren't supposed to tell her.
You remember now?
Bynie.
You always had trouble
saying "Brian."
I have a brother.
A real brother --
None of this foster bullshit.
We're blood brothers,
through birth and death.
Watching mom die --
It's amazing that
we survived that, isn't it?
The chain saw,
the flying body parts, the blood.
You were there, too.
Two days sitting in blood
before they found us,
but you were young
enough to block it out.
I've never forgotten
the day that we were...
- Born.
- Exactly.
Where's Deb?
I waited for you
before we got started.
- Debra!
- She's not in here.
Deb!
Debra!
This is not the way I
envisioned our family reunion.
Come on, let's just sit down
and have a beer.
Deb?
That was the best wipeout.
You didn't even cry.
Next time you
try my skateboard,
bend your knees, okay?
Hi.
Look out!
I didn't want to
do it this way.
Okay, let's run his description
against Interpol's fugitive list,
in case he isn't American.
Rudy Cooper?
His real name
is Brian Moser.
Angel, what the hell
are you doing here?
I got a hit on his prints
from a Tampa mental
hospital where he grew up.
He was institutionalized for
antisocial personality disorder.
At 21, they said he was cured.
They released him.
Run the name "Brian
Moser" for credit cards,
bank accounts,
real-estate holdings --
anything that might tell
us where he's got Morgan.
Listen up.
We've triangulated
officer Morgan's cellphone.
Last known location --
20 miles off the coast,
which means he's
got her on a boat.
Lieutenant, we have his real name.
We're digging into his records now.
His name's not gonna help
us find him in open water.
I want a coordinated search
with the coast guard.
- Waste of time.
- Chain of command.
Flyovers, helicopters,
whatever it takes.
Lieutenant, that signal
died last night.
By now, he has most likely
taken her to his final location.
Noted.
Let's get busy, people.
Flyovers look
good to the press,
but they won't find Morgan.
You think the press
matters to me?
It matters to Captain Matthews,
and he calls the shots.
Look, I know you need
to define yourself here
and putting me in my place
is one way to do that,
but one of our own is missing,
and we shouldn't waste
our time pissing on trees.
I agree.
I can also see why
you were reassigned,
and it has nothing to
do with incompetence
and everything to do with the
Captain trying to save his job.
Okay.
Now, I was hired
with the directive
to not make
your life easy.
So you're gonna
ignore the lead?
You don't know me very well,
but luckily for officer Morgan,
neither does the Captain.
Nothing personal.
I swore that I'd have a --
beer with you before
we got started.
You made that kind
of difficult.
Sorry.
You don't ever have to
apologize to me, Dexter.
Not for who you are
or anything you do.
Looks just like it used to,
doesn't it?
Who does it belong to?
Me.
I got it for you, actually.
I'm really more an
apartment person.
You're trapped in a lie,
little brother,
the same lie they
tried forcing me into.
- "They"?
- You know...
Doctors, therapists,
group leaders --
What a family they were.
You were never put
up for adoption.
Afraid not.
You were 3,
a little bird with
a broken wing.
First cop on the scene --
Harry Morgan.
He wanted to make
you all better.
But me --
I could see it in his eyes.
All he saw was a
fucked-up kid --
They all did,
so they locked me up.
I didn't even
know you existed.
Of course you didn't.
Harry wanted to keep
you all to himself.
And while you were being
raised by the Morgan family,
I only had the
memory of a family.
Me.
Mom always told me
to look after you.
Imagine how I felt
when I tracked you
down and found out
you were exactly like me.
I don't have to imagine.
I know what you've been going
through all these years --
The isolation, the otherness,
a hunger that's
never satisfied.
Well, you're not
alone anymore, Dexter.
You can be yourself
with me --
your real,
genuine self.
Takes the breath away,
doesn't it?
I think we're ready for Debra.
I've prepared her just
the way you like.
This time,
we'll do it together.
Does it have to be Deb?
It's the only way.
But she's my...
Fake sister
I know.
Tell me something...
Your victims --
Are they all killers?
Yes.
Harry teach you that?
He taught me a code...
To survive.
Like an absurd avenger?
That's not why I kill.
You can be yourself around me.
Who am I?
A killer...
...without reason or regret.
You're free.
You can be that way, too.
What about the code?
Damn it, Dex,
you don't have a code.
Harry did.
And he's been dead 10 years.
You can't keep him
sitting on your shoulder
like Jiminy
fucking Cricket.
You need to embrace
who you are now.
I don't know who I am.
Of course you don't.
You've been away from your
family since you were 3,
but I'm here now.
I can help you.
We can take this
journey together.
I can't.
Not Deb.
Oh, no. Don't --
Don't say that.
I'm very...
fond of her.
You can't be a
killer and a hero.
It doesn't work that way!
Morgan!
Cover the yard!
We're going into the house!
Fuck.
In the garage!
Through that door!
Cover this door!
Cover the door!
Come on. Stay with me.
Shit.
Maria, stay on the door.
He's trapped inside. I'm breaking in.
Cover me, man.
Get in.
Shit.
Chopper 1 to command --
We're broadening the
search to a 5-mile radius.
Any headache, dizziness?
I'm fine.
I just want to go home.
I'm afraid we have to transport
you to the hospital --
Standard procedure.
You're saying Rudy called you?
Why would he do that?
I think he wanted me to
try to talk him down.
He said he was having second
thoughts about killing Deb.
He seemed to feel like we
have some kind of connection.
He's not the only one.
He said he'd kill Deb if
I didn't show up alone.
Well, you almost
fucking got her killed.
I'm gonna request an immediate suspension
when we get back to the station.
You're gonna what?
Morgan, you shouldn't
be out here.
Are you questioning Dexter?
Morgan.
Back the fuck off my brother!
He just saved my life!
He's a fucking hero!
Want each of you to treat him
that way, god damn it!
Way to go, Deb.
I thought you were gonna burst
a frontal lobe out there.
Assholes.
Stop. You're gonna
dislocate it.
Oh, God, get it off me.
I'm gonna be sick.
Relax.
Here.
He's still out there.
Yeah.
And he didn't get
what he wanted.
No.
Think he'll try it again?
Maybe.
Yeah.
I'm gonna talk to Captain
Matthews about getting us
an officer stationed outside
your hospital room tonight.
No, I'm not staying in
a fucking hospital.
There's nothing
fucking wrong with me.
Well, you're not
staying at home.
Well, I'll just
crash with you.
Let's just wait and see what
the doctor says, all right?
Yeah.
Why me, Dex?
Why'd he choose me?
You're just lucky, I guess.
I was so scared.
I was so scared,
so scared.
I know.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Dad would be so proud.
- Dexter?
- It's me.
Paul, this is harassment.
Just tell me if
he's acting weird.
- Who?
- Dexter --
He hasn't been himself lately,
has he?
How could he be,
after what he did to me?
All right, that's it.
I'm done.
Call again,
and you can forget
about seeing the kids
this weekend or ever.
I am not gonna subject
them to your insanity.
Fine, if that's what it takes
for you to listen to me.
I just want to know
that they're safe.
Why are you doing this, Paul?
You want me to be miserable
and alone like you? Is that it?
All I want
is for you to
look for a shoe.
A shoe?
Could be in the kitchen.
Could be in the backyard.
It's missing.
I checked, and it wasn't in the items
that they got from the motel
room when I was arrested.
And why would it be here?
I was trying to figure out
why my ankle was so bruised.
Now I'm thinking it got banged
when Dexter dragged me out,
- when my shoe was knocked off.
- Good night, Paul.
Night.
Screw you.
What did I just do?
I drove away a brother who accepts me,
sees me,
for an adopted sister
who'd reject me if she knew
and a foster father
who betrayed me.
That's what it was --
A betrayal.
The most important
single fact about me --
I'm not alone --
and Harry kept it from me.
What do I really
owe him after that?
Mr. Morgan?
That's me.
Your sister has a few bruises,
but no major injuries.
Still, you should
keep an eye on her.
I'll write a prescription
for a mild sedative.
But she's okay, right?
She can go home with you
tonight, far as I'm concerned,
or we can keep her here at the
hospital -- it's your choice.
Don't worry.
The sheets are clean.
We aim to please
here at "Chez Dex".
I'll be sleeping on the couch
with a spring in my side
just to make sure you're
safe tonight, but...
We're gonna have to talk
tomorrow about a long-term plan,
after you get a
good night's sleep.
Deb?
Good night, sister.
I stopped by your
prosthetics lab
after I left Deb
at the hospital.
Your work's so good,
you even fooled yourself.
Sweet dreams, Bynie.
Hey.
You weren't supposed
to wake up.
I guess not.
Sorry.
Police recorded all your
knives as evidence.
Took a while to find
your dinner flatware.
Sterling.
I keep it for
special occasions.
Which you are.
I can give you more
tranquilizer if you want.
It's a service I
don't usually offer.
What am I --
One of your victims now?
You going to collect
a little sample
of Bynie's blood for
your slide collection?
No, you're not a trophy...
...but you need to be put down.
Why?
Because of your code?
The safety of my sister.
She's not your real sister.
She's a stranger to you,
and she'll always be one.
I tried to help
you by killing her.
I know that!
You should know this
isn't easy for me.
You've done more to deserve
my knife than anyone.
You're the only one I
ever wanted to set free.
You're the one that needs
setting free, little brother.
Your life is a lie.
You'll never be what you --
Sorry.
I can't hear any more...
'cause you're right.
How did you know he was here?
A neighbor saw the door open.
We got his fingerprints on the knife,
a note on the fridge,
and a single incised
wound to the neck.
Slight upward angle.
Even a stigmata of
hesitation in the stroke.
Looks like a clear suicide.
He does himself the same
way he did the hookers.
- Poetic.
- Retarded.
Look at him
-- He's dead.
The ice-truck killer
always flaunted his kills
like he was untouchable.
By taking his own life,
he's preventing us from
ever catching him.
I don't care why he did it.
I'm just glad he did.
Decaf mochaccino, nonfat, no whip --
your favorite.
I got your message.
How's Debra?
She has all her limbs.
Thank God she's alive.
That poor thing
must be a mess --
Falling for a serial killer.
What are the odds?
- What about you?
- What about me?
- Are you all right?
- Oh, yeah.
No.
I've been through a lot lately.
I could use a little
more time with you --
and the kids.
We could, too.
I'm sorry I've been so --
Next time, could you just
let me know what's going on?
I mean, when you
didn't return my calls, I --
started to get
a little paranoid.
I can be better about that.
Good.
Who knows?
You might even find I
can handle the truth.
I wish that was the case.
The reality is,
there's nobody left alive
who can handle my truth.
Doakes always sensed
I was hiding something.
Now he knows.
My devil danced
with his demon,
and the fiddler's tune
is far from over.
Sometimes, I wonder
what it would be like
for everything inside me
that's denied and unknown
to be revealed.
But I'll never know.
I live my life in hiding.
My survival depends on it.
Dearly damaged Debra --
She's here to face what's
left of the monster,
spit on his carcass,
mourn him.
She's in hiding now, too.
Harry's daughter
will be damned
if she lets anyone see what
she's suffering inside.
That's her tragedy.
My tragedy is that I
killed the one person
I didn't have to hide from.
And I'm the only
one who mourns him.
Everyone else would
probably thank me
if they knew I was the one
who drained him of his life.
Good job in there, Dex.
You sliced him up good.
In fact, deep down, I'm sure they'd
appreciate a lot of my work.
Way to take out the trash.
Thanks, buddy.
All right, Dexter,
protecting our children!
This is what it must feel like
to walk in full sunlight,
my darkness revealed,
my shadow self embraced.
Yeah, they see me.
I'm one of them...
in their darkest dreams.