Did you hear about this study
that found people
that were cool and popular
at 13
have problems succeeding
later in life?
Hmm. I'm doing okay,
and I was very popular at 13.
In school?
Oh, no. At home.
The servants would sing to me,
laugh at my jokes...
I wish I knew their names.
Does the study say what happens
to the unpopular kids?
You tell me-- you woke up
in bed with one.
Listen to this.
I just received an e-mail
from Wil Wheaton.
Leonard Nimoy's son is
working on a documentary
that he started with his
father before he passed away.
It's about Mr. Spock and
his impact on our culture.
Hmm.
Why is he writing to you?
Well, they're looking
for fans to interview,
and Wil thought
I'd be good for it.
Oh. Hey, high five.
Absolutely not.
Yeah, Penny,
you spent some time
in front
of the camera.
Any words of advice?
Yes. Don't take your shirt off
just because the director
said so.
This is a documentary
about Mr. Spock.
I'm sure if there's nudity,
it will be tasteful.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 9x07 ?
The Spock Resonance
Original Air Date on November 5, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(sword fight sound effects
on video game)
Hey. You got a minute?
Not really.
Visigoths are kind of up my butt
right now.
Pause the game, Howard.
“Howard”? Uh-oh.
Make room, Visigoths.
'Sup?
We need to talk
about redecorating this place.
Oh, no, not this again.
Look,
I get that you grew up here
and you're attached to things
looking
a certain way, but...
I want this to feel
like my house, too.
Oh, honey, of course
it's your house.
Why else would you
be cleaning it all the time?
(chuckles)
All right.
Let's start over.
I'm redecorating.
The furniture,
the carpeting, the walls.
I'm changing everything that
depresses me when I look at it.
Try not to be one
of those things.
May I say something?
Is it about how I can't have
new wallpaper
'cause your dad left when you
were little and your mom died?
Never mind.
Hello, Amy. It's Sheldon.
Yeah, I-I know
that we're broken up, but
I'm leaving this message because
I thought perhaps you'd like
to watch me be interviewed for
a documentary about Mr. Spock.
Or as I like to call it,
a Spockumentary.
Yeah, I'm going to use
that joke in the interview,
so try to laugh
like you're hearing it
for the first time.
You know, hysterically, hmm?
And with a tinge of sadness
that I'm no longer in your life.
I'm the one who thought
of “Spockumentary”"
And I'm laughing like I did
the first time I heard it.
(knocking on door)
Hello.
Hey, Sheldon.
This is Adam Nimoy.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
I admire your father's work
very much.
It's not every day I get to meet
someone whose life's journey
began in my hero's scrotum.
I told you.
This guy is gold.
Whatcha doing?
Oh!
Making myself a bologna sandwich
like my mom used to make me
after my dad left,
but before she died.
Okay, listen, I'm thinking
that maybe we can compromise
on the house.
I'm listening.
Let's just redo one room
and see how it goes.
That is reasonable.
But what room?
How 'bout this one?
No way. No, this is the room I
associate the most with my mom.
Then how 'bout the bathroom?
I want to change my answer.
Fine. Then the dining room.
I guess we didn't use it
very often.
Unless we had company.
Which didn't happen much
after my dad left and not at all
after my mom...
Great! I'm gonna go
pick out paint samples.
All right, we're just gonna
have a conversation.
Pretend the
camera's not here.
All right.
But this better not be
some elaborate scheme
to get me out of my shirt.
How long have
you known Adam?
A few years.
Mm-hmm.
And what are you
getting him back for?
Let's start with your
name and occupation.
Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
theoretical physicist, Caltech.
And what is your earliest memory
of the character Spock?
The first episode of Star Trek:
The Original Series I ever saw
was “The Galileo Seven.”
Uh, Spock had just landed
on the planet Taurus II.
Then my brother came in,
sat on my head,
and said, “Eat farts.”
After that day, I was hooked.
On Star Trek,
not my brother's
sphincter-based cuisine.
What was it about Spock
that appealed to you?
I think the same thing that
appeals to people everywhere,
the dream
of a cold, rational world
entirely without human emotion.
Spock came
from a planet governed
only by logic.
You know, on Vulcan,
when your brother asks,
“Why are you hitting yourself?”
the answer is,
“I'm not.
You're moving my arm.”
To which he says,
“Fascinating.”
And then you both watch
educational television.
(quietly): Aw. When he says
things like that,
I just want to hug him
and make everything better.
My brother was
mean to me, too.
Yeah, you probably
had it coming.
Do you have
any Spock collectibles?
I have many.
My most treasured
is an autographed napkin
given to me by my
very thoughtful friend Penny.
That's her over there.
Hi!
Look at that.
I'm in a movie,
my shirt stayed on.
Can we see the napkin?
Of course. Excuse me.
This will just take a moment.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
When did we get
a wall safe?
When there was no more room
in the floor safe.
When did we get
a floor safe?
When we got the security camera.
There's a
security camera?
Aquaman, protecting your home
since 2012.
Oh, my God.
We've done things on that couch.
Yeah. You don't have to tell me.
So, your father-in-law
is in there right now?
Yes. So back me up.
The house is good the way it is.
Oh, okay. Got it.
Hey. What's going on?
Hey.
Hey, Raj.
Dad and I were just talking
about taking down this wall.
You sure? It's a...
pretty great wall.
What's so great about it?
I'm sorry.
I did what I could.
Seriously? You brought Raj over
to take your side?
Your dad's on your side.
He's not on my side. He's doing
all the work for free.
That is so
generous of you.
I'd like to switch sides.
Look, uh...
I don't even think
you can take this wall down
'cause it's load-bearing.
Well, it's easy to find out.
Just go into the crawlspace
under the house and check.
When is your visa up?
Not only is it signed to me
but this is where he wiped
his mouth.
So we are currently in the
presence of Leonard Nimoy's DNA.
Um, doesn't Adam count
as Leonard Nimoy's DNA?
No offense, but this is
pure 100% Nimoy.
Because of your mother,
you're only 50%.
Which isn't bad,
but anything that you wipe
your mouth on gets thrown away.
Okay, enough
about the napkin.
What else you
hiding in there?
Wouldn't you like
to know?
I would.
All right then.
See? Just my valuables.
My passport, uh, my will...
You have a will?
Yeah-- my 1/18 scale
Wil Wheaton action figure.
I also have the other kind
of will,
and in it I will my Wil
back to Wil.
Will Wil want it?
Wil won't.
What's that ring box?
Oh. That is
an engagement ring
that I was going to give
my girlfriend Amy.
What?!
You bought her a ring?
No, no, no. This has been
in my family
for generations.
Except for a short time
when Comanches cut off my
great-great-great-grandmother's
finger and stole it.
Sheldon, that's awful.
No.
The Texas Rangers tracked them
down to their village
and slaughtered
every last one of them, so...
it was a happy ending.
Well, for my nine-fingered Nana.
Okay, back to the ring.
Does Amy even know about this?
No. She broke up with me before
I could broach the subject.
Oh, man, I'm sorry--
that must have been devastating for you.
No, not at all.
No, I'm fine.
You know, Amy had reservations
about our relationship,
so all worked out
for the best.
PENNY: I know. It just...
SHELDON: I said I'm fine!
We've gotten a little off-topic.
Allow me to make things
entertaining again
in this little Spockumentary.
That was Leonard's joke.
As a child,
when faced with a dilemma,
my mother encouraged me to ask,
“What would Jesus do?”
The answer to that was always,
“Love thy neighbor.”
But my neighbor had
a dead tooth, so...
that wasn't going to happen.
But...
that's why I changed it
to, “What would Spock do?”
Did you find that helpful?
Yes. Oh, for example,
three years ago
when I discovered Penny
was eating all my Pop-Tarts,
instead of getting angry
or vindictive,
you know, I got a floor safe.
I knew I could smell 'em.
What about
from when you were a kid?
Oh, certainly.
Uh, when I was eight years old,
Billy Sparks cornered me
in the playground.
I asked myself,
“What would Spock do?”
Then I grabbed Billy
on his shoulder
and performed
my first Vulcan nerve pinch.
Did it work?
Oh, no-- he broke my collarbone.
I can still hear it click.
That must have been
very upsetting for you.
Oh, not at all.
As I said, the entire point
of emulating Spock
was to rise above human emotion,
which I've spent
a lifetime mastering.
Oh... (sputters)
Excuse me?
I'm sorry.
I'm not here.
No. You went (sputters).
What does (sputters) mean?
Um...
You did go (sputters).
All right, fine.
Well, Sheldon, I'm no expert,
but aren't you completely
missing the point of Spock?
I mean, he liked to act
like he had no emotions,
but he was still half human.
Just like you.
I'm just saying,
you pretend you don't,
but you have feelings
just like everybody else.
Not true. No, look at me.
I had an engagement
ring to give a girl,
and instead,
she rejected me.
And am I emotional
about that? No.
No, I am sitting here
on a couch,
talking about my
favorite TV character
like nothing happened.
'Cause I am just like him:
all logical, all the time.
Sweetie, you're yelling.
Because when I speak
at a regular volume,
no one seems to believe me
that I've put
this Amy nonsense behind me!
(door slams)
This documentary
is gonna be awesome.
You gonna be okay down here?
Yeah. Yeah,
I feel like
an archaeologist.
Indiana Jones and
the Single-Family Dwelling.
Hey. Look!
Found a seashell.
Yeah, that's a rat skull.
(shrieks)
Relax.
There's enough droppings down
here without you making more.
Sorry. Do you have a...
sense of where we are?
Yeah. I think that's the den.
Oh. Okay, so we must be
under the dining room.
Uh-huh. Yep.
You know, I know you
don't want to hear this,
but it wouldn't take that
much work to turn that den
into a nursery.
Why wouldn't I want to hear it?
'Cause Bernie said
you didn't want kids.
That's not true at all.
I-I wish
she'd get pregnant, believe me.
I'm climbing on top of her
every chance I get.
(sighs)
In a... loving
and respectful manner.
Oh.
(clears throat softly)
The point is,
I really do want kids.
Huh.
I don't know why
she's lying to you.
WOLOWITZ: She's the one
who doesn't want kids.
In fact, every time I
bring up the subject...
Earthquake!
(Bernadette's feet
stomping rapidly)
Oh, my God,
we're gonna die!
Earthquake!
Aftershock...!
I can't believe Sheldon was
gonna ask Amy to marry him.
I know.
I also can't believe
he watched what we did
on that couch
and still sits on it.
Yeah.
Hello.
Hey, buddy.
How you doing?
Better.
Did Wil and Adam leave?
Yeah.
Do you think they're
going to put my outburst
in the documentary?
Definitely.
Oh, yeah.
Well, there's no point
in dwelling on it.
As the Vulcans say,
“Kup-fun-tor
ha'kiv na'ish Du stau.”
Do you know what that means?
No.
Are you telling the truth?
Nirsh.
Well, this is ridiculous.
Being upset about Amy
all the time
isn't accomplishing anything.
If I want to resolve
this situation,
then I need to take action.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to find her
and ask her to marry me.
And if she says yes,
we can put this behind us
and resume our relationship.
And if she says no...
well, then
she can just ponfo miran.
He didn't meant that.
So I should probably explain
why I kind of fibbed.
That would be nice.
I told my dad that
you were the one
who didn't want kids because I
didn't want to disappoint him.
But you were okay
throwing me under the bus?
Turns out yeah,
I didn't think twice about it.
Bernie, you don't need
to worry about me.
But I don't want
to see you miss out.
Raising children
was the most rewarding
experience of my life.
Oh, please.
Mom did everything.
All you did was
come home from work,
sit on the couch and drink beer.
How is that raising kids?
This is really
a conversation
for husband and wife.
(awkward chuckle) I'm gonna go clean up,
hit the road.
If your mother asks,
I was here till 10:00.
It's interesting your father
didn't help around the house
and Howard doesn't help, either,
so... in a way,
Howard's not only
like your father,
but he's also like the child
that you're afraid to have.
Why are you still here?
Fine, I'll leave.
But it sounds like
somebody needs a fresh diaper.
All right...
I admit...
that I don't help out a lot.
(chuckles softly)
And I need to work on that.
But...
(sighs) if we had a kid,
it would be different.
Why?
Because...
when my dad left,
I promised myself that...
if I ever had a chance
to be a father...
I'd always be there.
Okay, I'll think about it.
And this an actual
“I'll think about it,”
not like the
“can we get a motorcycle
with a sidecar
I'll think about it”?
It's an actual
“I'll think about it.”
I really believe
I'd be a great dad.
I know you would.
Speaking of...
making babies,
what do you say I wash up
and poke around your crawlspace?
(no voice)
Dr. Dana feels
he isn't that dangerous.
What makes you right and
a trained psychiatrist wrong?
Because she feels. I don't.
All I know is logic.
(scoffs):
Yeah, right.
(turns off TV)
You can just shut
your feelings off.
There goes television,
lying to us again.
We let you
raise our children,
and this is the thanks we get.
Leonard, how could I
have been so foolish
to try and follow
in the footsteps
of a made-up alien race
with no emotions?
(sighs):
Well...
now instead of idolizing
fictional characters,
you can focus on the real people
who are already in your life.
Those are very wise words.
Thank you.
They'd just be
so much more comforting
if they came
out of a television.
Captioning sponsored by CBS,
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org