Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
Well, there was this girl.
What did you do?
Nothing.
Really, it was just kissing.
All right.
So, we're still
getting married?
Yes.
Because we love each other.
And it's the happiest day
of our life.
Don't push it.
I need some time
to take a step back
and reevaluate our situation.
Oh.
Bye, Sheldon.
Well, Gollum...
...you're an expert on rings.
What do I do with this one?
So, what package
are you thinking?
Mm, this one comes with
music and flowers.
Oh, they even stream the whole
thing live on the Internet.
Why would we want that?
'Cause there's a lot
of gorgeous blondes out there
who don't believe they can land
a short, nearsighted scientist.
Let's give them hope.
Whatever. Put us
on the Internet.
I've always wanted a wedding
with a comment section.
I-If you're not into this,
we can do it another time.
No. No, I want to.
Look, we've put this
off long enough.
Let's do it.
Aw.
That's exactly what you said the
first time we slept together.
Oh, excuse me.
Sheldon.
Hey.
Leonard, have you
gotten married yet?
No. Why?
Good. Don't do it!
Why not?
Some important new information
has come to light.
Women are the worst.
I thought it was paper cuts,
but I was wrong.
No piece of paper
ever cut me this deep.
What happened now?
Amy has ended our relationship.
Oh, no. Seriously?
What's going on?
Amy broke up with Sheldon.
She did?
Is Penny crying?
No.
No, of course not.
They thrive on our suffering.
Buddy, I-I'm so sorry.
Is there anything I can do?
Yes. If I ever talk about
going out with a girl again,
roll your eyes at me
like I do to you
when you say dumb things.
Sheldon, uh, o-okay,
just because
you're going through this
with Amy
doesn't mean
that all women are bad.
Whatever.
Hey, I just heard
about you and Sheldon.
Are you okay?
Not really.
Can you come over?
Uh, actually I'm in Vegas.
Leonard and I
are about to get married.
Hold on.
You're getting married
and you didn't invite me?
Well, it was kind of
a spur-of-the-moment thing.
Wow.
Hope I can catch
the bouquet from here.
Amy, don't be like that.
Why did I just hear Amy's name?
Penny's on the phone
with her.
Did she say anything about me?
Never mind. I don't care.
Well, if you care,
you can find out and tell me.
Just don't be shocked when
you find out that I don't care.
Okay, will you relax?
You're not missing
anything special.
Hey.
She's upset.
Look, it's gonna be
a great wedding.
Look at you in
your little suit.
Amy's upset? Is it about me?
No, I think it's because
we're eloping.
Your marriage
is causing her pain?
Yeah, great, I take it back.
Go ahead and do it.
Yay for love!
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 9x01 ?
The Matrimonial Momentum
Original Air Date on September 2
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hello.
Oh!
What are you doing here?
When last we spoke,
you said you needed time.
Well, it's only been 11 hours.
The Lord of the Rings trilogy
was nearly 11 hours.
I made you watch that,
you said it was an eternity.
Sheldon, when I'm ready to talk,
I'll let you know.
Very well.
You seem to be
headed somewhere.
May I walk with you?
Sure.
Boy, I'm glad we're
going out again.
We're not back together.
Why?
Is there someone else?
Just couldn't wait
for that first notch
on your bedpost, could you?
If you must know,
I'm going to Howard
and Bernadette's
to watch the wedding.
And who's this guy
you're taking?
There's no guy!
Oh, you're going
to a wedding alone?
That's sad.
I'm not gonna be alone.
I'll be with my friends.
Your friends?
Well, I think you mean
my friends.
And why wasn't
I invited to this?
Maybe because the two of us
being there
would make them feel awkward.
We make everyone
feel awkward.
That's our thing!
They're running
a little behind.
Should be pretty soon.
Okay.
Hey, if you're hungry,
there's a breakfast buffet
at the strip club next door.
Thanks, but I don't like glitter
on my scrambled eggs.
I don't think the strippers
prepare the meal, but okay.
Look, it-it's not
how I pictured it either,
but I'm still glad
we're doing it.
Me, too.
You sure?
Yes.
And you promise
you're okay with
everything from the car?
Oh, my God, would you stop
bringing it up?
You're right.
I'm sorry.
We have the rest of our lives
to dredge stuff up from the past
and fight about it.
So what do you think?
Should we run next door
and grab a bite?
What if they call our names?
Oh, don't worry. They gave me
this vibrating coaster.
Oh, and the fairy tale
continues.
Thank you for doing this.
Our pleasure.
You feeling okay?
We were together for so long,
I honestly don't know
what I'm feeling.
Well, that's
understandable.
You forgot.
It's called "happy."
Howard.
I'm not saying
anything bad.
Just that she was in love
with her captor
and somehow managed to escape
from his dark and crazy dungeon.
I know
what you're going through.
My-my last breakup
was pretty tough.
Oh. What was her name?
Hey, it's a true story.
I don't need the third degree.
For God's sake, Sheldon,
what are you doing?
I didn't want
to come in.
I was told it would make
everyone feel uncomfortable.
So I'll just stay out here
and pretend that I don't
have to go to the bathroom.
Howard, do something.
I'm on it.
Sheldon, you being here might
not be making things better.
I see.
And is that why
everybody was invited but me?
They didn't invite
everybody but you.
Bernadette invited me,
and Stuart lives here.
Who wants hot cinnamon rolls?
So, when you hear the music,
that's your cue.
Any questions?
Oh, the package
that we paid for
said the aisle was supposed
to be strewn with rose petals.
Where are the rose petals?!
We're out!
You know what?
It's fine.
We can use the
potpourri from the bathroom!
Really, we're good.
Yup, just want
to get married.
Yeah.
Great.
I'll see you two
up there.
This is it.
I know.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Was that a yes
or no on the potpourri?!
No, thank you!
We're good!
Raj, you're probably wondering
why Amy and I aren't showing
any affection to one another.
Didn't even crack the top ten.
Well, you should know
that she recently
broke up with me.
I said I needed
time to think.
I'm sure you guys
will figure something out.
You hear that?
Raj is devastated.
Sheldon, shh.
The wedding's starting.
I see what's happening.
Sides are forming.
Well, if Bernadette's
on Amy's team, I pick Howard.
I'm not taking sides.
Fine, I guess
I'm stuck with Raj.
Really?
At least you
got picked.
Before I go any further,
have either of you
prepared your own vows?
Yes.
No.
You wrote vows?
Yeah.
Well, I don't have any.
You're kind of
making me look bad.
It's okay. I-I don't
have to say them.
No, no, no, go ahead.
I'll come up with something
mushy, you'll cry, we got this.
"Penny, we are
made of particles
"that have existed since the
moment the universe began.
"I like to think
those atoms traveled
"14 billion years through
time and space to create us,
so that we could be together
and make each other whole."
Wow.
Penny?
Right. Um... okay.
Leonard, I mean, you're not
only the love of my life.
I mean,
you're my best friend, and...
...you've got a friend in me.
You got troubles.
I got 'em, too.
There isn't anything
I wouldn't do for you.
We stick together,
and we can see it through,
'cause... you've got
a friend in me.
Is that the song
from Toy Story?
He loves that movie.
I do.
Aw, that was beautiful.
Yeah.
I mean, not like our
wedding beautiful.
No, we totally won.
Amy, I don't understand,
are we broken up or not?
It's like you can't
make up your mind.
It's because you're not
giving me any space to think.
Well, you should think fast,
because men can sire offspring
their entire lives,
but those eggs you're toting
around have a sell-by date.
You know what, Sheldon,
you've made this really easy.
You're immature, you're selfish,
you just insulted me to my face.
I don't need any more time
to think. We're broken up.
Amy...
Will someone take me home?
Yeah. Come on,
I'll give you a ride.
...symbolizes your eternal love.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
We did it!
I'm so glad
you guys could watch!
We'll say it was beautiful
in the comment section.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
No, no, no. Hang on.
I believe I'm supposed to
carry you across the threshold.
Can you?
Who do you think
carries Sheldon to bed
when he falls asleep
in front of the TV?
Okay, let's do it.
You gonna make it?
I'm okay!
Nicely done!
Thank you.
Finally, there's
a Mrs. Hofstadter
who isn't disappointed in me.
Well, the night is still young.
Everything all right?
Yeah. I guess.
Just tell me.
It's just, when we were kissing,
I couldn't help but picture
you with that other girl.
Oh, no.
No, come on.
I have a friend in you.
You said so.
You're right.
Just forget it.
Yeah.
Okay, listen. Uh...
If you're imagining that
it was sexy, it wasn't.
We-we were both drunk, and
she smelled like an ashtray.
The boat was moving a lot,
so I chipped her tooth.
Did you feel guilty?
No, she had
dental insurance.
Did you feel guilty
after kissing her?
Yes. I felt guilty as
soon as it happened.
I feel guilty
every time I see her.
What do you mean,
every time you see her?
What... do I mean?
Boy, that's a toughie.
You still see her?
Well, no, not socially.
But, you know,
just at work.
You work with her?!
How could you not tell me that?!
I wanted to tell you in the car,
but you told me to stop talking!
Oh, okay. So you're saying
this is my fault?
No, of course not.
Okay, l-look,
instead of fighting,
why don't we dim the lights,
um, get naked and make a baby?
I was trying
to lighten the mood.
It's not easy. You try it.
Hello, Mother.
Shelly! How's my baby doing?
I just wanted to let you know
that you can remove Amy
from your nightly prayers.
Unless you're open
to praying for
a beehive to fall on her head.
Oh, what's going on?
She broke up with me.
Oh, Shelly.
No, I'll be okay.
But I think that I'd like
to send the ring back to you.
Well, let's not be hasty.
Are you sure it's over for good?
It's over for me.
I'm done with women.
Like when I swore off Pop Rocks.
They both hurt you on purpose.
You want to tell me
what happened?
Are you going to say
it's all part of God's plan?
Good chance.
Then no, thank you.
Well, honey,
don't send it back yet.
Your sister's married,
and I'm not letting your brother
give my grandmother's ring
to that whore he's dating.
Wasn't Mary Magdalene
a woman of ill repute?
When your idiot brother
redeems mankind,
he can date whoever he wants.
I know it hurts now,
but it's gonna get better.
Yeah.
Everything's gonna be okay.
You've got so
much to offer.
Thank you.
Any man would be
lucky to have you.
That's true.
I just hope
I did the right thing.
I'm sure you did.
Maybe that's the problem--
you always do the right thing.
Maybe it's time to
do the wrong thing.
Like you're doing right now?
Exactly.
I asked you over and
over if you were okay.
Why would you go through with
the wedding if you weren't?
I thought I was okay,
but it turns out I'm not.
Okay, listen, I may not
have been entirely faithful,
but you,
you are not easy to lift!
Wow!
Well, marriage must agree
with you.
Well, you are just glowing.
I'm not glowing.
I'm upset.
Well, whatever it is,
it agrees with you.
Knock, knock,
knock, Penny?
Knock, knock, knock, Penny?
What's this?
Leonard told me what happened,
so I took it upon myself
to make you a hot beverage.
Oh. That's so sweet of you.
Yeah. I know.
Turns out, being sweet
isn't enough
to keep a girl these days.
I blame Madonna.
I'm sorry to hear
about you and Amy.
Well, I'm sorry
about Leonard.
Thought I raised him
better than that.
You know, it's bad enough
what happened,
but then he tried to hide
the fact that he sees her
all the time
at the university.
He does? Who is it?
Some girl named Mandy.
Mandy Chao?
Yeah.
Oh, you don't need
to worry about her.
She's brilliant and attractive.
She can do way better
than Leonard.
That's great.
Wait a minute.
I know this may
sound farfetched,
but I'm on the market now.
You know, if I dated Mandy,
that would teach both
Leonard and Amy a lesson.
That's ridiculous.
Oh, you're right.
I could never be with a woman
whose self-esteem was so low
she'd be with Leonard.
I'm with Leonard.
Yeah, I know. Forever.
Who would have believed
these things would happen to us?
Right?
I can't believe Amy
actually went through with it.
Hang on.
You knew that she was
going to end it with me?
Did you try
and stop her?
I told her to be true to herself
and do what makes her happy.
Do what makes her happy?
She plays the harp and
her car is paid for.
How much happier can she be?
Okay, look, it's not my fault
that she thought
you were a bad boyfriend.
I see.
Well...
I think I'll be going.
Sheldon...
No, no, no, no.
We are done here.
Would you mind
opening the door
and then angrily slamming it
behind me?
Sure.
Thank you.
And slam it hard,
because I am pretty steamed.
All right, Leonard,
hang in there.
Talk to you tomorrow.
What happened?
They just got married.
I don't know.
It's a mess.
They had a huge fight in Vegas.
Think they'll break up?
I don't know. Sounds pretty bad.
Penny's back in her apartment
all by herself.
Really?
Would you like to hear
another reason
why men are
better than women?
Sure, let's make it
an even hundred.
You would never kiss me
and make me say "I love you"
and then break up with me.
I wouldn't.
And you know why?
'Cause you're a man.
The champagne of genders.
Well, I may be a man,
but I think I'm the one
that screwed up on this one.
Yeah, well, and you admit it,
like a man.
All you hear
women say is,
"I'll just have a salad."
You know?
"Where's my lip gloss?"
"I think this element
should be called radium."
That last one was Madame Curie.
I figured that out.
You know what?
She was kind of an honorary man.
She had a penis made of science.
Can't believe I'm spending
my wedding night with you.
Really?
I never imagined it
any other way.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org