(birds singing,
insects trilling)
SHELDON:
It's nice to get back to nature.
Why don't I do this more often?
What a beautiful forest.
(gasps delightedly)
Hello, little butterfly.
What's your Na...
(screams)
Whatcha doing?
I was enjoying
some virtual reality,
until you ruined it
with your actual face.
What am I smelling?
Oh, it's car
air freshener.
I was simulating
the smell of the forest.
That's not what
the forest smells like.
Well, how would I know?
Why are you pretending
to be outdoors?
You hate it.
Hmm? Oh.
Amy showed me a compelling study
that demonstrated
the cognitive benefit
of spending time
in the wilderness.
Buddy, I am ready
to drive you
into the wilderness
any time you want
and leave you there.
Well, make your jokes,
but some of the participants
who spent four days in the woods
away from all technology
reported a 50% gain in reasoning
skills upon their return.
Okay, if that's true, why aren't
there more genius squirrels?
You may need this
more than I do.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 9x20 ?
The Big Bear Precipitation
Original Air Date on April 7,
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Here's your tea.
Oh!
Do not sneak up on a guy
when he's sitting on a log.
You know, if you really
want to be in nature,
why don't we rent a cabin?
Look, I'm sorry,
when did you even get here? I...
You know,
there's a cabin in Big Bear
that a doctor I work with
keeps offering me.
Because he's
hitting on you?
She.
Oh, good.
But I could get her.
We could all go
for the weekend.
It'll be fun.
Yeah... (clears throat)
Excuse me.
Here, look up "fun,"
get back to me.
You and I could still go
and have a nice weekend.
Sure.
Come on, Sheldon,
let's go with them.
I hardly think so.
You be sure and say hello
to all the mosquitoes,
bees, bears, snakes,
possums, poison oak,
oh, and last, but not least,
teenagers with guitars.
I'll see
if it's available.
You know,
if that study's real,
Leonard might come back
smarter than you.
Are you trying to manipulate me?
Yes.
Well done, it worked,
we're going.
Yay!
(bags rustling)
BERNADETTE: Come on, Raj,
give me a bag.
No, no, you're pregnant.
The only thing you carry
is our hope
for a better tomorrow.
Hey, where you been?
Uh, Raj took me
to the baby doctor
and then we swung by
the grocery store.
(tires screeching on game)
Did you get graham crackers?
I mean, are... what...
is the baby okay?
Yes and yes.
(sighs)
I didn't know you needed help
running errands today.
I didn't,
but Raj volunteered.
Really?
Yeah, ever since you told him
I was pregnant,
he's really been making
a fuss over me.
Oh. Well, I guess
that's kind of sweet.
Bernie, I just
forwarded you a list
of the top five lactation
consultants in Los Angeles.
I know my favorite,
but I'd love to hear
what you think.
And it just got weird.
Hey. Amy's downstairs.
Okay, one sec.
Uh, what-what you got
goin' on here?
I bought a baseball cap.
I can see that.
What team did you get?
Uh, Hufflepuff,
from Harry Potter.
Well, we'll be in the woods.
I'm ready to go.
Anything you'd like
to say to him?
Nice hat, Sheldon.
Thanks.
Why are you
so mean to me?
(woman screaming in pain)
(screaming continues)
What the hell are you watching?
Raj found all these
childbirth videos online.
This one is of a woman
giving birth in a river.
Okay, that is
the least Jewish thing
I've ever seen in my life.
You feel like Raj is getting
a little carried away
with all the baby stuff?
I don't think so.
He just wants to be
part of the experience.
All right, if you say so.
What's in the box?
Oh, it's an ultrasonic
microphone
so we can hear
the baby's heartbeat.
Oh.
That's cool.
Can we try it?
Actually, Raj ordered it.
He made me promise
to wait till he was here.
So he can be...
part of the experience?
Yeah.
I'm surprised he let us conceive
without him.
It's a sore spot--
don't bring it up.
It's so cute
and rustic up here.
I know.
Did you see they still have
a video rental place?
it's like Colonial Williamsburg.
Well...
cell service is down
to one bar,
so if anyone needs
medical attention
or to tell a stranger their
political views are stupid,
now's the time.
Have you ever been
off the grid before?
Once.
The battery ran out on my phone.
I had to wait
for my iPad to turn on.
I was afraid
he was gonna eat me.
Raj just pulled up.
I'm gonna say something to him.
Leave it alone.
He means well.
So you don't think he needs
to rein it in a little?
No, not really.
And you're not concerned
he's acting like somehow
this is his kid, too?
He's just trying
to be supportive.
Just supportive.
Not over-the-top in any way?
No.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hello!
You saw him carrying that.
Astronauts saw him
carrying that.
(gasps)
This place is great!
So nice of that doctor
to just let you use it.
Well, she is taking me
to an Indigo Girls concert,
so hold that thought.
Okay.
Well,
should we check
each other for ticks?
Sheldon, all we did
was walk in from the car.
Oh. Well,
suit yourself.
Who wants to check me?
On the other hand, safety first.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(rain falling loudly)
Wow, it's really
coming down.
This sucks.
And there goes our hike.
Oh, not our hike!
Now we have
to stay safe and warm.
You know, we could still go.
A little rain
isn't gonna kill us.
Have you been outside
in the rain with Sheldon?
No.
You'll wish it would kill you.
So what do we do now?
They have
some board games.
Eh, most of the Jenga
pieces are missing
and the Scrabble
only has seven tiles,
so unless you want to build
an unimpressive structure
with the word "SHNERPF"
next to it, move on.
Hey, let's light a fire.
Ooh, that sounds cozy.
I don't think
I've lit a real fire before.
Ah, it's basic thermodynamics.
I'm sure we can figure that out.
I could stack the logs conically
to facilitate airflow.
That would maximize oxygen
for optimal combustion.
(fire whooshes)
Right. So all we need is to...
Got it.
A scientist made that.
Look, Raj, you're my
best friend in the world
and I really appreciate
your enthusiasm about the baby.
Please, my pleasure.
And, of course,
Howie and I
both want you to be
a part of all this.
But we have to set
some boundaries.
I don't understand.
The three of us
aren't having this baby.
Just the two of us.
Oh...
Okay. Yeah, I get it.
I'll back off.
Thanks for understanding.
Of course.
I'll give you guys some space.
Let me just get this
out of your way.
You need some help?
No, I got it.
(clattering)
(grunts)
Raj... Raj, wait.
Please, Bernadette.
Let me leave with my dignity.
(thumps)
Hey, you guys want
to play a drinking game?
Oh, well now, well now,
we'll never win.
You always play
the drinking game.
Not the drinking game,
a drinking game.
To be fair, good at both.
What's the game?
All right, it's called
Never Have I Ever.
The rules are simple.
Someone says something
they've never done,
but if you have done it,
you take a drink.
I've never played that before.
(stammers)
Hey, now, wait.
Have we started?
Do I drink?
What is happening?
Okay.
Calm down.
I'll go first.
All right, let's see.
Never have I ever...
She's trying
to think of something
she's never done before.
This could take a while.
Very funny.
Okay, never have I ever...
Yeah, you know what?
Let's just circle back.
Okay, I'll go.
Never have I ever been arrested.
So I drink.
No, it's only
if you've done it.
Got it.
I can't believe
you've been arrested.
I can't believe Penny hasn't.
Sheldon, what did you do?
Well, I'm not proud of it,
but... I jaywalked.
Oh, no, it's like
a horror movie.
We're trapped in a cabin
with a maniac.
I'm surprised
you would do that.
No, I crossed
in the middle of the street.
And normally, I wouldn't,
but I saw an aggressive-looking
Girl Scout,
and it was the heart
of cookie season.
Anyway, there was
a police officer,
and he witnessed
the whole thing.
What-- he arrested you for that?
(stammers)
No, he didn't do anything.
So I said,
"You just saw me jaywalk.
Why aren't you
doing your job?"
You know?
"M-Maybe I should arrest you
for-for impersonating
a police officer."
And then you got arrested.
Oh, and how.
I feel like I just made
a horrible mistake.
Yeah.
But on the other hand,
I didn't kick him
out of our lives.
I just asked him
to back off a little.
Yeah.
What? Are you gonna cry?
(crying):
Yeah!
Is it baby hormones
or actually sad?
I can't tell anymore!
I'll go get him.
And bring back the bear!
This game's dangerous.
I could get you in trouble.
How?
Well, never have I ever
used Sheldon's toothbrush
to clean the sink.
Fine, is that
how you want to play this?
All right,
never have I ever come up
with a nickname
for my own genitals.
Never should've told you
about Alvin and the Chipmunks.
AMY:
Okay.
My turn.
Um...
Never have I ever
completely rocked
my girlfriend's world in bed.
(stammers)
Amy...
You know the rules.
Drink.
(clears throat)
Yeah, go ahead.
That's right.
All right, my turn.
Mm...
Oh, I know.
Never have I ever
kept a secret bank account,
because I think
my wife can't handle money.
Did I win?
I feel like I won.
I can't believe this.
You realize I make
more money than you?
I don't, I know,
but this isn't a big deal.
It's just a little savings
I put aside.
We're married.
We're supposed
to share everything.
What-- you mean, like,
your massive credit card debt?
(door slams)
I'm calling it.
I won.
I appreciate the apology,
but it's really not necessary.
I overstepped my bounds.
No, Raj, you've been great.
I just, I need to start
doing my part around here.
BERNADETTE:
I hear that.
Well, if that's the case,
is there anything
I can do to help?
Well, not right now.
But we could try out
that microphone you got us,
and listen to
the baby's heartbeat.
Really?
It's okay if I listen with you?!
Of course.
Can I squirt the ultrasound
jelly on your stomach?
Hey, look at that.
It's weird again.
(door opens)
Okay, you have
every right to be mad.
And what you said is true.
You do make more money than me.
So I had no right
to do what I did.
And I'm so sorry.
I hope you can forgive me.
How long have you had
this secret account?
A couple years,
but I just put a few bucks aside
every month for emergencies.
Well, how much you got in there?
$6,427.
$47 once my nana's
birthday check gets here.
My God, Leonard,
do you know
what I could do
with that kind of money?
No, I do,
and that's why I hid it.
What good is it
if you don't use it?
Uh, uh, you have shoes
you love, but never wear.
I have money I love,
but never spend.
We're kind of
a cute couple that way.
Again,
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
kept it a secret.
Well, I have a secret
I've been keeping from you, too.
Is it a secret bank account?
Because that would be awesome.
I hate my job.
Really?
Why?
Because I don't feel good
flirting with doctors for sales.
I mean, I know
I make a lot of money.
But I haven't been happy
for a while.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I know
how important it is to you
that I'm having some success.
That's not true.
Okay, really?
So you'd be fine if I went
back to acting
and waiting tables again?
If that's what you
want to do, yes.
Well, it's not
what I want to do.
Oh, yes.
Doesn't matter what I want.
Look, this job is
gonna get me out of debt.
So I'm gonna do the grown-up
thing and see it through.
Well, that is
the grown-up thing.
I guess.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You know,
never have I ever made love
in the forest
while it was raining.
Well, guess I gotta drink.
All right, here we go.
(microphone droning)
I'm not hearing anything.
Well, give me a second.
Are you sure you can do this?
Hey, who found
four dollars and change
on the beach
with his metal detector?
I buried it there,
so we could go home.
(heartbeat echoing, gasps)
Wait, that's it.
Wow.
Isn't that the best?
You guys made a person.
We did.
And I like to think
I helped.
(whispering):
You didn't.
SHELDON:
Oh, let me see.
Oh, um, never have I ever
drunk milk past
its expiration date.
Never have I ever
cancelled
a dentist appointment.
Oh, uh, never have I ever
put my foot in the ocean.
Never have I ever
honked if I liked anything.
Oh!
Uh... never have I ever
thrown, caught or touched
a Frisbee.
Never have I ever
put salt on my food
without trying it first.
Yeah...
Oh!
Never have I ever
pushed all the buttons
in an elevator.
(gasps)
Well, we all have a past.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org