Previously on Dexter.
- Oh, that's pretty.
- Gift from my first husband.
What'll it be, ladies?
How 'bout a foot massage
with those big, gorgeous hands of yours?
- They're kinda cold from scooping ice.
- But you're hot.
Miguel went missing last night.
Ellen's missing this morning.
I hope she didn't get
in an accident or something.
He did it. Miguel really did it.
Ellen.
You don't wanna have to think
about what she went through
to realize that she's really gone.
- Don't. Don't.
- Pero, coraz??n, she's gone.
You got me. I'm right here for you.
To get you through.
He's having an affair.
No. You don't know that.
When you've been married as long as we
have, you know when your husband's lying.
Anton is not officially a CI.
We used him as bait.
The Skinner has Anton.
Freebo owes you money?
I can get you money.
I loaned Freebo that money.
This is about respect.
Anton!
Morgan, get outta the way!
You found me.
You can't get away from me that easily.
Anton could so easily file a huge lawsuit
against the police department
once he finds out
how you fucked him over!
You don't know what the fuck
you're talkin' about!
You're the one I wanna spend time with.
My God... it's perfect.
You should just...
get out while you can.
I won't. I promise.
I gave you my shirt
linking me to Freebo's death.
I wish I had another one to prove to you
how important this partnership is to me.
The link between
Freebo's murder and Miguel.
It's not even human.
It's cow's blood. He's been using me.
I didn't create a monster.
I was used by one.
He used me.
How many was it, seven or eight balls?
I lost count.
Putting the 18th tee
in front of a body of water is criminal.
I kept on telling him, "Take the mulligan!
Please, take the mullig... "
This one right here, no.
- I finally got one over, didn't I?
- Yeah.
Just what I ordered - feigned
civility with a heaping side of betrayal.
It's becoming more and more clear
that I'm going to have to deal with Miguel.
Thank you, Chef.
Ah, Chef Babia.
Option one, I kill him.
But he's too high profile.
A popular ADA disappears.
The manhunt would be endless.
Everyone he knew would be scrutinized,
and that includes me.
He's also my best man.
I'd be expected to grieve.
How about this pumpkin
and sage ravioli here?
- Oh, no, that's...
- There you go.
Option two, get him
the hell out of my life.
But it's not that simple. He taught me
how to golf. I taught him how to kill.
I'm responsible if Miguel
takes another innocent life.
Tell them, Miguel. I can't wait.
Tell us?
We got a wedding present for you.
Chef Babia and his staff,
they're gonna cater your wedding.
Uh, wh...?
We wanted you to have the very best.
- It's too much. Really.
- I won't take no for an answer.
You might have to.
We're doing this for you. I insist.
So much for option two.
He won't just let our partnership dissolve.
He's trying to get me under his thumb,
and he's using Rita to do it.
No...
You are the very best man.
It's working.
OK, so, a toast.
To Dexter and Rita.
May your marriage
be as blessed
as we are to have you
to call friends.
Which leaves option three.
Get him under my thumb...
and keep him there.
God, we're barely moving.
So much for getting Astor home
in time for her bath.
At least the meal was worth it.
And it was great to see Sylvia and Miguel
getting along again.
Do we... have to serve food
at the wedding?
Yes. We have to serve food
at the wedding.
It's just if we can't afford Chef...
what's-his-name on our own,
maybe we shouldn't accept.
We can't say no now.
I mean, it would be insulting.
Believe me, Miguel's ego can handle it.
What's going on, Dexter?
It's just...
Miguel isn't exactly
who I thought he was.
You two seemed to be
getting along fine at dinner.
Yeah.
Wait a minute. Is this about Sylvia?
I mean, did you find something out?
More than I wanted to.
Oh, my God.
He's cheating on her.
- No, that's not what I...
- Oh, that bastard!
He looked me right in the eye
and said he wasn't having an affair.
Oh, God... poor Syl.
How long has it been going on?
Should I tell her?
What would I say?
I think we should just... stay out of it.
- Is it his secretary?
- It's not his secretary!
Could we please just drop this?
- But there is someone.
- I never said that.
All right, Syl said that Miguel's been
spending a lot of time with Maria LaGuerta,
which makes Syl uncomfortable
because they have history.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
Then that's who it is.
They're spending time together
because of a case.
Miguel's brother did die.
Which rekindled the relationship.
That's why you won't say anything.
You're protecting your boss.
Deb. Glad to see ya.
Fight?
His best friend is cheating on my best friend
and he won't tell me with who.
You have a best friend?
What'd you use on her, chloroform?
- I hope she was good.
- Aw, she was a champ.
She almost made it through Saw 1 and 2.
I'm kidding.
She was great. We bonded.
Hey.
Oh. Oh, you...
you have company.
Yeah. Um... this is Anton.
Anton Briggs,
the Skinner victim?
Just Anton.
And yes, the Skinner victim.
Uh, you know, your sister...
she saved my life.
Does this mean you're plus one
for the wedding?
Uh, we haven't really...
talked about...
Um, so, you're getting married.
Oh, kudos.
- Thanks.
- And a baby on the way.
I was hoping to walk down the aisle skinny,
or at least skinnier.
What?
Asshole.
Cocksuck!
Motherfuck!
Anton, wake up. You gotta go.
Fuckin' penguins!
It's just 7:30. I thought
you didn't have to be at work...
Your protective detail's gonna think
that you spent the night!
- I did.
- They're gonna think that we slept together!
- We have, Deb.
- Oh, God! Oh, God!
I know, but if they tell my bosses,
I'm gonna get in a shitload of shit!
Really? For sleeping with your boyfriend?
You are a key witness
in a case I'm investigating.
So if that comes out in trial, King's lawyers
are gonna have a fucking field day,
when we catch him.
So, um, are you sure
that's what this is really about?
Uh-huh.
Um... I gotta get in the shower,
so I'll call you later, OK?
Yeah. OK.
Revisiting option three,
getting Miguel under my thumb.
I need leverage.
Exposing Ellen's body
was supposed to achieve that.
But Miguel wrestled it away.
We have a suspect
for Ellen Wolf's murder.
Is she onto Miguel,
and do I smell leverage?
Toby Edwards, 32.
Oh, well.
Ellen's incoming phone records
show that he called her house three times
on the night of her murder - once at
11:10pm from the bar where he works,
and then twice more at 3:01 and 3:08am
from right outside her house.
She hasn't found the killer,
but she might have found a witness.
And I found my leverage.
Soderquist, vamos. Get an address
on this guy. Haul his ass in.
We're also getting a search warrant.
We're looking for a platinum wedding ring.
I've already catalogued
one wedding ring into evidence.
Well, she wore two.
One for each ex-husband.
Well, why would the killer
only take one ring?
Maybe he got interrupted.
Or he wanted a trophy.
Whatever it is,
we're gonna find out.
A potential witness, a missing ring.
Now Miguel and I have
something to talk about.
Hey, not so fast.
Not so fast.
I am taking donations
for Dexter Morgan's...
bachelor party.
Produced and directed by Vince Masuka,
a Vince Masuka production.
Dig deep now.
It's gonna be off the charts.
I'm gonna have Sergeant Cop-a-Feel,
Jo-Jo the Lezbo Go-Go,
Maureen the Limber Mermaid,
and her even more limber friend
Nadia the Russian gymnast.
What?
Vince, we're in the middle
of two big investigations.
Tell me about it. It's hard
to get people focused on this shindig.
What I mean is that maybe you
should keep the party low-key.
Are you kidding?
I've got a reputation to live up to.
I mean, if my show
does not make people vomit
and have an erection at the same time,
then I've let my audience down.
Strippers, yes. Hookers, no.
And none of that weird shit that you're into.
- Wow. OK, Sergeant Buzzkill.
- I mean it.
Anything illegal, I will arrest you.
Come on. I was just joking.
The party's for Opie out there.
A hooker is a terrible thing to waste.
Damn it.
I'm never gonna get my deposit back.
Yes, ma'am, your landscaper.
When was the last time you saw him?
OK. Do you have any empty structures
on your property
or unoccupied vacation homes
in the area?
Right, ma'am, we'll be sure to clear 'em
as fast as we can
so you don't have to re-sod your lawn,
you fuckhead.
What's this?
Surveillance report
from Anton's protective detail.
Very thorough.
He came over on official business.
Which took all night.
Sarge is gonna see that.
I'll tell him the truth,
that nothing happened.
So you're no longer
sleeping with the...
key witness in this investigation?
What's it to you?
You're right. It's your shield.
If you want people talkin',
be my guest.
You've run out of people
to transfer me to?
Your embassy isn't that big.
?yeme...
George Washington King.
No, no, no, do not transfer me back.
Esc??chame...
Homicide.
Sarge, line two. Says it's urgent.
Sergeant Batista.
I'll be right there.
- Cover for me.
- Is everything OK?
No.
It's all about strategy,
outmaneuvering the opposition,
bending him to your will.
What are you doing in my office, Dex?
Winning.
Hope you don't mind. Just keeping
my wits sharp while I waited for you.
You, uh, here to grab...
lunch or something?
Can't. Gotta get back to the station.
The Ellen Wolf case is breaking.
Breaking.
Which way?
It seems Lieutenant LaGuerta
has a suspect.
And who might that be?
Some guy who was...
outside Ellen's place round about the time
she was gettin' strangled.
Or was she stabbed first?
I can't remember.
He couldn't have seen anything.
You sure?
All right.
So what do we do?
We?
Huh.
We are partners.
Yeah, but see,
here's the thing, Miguel.
I don't really want a partner.
Hey, I'm not giving up
on our friendship, Dex.
Hell, I'm standing up at your wedding.
Yeah. But after that,
you go your own way.
And we both go back
to who we were before all of this -
you an honorable ADA
dedicated to upholding the law of the land...
- And you?
- A trusty spatter analyst
who always gets his killer.
In exchange for what?
I'm in a position to protect
the ADA's interests in this case.
I'll do what it takes to keep
the innocent people of Miami safe.
And that's what you want?
That's what I want.
Game over.
- Barbara Gianna?
- In there.
- What do we know?
- Not much.
The meds for the pain have her pretty blurry.
Hey, you that, uh, homicide guy
she keeps talkin' about?
- She talks about me?
- She says you snore like a motherfucker.
- Hey.
- Hey, yourself.
How you doing?
I feel like I got a Buick
parked on my head.
Wasn't raped...
if that's what you were thinking.
I just got beat on a little.
By who? Any ideas?
Mm, best I can tell...
some would-be john
saw me on the stroll.
Asshole followed me home.
So you got a look at him.
Mm-hm.
Tall, blond, good-looking.
Mm.
Strong.
My weapon was in my purse.
All I had were my keys.
Got my licks in.
He'll be a little...
less handsome tomorrow.
You did good.
- I'm glad you're here.
- Hell, yeah, I'm here.
You're not gonna go through this alone.
And, uh, just for the record...
I don't snore like a motherfucker.
Excuse me... we need to get
Detective Gianna upstairs for a cat scan,
- see if we can release her.
- Release her?
- I'm not that bad, Angel.
- Of course you're not.
I'll talk to you later, OK?
Detective Gianna thinks she got
a piece of the assailant with these.
You're looking for a blond guy, tall.
Could be a john.
Maybe one of your other decoys
might have seen him.
We're all over this. Thanks, Sergeant.
Get this down to the lab fast.
Angel.
What can I do you for?
I, uh, need you to test this for blood.
If it comes back positive,
run it through the criminal database.
No prob.
Might take a day or two for sequencing.
Uh, grease it.
I mean, it's... it's a priority.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Is this Ellen Wolf or the Skinner?
There's no case number.
Uh, it's...
It's more of... an internal thing.
You know? My eyes only.
Your eyes only.
Thanks.
I'm not hiding anything. I swear.
You were coming on to Ellen. I was there.
She came on to me. I flirted back.
It's part of the job, you know?
How you earn tips.
She left me 20 on a $30 tab.
You figured there was more
where that came from.
You called her again at 11:10pm,
then at 3:01 and 3:08am. That's pretty
late to be calling someone you just met.
I called on my break.
I told her I didn't get off work till after two.
She said to come over anyway.
And then I called again to tell her I wasn't
going to make it. She didn't answer.
I called one more time just in case.
No one picked up.
For someone so innocent,
he sure looks guilty.
Looks like a killer to me.
- He's not.
- Well, but he could be.
You wanna know
what I think happened?
I think that you showed up at her house
unannounced, looking for sex.
She wouldn't give it up,
you lost your temper.
That's not what happened.
Then you called twice to make it look like
you thought she was still alive.
That's crazy. You're not listening to me.
Any priors?
You seem to have a problem
with the word "innocent".
No one's getting framed for this.
- Hey, your ball game.
- Why are you here?
Curiosity.
You can't blame me, can you?
- So you didn't go over to her house?
- No. I went home.
You're fucking lying, Toby.
These two calls were routed through
a cell phone tower a block from her house.
- You were there!
- All right!
I have a fianc?©e...
...who's not gonna like
hearing about a booty call.
So you went there.
She changed her mind.
- You got angry...
- No. No!
I mean, yes, I went to her place,
but she didn't answer the door.
So I called - twice.
I figured she fell asleep.
I went home. I swear to God.
- Not much of a suspect.
- Not much of a witness.
Lieutenant, do you have a second?
Hmm. New development.
Never know what'll pop up.
Well... I'll know.
I'll keep you posted, as promised.
You're a good friend to have.
I'm just gonna stay here.
My curiosity's piqued.
He's lying through his teeth.
We can put him at the scene.
He's, uh, not our guy.
The fuck he's not.
Four people put him at the bar all night long.
And there's security camera footage of him
closing out when the vic went down.
The vic's name is Ellen,
and he was there. He's our guy.
The time code on the tape checks out.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant.
You were there
at three in the morning.
Did you see anyone else on the street?
- No. It was dead.
- No unusual activity?
There was some douchebag
with his high beams on.
- Blinding me.
- So someone was on the street.
He was coming the other direction
when I pulled up.
Actually, it wasn't high beams.
It was those big-ass halogens.
What kind of car?
SUV.
Dark. Blue.
Black. I-I-I don't know!
Something like that.
I am indeed a good friend to have.
And one can never have
too many friends, right?
My friend Miguel
isn't giving up without a fight.
He'll do whatever's necessary
to regain the upper hand.
If he controls LaGuerta,
he controls the investigation,
and my leverage disappears.
But she's a tough sell.
He won't get far.
I hope.
Ta-da!
You...
are so... beautiful!
Oh...
All right.
Now, you come over here
and admire yourself
while Nina checks the fit.
I feel like Cinderella.
Except for the whole
Disney virgin thing.
Oh, don't worry.
No one'll know Prince Charming
knocked ya up before the ball.
Hey, Syl, are you OK?
Yeah. I was just remembering
my wedding day.
I was never happier.
- It's supposed to get even better over time.
- Sweetie, your marriage will, I'm sure of it.
Things still aren't great with Miguel?
Well, we're working on it.
At least I am.
- And what's he doing?
- I wish I knew.
Do you? Really?
What the hell are you doing in here?
Forensics.
On which case?
The new bean-counter
is questioning this lab request.
- What is this key that you're testing?
- It's, uh... It's for an investigation.
Then put an active case number on it, OK?
With all these budget cuts,
they're flagging everything and coming
straight to me with all this bullshit
which I really don't need right now,
Dexter, OK? I don't need it.
OK. I'll straighten it out.
I'm sorry. I just...
No. I'll take care of it.
She's ripe for the picking,
and Miguel knows it.
He'll use her to protect himself.
And there goes my leverage.
Better keep an eye on her.
No, no, no, no. You can't cancel.
The party's in two days.
You're sorry?
Well, you can take your sorry
and shove it up your ass!
Fuck!
The erotic clowns just cancelled.
Why is this wedding happening to me?
Bro, let me help you out.
I've been the best man
at more weddings than I can count.
Never a groom, thank Christ,
but I've planned a ton of these.
Platinum Enterprises?
It's a full-service operation,
party boat, food, alcohol.
One phone call, and you're done.
Ask for Tammy.
God bless you, Joseph Quinn.
Hey. He lives.
- Hey, man.
- Good to see you up and moving, man.
Thanks, thanks.
Um... Morgan, she here?
Uh, no, she's out.
Running down a file
on the bastard who did this to you.
- We're gonna find him, Anton, I swear.
- Yeah, I know.
Hey, I just wanted to say,
I never meant for any of this to go down
the way it did, you know?
You didn't sign up for this.
Listen, I was the idiot who got busted in
the first place, right? So... it's kind of on me.
Yeah, but it was me thinking I was doing
you a favor keeping you off the books.
I should have told you
you were free and clear. I messed up.
I wanted to apologize to your face.
Deb told me that was a clerical error.
- So that was you?
- Yeah. I assumed she told you.
You lying son of a bitch!
You almost got me killed!
Shit!
- It's all right. Let him go.
- What the hell is this?
Ramos, let him go. Let him go!
This shit ain't over, man.
Anton...
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Anton, stop.
Goddamn it, will you just stop?
His punk ass deserved it!
You can't just walk into a police station
and punch a cop!
Here you are standin' up for him.
- I am not the enemy here.
- Debra, you lied to me!
Clerical error, my ass.
Quinn kept me as his CI bitch
when I could have walked away at any time.
You're right, I lied.
But telling you wasn't
gonna change what he did.
I almost died because of that prick.
Without that prick,
we wouldn't have found you.
You'll be lucky if he doesn't press charges.
What? Let him!
I'll sue this whole fucking department!
Don't talk like that.
I'll talk to Quinn.
Really?
Sure you're not afraid he might find out
we're sleeping together
- and tell everyone?
- He already knows.
And he hasn't told anyone.
Where the hell did that come from?
From your brother's surprised face
when he met me, Debra.
From your boot on my butt
- kickin' me out the door this morning.
- Are you serious?
I am this close to getting my shield,
and I'm putting it all at risk to be with you!
Then, Debra, why are you?
You feel guilty?
You feel responsible
for what happened to me?
Shit. You're bleeding.
You're gonna need new stitches.
Debra, I tell you what I'm gonna need.
I need for you to seriously
think about this.
Think about us.
No, no, para m?­, no.
I think I've had enough.
Wine...
invented for the sole purpose
of handling grief.
Hmm?
Believe me, I know.
When Oscar died,
I drowned my share of sorrow.
I know how you feel.
You miss her.
Just... Just...
Last Thursday,
I was having drinks with her.
And then the next day,
I'm staring down at her dead body.
If you're gonna end up in a grave,
it should at least be your own.
And so the only thing you got to go on
right now is that SUV, huh?
We're checking every
intersection surveillance camera
from Ellen's place to the cemetery.
Good. Good.
Thorough.
See, she's lucky to have you
watchin' out for her.
It's just like you watched out for me
with Oscar's case.
Some good that did.
Hey, Maria, come on.
You helped me.
You've always been important to me.
You know that.
You remember that weekend
when we took Oscar with us to the Keys?
I kept telling him,
"I am not sharing...
"the hottest girl in Florida
with my baby brother. "
And then you talked me
into letting him come.
He was so cute.
- Those skinny little legs.
- Mm-hm.
Up until that weekend, he was always
my annoying kid brother, you know?
Always in the way.
And then when
he was taken from me,
I kept on thinking back
to that weekend... you know?
Cause that's the way
I wanna remember him, like you said.
You know,
before all the drugs
and all the run-ins
with the cops and all that.
That little boy
with the skinny legs, my brother.
Sorry.
I wouldn't have had that memory
if it wasn't for you.
Seriously.
Thank you.
Gracias.
I miss that.
Oh, man, I don't know
what came over me.
It's OK. It's OK.
Hey, Lieutenant, I am sorry
to show up unannounced.
I know it's late, but I feel so bad
about that case number screw-up,
and I just wanted to...
Miguel.
- I'm interrupting.
- No, we're just, um...
- Casework.
- Talking casework.
If this was so urgent, Dexter,
you could have called me.
I know, I'm sorry. It's just...
I feel bad,
and this is too important.
The key I tested came from a colleague
in Monroe County.
His department
doesn't have our resources,
and I did him a favor. I'm sorry.
I know how you value the truth.
Look, don't worry about it.
Just let me know next time.
OK.
And call first.
Again, I'm... sorry to interrupt.
I couldn't let LaGuerta become
Miguel's collateral damage.
I need to keep his focus on me.
After tonight, I have his full attention.
Hey, there.
Please don't hate me,
but I may have done a bad thing.
Do I need to sit down?
I told Sylvia about Miguel and LaGuerta.
I'm gonna sit down.
I was trying on my dress.
We were talking about the wedding.
She seemed so sad.
I mean, I had to say something, didn't I?
- I suppose you did.
- So she called Miguel's office,
and his assistant said that he was
meeting with Lieutenant LaGuerta,
but then Syl checked with your precinct,
and neither of them is there.
So... she thinks Miguel
is at LaGuerta's?
What do you think she's gonna do?
- I'll call you tomorrow, hmm?
- About the case?
Sure. At the office.
Maria...
You fucker!
- You are too good a liar, Miguel.
- Syl, what are you doing here?
I don't know when you're telling the truth
any more.
You say you're at work. I believe you.
You say you're not having an affair.
I believe you.
Syl, nothing happened here, OK?
- I swear to you.
- You swore to me last Thursday...
when you were out all night.
You swore to me
you weren't with another woman.
But now I think you were here.
- Wait. Last Thursday, he was not...
- You...
You'll probably be a lot better
at seeing through his bullshit than I was,
being a detective and all.
- Good luck.
- Syl, come on, ven.
Don't touch me. I'm done!
- Syl.
- Get out of my life!
She... She's got it all wrong.
I'll straighten it out. All right?
- Hey, Francisco!
- What'll it be today, Mr. Morgan?
Olvidate, que ese pide lo de siempre.
I said you'd take the usual.
You're a creature...
of habit.
Come on, take a seat.
While you wait.
Kind of a bitch move there, man.
Sending my wife over to Maria's.
Surprisingly, it wasn't me.
Sure.
You wouldn't play games
with a man's family,
or, uh...
cause pain to an innocent woman.
Neither would I. That's why I wanted
to give you a heads up
that my office is talking about doing
a little ethics probe on your sister.
Cops don't come any cleaner than Deb.
Yeah, huh?
Like, uh, sleeping with a CI?
Cause it's all here in this surveillance report
for... what's-his-name, I got it right here.
Anton Briggs.
Now, mi'jito,
this don't look so good.
Pero...
I'm gonna keep a close eye on it...
just like you're gonna keep a close eye
on Ellen's case for me.
And any other favor I might have.
The usual, Mr. Morgan.
Here.
It's a copy.
Cause after all...
familia is sacred.
Right?
He has no idea
what door he just opened.
Mr. Dexter.
Hey, Norma.
The Prados, they're not home.
That's what I was hoping.
Did you know that Miguel
is gonna be best man for my wedding?
Yeah. I heard him talking about it
with Mrs. Sylvia.
Well, the groom is supposed
to buy his best man a gift.
And I know how much Miguel
loves Garcia M??rquez,
so I thought I'd pick up
a limited edition of one of his books.
Oh, he would like that very much.
Do you think it'd be all right
if I looked in Miguel's den
just to see what he already has?
Our secret.
OK.
Come in.
I'll be out in a jiffy.
OK.
Miguel stepped over a line,
and he'll keep stepping
until I have something he can't top,
something that could put him in jail,
if and when I want him there.
That's the only way he'll back off.
I know Miguel killed Ellen Wolf.
And I know he took
one of her rings as a trophy.
The question is, where did he hide it?
Somewhere no one else
would ever look.
Unless...
Unless they're me.
No more games.
Hi. Are you Vince?
Yeah.
I'm Tammy Okama.
Platinum Enterprises.
- May I sit?
- Yeah, sure.
- You're Tammy?
- Mm-hm.
I was expecting someone...
- Trashy?
- Yeah.
That's sweet.
So! We are planning a bachelor party.
Yeah, but, uh, keep it down,
because party boy's in the next room.
Oh! Well...
we have any number of themes
you can choose from.
Well, uh... what's your favorite?
Mm. I'd stick with a nautical theme.
- Riverboat casino, pirates in petticoats.
- Nautical's good.
Mm-hm. You have such nice eyes, Vince.
Hey, Dex, I got your message.
Did you get a DNA match on that key?
Uh, seems so.
Thank you.
I mean it.
So where's the report?
If Angel wants to kill this guy,
that's his business.
I'm done getting involved with friends.
I heard LaGuerta gave you shit for this.
It's all right.
But I knew that I can trust you.
Don't get involved.
I heard about Detective Gianna.
How is she?
What are you doing?
OK. No concussion.
Dex, the... the file.
Yep.
I know how hard it must have been
to see her like that.
I know what it is to...
want to rebalance an unbalanced world.
But it's just...
unbalanced, Angel, and that's it.
OK.
- OK.
- Some doors should stay shut.
You open it, it's too easy
to walk through it a second time.
I've seen it before. Recently, even.
I'll keep it in mind.
Thanks, Dex.
Well, at least I didn't teach him
how to get away with murder. I'm learning.
Thought you said you'd be gone
by the time I got back.
I'm just getting some work stuff here.
Just make sure you get everything.
I don't want you using it
as an excuse to come back.
Syl, look, I...
Jeez.
Damn it!
Please, sir,
this stain just wouldn't come out.
You know, once blood sets,
it's really hard to get out, so no charge.
Devon Parks?
Hey, Deb,
I wanted to talk to you
about the thing you got going with your CI.
Well, he's not a CI.
And we don't have anything going,
not anymore.
Well, that settles that.
Only a retard would have gotten involved
with Anton in the first place.
I don't know.
He seemed like a nice enough guy.
You seemed to like him.
When he went missing, all I could think was,
"Please, God, don't let him be dead. "
And then I get him back,
and all I can think is...
how wrong he is for me.
You know, like...
how bad it makes me look.
Doesn't matter that he makes me happy
or he makes me feel how you're supposed
to feel when you're with the right person.
Is that crazy?
I got nothin'.
God.
You are useless.
Love you anyway.
- Think this is funny?
- Not at all.
- They said that stain would come out!
- Fuck you!
I didn't get to where I am, who I am,
by letting some little gusano like you
walk all over me! Where's my ring?
It's not your ring. It's Ellen's.
Though you did leave
a nice, clean print on it.
Oh, there's plenty of blood
on your hands too!
Ethan Turner, Clemson Galt.
All deserving,
with nothing to tie me to their deaths
and no bodies to prove
that they're even dead.
Maybe in a court of law.
But how's that little bride of yours gonna feel
when she has to start
answering some questions?
Cause she's gotta wonder where you go,
what you do, who you really are.
She knows everything she needs to,
and it's gonna stay that way
or that ring might show up
someplace very inconvenient.
I am the last person you wanna fuck with,
because I will fuck you back
in ways you never even imagined!
An anonymous tip,
couple of search warrants. Hmm?
Who knows what the police might find in
your apartment or in that little boat of yours.
You got the ring!
I got City fucking Hall!
Wow. I didn't get it before, Miguel,
but you can't be reasoned with,
guilted, controlled.
This whole back-and-forth game
for leverage is pointless.
That's right!
I'll do what I want, when I want,
to whomever I want!
Count on it!
I will.
Thank you.
Harry was right.
He's always been right.
There are the innocent,
and there are the deserving.
Have Barbara Gianna ID this guy.
Some doors should stay closed.
Some people can understand that.
Harry also said it's all about choices.
Good and bad.
My search for connection
always ends in blood.
You get a good look at him?
Yes. How do I know
this is not a trap?
Oye. If I wanted you in jail,
I wouldn't have let you loose
in the first place, OK?
And you believe this man
knows where Freebo is?
He's the only one who does.
His name?
Dexter Morgan.
You want Freebo,
you want your money...
then you need to have
a long conversation with him.
Even Harry would agree
Miguel has left me no other choice.
As challenging as it will be,
it's back to option one.
I kill him.