Previously on Dexter...
I found a fucking lead
on the Skinner case.
The Skinner is using tree-trimming
as a cover for surveillance.
He watches from the trees,
and when the time is right, he grabs them.
Mr. King. We met at the scene of
our second victim, is that correct?
Yes, that is correct.
Mario Astorga?
I don't know anything.
Then why would George King
suggest otherwise?
What are you so afraid of, Mario?
This is the shirt I was wearing
when Freebo met his end.
That's his blood right there.
This shirt implicates me
in his death.
I trust you, and I want you to trust me.
But he's being secretive.
He's never home. He says he's with Dexter.
But I think it's a cover.
Freebo's final resting place.
Hiding a body in a cemetery.
You're fucking brilliant.
We need to go
after the root cause,
his bloodsucking, soulless
defense attorney, Ellen Wolf!
- We can't kill her.
- I see.
- This is personal.
- Fuck, yes, this is personal.
I'm asking you to do this
for me as my friend.
- I'm sorry. No.
- Well, then, fuck you!
Someone loaned Freebo some money
and is willing to skin people to get it back.
We're gonna spread the word
that Anton knows where Freebo is.
Which means that the Skinner
will be looking for me.
What are you hiding?
Anton is not officially a CI.
We used him as bait.
What, are you in love with the guy?
Anton, you in there?
Shit. Trimmed trees.
The Skinner's been here.
I'm ready to get my hands dirty.
I've always done the deed alone.
Never stood outside,
been a witness to this moment.
You've set something
in motion here.
Everything Miguel does from now on
is connected to you.
Today I wake up,
kiss the wife-to-be...
...feed the stepkids-to-be...
...dress myself
in the usual pants, shirt...
...and pretence.
But last night, it was no pretence.
Miguel and I took a life.
Together. And today,
someone knows my truth,
shares my reality.
I'm not alone.
Sylvia, good morning.
Sorry for coming over so early.
- It's OK.
- But...
I need to see your face
when I ask you.
Ask me?
Syl, what is it?
Miguel was out till all hours
last night.
He says he was with you.
Is that true?
Absolutely. We were...
just hanging.
- Being guys. You know.
- Miguel was telling the truth.
You see, there's nothing to worry about.
Dexter didn't get here till late.
- It was...
- It had to be almost midnight.
Miguel got home an hour ago.
Oh.
He's having an affair.
Oh, no. No, no.
You don't know that.
When you've been married
as long as we have,
you know when your husband's lying.
Something to look forward to.
Maybe Dexter knows
where he went.
I really don't.
But he did talk about a case
he needed to look over.
At the office.
This really isn't your problem.
I should go.
No. No, no, no.
You stay here for as long
as you need to, OK?
I'll just... leave.
Work.
With a detour on the way.
Dex.
Dex, man.
How you doing? You OK?
- I'm good.
- Me too.
It's like there was
an imbalance in the world,
and we righted it,
with our own hands.
- It was deserving.
- I don't know. I feel real.
Like, maybe for the first time in my life.
I know what you mean.
But if we're thinking
about continuing
- these extracurricular activities...
- Absolutely.
...you need to work on your alibis.
Syl stopped by this morning,
wondering where you'd been.
Ah, shit.
Co?o. I'm a moron.
I tried to cover for you,
but I thought you went home.
I'm sorry, man.
I went over to Jack's Hideaway
over on 57th. I was, like, so wired.
The next thing I know,
the sun was coming up.
Jack's Hideaway.
Don't worry about Syl.
I can handle that.
I got a motion hearing this morning, though,
I don't wanna miss.
I'll get better at this. With your help.
I stalked a wife-killer
at Jack's Hideaway last year,
grabbed him right at closing...
at 2am.
Sylvia said Miguel got home
an hour ago.
Did he just lie? To me?
Another detour.
- There's nothing here either.
- Well, what about the blinds?
- What about the glass?
- Checked them. Deb, there's no blood.
Anton didn't just follow
the Skinner out of here.
I'll keep looking.
- I think we need to recanvass.
- We've talked to everyone in the building.
What about the kids?
They're awake now.
- We'll talk to the kids.
- What do we got?
The Skinner has Anton.
Did you see the trees?
I saw them.
It doesn't mean he got nabbed.
The coffee pot was left burning.
I mean, he definitely left in a hurry.
What the hell was Anton doing
back in town?
He never left. He contacted me,
but he wouldn't agree to surveillance.
Who cares if he agrees? He's a CI.
That's why we used him as bait
in the first place.
Guys.
- No liner.
- The building trash dumpster.
Subscription renewal form
from Rolling Stone
- addressed to Anton Briggs.
- This is his garbage.
So the bag split on impact
with the dumpster here.
He threw it. Defensive move.
Why the hell didn't he use his fists?
He was hurt.
There's blood and some hair.
- Looks like he hit his head against the wall.
- How bad?
Hard enough to daze him. A blow from
behind could have propelled him forward.
So Anton comes down to empty
the garbage,
the Skinner clocks him,
he does a header into the wall,
throws the bag as a last ditch.
Skinner tosses him in the car
and peels out. Got tire marks here.
Fuck.
All right, we got a confirmed
missing person. Anton Briggs.
Find a photo. Get his face out
to all patrols and the media.
Set up a tip line. Pull in some off-duties
to man the phone bank.
Skinner's had him for 24 hours.
How long do you think he can hold out?
Well, the ME's report on the other victims
suggests the Skinner starts slow.
Probably to build fear.
Anton's a big guy. A lot of skin.
That's meant to be comforting.
George King, we need to bring him in.
We gotta find him first.
We got BOLOs out on him all night long.
Haven't found him yet.
We could search his house, though.
We're still holding King's foreman
on resisting arrest?
He give us anything
that'll buy us a warrant?
Mario Astorga clammed up.
Too scared of King.
He would rather be deported
away from his family than talk about King.
- Is that all we got?
- Yeah.
I'll try and find a flexible judge.
Let me know when it comes in.
I'll go sit on King's house.
We'll go sit on King's house.
Hey, I want this above board.
Use restraint. Wait on a warrant.
And I hope they find something
because even if we nab King,
we got nothing to hold him on past today.
A day can save a lot of skin.
I keep... I keep telling you.
You have to listen.
If...
If I knew where Freebo was,
I'd tell you.
Don't you fucking understand, man?
It was the cops. I was... I was fucking bait.
All right, all right, you're right.
I know where he is.
I can show you. I can show you.
All right, listen to me.
He owes you money, right?
He owes you money?
I can get you money. I can find you money.
I don't want your money.
I loaned Freebo that money.
This is about respect.
With your first cut, you had all night
to consider my questions.
This cut, you have only one hour.
And when I return, there'll be no rest.
Use the time to think about...
the skin you have left
to lose.
- Hi.
- Hi. How are you?
Are you screening your calls?
Ellen? I'm surprised you missed
the motion hearing this morning.
So was Chicky Hines.
Of course, Miguel was perfectly
happy to get a continuance.
Uh, listen, if you're sick,
I can bring you over a sopa de pollo.
Either way, let me know you're all right.
OK? Bye.
Miguel went missing last night.
Ellen's missing this morning.
Could be a coincidence.
Patrol's been set up here all night.
King's not inside.
Well, something in there's
gonna tell us where he is.
Warrant should be here soon.
Motherfuck.
Anton? Anton, you in there?
- Anton, are you in there?
- Hey, I don't hear anything.
Yeah, well, I do. I hear somebody calling
for help. That's probable cause, right?
We're doing this above board.
The warrant's on its way.
Right. Restraint.
What the fuck are you doing?
Anton?
Shit.
Hey, you're not the only one
working this case, Morgan.
- Prado here.
- Hey.
Just checking in.
How'd the motion hearing go?
Continued.
- That's too bad.
- Oh, no, serendipitous actually.
It worked in my favor.
Listen, you don't have
to keep on checking on me.
Yeah, I know, I'm just a...
- concerned friend.
- Well, don't be.
In fact, why don't you meet me
at Cojimar for lunch?
Cause I been coming up
with some more, uh...
projects.
Another kill so soon?
I can't. I gotta keep an eye
on the situation here.
I heard. The Skinner grabbed up
another victim, huh?
Let me know if I can help.
Adi?s.
Miami Metro hotline.
What location?
Who am I speaking with?
Can you spell that, please?
Anton Briggs' photo
hit the media an hour ago.
I'm gonna bring King's employee
up from holding, take another run at him.
Mario Astorga,
already in interview two.
- Thought I'd take a stab.
- I can handle it.
I know. But I wanna help.
Tired of standing
behind my glass wall.
Well, we can use the help today.
No, I knew,
I knew half those hookers
were pre-op trannies, but is it true...
their junk still works,
but nothing comes out?
It's called slug-fucking.
Hey. Hello.
Babe. Hey, Vice got word
you needed extra bodies.
- Thought I'd help out.
- That's cause you're the best.
- Aw.
- Mwah.
Hey, hey, get a room.
Actually, no, don't.
Miami Metro tip line.
Vince, you got a second?
- What the fuck are you doing?
- What?
Helping out on my day off.
You're welcome.
Good place to meet chicks
from other departments.
Yeah, well, that's my chick.
I don't want you talking your filth at her.
Whoa, whoa, hold up, gaucho.
I didn't bring that up. She did.
- Bullshit.
- Seriously.
She's like the Wikipedia of perv.
I gotta find me
a girlfriend from Vice.
She's awesome.
Fuck. Fucking nothing.
King could be anywhere.
Or right here.
Holy shit.
Remember,
we need his cooperation.
Restraint, right.
What are you doing at my house?
Mr. King, we have a warrant
to search the premises.
What are you looking for?
More like who. You wanna tell us
where you've been all night?
Oh, I work, ma'am. Nights. Mornings.
Trees keep growing.
It's a good business.
I'm only home to have breakfast.
You wanna grab a bagel
down at the station?
- Answer some questions?
- I'm happy to answer right here, sir.
What, you got somewhere
you need to be?
Trees.
They'll wait.
Am I under arrest, sir?
No, but we can hold you
for questioning.
- For the day.
- What are you, a lawyer?
No, wait, I forgot.
You're a fucking tree-trimmer.
I moved to this country
for its amazing liberties. I know my rights.
Great.
George King is hanging you out to dry,
Mario. I thought you might want a chance...
I've seen fear.
An-inch-away-from-death fear.
It'd be a shame to leave
your wife and your little baby behind.
His is real.
What makes you so scary,
George King?
You miss your country, George?
I like this country, sir.
- I like Miami, sir.
- Nicaragua can be a rough place, huh?
You in the military down there?
Death squads, Contras.
You woulda been about the right age
to get caught up in that.
You learn a few things there, George?
I learn respect, sir.
No interrogation techniques?
Maybe a little snatch and grab?
What do they call that? Renditioning?
Oh, I don't know that, ma'am.
Ma'am, sir.
You did learn respect.
Did you show any fucking respect
to Wendell when you tore his skin off?
How about Anton when you bashed him
over the goddamn head?
Morgan, you want a coffee?
Why don't you get a coffee?
Yeah.
Sure.
He looks harmless, doesn't he?
They usually do.
I don't know.
Maybe he's not our guy.
Well, you should trust
your instincts on this one.
- This one of your creepy insights?
- Why does it always have to be creepy?
Fucking tell me.
He's held life and death in his hands.
He likes it.
I knew it.
So how do I crack
this sick fuck's brain?
From what I've read
about these sick fucks,
they usually have some sort of... code.
I'd say disrespect is high
on his list of violations.
Maybe if you came at him
with deference.
Deference, huh?
Yeah, think about it.
Hey, Lieutenant.
I heard you say your friend Ellen is ill.
Was it a stomach thing?
Because I just read this article...
I don't know what it is.
I haven't heard back from her.
I left her three messages.
I'm a little worried.
Yeah, me too.
I hope she didn't get
in an accident or something.
Excuse me.
I have an errand to run.
A home office.
If she were sick,
this is where she'd be.
Her car's here. She could have gone
for a really long walk.
Or borrowed a friend's car.
Or maybe LaGuerta's right
and Ellen is comatose
in some hospital, post-accident.
One can hope.
Not that there are any signs
of foul play here.
But Harry did raise me
to be paranoid.
Blood. Damn it.
No. Miguel wouldn't do this.
We agreed Ellen Wolf is innocent.
Hello.
It's just blood. There's no body.
He wouldn't even know what to do with one.
I never taught him
how to dispose...
As far as Miguel knows,
the best place to dispose of a body
is beneath an open grave.
Good thinking.
- Hello.
- Uh, setups are in the kitchen.
- Miguel?
- Hi.
Any bites?
No, just nosy neighbors so far.
Syl's office said that she would be here.
Is she out back, or...?
No, she wasn't feeling up
to an open house, so I'm sitting it for her.
Well, you're a good friend.
Here. You should have these.
How about I make sure Syl gets them?
Miguel.
Flowers are a good start,
but can I be honest?
I like honest.
- You're an idiot.
- That's honest.
You were smart enough
to ask her to marry you,
and she's still
that same fantastic woman.
- You don't think I know that?
- Well, you're not acting that way.
I am not having a goddamn affair, OK?
- All right, let's say that's the truth.
- It is.
- Either way, you violated her trust.
- I just needed space.
I've got everything
falling apart around me now,
you know, Oscar, Ramon,
now my cases...
And the same things
are falling apart for her
because she's your partner.
You're a wise person, aren't you?
Well, if I am,
it's only because I've learned
from my many, many mistakes.
You have insight.
And I tell you what.
I'm gonna follow your lead.
So point the way.
Mr. King, I understand
that respect is very important to you.
Yes, ma'am.
And I'm sure you feel
that people have to earn your respect.
Yes, ma'am.
I feel like you've earned this.
What's the matter,
little gardener? Huh?
You feel disrespected?
You'll get used to it in prison
because your foreman Mario's next door,
and he is spilling his guts.
You are so sure
he's afraid of you. Why?
What did you do to him?
What did you do to Anton?
- What did you do?!
- Morgan! Morgan!
Fuck.
Help!
Aah!
Help me!
Hey. We're supposed
to be working together.
You keep going off half-cocked.
How am I supposed to trust you?
You trust me? Unbelievable.
You're lucky Batista wasn't watching the
monitors. What the fuck were you thinking?
I was thinking about Anton.
You oughta try it some time.
I want to find him just as bad as you do.
If you gave a shit about Anton,
you wouldn't have made him your fake CI
and he wouldn't be messed up in this.
You were too busy boning him
to provide him with protective surveillance.
You are so crossing the line right now.
Am I?
You knew Anton was in town.
And I fucking told him to call it in.
You should have called it in
your fucking self.
I know. It's my fault.
No.
You're right.
I used him.
I... just fucking used him.
We can only hold George King
for a few more hours.
We better get back to work.
Schedule says
there are four funerals today.
Graves back-hoed last night.
That's four
Miguel could have chosen from.
She's not here. That's one down.
That blood might not even
belong to Ellen.
Could be a client's blood.
Or the previous owner's.
Huh.
He did it.
Miguel really did it.
And I taught him how.
I guided him to this.
I created...
this.
I'm sorry.
Miguel's making
his own choices now.
Look who he chose.
She didn't deserve this.
You can say it.
Won't change anything, Dex,
whether I told you so or not.
Easier to accept it.
Cause there'll be plenty more
where Ellen came from.
No, there won't.
Hey, Miguel, is it too late
to grab that lunch?
So what do you think
of this George King sicko?
- Skinner suspect?
- Mm-hm.
I gotta go from here
to your precinct
to discuss whether we're gonna
file charges against this guy.
- You think he's the guy?
- He's the guy.
Skinner.
Well, if the law can't get him...
you and I can. In fact...
I could have this guy out on the streets
in a few hours.
You need some help on this one,
or is this another solo project?
We agreed to leave
Ellen Wolf alone.
Technically, we agreed
not to kill her together. And we didn't.
- Technically?
- I know. That's... That's bullshit.
I didn't tell you
because I know you wouldn't approve.
Cause she wasn't guilty.
We have a different definition of that word.
You got rid of her
because she got in your way.
Whatever happened
to serving justice?
Is that really why you do this, Dex?
To serve justice?
- We don't have to pretend with each other.
- That's what I thought.
OK.
I should have told you.
It was a chickenshit thing to do,
and I abused your trust...
a trust, by the way,
that wasn't easy to earn.
That's not lost on me.
I gave you my shirt
linking me to Freebo's death.
I wish I had another one
to prove to you
how important
this partnership is to me.
I'd take a little remorse.
You would know that I don't feel it.
Yeah, you'll feel it if you get caught.
I didn't leave any evidence.
They're just gonna think it was
one of her scumbag clients.
Right.
Right, just another lowlife
who beat and stabbed an innocent woman.
Again, different definitions.
Dex.
This is the nature
of a real friendship.
Hmm?
We're gonna disagree.
And when we do,
we just go our own way.
No. No more individual projects.
Individuality is what makes
America great, man.
I don't think that's what
our forefathers had in mind.
Look. I'm a big boy.
I know what I'm doing.
Eventually...
you're gonna trust that too.
I'll see you over at the precinct.
He thinks he's untouchable.
He's not. It's time he learned that.
Probably not a lot of leads
on that screen.
King's a ghost.
He grabbed Anton without
a single security camera in the area
picking up him or his truck.
There's not one shot
to implicate him.
So we'll have to get it out of King.
You gonna let Quinn do it on his own?
My time is better spent here.
Away from people.
You know, someone,
a good friend, actually,
told me I had a big wall around me.
I thought it made me a better cop.
I don't think it did.
They look at him
and see a defender of truth, justice,
and the American way.
I see a man about to learn
a hard lesson.
Tire tracks in the alley
are consistent with King's truck.
And several other thousand trucks
in the Miami Metro area.
King's company trims trees.
Trimmed trees were found
in every one of the victims' homes.
- That's the lead that nailed him.
- I don't know about nailed.
The trees at my place
just got trimmed too.
- But Mario Astorga...
- We're talking about a foreman.
A foreman who's terrified of his boss.
You can arrest my boss
on that same evidence.
He's the fucking guy.
- Sir.
- Miguel. May I?
We really need your help on this one.
And you do owe us
for getting Ramon off.
I do. But I can't very well charge Mr. King
with assault on a palm tree.
You have your ways, Miguel.
You've bent rules before,
getting people lost in the system.
We need to buy time for Anton Briggs.
For you, I'll do everything in my power.
We'll be right there.
Show time.
Dex, get your kit. You too, Masuka.
- Hey, it's called off-duty.
- Not any more.
You two, you stay on King.
Don't let up. We got another body.
Anton?
A female at the cemetery.
- Cause of death?
- Take your pick.
Severe beating, strangulation...
plus three stab wounds.
Whoever did this was not a fan.
You have no idea.
I think our killer's a pro. I haven't seen
many body dumps this clean.
I made sure of that.
Miguel getting caught
isn't part of the lesson plan.
Angel, don't let her see this.
No, they said it was her.
But it's not, is it?
Maria, I'm sorry.
No, I don't believe...
- Oh, my God.
- Walk with me.
Too many people are affected
when the innocent die.
That is part of the lesson plan.
No one is untouchable.
I learned that the hard way.
So will Miguel.
His own vulnerability
is about to become very real to him...
after the stage show ends.
- They won't find anything.
- I know.
So you're just making a point.
- Am I?
- We follow the code. Or else.
There are a lot of other subtleties,
but if that's what you've gleaned,
then yeah, that's my point.
You're a wise person, aren't you?
- You're being facetious.
- No, no, you have insight.
I'd be a fool not to follow your lead.
I think you're gonna save my life.
Is this real?
I should go make a statement
to the press.
I wouldn't want anyone getting ideas
about killing lawyers.
Lesson learned...
it seems.
Oh, good. Good. You're here.
Come here. Taste this.
This one.
And now this one.
Which one?
I'm more in the mood for steak.
No, this is for the wedding cake.
We have to choose one.
Chocolate or hazelnut?
Is Sylvia still here?
No, because of me.
I intervened.
Apparently, I'm a very wise person.
Apparently?
According to Miguel. He came
to the open house I was sitting for Syl.
- Really?
- We... We talked for a while.
Actually, I talked.
I just... I gave him some insight.
Insight.
He said he thinks I could...
Save his life.
...save his life.
Every word, bullshit.
When did he start lying? With Ellen?
Before her?
So, chocolate?
What about that shirt?
The shirt.
Dexter, what's wrong?
I have to go look at some blood.
Evidence. For a crime.
Hazelnut.
Maria, why don't you head home,
get some rest?
I can't.
I have to... do something.
Sure. I'm here if you need me. OK?
Tell me that we're close
on the Skinner.
Cause this Ellen Wolf thing
is about to take over.
Still running down tips,
but they're bullshit.
They'll keep being bullshit
because nobody saw King take Anton.
- What about Mario Astorga?
- As tight-lipped as King.
Maybe I can help.
She could use a win right now.
We all could.
You gonna charge King?
- Not with what you have.
- We release him, he's in the wind.
Anton's dead.
So has King asked
for legal counsel yet?
King knows we have nothing on him.
Why would he waste the money?
Technically, if he's not represented,
I can't walk in and offer him any deals.
Not on the record, anyway.
Come on. No one'll know the difference.
Till a year from now, the recorded document
shows up on CNN, uh-uh.
Actually, that camera's been
on the fritz.
It wouldn't surprise me
if it didn't record anything.
Freebo's blood.
The link between his murder and Miguel.
If I go down,
I can take Miguel with me.
A mutual assurance.
A symbol of trust.
- Mm-mm.
- Fuck. That's it?
No way we're gonna let
that monster walk.
Are we?
I hope we meet again.
I'd like to get to know you better.
But how well
can you really know someone?
How much do you want to know?
There's gotta be something.
All we got is Mario
who won't say shit.
We could start skinning him ourselves
before he'd talk.
Morgan, we're not skinning Mario.
I got a better idea.
Wanna share with the whole class?
No, just you. I need a partner on this.
Here we are. Home sweet home.
It's too bad Anton won't ever get to do that.
Thanks to you.
What?
Los ?rboles.
Holy shit.
- You told him I revealed things?
- We didn't tell him shit.
He knew you were in holding.
He must have thought you caved.
I didn't tell anyone anything.
I'm sorry. We didn't mean to get
your family caught up in this, all right?
- We'll do everything we can to help you.
- What can you do? Nothing!
You're right. We don't even know
where this guy is.
You gotta help me,
or I can't do anything to help you.
Then that's it. I'm sorry.
?Qu? va a pasar? Wait!
He has a building.
We went through all of his holdings. There's
no record of him owning any building.
He rents it with cash.
He had me go there and pay once.
- He's trying to grow trees to sell.
- Where?
On 164th under the highway.
It's all I know.
Mi familia.
Go inside. Lock the door.
I'll send a patrol car. Go.
It worked. Get in.
Thank you.
Anton!
Anton, are you in there?
Anton?
Watch out.
Fuck restraint. Here.
Morgan! Get out of the way.
It's me. It's OK.
You're safe.
I need an ambulance
at the 164 and the 94 ASAP.
Get an APB out on George King.
You found me. You found me.
You can't get away from me
that easily.
And the results are...
Maria.
Come on. I'll take you home.
I can't go home.
There's too much silence.
I know.
You don't want to have to think
about what she went through.
- Only to realize that she's really gone.
- Don't.
- Pero, coraz?n, she's gone.
OK?
And that's gonna hurt like hell.
I know that too.
But you have friends.
Hey, hey, hey.
You got me.
I'm right here.
OK? I'm right here for you.
To get you through.
My, my, my.
It's not Freebo's blood.
It's not even human.
It's bovine. Cow's blood.
He's been using me the whole time.
I didn't create a monster,
I was used by one.
He used me.
Miguel!
Nine holes tomorrow?
You bet.
Today I keep up the pretence.
But soon, maybe tomorrow,
Miguel will know exactly how I feel
because finally there's
an emotion I don't have to fake.
Today, I feel something real.