Previously on Dexter.
I loaned Freebo that money.
This is about respect.
Anton!
Morgan, get out of the way!
You found me.
I never meant for any of this
to go down the way it did.
I shoulda told you
you were free and clear.
- So that was you?
- Yeah.
- Debra, you lied to me!
- I am not the enemy here.
I need for you to seriously think about us.
Life vests?
We can't exactly load up the cart
with axes and machetes now, can we?
Last Thursday,
I was having drinks with her,
and then the next day
I'm staring down at her dead body.
She's lucky to have you
watching out for her.
It's just like you watched out for me
with Oscar's case.
Wait.
I told Sylvia about Miguel
and LaGuerta.
So she thinks Miguel
is at LaGuerta's?
You fucker!
You are too good a liar, Miguel.
- Come on, baby, listen to me.
- Don't touch me! I'm done!
Did you see anyone else on the street?
There was some douchebag
with his high beams on, blinding me.
- What kind of car?
- Dark, black, SUV.
Think that's funny?
Not at all.
They said that stain would come out.
I am the last person you wanna fuck with,
because I will fuck you back!
Count on it!
I will.
Even Harry would agree,
Miguel has left me no other choice.
I kill him.
- Get a good look at him?
- His name?
Dexter Morgan.
You want Freebo?
Then you need to have
a long conversation with him.
So this is how it ends.
I've pictured it a thousand ways,
but never this.
Me bound in the trunk of a car.
I am so fucked.
Must be what your victims feel like.
Trapped, hopeless.
You got any more words of encouragement,
or are you just here to gloat?
I'm here for moral support.
You were right about Miguel.
He must have sent Ramon after me.
- Dexter...
- I know I only have myself to blame.
I don't blame you for wanting a friend,
a normal life.
- You don't?
- I'm actually proud of you for trying.
It was brave.
Yeah.
Yay me.
I should have fucking killed Miguel
when I had the chance.
You still can, Dexter.
Don't give up.
Ow!
What is this?
Your bachelor party, hermano!
Ow! Ah, watch the grill, George Foreman.
All aboard the party boat!
Holy shit.
Your eye's already swollen.
Here he comes.
Ten minutes on.
Ten minutes off.
I'm sorry, Vince.
I just thought... I don't know.
That's fucking hilarious!
You were freaked, right?
Yeah.
Premium alcohol,
all-you-can-eat buffet,
plus high-class adult entertainment.
Kill me now.
You guys, this is... awesome.
No, no, that's fucking awesome!
Hey.
Hey, ladies, what's going on?
Hi, sailor.
The best man
arrives with his brother.
Designated driver or bodyguard?
I'll find out later.
Right now, time to put on my party face.
Bachelor parties.
While I do understand
the need for ritual,
I've heard these events
aren't really for the groom,
they're for everyone else.
I have plans to make for my own big day,
the day I kill Miguel.
OK, OK, let's get the music down.
Baja la m?sica.
OK, boys and girls!
Put those packages away, please.
So as you all know,
we're here to, uh,
celebrate the impending marriage
of our dear friend Dexter.
And while my job as best man
is to offer a few remarks,
you're gonna have to forgive me
for keeping them G-rated,
because, uh, I'm running for office after all.
Better run fast.
Dexter's a hard guy to get to know.
And for a smart guy,
sometimes he doesn't have the good sense
that God gave little chickens.
I mean, like this doughnut thing.
What's up with that?
You bring doughnuts to work
so that people can like you?
Thanks for the diabetes
and the clogged arteries, Dexter.
I mean, why don't you just stab
a pal in the ventricle, huh?
But in all seriousness, I, uh...
I wanna say a few words
about friendship.
Friends are always honest
with each other.
They can see past their differences.
When they have a conflict,
friends are there to forgive.
A true friend knows
when to bury the hatchet,
because friendship is a sacred bond...
built on trust.
And, Dex...
I have learned so much
from you about, uh...
trust.
So, co?o...
Hey - to Dexter!
To Dexter.
I have to be at work in 45 minutes.
Maybe I can squeeze in a power nap
and a quick shower.
Maybe not.
Hey.
Good morning.
Look, bagels. Soak up the alcohol.
Actually, I'm late for work.
How was it?
I... survived.
If you're wondering
if I did anything stupid...
I didn't.
Mmm, well,
it must have been very tempting.
Very.
Syl told me she kicked out Miguel.
How is he?
- Uh, I think he feels betrayed.
- Why?
He's the one who threw
his marriage vows out the window.
- Who does that?
- A man without a code.
Exactly.
So...
What?
Well, I mean, do you really want him
standing beside you
on the biggest day of our lives?
Actually, no.
But I thought I should play nice
till after the wedding.
Just think about it, OK?
- What is that?
- Oh.
It's a, uh, hour-by-hour schedule
for the day of.
There's hair and make-up for me.
Transportation,
pictures, ceremony.
Things are bound to go wrong.
The less left to chance the better.
Wise words.
- I'll make you a copy.
- Great.
But can we talk wedding stuff later?
- I really gotta get in the shower.
- You want some company?
Yeah. But I'm too late.
After last night,
they all think we share a secret,
but Miguel's the only one
who knows mine.
I could tell the rest of them,
but then I'd have to kill them.
Just like I'm going to kill Miguel.
Ow!
What am I,
the Morgan family punching bag?
Thanks for not inviting me
to Dexter's party, you ass.
It was a bachelor party.
Dongs and gongs required.
Unless you wanna be talent.
- In which case...
- Gross. He's my brother.
Not by blood.
Oh, thank God. My head.
Your head should be in the Ellen Wolf case,
Detective. Let's review.
Toby Edwards. Bartender slash booty-call.
Saw a black SUV outside Ellen Wolf's place
the night she died.
Miguel's black SUV.
- The grid we set up, what did we get?
- Jack diddly.
There's no traffic surveillance footage
of any black SUV
between Ellen's house and the cemetery
where her body was found.
Maybe I could kill him in his car.
It has that big back seat.
Let's recanvass. Somebody saw something,
and we're gonna find them.
Next order of business.
The Skinner.
George King. The Nicaraguan embassy
is still giving me the run-around.
Ramos. Go there in person.
Until we know King's true identity,
there's not much to go on.
And finally, Anton Briggs is coming in today
to go over his statement.
Today?
What's the matter,
you forget your lip gloss?
Quinn. I want you to stay clear.
No more sparring.
And, Morgan, I know he's your informant,
but I wanna cover it.
Get myself up to speed
with the case.
All right, people.
That's it. Go, catch bad guys.
Fuck you, lip gloss.
No unusual activity?
There was some douchebag
with his high beams on, blinding me.
Actually, it wasn't high beams.
It was those big-ass halogens.
- What kind of car?
- SUV.
Dark, blue... black.
Something like that.
Hola, Miguel.
Mmm, as?, as?.
Yeah, listen, after that scene
with Syl the other night...
I think we should talk.
That's great.
Get a 20 on Anton Briggs.
Have his Uni watchdogs bring him in.
- Hey.
Mwah.
- You always look so happy to see me.
- It's cause I always am.
I brought you these.
Italian hangover remedies
perfected by centuries of
overindulging ancestors.
There's saffron lemon risotto,
white pizza, cayenne tea.
Sounds great. But I'm not hung over.
I behaved myself last night.
I'm a plus one now, remember?
Still, man has his needs.
Trust me.
My needs are covered.
Cold feet?
What?
No, Rita's great.
Getting married's easy, Dex.
All you have to do is show up.
But killing Miguel Prado?
That'll require some finesse.
He's a public figure.
- Well connected.
- Dad, I got it.
Miguel dies, people notice.
Which means you can't
just make him disappear.
So I'll pin it on someone else.
How about your timeline?
Definitely after the wedding.
It'd be crazy to do it any sooner.
And an alibi?
The wedding night.
Rita's pregnant, exhausted.
After our wedding and a glass of
champagne, she'll be out like a light.
Unless she wakes up
and you're not there.
That is not the way you want her
to remember your wedding night.
Are you hiding or something?
Anton will be here in a minute.
I don't wanna see him.
I know it's real immature,
but if I see him, I'll just miss him.
So tell him.
I can't.
I need to be with somebody
who's got his shit together.
Somebody with a real job,
somebody with strong morals.
Somebody like Dad.
Dad wasn't perfect, Deb.
Yeah, well,
he wasn't a drug user or a CI.
Well, Anton's not a CI.
Dad still wouldn't approve.
You'd be surprised.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
Something.
You've had a bug up your ass
about Dad for months now.
What did he do?
You don't wanna know.
Now I really do.
He wasn't on the take.
He didn't break any laws.
He didn't cheat on Mom.
Bullshit.
Yeah, you're right.
Bullshit! Who?
A CI.
You always wanted to be like Dad.
Seriously?
Anton is here to go over his statement...
with you.
- I thought you were covering this.
- I was.
But you're the only one he trusts.
Well, it's really hard to find people
that you trust these days.
- Deb...
- Blow me.
My sister never says that.
Oops.
Shit, this was a bad idea.
Send in the other guy.
What?
It's pretty clear
you don't wanna be here.
I'm... Sorry, this is not about you. Um...
I mean, it's about you. It's just...
...something else just happened.
Are you OK?
No.
Can I help?
Um...
Take a look at this and see if there's
anything that you wanna change or add...
You know that's not why I'm here.
Right now I really need it to be.
What?
Is there a mistake?
No.
It's just, um...
these... words, they don't... really say it.
You know, what... what happened to me.
What do you mean?
Debra, I could...
hear it, you know?
The sound...
of the blade cutting into me.
That and, uh...
the sound of me screaming.
Like it was somebody else.
And I remember thinking,
"That guy screaming...
"he's gonna die. "
But, um...
then he just stopped.
Why?
To go through my pockets.
He took my wallet
and my cell phone.
Cocksucker even took my change.
Your change?
How fucked up is that?
He give you anything?
Nothing we can use.
We'll walk the crime scene,
see if there's anything we missed.
Whatever it takes
to fucking catch this guy.
Please tell me
you're not freezing sperm in there.
This only gets down
to minus 40 degrees centigrade.
Freezing sperm requires a vessel
to be at least minus 200.
What? I'm a donor.
It's my way of giving back.
God help the children.
Hey, um, is the, uh, server down?
- Why, what do you need?
- Um, I wanted to run a background check.
On who?
Tammy Okama.
You slept with her, didn't you?
Vince Masuka does not kiss and tell.
OK, fine, I banged her.
- And?
- And...
Wow. We just stayed up all night just...
just talking.
So you like her?
The problem is she likes me.
I mean, there's gotta be
something wrong with her, right?
Well, I'll let you know
when the server's up.
If home is where the heart is,
where do you go
when you don't have a heart?
In Miguel's case, a five-star hotel.
I used to know Miguel's schedule
inside and out.
After all, we were best friends.
But things change.
Now that Syl kicked him
out of the house,
he has a new routine I need to learn.
Can I get my keys?
I forgot something.
- There you are, Mr. Prado.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Or I could wait for him
to do something stupid.
Like ditching Ramon.
You close to your father?
No. He was, uh, deadbeat trailer trash.
- It's why I became a cop.
- You got a rich mother or something?
She died when I was five.
Why?
The car, the watch.
Just wondering
if you had a trust fund,
- or you were day trading, or something.
- No. I got an uncle in Boston.
He died, left me a building. Total surprise.
Huh.
Families are full of 'em.
Just wait till Dexter's wedding.
Brings out the best and the worst.
Weddings kinda suck
when you're single.
Single? I thought you and Anton were...
- We're not. Not anymore.
- Hmm.
So, uh...
you wanna, you know, carpool?
What?
High gas prices, you know?
Are you hitting on me?
I'm sorry.
Hello?
- Morgan.
- Hello?
Hello?
Goddamn it,
fucking cell phone reception.
It's Batista.
Probably wants a status update.
We should give it to him.
Hey, you have any change?
I saw a payphone up the street.
Think so.
Motherfuck!
Holy Jesus on a stick!
- What?
- No cell phone reception.
That's why George King took
Anton's change. To use that payphone.
We gotta dump the phone records.
Whoa.
Oye.
Si.
I'm glad you called today.
I was surprised, but, uh, glad.
The last thing I wanted to do
was put you in the middle of...
Maria, you gotta know that...
I've been thinking about us for a long time.
Way before Ellen Wolf, rest in peace.
- Cause, hey, what we had...
- We were different back then.
Really different.
So why is it every time I look at you,
I still feel the same way I felt
when we first met? Hmm?
- Water's boiling.
- Boiling, yes, ooh.
It's mi sopa.
And... I got you some Red Stripe.
- Oh, wow, great.
- Somewhere. Shit, I left it in the car.
Oh, I'll go get it.
No, no, no, no. You stay
and make sure it doesn't boil over.
OK.
Miguel probably thinks
he's getting lucky.
Looks like he's getting screwed.
They make a cute couple. Too bad
they're both lying through their teeth.
Don't go there, Miguel.
You start thinking LaGuerta's onto you,
you'll decide to do very bad things
to another innocent person,
and I can't let that happen.
Things to do today -
find a non-blowback way
to dispose Miguel's body.
I need you to run hair and fiber for me
against all victims for the last ten days.
- But I'm the blood guy.
- Who also does forensics.
Who I trust to keep a confidence
and the lab results off the record.
Well, keeping secrets
is one of my strong suits,
but I got my head handed to me the last time
I did some off-the-grid testing, by you.
This is different.
That was bureaucratic bullshit.
And this is,
"Do as I say, not as I do"?
You ever get a voice inside
nagging at you?
- I'm aware of the phenomenon.
- Well, I'm hoping I'm wrong about this,
but if I am and anyone finds out,
it'll bring a shit hurricane
down on the entire department.
And if you're right?
Same hurricane, different landfall.
Got it. Either way, I need a raincoat.
No, I don't want you getting
into any trouble over this.
Use my authorization code to make it
happen. Procedure above board, results...
under the table.
- You good with that?
- Absolutely.
If you need something
under the table, I'm your guy.
That didn't come out right.
How soon before you can get back to me
with this?
ASAP.
Accessing samples from homicides
in the last ten days.
Fast-tracked and confidential.
Authorization code requested.
Processing.
Approved.
You're the best.
I have to be.
MUDs and LUDs from that payphone.
George King was using it like an office line.
He called clients, he called workers,
he ordered Nicaraguan takeout.
- That doesn't help us.
- Well, maybe it does.
I just got off the phone with some lady
that he called up in New Jersey.
She winters down here
at Coconut Grove.
She just rehired George King
to re-landscape their lawn.
- So?
- So he knows the place is empty.
- You think he'd be using it to lay low?
- We got fuck-all else.
Vince.
The server's back up,
so I ran your girl.
Bad news. She's got a rap sheet.
She rammed her car into someone else
over a parking space.
- Yeah.
- Big fine, anger management.
That means she's got issues.
So she's not outta my league.
Happy to help.
Both Caucasoid, evenly distributed
pigment granules, same dye job.
In other words, both Ellen Wolf.
No news there.
Do I let LaGuerta in on this?
But why stir up the hornet's nest?
Miguel's going to get the justice
he deserves soon enough.
- Hey, Dex.
- Hey.
Too late to bring a date
to the wedding?
No, Rita's still collecting RSVPs.
What you working on?
I, uh, found a grey hair.
I was curious.
Oh, dude, I've totally done that.
You're bald.
Oh.
- Maybe we should call for backup?
- Let's see what we got first.
Someone took the jungle cruise
at Magic Kingdom.
Creeping mother of Mary!
Hey.
Door.
Fuck, there he is!
Go around front.
Requesting all units, 931 Harbor Drive.
Fuck!
- Jesus, Quinn, are you OK?
- Ow!
Officer down.
931 Harbor Drive.
Requesting an ambulance,
Also air surveillance of our 20.
What's this?
Dexter, I need to see you for a minute.
- You found the hair analysis results?
- Sorry, it...
You were out, and they were
just sitting there,
and I really needed to know
what came back.
So... now you know.
Question is,
what are you gonna do?
It's complicated.
I understand complicated.
Maybe I can help.
OK.
You're close with Miguel Prado,
and so am I,
which is what makes this very difficult.
What's this gotta do with Miguel?
Ellen Wolf was threatening
to wreck his career.
Well, he has a black SUV
and no alibi for the night she died.
You think Miguel had something
to do with her murder?
I found this sample in the back of his car.
I... I told you this was complicated.
Dexter.
I need your word this stays between us.
Yeah, you have it.
No wonder all the secrecy.
I'm assuming there's no chain of custody
on this?
I'll go to a judge for a warrant,
get evidence through proper channels.
Which will tip off Miguel
and put LaGuerta in his crosshairs.
You really think a judge
is gonna issue a warrant
against a well-respected officer of the court
without probable cause?
I don't know, Dexter.
I... I can't do nothing.
Not after these results.
Maybe you could sit on it.
For a while. Let Miguel think...
he got away with murder.
It'd give you time to build a solid case.
I've got some serious
soul-searching to do.
Take as long as you need.
Thanks for your help, Dexter.
Yeah.
While LaGuerta's deciding,
I'll be eliminating her problem.
And George King's going to help me.
I'll copy his MO.
They won't even look for another suspect.
What happened?
King.
I told him to go home, but he's hell-bent
on proving he has cojones of steel.
- You good?
- Superficial cut. Let's keep moving.
All right, get me your report
as soon as you can.
The brass is gonna be asking questions.
We had aerial surveillance,
a security perimeter, at least 50 officers.
It's like George King is a ghost.
Sorry, Sarge.
I'm not. I need King out there long enough
to peg Miguel's murder on him.
How long have you known?
Huh?
About Dad and his CI.
Uh... couple of weeks.
Camilla told me right before she died.
- I didn't know if I should...
- Tell me?
Yes, whenever you have
an earth-shattering, ball-crushing,
mind-fuck of a secret,
you should tell your fucking sister.
Sorry.
You can get that now.
Rita wants to know
if you're bringing Anton to the wedding.
Bad timing.
No, I'm not bringing him.
Quinn sort of asked
if I would go as his date, but...
as much as I'll hate going stag
to my own brother's wedding...
being Quinn's date
depresses me even more.
He seems OK.
Yeah, he's fine.
On paper he's a cop.
Good career.
Like Dad.
Yeah.
Well, it seems I don't know Dad
as well as I thought I did.
Turns out I'm just as big
a fuck-up as he was.
You're not a fuck-up!
You're the hardest-working person I know,
you're loyal to a fault.
In all the years I've known you,
you've never let me down.
You should be my best man.
What?
Miguel is your best man.
He's not even a good man.
I shoulda asked you in the first place.
So why didn't you?
I don't know. I...
thought the best man
was supposed to be a man.
But I trust you...
more than anyone.
That's way more important.
You better not be doing this
because you feel guilty.
Would you just...
stand up for me?
Abso-fucking-lutely.
Hey!
Long time.
Too busy with that new boyfriend of yours
to come down and talk shit with me?
What? Word travels.
Well, not fast enough.
We broke up.
Hey, fuck him. His loss.
Yeah, well...
I kinda need a favor.
That's what I'm here for.
What you need?
All the records you have
on my dad's confidential informants.
Your dad?
I know it's a big dig,
but I just need the female Cls,
and probably just the attractive ones.
Someone said something to you...
about Harry and one of his Cls?
His attractive female Cls?
Why, you know something?
What I know is, your dad wouldn't be
the first cop to fuck around on his wife.
Look, I know you have
a lot of requests, but...
But nothing.
My dad stepped out on my mom.
Woulda cut off his dick if I coulda.
- I'll put a rush on it.
- Thank you.
Miguel's a night owl
and a newly minted bachelor,
no way he's in bed this early.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not going to sleep.
The way the Prados
are knocking them back,
they're not going anywhere soon.
Just as well, I have some stalking to do.
Hotel Belvedere.
- Miguel Prado, please.
- Yes, sir. I'll connect you right away.
Got it.
Excuse me.
- Si?
- Could I get a turndown service?
- Room 138.
- Mm-hm.
Thanks.
Hello?
Yeah.
I- I'm sorry,
you're breaking up.
Can I call you back on a landline?
OK, bye.
I'm sorry, that's my boss.
Can you come back later?
Oh, s?.
- Gracias.
- De nada, se?or.
I can park right there, use this
as my point of entry and make the grab.
I'm in and out undetected.
A life vest? Shit.
He's been back to that hardware store.
He's planning to kill again.
Fucking Miguel and his innocent victims.
That's why he's at the bar.
Get Ramon blackout drunk so Miguel
can claim he was here the whole time.
Tonight's the night.
Maria?
Lieutenant, Dexter here. Hey, I came across
something you'll be interested in.
Kinda has to do with the whole
Miguel Prado, Ellen Wolf thing
you wanted me to look at.
You there?
We should meet.
I'll be at the Rising Moon Caf?
at 91st and Channel at 8pm.
Uh... I'll try your cell.
Jesus!
Finally.
No, no, no, no, man.
Oh, God.
Maria.
Oh.
OK.
OK, OK, I know...
I know I...
I crossed the line here.
I know that now.
It doesn't have to come to this.
But it always does.
I had higher hopes for you, for us.
But I finally just have to accept it,
I'll always be alone.
That's not true.
You talking truth? That's good.
You actually had me believing
I could have a friend...
cause I swallowed your bullshit.
It wasn't bullshit!
Shh.
I tried.
I tried to crack that damn armor of yours.
Because I saw the possibility.
I still see the possibilities.
So this is my fault
for being a shutdown?
No, I just want you to let me in!
Why the fuck would I do that now?
Because I know you.
Dexter, I know you better than anyone else.
No, there've been quite a few
who've seen the real me as they...
laid on that table.
You're all just...
unchecked versions of myself...
what I would have become
without my father's code.
They deserved it!
I'm not like them!
You are.
Admit it.
- I'm like you.
- No. No. No, no, no, no.
I know I'm a monster.
I accept you.
I accept you, Dexter, like a brother.
I killed my brother.
I killed yours too.
Oscar?
You?
I didn't plan to,
but it was kill or be killed.
You!
You killed Oscar!
What did you say...
in your bachelor party speech?
Friends are always honest.
Friends forgive.
But I don't forgive you.
And I don't get to have friends.
You little freak!
You think I'm done with you?
You think this ends here?
It doesn't!
It does for you.
Adi?s, amigo.