??????????????????
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
???? ?2??5?
-=??????=-
?????ID
????KevinVan
Dexter:
PREVIOUSLY ON "DEXTER"...
Dexter: WHAT'S THIS BIG BREAK
IN THE BAY HARBOR BUTCHER CASE
I KEEP HEARING ABOUT?
Debra: MASUKA FOUND
MICROSCOPIC ALGAE
INSIDE THE GARBAGE BAGS
WITH THE BODY.
IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE ROCKS, BABY.
THE ROCKS?
YEAH, THE ALGAE WE FOUND
ON THE ROCKS.
THE BAY HARBOR BUTCHER USED THEM
TO WEIGH HIS BAGS DOWN.
WE'RE ASSUMING HE PICKED THEM UP
WHERE HE DOCKS HIS BOAT.
Dexter:
OCTOBER 3, 1973 --
LAURA MOSER
AND THREE OTHERS FOUND
CHOPPED UP
WITH A CHAIN SAW.
APPARENTLY A DRUG DEALER
DIDN'T APPRECIATE
LAURA AND HER FRIENDS
STEALING HIS COCAINE.
WHAT IS IN THAT REPORT THAT
HARRY DIDN'T WANT ME TO SEE?!
YOU WERE LEFT THERE
FOR DAYS,
STARVING,
IN BLOOD TWO INCHES THICK.
DEXTER,
THIS IS MY MOTHER.
GAIL.
HE'S HIDING SOMETHING.
I'M SURE OF IT.
DID YOU KILL YOUR WIFE?
YEAH.
DON'T MAKE ME DO IT,
CURTIS!
DEBRA, ACTUALLY.
I'M GABRIEL.
OH, YOU'RE INTO THE KINKY STUFF,
HUH?
NO, THE LAST GUY I HAD SEX WITH
TRIED TO KILL ME.
OH, THERE'S MY SPONSOR.
REALLY? WHERE?
DEXTER, MEET DEXTER.
I'M GONNA HELP THE TWO OF YOU
GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL ME ALL
YOUR DEEPEST, DARKEST SECRETS.
BUT THE PERSON
WHO DID THIS...
IS A PERSON JUST LIKE ME...
LIKE YOU.
WE'RE ALL GOOD, DEXTER,
AND WE'RE ALL EVIL.
THIS WOMAN SEES ME.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW IT,
BUT SHE'S LOOKING
BEHIND THE MASK,
AND SHE'S NOT TURNING AWAY.
Man: UH, HERE'S YOUR CAPPUCCINO
AND SCONE, MA'AM.
CAN I HELP THE NEXT PERSON,
PLEASE?
MOST PEOPLE HATE LONG LINES.
HI. CAN I HAVE A COFFEE
AND A DANISH?
THE BANK, GROCERY STORE,
COFFEE BAR.
NOT ME.
BUDDY, YOU MIND?
OH.
WANT A REAL GLIMPSE
OF HUMAN NATURE?
STAND IN THE WAY
OF SOMEONE'S MOCHA LATTE.
IT ALSO REMINDS ME THAT
THE GOOD PEOPLE OF MIAMI AND I
AREN'T SO DIFFERENT.
THEY HAVE NO MORE IDEA
OF WHAT I AM THAN I DO.
Man #2: ALL I'M SAYING IS
THESE GUYS HAD IT COMING.
SO WHAT,
JUST CHOP THEM ALL UP?
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
WHOEVER'S DOING THIS SHIT
DESERVES A GODDAMN MEDAL.
Man:
THAT'LL BE $4.20, MA'AM.
SORRY, MY WALLET'S
IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
OH, I GOT IT.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH, I INSIST.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU'RE A GODSEND.
OH, SWEET MARY,
MOTHER OF FUCK, THAT'S GOOD!
I THINK YOU MIGHT HAVE
BROKEN A COMMANDMENT
SOMEWHERE IN THERE.
BURNING THE LATE-NIGHT OIL
WITH THE TASK FORCE?
HARDLY -- TILL WE GET THE REPORT
BACK ON THE ALGAE,
IT'S JUST ONE BIG
REACH-AROUND.
THE ROCKS I USED
TO SUBMERGE MY VICTIMS
MAY EVENTUALLY SINK ME, TOO,
BUT IF I'M LEARNING ANYTHING
IN RECOVERY,
IT'S "ONE DAY AT A TIME."
BAY HARBOR BUTCHER.
GIVE ME ONE SHOT --
I'D PUT A BULLET
IN THE FUCKER'S HEAD.
YOU REALLY FEEL THAT WAY?
HE'S KILLING PEOPLE, DEX.
IF DAD TAUGHT US ONE THING,
IT'S THE VALUE OF HUMAN LIFE.
YEAH, BUT I THINK WE HAD
DIFFERENT HOMEWORK ASSIGNMENTS.
DISPATCH.
SEE YOU TONIGHT?
MM, I THINK I'M STAYING
AT GABRIEL'S.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
TAKING IT SLOW.
WE ARE.
NO SEX, JUST CUDDLING.
MY LITTLE SISTER,
THE CUDDLER.
I GOT A SCALDING-HOT BEVERAGE
HERE, DEX.
DON'T MAKE ME USE IT.
LOVE YOU, TOO.
I NEVER REALLY GOT
THE WHOLE SUPERHERO THING.
BUT LATELY, IT DOES SEEM
WE HAVE A LOT IN COMMON --
TRAGIC BEGINNINGS...
SECRET IDENTITIES...
PART HUMAN, PART MUTANT...
ARCHENEMIES.
GREAT WAY TO START
THE DAY, HUH?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE MOVING BACK
INTO YOUR OFFICE, BOSS?
I'D RATHER BE HERE.
WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME?
BLUNT FORCE TRAUMA.
THE BLOOD SPATTER HERE
ON THE COUNTER
SUGGESTS THAT THIS IS WHERE
THE INITIAL BLOW OCCURRED.
IMPACT SPATTER
IS CONSISTENT
WITH REPEATED BLOWS
TO THE SKULL.
THE VICTIM TRIED TO FLEE
TO THE BACK DOOR
BUT DIDN'T GET FAR.
WHO IS HE?
DENNY FOSTER --
WORKED HERE.
OWNER SAID
HE CLOSED UP NIGHTS.
ROBBERY?
THERE'S NO MONEY MISSING
FROM THE REGISTER.
SOMETHING THIS BRUTAL
IS PERSONAL.
WANT TO MEET
YOUR PRIME SUSPECT?
HE HAS FINS.
SHOULD WE CALL
THE SUPER FRIENDS FOR HELP?
NO, I GOT IT COVERED.
I FOUND TRACES OF BLOOD
HERE ON THE BASE.
I'LL BRING IT BACK
TO MY LAB,
CONFIRM
IT'S THE MURDER WEAPON.
OKAY.
Doakes: GOT A NEXT OF KIN
WE CAN NOTIFY?
UH, DENNY WAS,
LIKE, A LONER --
WHO'S THAT?
THE DARK DEFENDER.
DENNY HAD THIS GREAT IDEA
TO PUT A SPIN
ON THAT VIGILANTE SERIAL KILLER
WE GOT RUNNING AROUND.
DEFINITELY HAS A NICER RING
TO IT
THAN
THE BAY HARBOR BUTCHER.
I'M CONDUCTING
AN INTERVIEW HERE, MORGAN.
DENNY WAS TRYING TO SET UP
THE DARK DEFENDER
AS A GRAPHIC NOVEL.
"STALKER OF THE NIGHT,
HIS BLADE OF VENGEANCE
TURNS WRONG INTO RIGHT."
I NEED SOME AIR.
THANKS A LOT.
"THE DARK DEFENDER."
NO, MIAMI'S TOO HOT
FOR ALL THAT LEATHER.
THE FIRST TIME I GOT HIGH,
I WAS 15.
NO, THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
I WAS 14.
NO, WAIT.
I WAS DEFINITELY 15 BECAUSE
IT WAS MY FRESHMAN YEAR.
I REMEMBER NOW BECAUSE I WAS
DATING SUSIE MITCHELL.
WE BROKE UP 'CAUSE I CALLED HER
BY HER SISTER, SHARON'S,
NAME ONCE.
SHE HATED WHEN PEOPLE DID THAT.
WHAT SHE DIDN'T KNOW WAS
THAT I HAD A THING FOR SHARON.
SHARON DIDN'T WANT ANYTHING
TO DO WITH ME, SO...
Laura:
DON'T YOU HURT MY BABY!
[ Echoing ]
DON'T YOU DARE!
DON'T LOOK.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
MOMMY LOVES YOU.
DON'T YOU HURT MY BABY!
IT'S OKAY, MOM.
YOU'RE SAFE.
MMM. THAT'S HOT.
WHERE DID YOU DRIFT OFF TO,
ANYWAY?
I WAS HAVING
THIS BIZARRE DREAM
ABOUT MY MOTHER.
SAY NO MORE.
OEDIPUS COMPLEX --
EXPLAINS A LOT.
SO, WHAT WERE YOU DOING
TO YOUR MOTHER IN THIS DREAM?
SAVING HER LIFE.
SHE WAS MURDERED...
WHEN I WAS A BOY.
I WAS THERE.
I SAW IT HAPPEN.
I'VE NEVER TOLD
ANYONE THAT BEFORE.
COME ON.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT MAYBE YOU
WEREN'T SAVING YOUR MOTHER
IN THIS DREAM?
MAYBE YOU WERE
SAVING YOURSELF.
THAT'S NOT WHAT HAPPENED.
DON'T BE SO SURE.
WHEN I GOT CLEAN,
ALL THE SERIOUSLY
FUCKED-UP REASONS I USED
IN THE FIRST PLACE
BEGAN TO SURFACE.
THIS COULD BE WHERE
YOUR ADDICTION STARTED.
I HOPE WHOEVER DID IT
GOT THE BLOODY CHAIR.
THERE WERE THREE MEN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO THEM.
DEXTER, IF THESE GUYS
ARE BEHIND BARS,
YOU NEED TO CONFRONT THEM.
IF THEY'RE DEAD, HELL,
GO PISS ON THEIR GRAVES,
BUT YOU NEED TO DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES
SO YOU CAN GET CLOSURE.
HOW ELSE DO YOU EXPECT
TO GET BETTER?
I NEVER EXPECTED
TO GET BETTER.
MY METH LAB'S
IN THE SOCK DRAWER.
THIS LOOKS BAD,
DOESN'T IT?
YEAH.
THE CUTE PANTIES HELP.
WOULD YOU BELIEVE I'M TRYING
TO GET TO KNOW YOU BETTER?
BY RIFLING
THROUGH MY STUFF?
I'M RETARDED.
AND YOU'VE BEEN SO GREAT.
YOU KNOW HOW I TOLD YOU
THE LAST GUY I HAD SEX WITH
TRIED TO KILL ME?
WELL, THAT WAS
KIND OF TRUE.
HE WAS
THE ICE-TRUCK KILLER.
WHO IS HE?
NOT FUCKING FUNNY.
COME ON, DEB.
I NEVER HEARD OF HIM BEFORE.
STOP IT.
DON'T SCREW WITH ME.
DEB, I'VE BEEN
IN EL SALVADOR
VISITING FAMILY
FOR SIX MONTHS.
I JUST GOT BACK.
YOU SOUND LIKE EVERY OTHER
JACKASS OUT THERE WHO THINKS...
I'M A TROPHY FUCK.
YOU HAD NO IDEA WHO I WAS
WHEN YOU HIT ON ME AT THE GYM?
WHEN I HIT ON YOU
AT THE GYM,
IT WAS BECAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU WERE HOT.
GOOD ANSWER.
SO, WHAT'S HOT ABOUT ME?
IT'S IN THE CORNER!
DON'T HURT IT!
OH, GOD, DEXTER,
BE CAREFUL.
USE A BROOM.
IT MIGHT HAVE RABIES.
OH, IT'S RIGHT THERE!
GET IT!
WATCH IT!
CAREFUL.
YAY! ALL RIGHT!
HE GOT IT!
YAY!
MY HERO.
ALL RIGHT, KIDS.
SHOW'S OVER.
COME ON.
LET'S GET DRESSED FOR SCHOOL.
SO, ANY ARMADILLOS
IN MICHIGAN?
NO.
WE DIDN'T USED TO HAVE ANY
IN FLORIDA.
NOW IT'S LIKE AN INVASION.
"ARMADILLOS ATTACK!"
YOU THINK YOU'RE CHARMING,
DON'T YOU?
I'M SURE THAT PROBABLY WORKS
FOR YOU MOST OF THE TIME.
IT DID FOR PAUL.
I KNOW WHAT YOU ARE.
CONFUSED?
I FOUND THESE
IN A DRAWER.
TELL ME, DEXTER,
WHY WOULD RITA PRINT OUT
NARCOTICS ANONYMOUS LITERATURE
IF PAUL'S DEAD?
BECAUSE RECENTLY
I ENTERED THE PROGRAM.
I KNEW IT.
I WOULD NEVER HURT RITA
LIKE PAUL DID.
BECAUSE I'M NOT GONNA GIVE YOU
THAT CHANCE.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE YOU PULL HER UNDER
JUST LIKE HE DID.
HAVE YOU DISCUSSED ANY OF THIS
WITH RITA?
NO, BUT I WILL IF YOU DON'T
DO THE RIGHT THING HERE.
IF YOU TRULY CARE ABOUT THIS
FAMILY LIKE YOU SAY YOU DO,
YOU WILL LET MY DAUGHTER
AND THOSE SWEET CHILDREN GO.
THE ALGAE ON THE ROCKS WAS
EXPOSED TO BOTH ZINC AND LEAD.
THERE ARE ONLY THREE MARINAS
NEAR BAY HARBOR
WHICH HAVE RESTRICTED
WATER FLOW
THAT WOULD ACCOUNT
FOR SUCH HIGH LEVELS
OF THESE SPECIFIC
POLLUTANTS --
TURKEY CREEK, SUNSET KEYS,
AND CORAL COVE.
ANYONE FAMILIAR
WITH THESE MARINAS?
CORAL COVE IS WHERE MY DAD
KEPT OUR FAMILY BOAT.
MY BROTHER USES THE SLIP NOW.
I'LL BET HALF THE FORCE
HAS BOATS OUT THERE.
IT'S ONE OF THE FEW
MARINAS LEFT
THAT'S AFFORDABLE
ON A COP'S SALARY.
MORGAN AND I WILL
TAKE THAT ONE.
SODOQUIST AND LEE,
TURKEY CREEK IS YOURS.
AND, HILL AND RAMOS,
YOU'VE GOT SUNSET KEYS.
THE REST OF YOU WILL STAY HERE
WITH DETECTIVE BATISTA.
WHEN THE TEAM REPORTS IN,
RELAY THE INFORMATION
BACK TO ME.
IF OUR KILLER'S BOAT IS OUT
THERE, LET'S FIND IT.
SORRY IT TOOK SO LONG.
COULDN'T SEEM TO FIND
ANY OTHER CRIME SCENE FILES.
PROBABLY LOST IN STORAGE
SOMEWHERE.
ANYWAY, THAT'S WHAT I WAS ABLE
TO DIG UP.
JUST ONE FILE?
THERE WERE THREE MEN ARRESTED
FOR THOSE MURDERS.
WELL, ONE'S DECEASED,
ONE'S DOING LIFE
WITHOUT POSSIBILITY,
AND THAT'S THE ONLY ONE
THAT'S STILL AN OPEN CASE --
SANTOS JIMINEZ.
WHY'S IT AN OPEN CASE?
JIMINEZ TURNED
STATE'S EVIDENCE,
WENT INTO WITNESS
PROTECTION.
THERE'S A BUSINESS ADDRESS
IN THERE FOR HIM.
I GUESS AFTER 34 YEARS,
HE FIGURES ALL THE PEOPLE
WHO WANT HIM DEAD ARE LONG GONE.
HE FIGURED WRONG.
IF YOU CAN'T FIND
WHAT YOU NEED,
THERE'S AUDIO TAPES
CROSS-REFERENCED WITH THIS FILE.
TAPES?
YEAH, SEE THAT NOTATION?
THERE WAS A CRIMINAL INFORMANT
WORKING A COCAINE BUST
FROM THE INSIDE.
I'LL TAKE THIS, TOO.
OKAY.
HARRY ALWAYS SAID,
"NEVER MAKE THINGS PERSONAL --
CLOUDS YOUR JUDGEMENT."
BUT I'VE BEEN LIVING IN A FOG
WAY TOO LONG.
Harry: TODAY IS FRIDAY,
SEPTEMBER 28, 1973.
THIS IS DETECTIVE
HARRY MORGAN.
DAD.
CASE FILE --
Laura: I CAN'T FUCKING
DO THIS ANYMORE!
I HAVE TO KNOW WHEN THE NEXT
SHIPMENT'S COMING IN, LAURA.
LAURA MOSER -- MY MOTHER.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
HARRY, I'M SO SCARED.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
YOU JUST NEED TO CALM DOWN.
I ALREADY TOOK THE COCAINE
AS EVIDENCE,
JUST LIKE YOU ASKED --
WHY ISN'T THAT ENOUGH?
IF WE WANT ESTRADA AND HIS MEN
BEHIND BARS,
WE HAVE TO CATCH THEM IN THE ACT
AT THE SHIPYARD.
HE'S GONNA FIND OUT,
AND THEN HE'S GONNA KILL ME.
HARRY, LISTEN TO ME.
I THINK SOMEONE MAY HAVE
FOLLOWED US TO THE PARK.
IF WE WERE FOLLOWED,
I WOULD HAVE NOTICED.
I JUST NEED YOU TO HOLD OUT
A LITTLE LONGER.
THIS WILL ALL BE OVER SOON.
I NEED TO PICK UP BRIAN
AT SCHOOL.
I WON'T LET ANYTHING HAPPEN
TO YOU...
OR YOUR BOYS.
YOU HAVE MY WORD.
HARRY BROKE HIS WORD.
HE WASN'T CALLED TO
THAT CRIME SCENE BY CHANCE.
IT WAS HIS CASE.
LAURA MOSER WAS HIS INFORMANT.
HARRY KNEW MY MOTHER.
OUR SUSPECT IS 6'2",
380 POUNDS, HISPANIC,
DRIVES A 1971 FORD PICKUP.
CIRCULATE HIS DMV PHOTO.
HEY.
I'VE GOT GOOD NEWS.
ME TOO.
TURNS OUT OUR VIC, FOSTER --
HE HAD A BLOG.
HE WAS IN SOME
ONLINE GEEK FLAME WAR
WITH A GUY CALLING HIMSELF
"CORNDUDE."
THE D.A. FINALLY SIGNED OFF
ON YOUR REVIEW.
THERE WON'T BE ANY CHARGES.
THIS CORNDUDE'S REAL NAME
IS BENJAMIN ALVARO.
ANYONE FROM THE SHOOT
ROLL-OUT TEAM
TALK TO YOU
ABOUT COUNSELING?
WHY THE FUCK WOULD
I NEED COUNSELING?
'CAUSE YOU SHOT A MAN
LAST WEEK, JAMES.
THAT'S TWO SHOOTINGS
IN LESS THAN SIX MONTHS.
COME ON,
IT'S GOT TO TAKE ITS TOLL.
I'M FINE,
BUT THANKS ANYWAY.
THE SUSHI PLACE NEXT DOOR
HAS A SECURITY CAMERA
THAT COVERS THE PARKING LOT.
YOU KNOW, DEPARTMENT'S
CHAPLAIN'S GOT A GOOD EAR.
MARIA, CAN WE STAY
ON THE GODDAMN POINT?
THE CAMERA CAUGHT
THE LICENSE PLATE
OF A
GREEN-AND-WHITE PICKUP.
IT BELONGS TO ALVARO.
TIMECODE PUTS HIM HERE
AFTER THE SHOP CLOSED.
SO SEND SOME UNIs TO STAKE OUT
ALVARO'S HOUSE,
AND YOU AND I WILL TAKE
WHERE HE WORKS.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
I'VE GOT SIMMS AND GILES ON IT.
I GOT BACKUP.
COME ON!
IT WILL BE LIKE OLD TIMES.
NINA, I JUST GOT A CALL
FROM MY ATTORNEY.
WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT
THIS VISITATION BULLSHIT.
CAN YOU JUST TRY DEXTER'S
OFFICE AGAIN?
MISS,
HE'S NOT PICKING UP.
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET THIS.
EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU A FRIEND OF DEXTER'S?
I'M, UH, HIS DECORATOR.
LOVE THE HAT.
TERRENCE, UH, GIVE HER
A VISITOR'S BADGE.
I'LL --
I'LL TAKE HER UP.
ANGEL BATISTA.
I'M DEXTER'S BEST FRIEND.
NICE TO MEET YOU...
ANGEL BATISTA.
MY WORK REQUIRES ME
TO BE AN EXPERT
IN ANALYZING PATTERNS.
NOW A PATTERN KEEPS EMERGING
FROM MY PAST
THAT'S ALL TOO FAMILIAR --
HARRY LYING TO ME.
NO WONDER HE DESTROYED THE FILE
ON MY MOTHER'S DEATH.
IT WASN'T TO PROTECT ME.
IT WAS TO BURY HIS OWN GUILT.
Batista:
LOOK WHO I FOUND.
LISTEN, WHEN YOU'RE DONE
WITH HIM,
MAYBE YOU CAN COME OVER
TO MY PLACE.
IT'S A MESS.
NEEDS A WOMAN'S TOUCH.
YEAH?
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO ANGEL?
DEXTER,
THESE ARE AMAZING!
LILA,
YOU CAN'T BE IN HERE.
DID YOU FIND OUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE MEN RESPONSIBLE
FOR YOUR MOTHER'S MURDER?
DEAD OR IN PRISON --
EXCEPT FOR ONE.
HE CUT A DEAL.
NOW HE LIVES IN NAPLES, FLORIDA.
HE RUNS A TAVERN.
AND WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT IT?
NOT SURE YET.
AND YOU'RE NOT
THE LEAST BIT PISSED OFF
THAT THIS MAN GOT AWAY
WITH MURDER?
NO.
YOU SURE?
MAYBE A LITTLE.
THEN GO AND TELL HIM.
HEALING IS ALL ABOUT
FOCUSING YOUR RAGE
ON THE PERSON
THAT'S HURT YOU.
NAPLES IS, WHAT...
TWO HOURS AWAY?
WE COULD GO TONIGHT.
OKAY.
PICK ME UP AFTER WORK?
ALL RIGHT.
CAN I HAVE ONE OF THESE?
SURE.
WHAT IS THIS STUFF?
IT'S CORN SYRUP AND DYE.
IT'S MY OWN RECIPE.
MMM. NOT BAD.
THANK YOU.
OH, GOD!
WHO DOESN'T FIX
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
SO, I'M THINKING WE'RE ASSUMING
OUR KILLER OWNS A BOAT,
BUT WHAT IF HE --
HOW DO YOU STAND
THIS MIAMI HEAT?
MAKES MY TOES SWELL UP.
OH, SO, ANYWAY,
I WAS THINKING, WHAT IF THE
KILLER'S BEEN RENTING A BOAT?
I CAN CROSS-REFERENCE
SOME NAMES OF --
YOU LIKE CUCUMBER SANDWICHES,
OFFICER MORGAN?
I-I DON'T KNOW.
ANYWAY, UH, WE HAVE
SOME OF THE DATES
OF WHEN THE VICTIMS
WENT MISSING.
IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE CREAM CHEESE.
SO WE COULD CROSS-REFERENCE
THOSE DATES
AGAINST THE RENTAL LOGS,
AND MAYBE THE SAME NAMES
WILL POP UP.
DID YOU HEAR ANYTHING
I JUST SAID?
NOT ONE WORD.
IT'S 1:00.
I ALWAYS STOP AND EAT LUNCH
AT 1:00.
YOU'LL LEARN THAT ABOUT ME.
WHY DON'T YOU SIT DOWN?
YOU'RE WELCOME TO CONSIDER IT
AN ORDER IF THAT HELPS.
THE SHOES, TOO.
SHOULDN'T WE BE --
I DON'T KNOW --
INVESTIGATING THE AREA?
YOU'RE VERY FIDGETY.
ANYONE EVER TELL YOU THAT?
YES. MY FATHER.
YOU APPLYING FOR THE JOB?
JUST AN OBSERVATION.
I'M SORRY.
I'M CONFUSED.
ARE YOU CRITICIZING ME
FOR WANTING TO DO MY JOB?
YES.
IT'S 1:00.
LOOK, THE LAST TIME
I WAS AROUND BOATS,
A KILLER
WAS KIDNAPPING ME,
WHICH MIGHT EXPLAIN WHY
I'M LIVING WITH MY BROTHER
AND SNOOPING
ON MY NEW BOYFRIEND.
SO FORGIVE ME FOR BEING
A LITTLE FIDGETY,
BUT IF IT'S LUNCH
WE'RE TALKING,
I'M GONNA EAT
A FAT PORK SANDWICH,
AND I'M SURE AS SHIT
NOT GONNA EAT IT HERE.
DEBRA.
WHAT?!
THIS ISN'T
A COMMERCIAL MARINA.
I HAVEN'T SEEN
A SINGLE RENTAL I.D.
ON ANY OF THESE HULLS.
BUT I CAN SEE THE UPKEEP
ON THIS PLACE IS DISMAL.
UNSECURE PERIMETER,
POOR LIGHTING.
COME OUT HERE AT NIGHT,
NO ONE WOULD KNOW
WHAT THE HELL YOU'RE DOING.
THAT'S WHY I'M GOING TO ORDER
24-HOUR SURVEILLANCE
ON THIS MARINA
AND THE TWO OTHERS.
AS SOON AS I FINISH
MY LUNCH.
AHH.
I FINISHED MY SPATTER REPORT,
PUT IN FOR A PERSONAL DAY,
LEFT WORD WITH RITA.
NAPLES, HERE I COME.
I CAN'T REALLY FOCUS MY RAGE
ON THE MAN
WHO KILLED MY MOTHER,
NOT WITH LILA ALONG
FOR THE RIDE.
BUT I CAN PREPARE FOR THE DAY
WHEN I DO.
WHERE ARE YOU OFF TO
SO EARLY?
UM, GETTING OUT OF TOWN
FOR THE NIGHT.
DON'T WAIT UP FOR ME.
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE WEEK?
THOUGHT I'D, YOU KNOW,
TAKE THE MINIVAN OUT
ON THE OPEN ROAD.
WHO ARE YOU?
GOOD NEWS IS YOU GOT THE PLACE
TO YOURSELF
IF YOU WANT TO TIE UP
GABRIEL AGAIN.
YEAH, THAT ONE NEVER
FUCKING GETS OLD.
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET BACK.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT CORAL COVE.
WHAT ABOUT CORAL COVE?
THE ALGAE ON THE ROCKS
SENT US THERE.
IF I WERE YOU, I WOULD SERIOUSLY
CONSIDER MOVING YOUR BOAT.
SECURITY OUT THERE
SUCKS ASS.
THAT'S KIND OF THE POINT.
THIS LITTLE GREEN ALGAE
MAY AS WELL BE KRYPTONITE.
IF IT'S EVER TRACED BACK TO ME,
I'LL BE HELPLESS.
IS THIS A RENTAL?
NOPE, SHE'S ALL MINE.
SO YOUR MINIVAN'S A SHE,
IS SHE?
YOUR GIRLFRIEND
MUST BE JEALOUS.
IS SHE COOL
WITH YOU DOING THIS?
I DIDN'T TELL HER.
RITA'S MOM FOUND OUT
I'M IN RECOVERY.
SHE WANTS ME TO LEAVE RITA
AND THE KIDS.
SHE COULD BE RIGHT.
I CAN'T ABANDON THEM.
SO, WHAT ABOUT WHAT
YOU'RE GONNA SAY TO THIS GUY
WHEN YOU GET THERE?
I'M SURE I'LL THINK
OF SOMETHING.
WHY DON'T YOU PRACTICE
ON ME?
I'D...RATHER NOT.
JUST TRY.
OUT LOUD.
I FEEL LIKE...
...YOU STOLE MY LIFE.
AND?
I'M NOT THE PERSON
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE.
IT'S LIKE I'M HOLLOW.
THAT'S GOOD.
GO ON.
I HIDE IN PLAIN SIGHT...
...UNABLE TO REACH OUT
TO PEOPLE...
CLOSE TO ME.
I'M AFRAID...
...I'LL HURT THEM.
LIKE I'VE HURT
SO MANY OTHERS.
THIS IS WHAT
HE MADE ME BECOME.
THEN THAT'S WHAT
YOU SHOULD TELL HIM.
WHAT DO YOU REMEMBER MOST
ABOUT YOUR MOTHER?
SHE HAD LONG HAIR.
SOFT...
...LIKE HER HANDS.
THAT'S ALL.
YUP...
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES.
YOU LIVE FOR THIS
AND YOU KNOW IT.
WE COULD ALWAYS
GET IN THE CAR
AND PASS THE TIME
LIKE WE USED TO.
[ Laughing ] NO.
NO.
I'M NOT GOING DOWN
THAT ROAD AGAIN.
Man: Code 1, suspect's vehicle
spotted -- one on board.
Headed your way.
COPY THAT.
[ RADIO BEEPS ]
I'LL TAKE LEAD.
I GOT IT.
WE DON'T WANT THIS GUY
TO DO ANYTHING STUPID
IN A CROWD OF PEOPLE.
GODDAMN, THAT'S WHAT YOU OUT
HERE FOR -- TO BABYSIT ME?
I'M OUT HERE BECAUSE
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
HOW MANY FUCKING WAYS
TO SUNDAY
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU
THAT I'M FINE, MARIA?
YEAH, AND THAT'S WHAT
WORRIES ME.
YOU'RE FINE
WITH KILLING TWO MEN?
YOU'RE FINE?
BEEN MORE THAN TWO.
THIS ISN'T THE ARMY, JAMES.
THIS IS MY DEPARTMENT.
I NEED TO KNOW THAT YOU ARE FIT
FOR DUTY.
THAT'S MY JOB
AS A LIEUTENANT!
THAT'S ALL YOU CARE ABOUT
IS YOUR JOB,
EVEN IF IT MEANT DOING
PASCAL'S MAN TO GET IT BACK.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
ABOUT BERTRAND?
I DIDN'T FOR SURE
UNTIL JUST NOW.
I KNOW YOU, MARIA.
WE RODE TOGETHER FOR TWO YEARS.
WHEN YOU WANT SOMETHING,
YOU GET IT.
PASCAL WAS IN YOUR WAY.
WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT THIS.
YOU ALL UP
IN EVERYBODY ELSE'S SHIT
AS LONG AS IT AIN'T YOURS.
THERE'S ALVARO.
WAIT UNTIL HE GETS OUT
OF THE CAR.
HOW LONG YOU GONNA KEEP
WIPING MY ASS?
UNTIL I SEE
MY OLD PARTNER AGAIN.
ON MY GO.
ON THE GROUND,
MOTHERFUCKER!
HANDS WHERE
I CAN SEE, ALVARO!
Lila: REMEMBER,
THIS IS ABOUT YOU.
NOT ABOUT HIM.
IT'S ALL RIGHT
IF WE GET THERE
AND YOU CAN'T GO THROUGH
WITH THIS.
I KNOW.
'CAUSE WE CAN COME BACK
ANOTHER TIME.
NO.
I WANT TO MEET HIM TONIGHT.
THIS ISN'T ART.
THIS IS COTTAGE PORN.
THAT'S RITA.
SAY NO MORE.
I NEED TO TAKE A SHOWER ANYWAY.
DON'T LEAVE
WITHOUT SAYING GOODBYE.
HI.
Rita: Hey.
It's so good
to hear your voice.
I was starting
to get worried.
YOU STILL ON THE ROAD?
No, I just got in.
OH. WELL,
YOU SAID YOU'D CALL.
WHERE ARE YOU?
I DECIDED TO LOOK UP SOMEONE
FROM MY PAST.
THAT'S WHAT
SUDDENLY CAME UP?
Yep.
Dexter, what's going on?
WELL, AFTER THIS MORNING,
I FIGURED IT'D BE BETTER
IF I KEPT MY DISTANCE.
WHAT -- WHAT HAPPENED
THIS MORNING?
LET'S JUST SAY YOUR MOM ISN'T
A BIG FAN OF MEN IN RECOVERY.
OH, SHIT.
Look, this means
nothing, okay?
I'm gonna take care
of this.
Now, when are you
coming back?
UH, TOMORROW MORNING.
PROMISE ME YOU'LL STOP
BY THE HOUSE FIRST THING?
SURE.
I'm so sorry about this,
Dexter.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
OKAY.
WHY ARE YOU NOT
IN THE SHOWER?
I KNOW. I'M JUST CHECKING
SOME E-MAILS.
WE HAVE TO BE AT THE RESTAURANT
IN HALF AN HOUR.
SURE YOU DON'T WANT
TO JOIN ME?
YOU STINK.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THOUGHT YOU
LIKED IT DIRTY.
"ICE PRINCESS"?
FUCK.
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
DEB, WHAT DID I DO?
YOU LIED TO ME!
YOU'RE A WRITER!
I-I'M TRYING TO BE, YEAH!
I SAW ALL OF THOSE E-MAILS
YOU SENT TO THOSE PUBLISHERS --
THE ICE PRINCESS!
OH, YOU WENT THROUGH
MY E-MAIL!
ALL YOU WANTED WAS TO GET CLOSE
ENOUGH TO ME
SO YOU COULD SELL A BOOK ABOUT
ME AND THE ICE-TRUCK KILLER!
THAT'S CRAZY, DEB.
THOSE LETTERS --
FUCK YOU!
DEB!
WHAT CAN I DO YOU FOR?
DRINK?
BEER.
WHATEVER'S ON TAP.
UNA FR?, COMING UP.
WAY TO DITCH ME.
You were in the shower.
SO, ARE YOU THERE?
DO YOU SEE HIM?
HE'S STARING AT ME.
YOU GONNA SAY SOMETHING?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GONNA DO YET.
I SHOULD GO.
WELL, CALL ME WHEN YOU FIGURE
IT OUT. ALL RIGHT?
THREE BUCKS.
Rita:
YOU HAD NO RIGHT!
HE'S AN ADDICT, RITA.
HE IS NO GOOD FOR YOU!
HE'S ALREADY GOT YOU
SMOKING AGAIN.
YOU TURNED YOUR BACK ON ME
AND YOUR GRANDCHILDREN.
THAT WAS NOT MY FAULT.
I TRIED TO WARN YOU
ABOUT PAUL,
BUT YOU RAN AWAY
WITH HIM ANYWAY.
I WASN'T RUNNING AWAY
WITH PAUL.
I WAS RUNNING AWAY
FROM YOU.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW MUCH IT HURTS ME
TO SEE YOU MAKE
THE SAME MISTAKES AGAIN?
I'VE HAD MY FAIR SHARE
OF MISTAKES.
AND GUESS WHAT --
YOU WERE RIGHT ABOUT PAUL.
HE WAS A TERRIBLE MAN.
BUT FOR THE FIRST TIME,
I FEEL SAFE AND LOVED,
AND THAT'S BECAUSE
OF DEXTER.
I CAN'T TALK TO YOU
WHEN YOU'RE LIKE THIS.
I'M GOING TO BED.
THIS IS MY LIFE, MOTHER.
IF YOU CAN'T BE HAPPY
FOR ME,
THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T
BE HERE.
IF YOU WANT TO ABANDON ME
AND THE KIDS AGAIN, FINE.
THAT'S YOUR CHOICE.
BUT DEXTER IS NOT
GOING ANYWHERE.
LAST CALL
WAS 30 MINUTES AGO.
YOU HEAR ME?
I NEED YOU TO FINISH
THAT UP.
SORRY.
I'M AVOIDING GOING BACK
TO MY MOTEL ROOM.
I'M VISITING FROM MIAMI.
YOU EVER BEEN THERE?
I CAN'T SAY THAT I HAVE.
HOW LONG YOU LIVED
IN NAPLES?
OH, A FEW YEARS NOW.
YOU LIKE IT?
ALL RIGHT, CO?.
GO.
OKAY.
THIS IS GONNA BE AWKWARD.
I NEED TO TELL YOU
HOW I FEEL.
NO, WHAT YOU NEED TO DO
IS LEAVE
BECAUSE YOU BEEN EYEBALLING ME
ALL NIGHT.
YOU REALLY
SHOULDN'T DO THAT.
I SAID GET OUT OF MY BAR.
OKAY. JUST LET ME SAY WHAT
I NEED TO SAY, AND I'LL GO.
YOU STOLE MY LIFE.
[ Chuckling ]
WHAT THE FUCK?
YOU ARE REALLY BEGINNING
TO PISS ME OFF.
I'M NOT THE PERSON
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
BECAUSE YOU TOOK SOMEONE
FROM ME.
I WILL BEAT
YOUR FUCKING HEAD IN
IF YOU DON'T WALK OUT THAT DOOR
RIGHT NOW!
I TRIED LILA'S WAY.
1973!
AAH! AAH!
AAH.
THE PORT OF MIAMI!
A SHIPPING CONTAINER!
A CHAIN SAW!
LAURA MOSER!
YOU REMEMBER NOW?
PUTA MADRE.
YOU GOT ME CONFUSED
WITH SOMEONE ELSE!
AAH!
I KNOW EXACTLY WHO YOU ARE!
YOU MADE ME INTO WHAT I AM!
OKAY! I-I KILLED HER.
I HAD TO!
DID YOU?
DID YOU HAVE TO?
DID YOU HAVE TO SAW HER
INTO LITTLE PIECES?!
DID YOU HAVE TO LEAVE
TWO LITTLE BOYS
SOAKING IN A POOL
OF THEIR MOTHER'S BLOOD?
ESTRADA WOULD HAVE KILLED ME
IF I DIDN'T.
YOU SLAUGHTERED HER
LIKE AN ANIMAL
BECAUSE SHE STOLE
HIS PRECIOUS COCAINE.
NO. WE FOUND OUT SHE WAS
A SNITCH FOR A COP.
SHE WAS FUCKING HIM.
WHICH COP?
I DIDN'T KNOW HIS NAME.
I FOLLOWED THEM TO --
TO A PARK.
MY MOTHER AND HARRY --
THAT'S WHAT GOT HER KILLED?
I'M NOT DONE WITH YOU YET.
ISN'T THIS WHAT HEROES DO --
AVENGE LOST LOVED ONES?
WHAT?
EVERYTHING OKAY?
Dexter, what's wrong?
I THOUGHT I COULD RESIST.
JESUS...ARE YOU USING?
NO, BUT I'M ABOUT TO.
Tell me where you are
and I'll get in a taxi
and I'll come get you.
I HAVE TO DO THIS.
NO, YOU DON'T!
JUST TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE.
YOU'LL BE TOO LATE.
DON'T YOU BLOODY DO THIS.
YOU ARE STRONGER THAN THAT.
I'M NOT!
Yes, you fucking are.
You've come this far.
IF YOU TURN BACK NOW,
YOU'LL GO RIGHT BACK
TO THE WAY YOU WERE --
hollow, angry,
ALONE.
I will get you through this.
I swear.
JUST COME BACK TO ME.
OKAY?
DEXTER?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
IT'S OKAY.
I DIDN'T...
Shh. IT'S OKAY.
I DON'T CARE
WHAT YOU DID.
IT'S OKAY.
BABY.
WHAT ARE YOU STILL
DOING HERE?
MAKING SURE OUR MARINA
SURVEILLANCE IS IN PLACE.
YOU FORGET SOMETHING?
I'M WORKING UP
RENTAL LOGS...
...ON THE OTHER
TWO MARINAS.
YOU DON'T GIVE UP,
DO YOU?
I'M WIDE AWAKE ANYWAY.
DEXTER'S OUT OF TOWN.
I DON'T REALLY SLEEP
WHEN I'M THERE BY MYSELF.
WHAT ABOUT
THE NEW BOYFRIEND?
WE SORT OF BROKE UP.
WELL,
I BROKE UP WITH HIM.
GUESS YOU WON'T BE NEEDING
THIS, THEN.
WHAT'S THAT?
BACKGROUND CHECK.
YOU SAID YOU SERE SNOOPING.
JUST THOUGHT I'D HELP.
YOU RAN A BACKGROUND CHECK
ON MY BOYFRIEND?
WHAT'S IT SAY?
GABRIEL'S CLEAN --
WELL, EXCEPT FOR THOSE
PARKING TICKETS.
JUST BECAUSE HE'S NOT
A CRIMINAL
DOESN'T MEAN HE'S NOT
AN ASSHOLE.
I WENT THROUGH HIS E-MAIL.
I KNOW,
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
I MEAN...HE WAS USING ME
TO SHOP AROUND A BOOK
ABOUT THE ICE-TRUCK KILLER.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT KIND OF WRITER
GABRIEL IS?
CHILDREN'S BOOKS?
"THE ICE PRINCESS"
IS A CHILDREN'S BOOK.
HOW COULD I BE
SO FUCKING STUPID?
WHEN MY WIFE MET ME,
SHE WAS CONVINCED I WAS A SPY.
CONNIE DIDN'T KNOW IT,
BUT SHE WAS ACTUALLY RIGHT.
YOU RAN A BACKGROUND CHECK
ON HER?
[ CHUCKLES ]
NO NEED.
MUST BE NICE...
TO JUST KNOW LIKE THAT.
SHE DIED...TWO YEARS AGO.
CANCER.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S HOW I LOST MY MOM.
I SHOULD GO.
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
THAT BOYFRIEND OF YOURS --
DID HE EVER GIVE YOU A REASON
NOT TO TRUST HIM?
NO.
BUT I DON'T THINK
IT MATTERS.
I MEAN,
I WENT INSANE ON HIM.
HE'LL NEVER FORGIVE ME.
ANY BROKEN BONES INVOLVED?
FACIAL CONTUSIONS?
NO.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
HOW I GOT INTO THE PROGRAM?
I'D USED FOR YEARS --
BINGE, CRASH.
THOUGHT I HAD IT
UNDER CONTROL.
THEN I MET MARCO.
WHAT A SHIT.
THOUGHT HE WAS MY BOYFRIEND,
BUT HE TURNED OUT
TO BE MY DEALER.
BASTARD HAD ME SO STRUNG OUT
BY THE TIME HE LEFT,
NOTHING MATTERED.
NOTHING WAS LEFT...
...BUT RAGE.
ONE NIGHT...
I WAS SO FUCKED UP --
GOD.
I WENT TO HIS HOUSE,
AND I BURNED IT TO THE GROUND.
WHAT I DIDN'T KNOW WAS THAT
MARCO WAS PASSED OUT INSIDE.
THEY BLAMED THE FIRE
ON HIS DRUGS.
BUT IT WAS ME.
HE DIED BECAUSE OF ME.
THAT NIGHT,
I WENT TO MY FIRST MEETING.
SEEING THAT SIDE OF MYSELF
WAS TERRIFYING.
THAT I COULD POSSIBLY DO THAT
TO ANOTHER PERSON.
DID HE DESERVE IT?
YES.
THEN YOU DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING WRONG.
HEY, YOU.
I WASN'T EXPECTING YOU
THIS EARLY.
I DIDN'T HIT ANY TRAFFIC.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME
FOR BREAKFAST.
WHERE'S YOUR MOM?
OH, I DOUBT SHE'LL BE
JOINING US.
SHE'S BEEN IN HER ROOM
ALL MORNING.
MY GUESS IS SHE'S PACKING.
MAYBE I SHOULD GO.
NO.
NO, YOU'RE STAYING
RIGHT HERE
BECAUSE YOU'RE A PART
OF THIS FAMILY.
ARE YOU SURE?
I'VE PUT YOU THROUGH
SO MUCH LATELY.
I'M HERE FOR YOU, DEXTER...
NO MATTER WHAT.
WHAT'S THIS?
THE PATCH.
I HAVE SOME QUITTING
OF MY OWN TO DO.
SIT.
IS THAT ANYTHING
IMPORTANT?
NOPE.
MORNING.
MORNING, DEXTER.
HI...GAIL.
SO, RITA ASSURES ME THAT YOU ARE
COMMITTED TO GETTING BETTER.
I AM.
THEN I WANT TO BE HERE
TO HELP.
IN FACT, I'VE DECIDED
TO STAY IN MIAMI.
I E-MAILED THE SCHOOL BOARD
MY LETTER OF RESIGNATION
THIS MORNING.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR HOUSE?
I'LL PUT IT ON THE MARKET.
SWEETIE, I THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT YOU SAID LAST NIGHT.
I HAVEN'T BEEN HERE FOR YOU,
AND I WANT TO CHANGE THAT.
YOU KNOW, MY SISTER'S LOOKING
FOR A NEW APARTMENT.
I'M SURE WE CAN HELP YOU
FIND ONE, TOO.
WELL, DON'T BE SILLY.
I'LL BE LIVING HERE.
DEXTER, BE A DEAR AND PASS ME
THE CREAM, PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
HARRY TAUGHT ME TO LIE
AND KEEP MY DARKEST SECRETS
FROM THOSE AROUND ME...
WHICH IS WHY I NEED
TO MAKE SURE
THERE'S NOT A TRACE
OF BLOOD LEFT ON MY BOAT.
HE ALSO TAUGHT ME
NOT TO RUSH TO JUDGMENT.
THINGS AREN'T ALWAYS
WHAT THEY APPEAR TO BE...
...INCLUDING HARRY.
AND WHAT ABOUT ME?
AM I THE TWISTED
BAY HARBOR BUTCHER...
OR THE VALIANT DARK DEFENDER?
ONLY TIME WILL TELL.
FUNNY THING IS I'VE MET SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T CARE WHAT I AM.
I SUPPOSE EVERY HERO
NEEDS A SIDEKICK...
EVERY VILLAIN,
A PARTNER IN CRIME.
ALL MY RELATIONSHIPS HAVE BEEN
BUILT ON NOT KNOWING.
BUT THAT MAY BE CHANGING.
IMAGINE THAT --
A LIFE WITH NO MORE SECRETS.
??????
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
????