Previously on "Dexter"...
we have to catch them
in the act at the shipyard.
He's gonna find out,
and then he's gonna kill me.
Harry knew my mother.
Why would rita print out
narcotics anonymous literature
If paul's dead?
Because recently
i entered the program.
How many fucking ways
to sunday
Do i have to tell you
that i'm fine, maria?
This is my department.
I need to know that you are fit
for duty.
That's my job
as a lieutenant!
I always stop and eat lunch
at 1:00.
You'll learn that about me.
Why don't you sit down?
You're very fidgety.
Anyone ever tell you that?
My father.
You applying for the job?
Well,
you said you'd call.
Where are you,
and when are you coming back?
Uh, tomorrow morning.
Promise me you'll stop
by the house first thing.
I'll see you soon.
Is she cool with you doing this? I didn't tell her.
I don't care
what you did.
I'm no longer sure
who made me what i am.
Funny thing is i've met someone
who doesn't care.
I want to talk to you
about coral cove.
What about coral cove?
The algae on the rocks
sent us there.
If i were you, i would consider
moving your boat.
Security out there
sucks ass.
When i get back,
i need to hit the marina
And make sure there's
no blood traces on my boat.
This isn't
a commercial marina.
But i can see the upkeep
on this place is dismal.
That's why i'm going to order
24-Hour surveillance
On this marina
and the two others.
There's another shipment
coming in tomorrow.
Cocaine.
How much?
300 bricks,
give or take.
Can you get your hands
on some?
Harry, that wasn't part
of our agreement.
Look, laura,
we need hard evidence.
Otherwise, it's just your word
against estrada's.
I'll protect you.
I promise.
You better.
Meet me later?
Laura,
the tape's still rolling.
Very convincing.
What was that?
Laura,
the tape's still rolling.
Damn it.
My mother -
Confidential informant...
and mumbler.
Whatever sweet nothings
she had to whisper
I probably don't want to hear.
It seems that my foster father
And my biological mother
were having an affair.
It's bad enough
i can't shake the visual,
But the questions -
Did he blame himself
for her death?
Is that why he took me in?
Did he love her,
or was he just using her?
Was he using me?
I always thought harry's code
Was on-The-Spot
creative problem-Solving,
But maybe he planned for me
to settle the score all along.
It's times like this i wish
i really were a drug addict.
I had emotional problems
as a kid
Because of what happened
to my mother.
And harry tried to said
he was trying to help me,
But all we ever talked about
were his rules.
I spent so much time
Trying to live up
to his expectations
Because i thought he had
my best interests in mind.
If you're going
to come over this late,
The least you could do
is bring me a coffee.
Sorry.
Cappuccino -
Make a note of it.
Truth is, dex,
It doesn't really matter
why harry did what he did.
The result's the same.
You have an addiction.
Do you think harry
made me what i am?
Plenty of people
go through trauma
Without turning
to addiction.
Whatever harry taught you
led you down the wrong path.
But i've built everything
in my life
On what harry said
i was supposed to be.
My job, my girlfriend -
It's all what harry
told me i needed.
What do you think you need?
I have no idea.
Whatever's inside you
Is splattered all over
that paper
That i took from your lab.
Looks messy.
It probably is.
Look, dexter...
everyone has a moment
when they realize
That their value system is
different from their parents'.
Mine was in college,
But, hey, maybe you're
a late bloomer.
Lucky me.
Damn right, lucky you.
You get to have
a fresh start.
Whatever you thought,
whatever you did doesn't matter.
Now you get to figure out
who you are.
I went to lila for answers,
But now all i have
is more questions.
Who am i?
What do i need?
What do i want?
Coffee - I really want
a cup of coffee.
What up, half-Day?
Is there coffee left?
You're late.
I fell asleep
before you got home last night.
Were you at rita's?
You're welcome, ass.
Your brother
looks like shit.
Tell me about it.
I may be
out of line with this,
But did he
fall off the wagon?
What wagon?
The only wagon dexter's ever had
is a radio flyer.
Your brother's a junkie.
Isn't he?
Dexter?
Are you high?
He's never even smoked
a cigarette.
I'm glad you got
some new material, though,
'Cause "freak" and "psycho"
were getting kind of tired.
Agent lundy.
So, i hear a rumor
You're tracking all
our internet activity.
So, is it true?
'Cause i can explain
all that she-Male stuff.
I need my team outside
in five minutes.
That sounds important.
I just got a major break
in the investigation.
Patrol found some guy saying he
escaped the bay harbor butcher.
He claimed he was captured
a couple hours ago.
Well, that's a neat trick,
considering i was asleep -
At least trying to sleep.
This could be good news
for me.
Morgan.
Yes.
The other morgan.
I'd like you to join us,
if you can spare him.
That's fine with me.
Is there blood?
Not that i'm aware of, no.
But what about masuka?
Yeah, uh, i'm the lead
forensics investigator.
Masuka's lab work
is more pressing.
I need him to hold down the fort
at the station.
He totally saw
the she-Male stuff.
So, what do you say?
I'll buy you lunch after -
Pork sandwich, right?
Uh, yes. Sure.
Good.
I figured it was time to get
a fresh perspective on the case.
Rumor has it you have a knack
for attracting serial killers.
I hear the same about you.
Dexter also enjoys long walks
on the beach and foreign films.
Then we've got
a lot to talk about.
All right.
See you later.
He knocked me out.
Then when i woke up,
I was tied up
in that train car over there.
You said he used rope?
Dumb fuck.
I stretched it out enough
so i can get my legs free
And then busted out of there.
Ran across the road, almost got
hit by that guy in the car.
So, that's the alleged victim
of the bay harbor butcher.
But i've never seen him
before in my life.
Dex!
O'connor, singer...
make sure you take pictures
of those footprints.
Hey, dex.
Hey.
So, the victim says the butcher
held him in this train car.
Lundy wants you to search
for trace evidence.
Your spidey sense
tingling yet?
We'll see when i get inside.
Take your time in there.
We've never been this close
to this pendejo.
Closer than you think, amigo.
He may have borrowed
my pseudonym,
But this guy doesn't know
The first thing
about my techniques -
Amateur.
What makes you think
it was the butcher?
Well, he told me
That the bay harbor butcher's
gonna clean up miami.
He said, "you're gonna get
what you deserve. "
And what do you deserve,
mr. Henry?
Well, look...
the butcher kills criminals,
right?
I just got out of jail,
you know -
Six years for aggravated assault
and home invasion.
He kills murderers.
You didn't kill anyone,
did you?
All right, i gave this old guy
a heart attack.
It's not like i was doing it
on purpose, all right?
I- I used to hit, you know,
retirement homes, communities.
Snowbirds are easy targets.
And i don't do that anymore.
I did my time.
Your mother
must be so proud.
I want to check out
the train car with your brother.
Why don't you keep an eye
on our friend here
While we confirm
his story?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Killing tools left behind -
I'd never be this careless.
Whoever did this would
never pass harry's muster.
Then again,
neither would harry.
He lied about my past.
He cheated on my foster mother
with my biological mother.
Maybe lila's right. It's time
for a new set of standards.
If you were
the bay harbor butcher,
Would you use
a place like this?
Actually, yes.
Locationwise,
it's not a bad choice.
It's quiet, remote.
Could use an upgrade in
the lighting department, but...
so, you think
this is our guy?
Not exactly.
From what i understand,
The conditions in this space
don't support his m. O.
It's filthy,
for one thing.
Butcher's clean,
orderly...
...and some people
would say compulsive.
Really? You think
he's compulsive?
This doesn't fit, either.
A hatchet is sloppy.
The butcher uses precise
surgical instruments.
Well, he's not
that predictable.
Is he?
Mixes it up -
Different tools every time.
And never rope.
He uses duct tape
and plastic wrap.
Plastic wrap -
How can you tell?
Depression patterns
in the skin.
Maybe the butcher's
having an identity crisis.
It's entirely possible.
But not likely.
My guess is we're looking
for a vigilante
Inspired by
the butcher's principles.
Bet he never thought
he'd be a role model.
I bet you're right.
So, any new leads
on the real guy?
Not yet.
We're hoping the cameras
will turn something up.
Cameras?
In the marinas.
Put them in
a couple of days ago
To monitor
for suspicious activities.
Good news for all those cops
who keep boats at coral cove.
You've got one, too,
right?
Yeah. Yeah.
We've been needing a security
upgrade for a long time now.
Has lundy seen me on the tape?
Is that why he invited me
along today - To mess with me?
Hey.
I'm sorry if i was short
with you this morning.
You know i'm lost
without my morning coffee.
Whatever.
How was your playdate
with lundy? Did you bond?
You didn't tell me
They put up security cameras
at the marinas.
It's not like
they're doing us any good.
We have to update
the station's computer system
Before we can synch up with
lundy's high-Tech equipment.
So the cameras
aren't recording?
Well, they are, but nobody's
seen any of the footage.
Lundy said it should be fixed
by tonight.
Well, that's a relief.
Your mom told me
About your cultural presentation
at school.
Did your teacher assign you
a country yet?
Saudi arabia.
No. That's israel.
I won't tell the saudis
you said that.
Looks like cody's
enjoying himself.
Dexter's very patient
with him.
Dexter's a saint.
Where's astor?
Uh, she's by the water.
I want to say goodbye.
I got to go.
I was supposed to meet lila
10 minutes ago.
Who's lila?
His sponsor.
Really? A woman?
Yes, mom.
Dexter's sponsor
is a woman.
Is that a problem?
Is she attractive?
Mom -
I'm just curious.
Is she?
I have an idea.
Why don't you and lila
have dinner with us?
Well, that's very kind of you,
gail, but, um...
i think it would be really nice
if we got to know the woman
You've been spending
so much time with.
Look, mom,
they're doing step work.
But they have to eat,
right?
Oh, here. Let me help.
Thank you.
Mm-Hmm.
So lovely of you
to have me over.
Now i can put names
to faces.
Dexter talks about you
all the time.
Good things, i hope.
Dexter never says a bad word
about anyone.
Tell me, lila.
What exactly
are you recovering from?
I'm a meth addict -
Sober five years.
I don't know much
about meth.
Rita's ex-Husband
shot heroin.
Like dexter.
Guess we know your type,
don't we?
Just can't seem to help myself.
Huh.
You have nothing to worry
about... with dexter, i mean.
I'm sitting right here.
I didn't mean to imply -
No.
I completely understand.
Rita's your little baby.
You have every right
to be concerned.
But if i can reassure you,
Dexter's doing
incredibly well.
Well,
i'm happy to hear that.
And i'm sure it's got everything
to do with the two of you.
From what he tells me,
you're very supportive.
Dexter's lucky to have you.
Well... that's very sweet
of you to say.
So, lila, tell us more
about yourself.
Um, dexter tells me
you're an artist.
Yeah, she does amazing things
with a blowtorch.
What's it called?
Uh, talent.
But i'm, uh... i'm not
the only artist at the table.
Dexter?
Since when?
It's not really art.
She's talking
about a blood-Spatter pattern
She took from work.
What kind of career choice
is blood spatter, exactly?
He helps
catch criminals, mother.
And it makes
perfect sense, really -
What with dexter's mother
and everything.
You know...
she's... dead.
Forgot the bread.
Dinner was fantastic,
rita.
And this dessert -
Wow.
I never thought
i'd say this,
But i kind of like her.
Yeah, me too.
She's really helping me.
I wish she didn't have
to help you tonight.
Why?
What are you thinking?
Mmm, my mom
could watch the kids.
I have to swing by
the office tonight.
I need to take care
of something really important.
Oh, i mean, can't it wait
till morning?
I promise
we'll go straight to bed.
You're very convincing,
But it needs
to get done tonight.
Just give me an hour,
okay?
Meet you
back at my place?
Okay.
I still think it's funny
you write children's books.
Yeah, a big, tough guy
like me
Should be doing something manly,
huh, like wrangling cattle.
I don't even know
any kids' books.
My dad told me cop stories
before bed.
It was really the only alone
time i ever got with him.
You okay?
Yeah.
Sorry -
Just an annoying day at work.
You know that fbi guy
i was talking about?
I was really starting to feel
like i was his go-To girl,
But...
he realized dexter
is the superior morgan.
I should be used to it,
you know?
It was like that
with my dad, work.
I guess i just hoped with lundy
it would be different.
Why?
I don't know.
I respect him.
He's great at his job,
supersmart,
And, like, funny,
but in this really dry way
Where he doesn't even
know it.
You love him.
What?
No.
You do. You totally have a crush on grundy. Lundy.
Oh, now you're getting touchy
about it.
I don't have
a crush on him.
He's like my dad,
except i spent my whole life
Trying to get my dad
to notice me,
And he actually pays attention
to what i have to say.
And grundy loves you.
Oh, fuck off.
Lundy's good -
Double-Locked...
and a bit beyond my expertise.
I could try to crack it open,
But in my own station...
too risky.
I can do this more often now
that my mom's in town.
I feel
like we're being bad.
Bad - Bad is good.
Oh, let the machine
get it.
Hey, dex,
just calling to check in -
Thought we could do
the debriefing on dinner.
I thought it went well,
don't you?
Mmm. I'd say so.
Rita's sweet -
Very martha stewart.
I love martha stewart.
God, her mum -
She's got quite the rod
up her ass, doesn't she?
By the way, i am such a twat.
I can't believe i almost
slipped up about your mum.
Mind you,
it could have been worse.
I could have spilled the beans
about our road trip.
Don't you dare!
Can you imagine rita's face
if i told her
That you and i had spent
the night together in a hotel?
Anyway...
you and lila stayed
in a hotel together?
We had adjoining rooms.
Adjoining rooms? Right.
God,
i am such an idiot.
I can't believe i defended you
to my mother
While you were off
sleeping with another woman.
Rita, wait.
I thought
you were different than paul,
But you're the same.
You know what?
Actually, you're worse.
You made me trust you.
Rita, please,
will you just let me explain?
I've had it!
I have been patient
and understanding,
But there's only
so much i can take.
You're a liar and a cheat,
and i am through.
It's over, dexter.
Tracy jenkins was given
the liver
Of a 9-Year-Old
accident victim...
hi, honey.
I thought you were spending
the night at dexter's.
We had a fight.
I think we broke up.
What?
Oh. Shh.
Yesterday i was so hopeful -
A new me, a new life.
But a life without rita
seems strange.
What in the name of fuck
are you doing up so early?
I got to get
to the station.
Are you okay?
You seem weird -
Weirder than usual.
Rita broke up with me
last night.
Seriously?
What happened?
It's a long story.
I've got time.
Yeah... but i don't.
Cliff notes.
She thinks
i did something bad,
But i didn't.
Did you tell her that?
I tried, but she dumped me
Before i had
a chance to explain.
She said, "it's over,"
and left.
Well,
did you go after her?
Was i supposed to?
You're such a guy.
When i get pissed, i say stuff
i don't mean all the time -
"I hate you,"
"I faked it,"
"You're hung like a grape. "
You lost me.
When rita said, "it's over,"
I'm sure she didn't
actually mean it's over.
Stop being a douche bag
and go fight for her.
She's fucking perfect.
I know.
Hello?
Oh, hey.
Sure, i'll be right there.
Yeah. I'll tell him.
Bye.
Who's that, gabriel?
No, lundy.
He's holding a meeting
at the station
About the bay harbor case.
He specifically requested
that you be there.
I missed my window.
He's already seen the footage.
Me? Why?
Because you're
his new butt buddy.
You gonna be okay?
Check back with me later.
The show has already started,
But have they seen
the feature presentation -
"Bane of
the bay harbor butcher,"
Starring dexter morgan
as himself?
So, it's all synched up?
Yep, you can watch
streaming video of the marina
Right now if you want to.
Yeah. Maybe you'll get to see
some pontoon poon.
Did you... need something?
That's not my marina... yet.
I'll be making
my on-Screen debut soon enough.
I've got to figure out a way
to get to those video files.
The media frenzy
about the bay harbor butcher
Has come back to bite us -
Big surprise.
Now we've got a wannabe
vigilante out there
Who liked the butcher's style
and thought,
"Hey, i should try this
at home. "
He attacked this man -
John henry,
Ex-Convict,
preyed on the elderly.
It gets better.
I have already received
reports of ads
On craigslist
and coffee-Shop bulletin boards
Requesting the services
of the butcher.
People think they've found
their own personal batman.
This is not good news.
If this kind of thing
catches on,
We're looking at an epidemic.
Kind of like herpes.
Fucking-A, masuka,
i'm trying to listen.
One in four, morgan -
One in four.
Vigilante justice is
domestic terrorism.
And terrorism prevention
is the fbi's top priority.
I have done my best
to be diplomatic,
But if we lose one life
to a vigilante,
I will pull this case
from miami metro
And hand it over
in full to the bureau.
That's a promise.
That's a disaster.
It'd be raining feds in miami.
So, if we want to keep
the investigation here,
We need to nip this
in the bud,
Make an example
of our would-Be vigilante.
The last thing we need is
a bunch of weekend warriors -
I think
i found a suspect.
Could you?
Ken olson.
Olson's mother
was hurt badly
In a home-Invasion robbery.
Guess who hurt her.
Oh, please tell me john henry,
our train-Car victim.
I think olson attacked him
for revenge.
Any evidence?
Only circumstantial.
Can you get him in here
for questioning?
Can't find him.
Okay. Leak this to some
of your media contacts.
Let's beat this guy
out of the bushes.
Nice work, detective.
Let's get moving.
I need hard evidence on this
olson character, and fast.
And if you can find the guy,
even better.
The full force of the fbi -
That's the last thing i need.
I've got to make sure lundy
gets his man...
after i figure out a way
to erase the marina files
And make up
with my girlfriend.
And then maybe i'll tackle
world hunger
Because things
can't really get much worse.
There's another shipment
coming in tomorrow.
Cocaine.
How much?
300 bricks,
give or take.
Turn it off.
That wasn't part
of our agreement, harry.
I said turn it off.
I heard what you said.
I just don't take orders
from you.
Is there a reason you're
in my lab, sergeant doakes?
Is there a reason
you're listening to tapes
As old as you are,
morgan?
I had a little talk
with your sister.
It turns out she didn't know
you were in program.
Anonymous, sergeant.
How long did you say
you been clean?
Actually, i didn't, because it's
none of your goddamn business.
So, if i were to take
a hair from your desk
And run it for drugs,
It would come back
positive, right?
Because why would someone
Pretend to be an addict
if he's not...
unless he's got something
A hell of a lot worse
to hide?
Back...
the fuck...
off.
You want to hit me?
Go for it.
I've been waiting for a chance
to take your ass out.
I know how you feel,
sergeant.
I want to file a formal
complaint against doakes.
Jesus, dexter,
the two of you -
He crossed the line,
lieutenant.
He broke into my lab.
He went through my personal
things. He threatened me.
He's probably gonna start
tailing me again.
Sergeant doakes tailed you?
For weeks, maybe longer.
Okay, you have every right
to file a complaint,
But before you do that,
I'd like the chance
to talk to james myself.
He's really not much
of a talker.
I'm asking you, as a personal
favor to me, to hold off.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Okay, in the meantime,
i strongly encourage you
To take a break
for a couple of hours.
Just go somewhere.
Cool off.
No.
Excuse me?
I need to be here,
lieutenant.
This is really not a good time
for me to leave.
It isn't a suggestion, dexter.
It's an order.
Clear the station.
Clear your head.
I don't want to see you here
until after lunch.
Understood?
Blimey, look at you.
You want to tell me
what's going on?
What's going on?
Being the new me sucks.
I'm about to be found out
at work for what i am -
For what i really am.
And i can't do anything
to stop it
Because i got kicked
out of the office to cool off.
Well, that seems to be
going well for you.
Add to that the fact
that rita heard your message
And dumped me last night.
I tried to explain to her
that nothing happened,
But she wouldn't listen
to me.
Nobody fucking listens
Listen, you need
to calm down, okay?
Last time i saw you like this,
you came back covered in blood.
So?
You're the one who said i'm
supposed to feel my feelings.
Well, now i'm telling you
to get them under control.
You don't understand.
Why don't you make me?
Which step was that?
The naughty one.
What are you thinking?
Absolutely nothing.
I guess we found a way to quiet
the voices in your head.
I guess so.
How do you feel?
Much better, actually.
I guess i must be
a good sponsor after all.
Definitely.
And where are you
off to?
I still have that thing at work
to deal with.
Well, come back tomorrow.
I promise you
some serious recovery.
Hello?
Dexter, hey.
You at work?
Uh, i will be soon.
I was just taking a break.
What's going on?
I'd really like
to get together and talk.
I don't like our last
conversation ended.
Me neither.
You said you wanted
to explain,
And i owe it to you
to hear you out.
I owe it to us.
Oh.
Wow, okay.
So, can you come over
after work?
Sure.
Great.
Apparently my new life
involves a love triangle.
I'm that guy.
The voices are back -
Excellent.
James!
You were tailing dexter?
What the hell
were you thinking?
If you wanted to have lunch,
you could have asked.
If dexter files a complaint,
You will be kicked
off the force, end of story.
There's a reason he hasn't
reported me until now.
He's hiding something, maria.
I can feel it.
Is this another one
of your conspiracy theories?
It's instinct and a hell
of a lot of experience.
I've spent years looking
the enemy in the face,
And i'm telling you
morgan is dangerous.
Your instincts haven't been
that great these days, james.
Two shootings
in the last six months,
Stalking
a police employee -
Listen to me.
Morgan lied
about the ice-Truck killer.
That crack pipe knew
way more than he ever told us.
He was trying
to protect his sister.
You of all people
should understand that.
I followed him
to an n. A. Meeting.
That asshole
lied about that, too.
You're obsessed.
I'm not.
You are,
and i need you to see it...
as your boss
and as your friend.
We've been
through this before,
And last time it cost you
our relationship.
This time it's gonna get you
kicked off the force or worse.
I'll take my chances.
Let it go.
I mean it.
Leave dexter alone.
The batista suspect
come in yet -
The wannabe vigilante?
Olson just came in -
Saw himself on the 3:00 news
And showed up
with his lawyer.
I hope we nail his ass
to the wall.
I love it
when you talk dirty.
Morgan.
Right here.
Oh, the other morgan.
I didn't know
you were a smoker. Hmm.
Have you seen
dexter morgan?
Oh, he's on a break.
Why?
Detective batista's got
a suspect in interview room one.
We think
he's the would-Be vigilante
Who attacked
our train-Car victim.
I need morgan to take
some scrapings for evidence.
You want to use
dexter again?
Isn't masuka
on your task force?
Yes, he is.
So, mr. Olson,
The man who assaulted your mom
was attacked yesterday.
Did you know that?
Nope.
Can't say
i'm upset, though -
Son of a bitch
almost killed my mom.
My client's emotional,
detective.
I'm sure he's not trying
to say he's -
Any idea
who might have done it?
I don't know.
Maybe it was the butcher.
If you ask me,
a guy like that
Should be running the police
force, not hiding from it.
Is this a lion
or a hippo?
I think it's a lion.
Tastes like a hippo.
Animal cracker?
No, thank you.
What do you do for a living,
mr. Olson?
I just lost my job.
That's too bad.
I see that you have
a minor assault record
And no alibi
for yesterday morning.
I'm sure my client didn't
realize he needed one.
Do you have a girlfriend,
mr. Olson?
She just broke up
with me.
Why, you interested?
Just curious.
Now, this is a lion.
All right, let me
keep this all straight.
No job, no relationship.
You got guns
and a minor assault record.
And i voted for george bush
both times.
I'm sorry, detective,
were you getting at something?
What he's getting at,
mr. Novik,
Is that your client
fits the four-Point profile
Of someone who'd commit
a vigilante offense.
I think you're
a ticking time bomb.
You ask me,
you just needed a reason
To take the law
into your own hands.
And the butcher
was the perfect excuse.
You don't know me.
We know
you attacked john henry.
You need proof to make those
kinds of accusations, detective.
You heard the man, detective.
We've got work to do.
Make yourself comfortable,
mr. Olson.
We're just getting started
with you.
That's my marina.
And in less than 30 minutes,
i'll be on that screen.
I need to take care of this,
and fast.
I'm out of time.
I need an idea, a sign,
anything.
What would the old dexter do?
Definitely not that.
No security cameras.
Apparently the new dexter's
stuck in high school.
Maybe i am a late bloomer.
A fire drill?
Are you kidding?
We have work to do.
It's probably one of those kids
in the bullpen.
It's something
i would have done.
Well, at least
it stopped raining.
All clear. Everybody out.
All clear! Everybody out!
Respect the vest.
Don't make me take out my hose.
Like it never happened.
If only the rest of life
were so easy to figure out.
Hey, where you headed?
I figured you'd be first in line
to check out the firemen.
I have to arrange
protective custody
For that piece-Of-Shit
train-Car victim.
Why?
Because we have nothing
on olson -
Not even enough to get a warrant
to search his place.
Is that olson's file?
If we don't
get something soon,
Lundy's gonna have
to let him go,
Which means olson's
gonna kill again,
Which means we lose the bay
harbor butcher case to the fbi,
Which means we're all fucked.
Some more than others.
No shit.
Till lundy showed up,
I just felt like the dipshit who
slept with the ice-Truck killer.
If he pulls the plug, i go back
to being the resident retard.
Chin up,
little sister -
These things have a way
of working themselves out.
I just have to find
a piece of evidence
To make sure lundy
catches olson fair and square.
Looks like i have a fan club,
membership of one.
Why you so interested
in the bay harbor butcher?
Who the fuck are you?
Holy shit, you're him,
aren't you?
Stop. Stop.
Don't kill me. Don't kill me.
I'm like you.
I take out criminals.
You mean you try...
pitifully.
No, that was
just the last one.
He got away.
I should have never
made it personal.
You've killed others?
That's what i'm trying
to tell you.
First was a drug dealer -
I ran him down with my car.
It felt -
It felt fucking great,
Even better than the free stash
i got off him.
And then this guy at work
Found out
i was fucking his wife.
He started to beat on her,
So i pushed him
down a stairwell.
The cops thought it was
an accident, but it was me.
See, you can't kill me.
I wasn't going to...
until now.
This is what the kill room
should look like -
The inside
of a big plastic bag.
Of course, i spent hours working
in this train car yesterday,
So i'm not too worried
about trace evidence.
To your credit,
your location was well chosen.
It just needed
a little cleaning, a few lights,
Proper tools, of course.
I did it because of you.
No.
You attacked those people
because you wanted to.
Yeah,
but you inspired me...
i didn't.
... with your principles.
They're not my principles.
Of course they are.
Don't tell me who i am.
My whole life, i've done what
someone else said i should do,
Been who he said
i should be.
I followed his rules.
I stuck to his plan.
I never stopped to think
About what i wanted
and what i needed.
And now i don't know
who i'm supposed to be.
I'll tell you
one thing, though.
I'm not
the bay harbor butcher.
I'm certainly not
anybody's role model.
What are you talking about,
then? Who are you?
I'll let you know
when i figure that out.
Though, i got to tell you,
I am well on my way,
Because, as sure
as i'm standing here,
I don't need to kill you.
That's a relief.
I mean that need
that comes from within
That always drives me
to this table -
I don't feel it.
I'm in recovery.
Well, i mean, i knew
you weren't gonna kill me.
No, i'm gonna kill you.
I have to.
I just don't need to.
It's very empowering.
Anyone in there,
make yourself known!
Arm.
Leg.
Head.
It's olson,
gift-Wrapped.
It would seem the butcher
is watching us,
Tracking
the investigation.
That wouldn't be
too hard to do.
But why'd he leave the victim's
body for us? That's a first.
Probably didn't take
too kindly
To the idea of olson
imitating him.
It's a pretty good way to
discourage others, don't you think?
I hate to say it, but he
probably did us a favor.
You take the law
into your own hands,
The bay harbor boogeyman's
gonna get you.
This is the first time
we've set foot in a place
Where the bay harbor butcher's
actually been.
Let's get busy.
Anybody seen lundy?
Over there on the phone.
He's talking to d. C.,
i think.
Oh, shit. Is he gonna
pull the case from us?
Sure,
have robinson call me.
He's got my cell.
I came over here to get
some privacy, officer morgan.
Well, sorry.
Too much background noise
over there.
Hearing's the first thing
to go.
Or is it memory?
I always forget.
You gonna pull
the case from us?
You said
if anybody died -
At the hands
of a vigilante.
This was our killer.
I'm afraid
you're still stuck with me.
Will your brother
be here tomorrow?
Yeah, i think so.
I'll tell him you want him
within shouting distance.
Hey...
what just happened?
No, it's cool.
He's always been
the family superstar.
Who? Dexter, your new go-To guy.
Oh, this isn't about dexter.
It's about masuka.
I can't stand him.
If i hear
one more titty joke,
I'm afraid
i'll punch him in the face.
Really?
Any north unit,
request has been made
For 42 escort
from orange belt to j. M.S.
Hey.
Come on in.
Sit down.
I was angry before
when you tried to explain.
This time i'll listen.
I'm sorry i didn't tell you
about the road trip.
Lila...
came with me to naples...
as my sponsor.
That's all.
Why would you need her
in naples?
You remember
when i went out of town?
I went to find the man
who killed my mother.
What are you talking about?
A lot of stuff has been
coming up for me in recovery,
Things i never thought
i'd deal with.
I watched my mother die
when i was 3.
Oh, dexter...
i'm so sorry.
She was murdered
in front of me.
I saw it happen.
I think that has
a lot to do
With why i'm...
why i do the things i do.
Of course.
Of course, it makes sense.
I found the man who killed her
in naples.
I thought maybe
if i talked to him,
I could find
some kind of closure.
That's why lila came with me -
For support.
Oh.
What?
This was a huge moment
in your life, dexter...
and you chose to include lila
but not me.
She's my sponsor.
And i'm your girlfriend.
I was afraid
you wouldn't understand.
Okay.
So, let me try
to understand now.
You and lila
went away together
As sponsor and sponsee.
And you really did have
adjoining rooms.
Yes.
So, you didn't have sex
that night?
No.
Okay.
Not that night.
Leave.
Rita...
no, please.
Leave now.
There was a time
I would have done anything
to protect rita.
I would have even lied.
But today i told the truth...
even though i knew
she'd get hurt.
Maybe i am leaving
the old me behind.