Previously on Dexter
I was working on my piece
with the blowtorch
and it just caught on fire.
I was so scared.
We could always get in the car
and pass the time like we used to.
You're giving Doakes to the press.
He's not your man.
Your credibility was
compromised the second
you failed to report a phonecall
from the subject of
a goddamn FBI manhunt.
Who joined who in the
shower this morning?
How about in the future I set
the alarm 10 minutes earlier?
Future, i'm liking the sound of that.
A woman named Lila Tourney has filed
sexual assault charges against him.
That fuckin' bitch!
I could loose everything over this.
Lila, why can't you just let me go?
Because I'm your real soulmate.
Not Rita.
Jesus fuckin' Christ, you're
the Bay Harbor Butcher.
I really hate that name.
What's it gonna be, Morgan?
Kill me now, or set me free!
Don't worry I send the
FBI away soon enough.
You're still trying to frame me?
Mission accomplished. One more nail
in Doakes' coffin.
We got him.
So you have a tip, not Doakes.
The park manager said our target
was headed into the everglades.
We will have the son of a bitch
in handcuffs in 24 hours.
Do not ever go to Rita's house again.
Stay away from Rita, stay away from me!
Whether you live on your own
or emigration haules your sorry ass away
I don't give a shit.
But I don't wanna give you one more day
to fuck with the people I care about.
Previous destinations.
They found Doakes' fuckin' rental car.
Did they find Doakes?
No, not yet, but the
search grid's closing in.
Hey, who's out there?
Anybody out there?
You've arrived at your destination.
Somebody in there?
Hello, who's out there?
I need some help.
Get me outa here!
Who are you?
Just open the door!
I'm being held captive.
Leave the mess for once!
Walk away from the mess!
You know I can't do that.
We need you. Lundy is mobilizing
every agency in five counties.
We're closing in.
You have a rental car,
you don't have Doakes yet.
God, come on!
I'm only helpful if there's blood.
Maybe we'll shoot him.
Then you'll need a paramedic not me.
You're afraid of to face Doakes?
Yes, of course I'm afraid to face him.
And I have dishes to do.
Fine, I'll let you know when it's over.
It's Doakes, you fucking hate the guy.
I used to, I can't even afford to think
of him as a person anymore.
Would you get going?
I tried.
If they find Doakes locked inside a cage
it will seriously
undermine my frame job.
I need to beat them to that cabin.
Waiting out there in the everglades
there are hordes of county sheriffs
search parties and gravinous reptiles.
And in this corner
of wearing dark trunks
the mighty Dexter.
Drive much!
I need a miracle.
There's a switch.
Right behind you on the wall.
Damn, it's good to see another face.
I never thought I would.
I'm Sergeant James Doakes. Miami
Metro Homicide.
Who put you in that?
A fuckin' psycho.
And he could be back in any minute.
Grab that key right
behind you on the wall.
Who is he?
He's name is Dexter Morgan.
I need you to open this gate.
Why would he do that? You even...
Because I found out that he's
the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Please, just open this fuckin' gate!
He's the butcher?
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
What's in there?
Exactly what you think it is.
It's evidence.
And I saw it happen.
I really need to get
out of this cage, lady.
Poor thing, all alone.
I'm okay.
Just open the gate!
Not you, Dexter.
Such an enormous secret.
One, there has got to be.
No wonder he is so shut down.
What are you? His accomplice?
His soulmate.
You can't leave me in here like this.
You'll be in excessory.
I'm not gonna leave you.
Not like that.
The fuck are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
No, turn it off, no!
Doing this is thing is murder.
Open this fuckin' door!
This is fuckin' murder!
m-
o-t-h-a
f-
u-c-k-a
Hey, Dexter Morgan,
Miami Metro PD Forensics.
I'm here to join the search for the
Bay Harbor Butcher
Search is on hold right now
until they sort out the confusion.
Confusion, huh?
Yeah, it's a real mess.
Take a right at the fork
park outside the line of the firetrucks.
Confusion requires firetrucks?
When something beyond reason happens
it turns sceptics into believers.
Believers in a higher power.
But what kind of power did this?
How the hell did you get here so fast?
I just got here and took
a helicopter with Lundy.
I broke a lot of speed limits.
After you left I realized you were right
I didn't wanna miss the action.
What happened?
They think a propaine tank exploded.
How?
Do I look like a fuckin' firechief?
They find a body?
Just bits and pieces so far.
Was it spontaneous combustion?
Divine intervention?
If you believe that God makes miracles
you have to wonder if Satan has a few
up his sleeve.
But when you don't believe in anything
who do you think got a time like this?
We got a floater.
He got the left off.
Separation.
Gaping area is a pultrified tissue.
Extensive fourth degree burns.
Big ass fuckin' explosion.
What else can you give us?
These lines around
his eyes aren't burnt.
He was squinting. Alive when happened.
What else.
Teething intact. Dental record
should give us a positive ID.
Goddamn it Masuka, is it Doakes?
Male, african american.
About the right length torso.
Heavyly muscled.
I think it's him.
This are the same kind of tools
that scuba dive class found.
He'd need them to make
cuts that clean.
Those come from the suspect?
No, they belong to a second body.
And whoever he was,
he was dead and dismembered
before the explosion.
So this is where the butcher
did his dirty work.
It's a perfect location
for a killing room.
It doetsn't get any more
remote than this.
No, it couldn't.
This is good news gentlemen.
And lady.
Right. All right.
We keep the search on
until we get a firm ID
on that body in the water.
You agree with them?
The evidence is compelling.
Overwhelming actually.
Guess, we got our man.
Oh, shit! Laguerta is here.
Lieutenant!
Ah..
I wouldn't if I were you.
Is it James?
We don't know yet.
Apparently miracles are subjective.
I can't exactly feel Laguerta's pain
but I can appreciate it.
Doakes wasn't so bad in the end.
But the truly tragic thing would be
to let his sacrifice go to waste.
There is only one way
I can think of to honor him.
I have to embrace my freedom.
Sleep.
What a concept!
I can't believe I actually
contemplated turning myself in.
This is so much better
than a prison cell.
I can squeeze fresh orange juice.
Savour a fine french roast.
Grab a morning work out.
Okay working out I could
have done in prison.
Let's go.
I'm free.
Dexter.
Sorry. Hope I didn't scare you.
What are you doing out there?
I forget the kids are still asleep
I didn't wanna ring the bell.
Why are you here?
I forgot the kids are still asleep.
That was.
Unexpected.
Yeah, wanted out of some
unexpected time on my ass.
Like 20 years to house.
I don't know if this is a
good idea Dexter.
I was just getting used
to you from a distance.
I know. You've been like a mirage.
-
You're the one that went away.
Yeah, I did.
I kinda forgot who I was.
I got it straight now.
Keep it straight.
Or there won't be your next time.
I know that.
Mom!
It's the sex police.
How come, you're still in bed?
I overslept.
Will you make us pancakes please?
What's under there?
Um...
Ow...
Hi!
Hi, Dexter!
Are you guys back together?
I guess we are.
Over.
Under..
Over...
Under.
Let me do myself!
No, I wanna do it.
I'm gonna be late.
So what? The case is closing.
I still need confirmation
on Doakes' body.
And if it's him?
Then it's over.
The case, not us, right?
We still have the wrap up to do.
Cataloging, conforming.
Filing, more filing.
So we got time?
Plenty.
Time enough for a vacation?
Now, you're talking.
Toes in the sand.
Tequila.
Little teeny bikini.
How about a parka?
A what?
I've had my fill of heat.
No more heat.
You look great in a parka.
Ever heard of the lake Hyppowash?
Can't say that I have.
Wonderful icefishing.
Very romantic.
Fine.
Fuck it.
Let's just go.
Morning, Dex.
Doughnut?
I'm uh, not really feeling
my doughnuts today, Dex.
You know what I mean...
Uh... no?
Oh... Right.
Mmmm, doughnuts!
Hey, are you free?
Vince, you have no idea.
Good.
How 'bout a dozen boxes
of burnt out shipment
from the cabin to catalog in?
Lieutenant.
Special Agent Lundy,
I was just looking more closely
at the dates of James' special
forces missions and...
We have a positive ID on the body.
And...
There may be and additional
date, which puts him out of the country.
The burnt victim is Sergeant Doakes.
Dental records confirmed it.
And the other body?
Jose Garza
A murder fugitive who has
been living under the alias
Chris Harlow.
The body was dismembered.
Consistent with our other victims.
Deputy director Adams is closing the case.
I see.
Lieutenant.
All the evidence points to
James Doakes as the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Conclusively.
I wanted you to
hear it from me first.
I'm truly sorry.
I don't know why they keep
hauling crap from the
cabin in here.
We know what we need to know.
Doakes was a suicidal maniac.
I believe the term is homicidal
maniac. Not that I am judging.
Yeah, whatever Morgan. He blew himself up.
That's what I'm saying.
I thought I heard somebody say
the explosion was a propaine accident.
Right. Doakes accidentally turned
on the propaine valve
and then he accidentally
turned the stove on.
The stove was on?
It was in the official
fire investigage report this morning.
I mean...
I guess it could be that Doakes
didn't realize fire and gas are a bad combo.
But, my money is on suicide.
A bad ass like Doakes?
Would rather burn then get burned.
It's a good line for my movie.
I better write it down.
You're writing a movie about Doakes?
Like you know?
Rather burn then get burned.
...
I just checked, I didn't see
any GPS device in the minivan, Dexter.
Did you check the glovebox?
It's a grey rectangular
it's about the size of a paperback book.
No, it wasn't there.
I even looked under the seats.
You think someone stole it?
Maybe. Thanks Rita, I'll see you tonight.
If someone stole my GPS
it would have let them straight to Doakes.
Who do I know with a nasty
habit of stealing?
Lila... My miracle worker.
Looks peaceful in there.
Doesn't it?
Glad, you called.
I was afraid, maybe you'd left town.
Seems I found a good reason to stay.
I won't.
And your victim.
You mean you...
That's why you asked to meet
at the aquarium. Public place...
others around.
I won't slip my needle into your neck.
Is that how you do it?
It's one of the ways.
You're afraid of me now, aren't you?
Who has been afraid of you, Dexter?
Why?
The first time I saw you
I could see how hopelessly
consumed you are by your need.
You lied to me.
All that time as my sponsor.
You said all you wanted was to
help me control my addiction.
Would you control it?
That's not what you really wanted.
Was it?
What do you think I wanted?
To know what it's like.
To feel something that deeply.
Anything.
That's why you hang
out in recovery groups.
You're emotionally colorblind.
You use the right words
you pantomime the right behaviour
but the feelings never come to pass.
It's not true.
It is Lila.
You know the dictionary definition
of emotions. Longing, joy, sorrow.
But you have no idea
what any of those things
actually feel like.
You're wrong. I have feelings for you.
You wanna have feelings for me
but they are just impulses.
Enough.
They are primitive responses
to immediate needs you know
all the words but you can't hear the music.
Lila.
I'm just like you.
Hey!
I was down to my last hope.
So was I.
And he told me, who you are.
I thought that was a secret worth protecting.
Most definetly.
Wish you could have seen it, Dexter.
The explosion was...
brilliant.
More like my father I've ever imagined
I've created a monster of my own.
Told you.
We're meant to be together.
Lila, I'm sorry
I pushed you away.
I know how frightening it
must have been for you.
I've been scratching to get in.
But it's okay. I'm in now.
And I'm not going anywhere.
I am.
Even with Doakes gone
I'm starting to think it's
too dangerous for me here.
I need to move on, to disappear.
I've already said my goodbyes.
Let me come with you.
I was hoping you'd say that.
How long would it take you
to get ready?
To close my accounts
shut my business.
Tomorrow afternoon.
Go home and pack!
I'll call you tomorrow.
I can't wait to go away
with you, Dexter.
I can't wait.
You're going away with me all right.
In a garbage bag.
But it went all right?
Sure for an internal affairs investigation.
I spent two hours saying: no
I did not rape Lila Tourney.
She's bad shit, nuts, wacko
I started to run out of adjectives.
I got a few you could use.
The good news is, the department
is dying to drop the charge.
They are dodging off bullets
with this whole Doakes thing.
Good. So when they find out
your so called victim fled Miami
You'll be reinstated.
Lila went away?
She fuckin' better.
I droped by her house last night
and told her to haul her sluggish
ass out of town before she's deported.
To defend me?
'course. For you and for Dex.
You to window lookers
needed somebody to snap you out of it.
It's good to know someone's
pulling for you when you're down.
Okay. I get the point.
Are you sure Lila got the message?
Yeah, totally...
I made it pretty clear.
Excuse me...
Donations can be made directly to me.
Donations, for Sergeant Doakes'
memorial service.
You gotta be kidding.
This what we do to a fellow officer.
Thanks again.
Excuse me, lieutenant.
I was wondering...
Checks payable to cash.
Actually I just wanted to
offer my support, sympathy.
Whatever the fuck if you wanna talk
Thank you Morgan, I can manage.
I'm not so sure...
I mean...
You're collecting money to honor a killer.
I'm not honoring the Butcher.
I'm honoring James Doakes.
Respectfully Maria, that's denial.
So it is.
You're choosing to be in denial?
Conscious denial.
But the case is closed.
I'm not gonna pursue it.
But I knew James, I knew him
as a partner and as a friend.
And I have to keep on believing
that that is who he was.
Because if he could
pile all that other fucked up shit
I don't think I could ever...
...trust anyone again.
That's right.
Or yourself.
I'll leave a check in your office.
Strange to have a creation out there.
A deeply mutated version of yourself.
Running loose and
screwing everything up.
I wonder if this is how parents feel.
Lila!
What the fuck?
Dex!
What are you doing here?
I came to make sure Lila left town.
Yeah, me too.
And if she was still here you
were gonna what?
Wrestle her? Jesus!
Whopy here.
The door was open.
I just stepped out to
buy some snacks for the road trip.
Come to say goodbye?
Actually we came to see
that you're cleared out.
But now that we see you're
on your way we're good to go.
Have a nice fuckin' life!
You're not coming with me then?
Oh my god! What did you do
to make her so patheticly crazy for you?
Is it your dick dance?
Oh well, okay.
Um..
I better be on my way then.
I think that's my bag.
I must have left it
last time I was here.
No, I'm pretty sure it's mine.
I could open it up for you
if you like so you can check yourself.
No, it's my mistake.
Okay.
Good bye then.
Have a nice flight!
Don't forget your broom!
Hello, this is Lila
please leave your name and number
and I will bring you
back as soon as I can.
Lila, where are you? I'm ready
to hit the road.
Hope you're not mad about
that thing with Deb, I had to lie
I don't want her to know we're
running off together.
Call me right away.
I miss you.
Frank!
Bedroom.
What are we doing at home
in the middle of the day?
She asked, hoping for sex.
You're packing already.
Good thing i got my touqe.
Debra, slow down.
Oh wait, I got a parka.
Do you know how hard it is
to find a parka in Miami?
When do we leave?
Not we. Me.
Debra, I just got a call from DC.
A pat on a body was identified in Oregon.
My flight leaves tonight at 7.
You gotta be fuckin' kidding me.
I wish I were.
But it's too soon.
If you're leaving we gotta
work out logistics.
Logistics...
Yeah. We got a lot of shit to figure out.
Weekend visits and regular flights
and frequent flier plans.
I got my calendar.
Hey..
Do you honestly wanna
go down this path?
You're right I don't.
Long distance relationships never
work out. Not even in the movies.
Fuck it!
What are you doing?
Logistics.
Taking a leave of absence.
You're not thinking this through.
What's to think about?
I'm going with you. It's just a job.
It's more than that to you.
Okay I love my job.
But not as much as I
love being with you.
Just. Do me a favour.
Take the afternoon
and think about this.
Fine.
You do me a favour and buy me a goddamn
ticket on your flight.
I'm going home to pack and
I'll see you at the airport.
That was delicious.
Yeah, what you like better
???
Can we have some snack?
????!
No running in the house please!
Yeah, real mature.
Captain!
You called for me?
Oh, hey Dexter!
Yeah, I recieved a phonecall from
a woman says she's a friend of yours.
Who?
She wouldn't give her name.
But claims to have vital information
on the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Any idea who she might be?
English accent?
That's her!
I think she might have a
personal issue with me.
This is the same woman who tried
You might wanna avoid her.
Not a chance.
Now this case is closing
and I can't afford to
leave any loose ends.
She said she was coming in?
Whithin the hour.
And you said she mentioned my name.
Specifically.
Well, stick around!
We'll sort this thing
out together. Okay?
If Lila plans to turn me in
why would she drop my name
to the captain and give me a chance
to intercept her? It doesn't make sense.
Unless she wants me here
so she can hurt me some other way.
Rita.
Astor!
Cody!
Guys!
Lexy!
Where are the kids?
I can't remember.
Dexter!
I got your message what is it?
What's going on?
The kids are missing
I'm so sorry, I didn't
mean to fall asleep.
We have to call the police.
Call Deb, she'll have the entire force
looking for them.
You see if any of the
neighbours saw anything.
I'll drive around the area.
I promise we'll find them.
We're going to terminal
7 Miami International.
Morgan.
Debra, it's Rita.
Hey, I'm just, I'm getting in a cab.
Look, Cody and Astor are missing.
Did you call the police?
Dexter said to call you.
Okay, you just sit by the phone
I take it from here.
All right.
Could you just wait?
You don't wanna go to the airport?
Of course I wanna go to the airport.
I just said wait!
For chrissake, honey,
make up your mind!
Why?
Why do I have to make up my mind?
Goddamnit!
Here.
Hi, Dexter.
Hey, Dex.
Hey, guys, you're having fun?
Superfun! Lila's so nice.
Where is Lila?
I'm over here.
Couldn't we have it all Dexter?
Dexter!
Stay on the bed guys, don't move!
Dexter.
Look away, both of you!
Astor, you first!
You're gonna help your brother.
Go, run, find help!
Come on Dexter!
I can't fit.
Shit!
What do you remember from before?
You know, before we took you in.
Nothing.
Good.
Because what happened was too strong.
Son, it got into you truly.
And it's gonna stay there.
It's gonna make you wanna kill.
And you won't be able to stop it.
So I'm gonna be like this forever?
Yes.
You're gonna be okay.
I got you.
I'm so sorry about all of this.
It's over now. They are safe.
You're safe. That's all that matters.
Come on.
You two.
Secure the perimeter
and have the firechief come see me
as soon as he gets here.
Put out an APB on Lila West
aka Lila Tourney
suspected arsonists
5.7, black hair,
pale like a fuckin' corpse.
Fuckin' corpse, got it.
You're wasting your time
she's not coming back.
Not after this.
Yeah, I wouldn't bet on it.
She won't.
She's a survivolist.
How did you know the kids were here?
One of the neighbours
saw them walking with a strange woman.
It wasn't much of a lead, but...
Lila has gone after everyone
that's close to you.
What?
It's pretty impressive. It seems
it wasn't too long ago
I was taking care of you.
I like it better this way.
I can see that.
Why is this man not on the way
to the hospital now?
I'm fine, Deb.
You're not fine.
Your eyebrows are singed.
How can you be so fuckin' relaxed?
I'm good at compartmentalization.
You're little weird, Dex.
That's not gonna change
I'm gonna be this way, forever.
I can live with that.
Just mourn it up! Okay?
I passed through the flames
and rose from the ashes.
Again.
I've never been one to put much weight
to the idea of a higher power.
But if I didn't know better
I have to believe that some force
out there wants me to keep
doing what I'm doing.
Dexter.
You wanted to be close to me Lila.
This is the most I have to offer.
I can't feel my legs and my body.
Good. I went with a spinal epidural
instead the tranquilizer,
I've got a plane to catch.
And you don't need to feel this.
You killed an innocent man.
I did it for you.
You tried to kill the
children for me too.
Don't do this!
You taught me to accept what I am.
And to trust in the one thing
I know with absolute clarity.
Thank you.
Not long ago I had a dream
that people could see me for what I am.
And for a brief instant of time
the world actually
saw my bodies of work.
Some even cheered.
But as it turns out,
nobody mourns the wicked.
Sorry, James.
I think Harry knew that from the start.
That's why he gave me a code.
It cost him his life.
But it kept me alive
through incredible trials.
The code is mine now.
And mine alone.
So too are the relationships I cultivate.
They're not just disguises anymore.
I need them.
Even if they make me vulnerable.
My father might not approve.
But I'm no longer his disciple.
I'm a master now.
An idea transcended into life.
And so this is my new path.
Which is a lot like the old one.
Only mine.
To stay on that path I
need to work harder.
Explore new rituals
evolve.
Am I evil? Am I good?
I'm done asking those questions.
I don't have the answers.
Does anyone?