Previously on Dexter...
I'm on edge. 38 days have passed
since I killed my brother.
In that entire time,
I haven't had a single night to myself.
Sergeant Doakes makes sure of that.
With Doakes tailing me,
my life's been all Jekyll and no Hyde.
My brother would be so disappointed.
Don't forget,
tell the universe what you need.
I really need...to kill somebody.
I've been waiting a long time for this.
What the fuck?
I'll be OK. I followed the code.
The stalk was good.
I'm just a little rusty
since killing my brother.
Debra can't sleep
in an empty house any more.
I guess that's what happens
when your fianc? tries to slice you up
into small, bloodless pieces.
Welcome back, Morgan.
Thanks.
You just got to look her in the eyes
to know she's not right.
- Excuse me, are you...
- What the fuck are you doing?
Rita, I'm not doing real good in here, OK?
Will you help me?
I found the fucking shoe, OK?
Great! I'll call the lawyer in the morning.
No! I'm not gonna let you
drag Dexter into this.
Paul's dead.
And I could have helped him.
That was his own fault.
Was it?
- What's the matter with you today?
- I'm just a little off my game. I'll get it back.
Rafael!
- It felt like she was asking me something.
- That's her son.
She says she knows who killed him,
Some guy named Little Chino.
She wants you to find Little Chino
and kill him like a dog.
Eva.
Are you willing to testify
that Little Chino picked up your son
on the night of his death?
Come on. Don't back down now.
I want him to pay.
A challenge, a mountain to climb.
I need this one.
The scene of the failed crime,
no better place to try again.
I don't normally experience failure.
39 days, 22 hours and 18 minutes
since I killed my brother.
I am cursed.
Two treasure hunters
made a ghastly discovery today
when they stumbled on what appears to be
an underwater graveyard
in a crevice off the coast of Miami.
That means there might be
a new mass murderer out there
way worse than the Ice-Truck Killer.
I'm drifting.
I finally get a chance to kill and I can't do it.
And a second chance, and he gets away.
And now all my secrets
are floating to the surface.
Where is the orderly,
controlled, effective Dexter?
How did I lose him?
How do I find him again?
I'm drifting...
...but not to sleep.
...the gruesome discovery
off the coast of Florida yesterday.
Police are still searching through evidence
lying at the bottom of the ocean.
Sources say there could be multiple victims
in what appears to be the work...
Here I am, back in the belly of the beast.
But how can I solve a crime when
I can't even solve what's wrong with me?
Yet duty calls.
Eight confirmed.
- Eight confirmed. Here?
- No. Here is just one.
Eight confirmed victims
of the Bay Harbor Butcher.
The "Bay Harbor Butcher"?
That's what the press is calling
whoever dumped those bodies offshore.
Has a nice ring to it, no?
Well, it's a little...
- lurid.
- Lurid and possibly wrong.
Part of me is hoping they found
the Ice-Truck Killer's dumping grounds.
Tell me about it. The last thing Miami needs is
another serial killer.
Eva Arenas. All she wanted was justice
against the 29th Street Kings
for whacking her son.
- First she's the messenger...
- Now she's a goddamn message.
Death by machete. Again.
We got a bolo on Little Chino. Gang crash
unit, all local patrols after that cabr?n.
Last thing I want is for the cops
to bring Little Chino in.
He's mine.
Why don't you take a picture, Morgan?
It'll last longer.
What would I do
without you, Sergeant?
Please, se?ora. Please, slower.
She's saying you fuckin' cops
don't do nothin'.
Grandma really talks like that?
Not exactly. But you get the point.
Right, bitch?
Fucking people don't want our help.
Shit. She had a little girl.
I know.
This stuff never gets to you?
I'm more of a "crying on the inside"
kind of guy.
Wow. He makes the Ice-Truck Killer
look like a goddamn artist.
Sorry, Morgan.
What?
I'm so over that.
You just prove it to me.
You can't.
You're just fucking with me!
I'm gonna have to put you on hold.
Fianc?.
Incarnate. Couldn't pick a worse time, right?
Hey, Esmee.
How about you take off,
let me handle this?
I couldn't let you do that.
I'll write up the report and email it to you
for signature.
OK?
I want Morgan to report to me first thing
in the morning about that bar fight of hers.
Maria...
I owe you.
In there!
Somebody else get in there now!
Mommy!
Seeing her mother that way.
Can you imagine that?
I can't even go there, Angel.
This one's on us, man.
If I had killed Chino last night,
that little girl's mother would still be alive.
I gotta find Chino before he finds me.
...bringing to an even dozen
the number of bodies found offshore.
I have to focus, tune everything out.
So far, the authorities
have no clue as to the criminal.
If I don't, being linked to my bodies of work
will be the least of my worries.
Shit. Little Chino?
He was out there.
The timing could be better.
Yeah, plus I don't have my tools.
It does give me the chance
to tie up one massive loose end.
- It's you, Sergeant.
- Who else you got following you?
Apparently no one.
Go ahead. Try it. I've been waiting.
This neighborhood...
it's full of crazies.
I'd lock my doors.
Bathroom's all yours.
Kind of always was.
We run out of glasses?
Clean ones.
Come here a sec. I found a couple of places
on craigslist you should check out.
Got two bedrooms, two baths,
limited water views,
- has its own gym.
- Hate it.
All right.
One bedroom, one bath,
Art Deco building.
Shitty neighborhood.
It gets morning sun.
Come on, Deb, give it a chance.
I appreciate the brotherly love,
but I've got the lieutenant in like an hour.
See you at the job.
I will not kill my sister,
I will not kill my sister.
- Hey, you.
- Dexter?
Astor? Sweetie, what's the matter?
Mom's acting all weird and stuff.
- What kind of weird?
- She keeps talking to people on the phone
about my dad,
then she starts yelling at them.
- Then she yells at me and Cody.
- I'm on my way.
No, no.
Calm is what I was 35 minutes ago.
Pissed is what I am now.
Hey, who wants Eggos?
I got blueberry or chocolate. Or both.
- Both.
- Don't care.
Assholes. They did everything but help.
Which assholes were you talking to?
Funeral home assholes.
You're having a funeral for Paul?
For Paul, for the kids, for me.
We had this old insurance policy.
It's about $5,000,
but it should cover everything.
You know, the county
will bury Paul for free.
I mean, he wasn't even your husband.
Any more.
Technically.
Then you could use the insurance money
for a starter scholarship for the kids?
Dexter, I didn't ask for your help
or your advice.
I'll never understand
how people deal with death,
why they can't just put it in its place.
And now I have to find someone
who knows I'm looking for him,
not exactly ideal in
the "element of surprise" department.
And I have to find a new way
to dispose of Little Chino's body.
If I can close the deal this time.
You totally douched me in there.
You clocked a guy in a bar
who touched your arm.
I told the lieutenant
you weren't ready for active duty.
Well, thank you
for the fucking vote of confidence.
Nice.
13 confirmed.
The buzz in the halls
is that the feds are coming in
- on the Bay Harbor bodies.
- Well, that figures.
The FBI does all the heavy lifting,
Captain Matthews takes all the credit.
Nice political move
when you're bucking for Deputy Chief.
- Any idea who the FBI is sending?
- Some guy named Lundy.
Frank Lundy?
He's a rock star.
The Green River Killer, the DC Sniper.
- If the case was impossible, he broke it.
- Now, James,
I'm damaged goods around here, but you,
you should do whatever you can
to get on Lundy's task force.
- It's a career-maker!
- Hey.
Just visualize that door of opportunity opening
up wide for you, bro,
- and just walk right through it.
- Angel, you keep up with this woo-woo shit,
I'm gonna walk right through you.
You were right.
Little Chino. Shit.
This guy is officially the highest point
in all of Florida.
What is he doing here?
People tell me you're looking for my client.
People tell you right.
Fuck, he's big.
The harder they fall.
That come with a story?
- I cut myself shaving.
- Well, you should be more careful, amigo.
Lieutenant, my client has been
harassed by this department.
- We're considering...
- Oh, cut the shit, Raul.
There was another murder in East Kendall
yesterday and my client...
Word on the pavement is
you're looking for me regarding this...
- tragedy.
- You bet your ass we are.
The victim was the mother of one of
your compadres who we know you killed.
But can't prove, right, Officer?
It's Detective. And can't prove yet.
Show them the disc.
Time stamp is yesterday afternoon,
same time as...
- Eva Arenas' TOD.
- That's bullshit.
- Anyone could reset a time stamp.
- Check it out.
Yesterday's paper.
That arrogant prick. He knew
we'd peg him for Arenas' murder,
so he covered his ass,
had someone else do the deed.
- That makes him an accomplice, right?
- Not without evidence.
Cut him loose.
Red rover, red rover,
send Chino back over.
Yo, Dex, check this out.
13 and counting.
They're so swamped up there
they had to bring in outside talent,
which would be moi.
Bet this guy never expected his work
to see the light of day.
Bet you're right.
It can't be easy
to hide a body nowadays.
- You shitting me?
- Hypothetical.
You're the Bay Harbor Butcher. How do you
make sure a disposed body stays disposed?
Tons of options. Everglades,
alligators, pig farms,
sulphuric acid, wood chipper, incinerator.
Hell, even meat pies.
- The mind boggles.
- Don't all those run the risk of contact
- with the outside world?
- You got a better idea?
No.
And that's the problem. Where
do I put Chino when I'm done with him?
Captain's coming up with that FBI guy.
He's got a fuckin' entourage.
All right, listen up, everyone. Briefing room in
two minutes for Show and Tell.
All right.
The Bay Harbor Butcher case
is now a Miami Metro case.
And it is shaping up to be
the biggest one in our history.
We're now at 14 confirmed.
The FBI has sent over their top man,
Special Agent Frank Lundy,
to help solve this crime.
Now...
this will not be
a jurisdictional circle jerk.
This will be a shining example
of two agencies working together
for the public good.
Agent Lundy.
Hello, everyone. There is no such thing
as the perfect crime,
not in my experience, anyway.
With your help and with the mistakes
this person has made
and will eventually make,
we'll find whoever did this awful thing.
I need everyone in every department
up to speed on what we are doing,
while I review your files
and put our task force together.
So, let's get a jump-start
on the Bay Harbor Butcher,
a moniker which, by the way, repulses me.
Well, we have something in common.
Can someone get the lights?
The first report from the field
had these parts as coming from one body.
Actually, it's two.
There's been speculation
that this human harvest
might be connected to a case
you've recently solved.
But there are several inconsistencies between
the two sets of body parts,
gender, exsanguination,
specific methods of dissection.
Not to mention my guys deserved it.
The evidence just isn't there to piggyback this
onto the Ice-Truck Killer.
We're looking for a different suspect.
All information is to be disseminated...
Miss me, brother?
...all agency protocol...
Putting it plainly...
I can't afford to lose it like this, not with
Special Agent Rock Star on my case.
Do not discuss this case.
I need to clear the decks.
And my head.
I'm coming for you tonight, Little Chino.
And this time there won't be any screw-ups.
Just slam in your CO2 cartridge here,
put in your tranq dart and let her rip.
Wham, bam, lights fuckin' out.
So, 'gators giving you trouble, Dex?
They ate my puppy.
This sucker, you load her up right,
she'll take down a goddamn grizzly.
Now, you may have to get closer
than you'd like,
but she'll do the job, I promise you that.
So which will it be?
Both.
Excellent.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, fuck.
First time?
Sort of.
Yeah, I've been boxing since I was ten.
- Tough neighborhood?
- Tough family.
And those are just my sisters.
Want some help?
- I'm doing enough damage on my own.
- Is that a yes or a no?
That was a yes. It sounded like a no,
but...
Yeah. Yeah.
Good answer.
First...
you need to wrap your wrists
so you don't hurt yourself again.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Yo, Deb!
You scared the shit out of me.
How are you doing?
How am I doing?
I saw the man I thought I loved...
No, did love,
up on some goddamn screen
with a gallery full of women
that he murdered and cut into pieces.
- Deb, I...
- Don't.
You fuckin' asked.
So, how am I doing?
I'm just fine.
I might be playing fast and loose
with my father's code,
but I don't think Harry would disapprove...
considering.
Attaboy, Chino, a little closer.
Come on, don't get the shakes now,
this is no time for performance anxiety.
I've been waiting for you.
Take him! Tommy!
I'll get his ass!
No, no, no! I don't know
where the fuck he is!
We're out here all night long if we have to.
You find him, OK?
What the hell is wrong with me?
Dexter, someone's coming.
It's OK, I got you.
Please don't hurt us!
God. Oh, my God.
No! Dexter, don't leave me!
Biney!
Don't leave me!
Dexter, please don't leave me!
Biney!
Biney! Biney!
Brian, my brother.
Somebody must have seen something.
Seeing and talking are two different things.
- You want me to knock on some doors?
- Or maybe some heads.
Sorry I'm late.
What fucking asshole left this here?
It's Special Agent Fucking Asshole.
- Morgan, right?
- We got witnesses to interview.
You seen my brother?
Oh. Excuse me.
Excuse me, sir.
Do you have a minute?
Or three. Good tea takes time.
- What's up, Sergeant?
- It's about your task force.
I think I can bring something to it, sir.
I've looked into your jacket, Sergeant.
You've done some fine work
here in Homicide.
- Miami Metro's lucky to have you.
- Thank you, sir.
But I don't think
you'd be a good fit for my team.
- I thought you just said I was qualified.
- I said you'd done fine work in Homicide.
Frankly, Sergeant, you're more
of a leader than a team member.
I'm not convinced you play well with others.
Excuse me.
Can somebody clean this shit up?
I feel like a jigsaw puzzle missing a piece
and I'm not even sure
what the picture should be.
I've been calling you for hours.
Kind of pulled an all-nighter.
Dexter, I called the station.
I was off the clock.
It's this huge case I'm working.
It's...
It's taking me to places
I never thought I'd go.
What?
I've been thinking a lot about Paul's death and
how I'm gonna deal with it.
- And?
- First of all,
I'm not gonna let the county bury him.
I'm using the insurance money
to give Paul a proper funeral. It's in an hour.
Rita, Paul was such a...
...destructive force,
why can't you just put him behind you?
It's about saying goodbye.
Goodbye to him and the grip
he had on my life. It's called moving on.
Go clean yourself up.
The kids are expecting you.
- I'm just gonna make you late.
- Damn it, Dexter!
I need you there too.
You have no idea what this feels like.
Just give me ten minutes.
Can't wait to get another door
slammed in my face.
Yeah. If I lived in this neighborhood,
I wouldn't talk to the cops either.
Brave guy like you?
It's about survival.
These people have families, kids.
It's not easy to talk when you got the 29th
Street Kings playing whack the witness.
- It just takes one, right?
- That's it.
Put that out into the universe. Right?
- Miami Metro. Can we talk to you?
- Go to hell!
OK, but before we do that, ma'am,
can I ask you a few questions?
- How many is a few?
- Three. But one's a two-parter.
- Go away before I call the police!
- We are the fucking police!
I ain't talking to no one!
- Look at the bright side.
- What bright side?
Karmically, we're batting 1,000.
There's something balancing
about that kind of consistency.
God damn it!
Morgan!
Aw, shit.
You think you can spray-paint your gang crap
on a police car and get away with it?
Get off! Unless you want to fuck me
like you fucked the Ice-Truck Killer!
You gangbanging-wannabe piece of shit!
No, please.
I'll tell you where the shit is,
the drugs and shit.
- Please don't shoot me, miss.
- Morgan!
If I believed in God,
if I believed in sin,
this is the place where
I'd be sucked straight to hell...
if I believed in hell.
Come on, Dexter. It's all right.
But that is not the entire story
of who this man was.
Born into innocence
as are all of God's children...
...are truly the living personification
of God's...
...through the magic of family,
giving love and receiving love,
that he truly flourished.
It was with his children
that he, for all his blemishes,
re-embraced the perfect innocence.
And it was through his children that once again
God smiled on Paul Bennett.
And now the family will come forward
for a few moments of silent prayer.
I hope you found your peace, Paul.
Bye, Dad.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you...
Father.
I'm not sorry.
You're still here.
Never left.
Yeah, you did. I killed you.
No. You just took my life.
So how do I make you go away?
Well, you could try doing
what these people are doing.
I'm not like them.
Well, if it helps,
I can tell you it's not your fault,
what you did to me.
I never said it was.
But you feel it.
How do you know that?
It's human nature.
I'm not human.
No.
You're just fucked up.
I need to let you go.
You think it's as simple as that?
Nothing's simple.
Does this mean you'll be my dad now?
- 29th Street Kings?
- Yeah, we got 'em.
SWAT did a sweep on some auto shop those
animals were using as a front.
Maybe we didn't get them on murder,
but we busted their asses on drugs, weapons
and money laundering.
Half of them are three-strikers,
so they're gonna go away forever.
Thanks to Officer Morgan.
Hey, something you should know.
Deb pulled her gun on an unarmed boy
to get him to give up the gang,
some kid named Joey Nunez.
- Thanks, Angel, I'll talk to her.
- All right.
I'll give her one thing, though,
she's in motherfucking good shape.
Here comes another one.
Did we get Little Chino too?
That cocksucker wasn't there.
That's too bad.
- What you got?
- None of your business.
Yeah.
Excuse me, Esmee,
I opened this by mistake.
It said Lieutenant.
No worries.
Today, Maria, it is all about the win.
I think we really should enjoy this.
Stop me if you think I'm speaking out of turn or
above my station,
but we really don't use department resources
around here for personal matters.
- What are you talking about?
- Well, let's, for argument's sake,
say those phone records
belong to your fianc?.
It could open up a shit-ugly can of worms you
might not be able to close.
Only if someone mentions it.
This is me not mentioning it.
Maria.
I'm new at this,
this...not trusting the man
that I thought that I loved...
and...
I really appreciate your support.
Hey, Deb, it's me.
Again.
You're probably at the gym.
I got some unfinished business
outside the office.
I'll probably be a little late tonight.
I'll catch up with you later.
It was simple, really.
All I had to do was put myself
into the mind of a killer,
hardly a stretch.
It was only a matter of time
before Little Chino went after Joey Nunez
for snitching him out.
Here's hoping I'm back on my game.
Trust me, you're not
going anywhere this time.
Who the fuck are you?
Now...
that kind of talk is just gonna bring you closer
to your victims.
Are you a cop?
'Cause I was cleared on that bitch.
No, maybe you didn't do the deed,
but her blood is on your hands.
A lot of blood is on your hands.
What do you care about these people?
Actually...
Agh! Fuck. Fu...
...I don't.
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm not so much doing this to you
as I'm doing it for me.
I never killed no kid.
But you killed most of her.
Her mother.
Her brother.
Her innocence.
You leave pain wherever you go.
You kill me...
what do you leave behind?
A world without you.
Look at that. Steady as a surgeon.
This kill was just the first of the loose ends
I needed to tie off.
I also found a newer,
safer place to dump my trash.
Moving at over four miles an hour,
the Gulf Stream is one of the world's
most powerful deepwater currents.
This time tomorrow,
Little Chino will be north of Palm Beach.
After that, it's on to Georgia, South Carolina,
North Carolina, until eventually...
Well, let's just say,
the North Atlantic's a pretty big place.
Hey, you.
- I need to see you.
- I was just dropping somebody off.
- Can it wait?
- No, it can't.
All right, then.
A shoe?
You wanted to see me about a shoe?
It's Paul's shoe.
OK.
What do we do with it?
Paul kept insisting to me
that you knocked him over the head,
dragged him to his motel
and shot him up with drugs.
Sounds like one of his stories, huh?
He asked me to look in the yard
for his shoe.
Finally, I did.
- Maybe...
- No, let me finish, Dexter.
I didn't have a lot to hope for until I met you.
You gave me something to believe in
when I didn't even believe in myself.
And maybe I was...
maybe I was so desperate
that I looked the other way.
Paul begged me to help him.
And what did I do?
I hung up on him.
And he was so upset,
he got into a prison fight,
and he was beaten to death with a pipe.
That's not your fault.
Part of it is.
Part of me believes that,
with all of Paul's flaws...
he paid the price for my dreams.
Did you attack him, Dexter?
I'd understand if you did.
He attacked me.
I hit Paul to protect you and the kids.
It was totally an act of impulse.
OK.
Where did you get the drugs?
Stolen from the evidence locker.
Wait.
Wait, you mean...
First you tell me that you...
acted on impulse,
and then you tell me that you stole the drugs
from your police station?
I mean, what are you trying to say?
That you planned on acting on impulse?
- It's all kind of jumbled now.
- How did you know how to cook the heroin?
How did you know what dose
to give a big guy like Paul?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, why didn't I see this?
They were your drugs.
Now it makes sense.
That's where you disappear to at all hours
of the night like Clark fucking Kent.
Look, if there is anything left between us,
you will answer me this one question
and you will tell me the truth.
Are you an addict?
Yes, I have an addiction.
Oh, Dexter.
That's good.
That's the first step,
admitting you have a problem.
We'll get you into a program.
We'll get you the help you need.
And I will be there for you.
If the eyes are the windows to the soul,
then grief is the door.
As long as it's closed, it's the barrier between
knowing and not knowing.
Walk away from it
and it stays closed forever.
But open it and walk through it...
and pain becomes truth.
And now I'm faced with the struggle
for my own survival
that I always knew was coming.
I've been preparing for this my entire life.
When all is said and done, Chino,
you're the same size as everyone else.
Hey, Dex, what the fuck?
Hold on, I'm coming!
It's annoying, isn't it?
I'm not taking the bait.
- You're up late.
- Yeah, just surfing.
You go to the gym?
Then I was sort of driving around.
Around what?
Around town.
- Because?
- I saw some buildings
with some "For rent" signs.
I'm gonna check 'em out.
Then Chez Dexter can return to its original,
semi-lived-in, museum-quality state.
- Deb, you don't need to do this.
- Yes, I do.
You don't need to do this now.
Well, what about the video tours
of eligible apartments?
Temporary insanity.
You sure?
No. Get out.
Asshole.
This way I can take care of my sister
the way Harry would have wanted.
You really reek.
You're right. Like a fuckin' sewer.
For every door that closes...
Fuck.
Sorry.
It was always right there.
I had to say goodbye in order to reconnect
with what's really important...
with who I was...
with who I have to be.
Rest in peace.