Sheldon, your food's
getting cold.
I'll eat later.
Right now, I'm suckling
at the informative bosom
of mother physics.
It's hot when
Sheldon talks dirty.
So, I found this Web site
where you send them pictures,
they sculpt your head
and make an action figure
out of you.
How awesome is that?
Oh, let me see.
Yeah, you can pick
your wardrobe.
You can even choose
your accessories.
Leonard, you can get
a little asthma inhaler.
Oh, this is neat.
Think about all
the action figures
we've bought over the years.
It would be kind of cool
to have ones that look like us.
Don't you think?
Yeah, if that's your idea
of what's cool,
you should get one.
Yeah, so, I'm out.
What do you think,
Sheldon?
Want an action figure
that looks just like you?
Would it come with kung-fu grip?
No.
Don't waste my time.
You get that these are
personalize action figures.
Honey, if you want one,
just get one.
You're still
out, right?
Yep.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 6x14 ?
The Cooper/Kripke Inversion
Original Air Date on January 31, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
A hush falls over the crowd
as Cooper studies the board.
He makes his move.
He's dividing both sides by "I."
He's adding back
the coefficient.
He has a value for "P."
He's plugging that back in.
He takes the derivative,
and he solves the equation.
The crowd goes wild.
Nobel! Nobel!
Cooper?
Nobel.
Kripke.
Don't look at my board.
What's that?
That's a drawing
of a really cool train.
Don't look at that, either.
What do you want?
I have some
bad news.
You're working
on a grant proposal
for a new
fusion reactor.
I'm working on a grant proposal
for a new fusion reactor.
The university is only allowed
to submit one proposal.
So they asked you to pack up
your things and ship out.
That's hard cheese, Barry.
You're one of the good ones.
No, they're making us
work together.
That's ridiculous.
I am one of the great minds
of our generation.
I work on a level so rarified
you couldn't
even imagine it.
I said stop looking
at my cool train!
Hmm.
Kind of a strange place
to put a picture of you
and Bernadette.
Well, I wanted everybody
to know I love my wife.
And nobody to know I forgot
to turn off the laser.
They're here.
Our action figures
have arrived.
This is the best $500
I've ever spent.
$1,000 on action figures?
How can you afford that?
Easy-- his family's loaded,
and Bernadette has a great job.
My wife came with both
fun bags and money bags.
Say hello to an exact
scale model of me.
Oh, I'm not dark chocolate.
I'm melt-in-your-mouth caramel.
Oh, man.
Look at my nose.
Maybe it's a shipping problem.
What?
Yeah.
Maybe Wesley Snipes
and Toucan Sam
just got action figures
that look like you guys.
This sucks.
I can't believe
I wasted all that money.
Aw, and my girlfriend
wouldn't let me get one.
Look at my face.
Do I look smug?
I feel smug.
I hate it when you make me
sit through all the credits.
Well, sometimes there's
a secret ending,
like in The Avengers.
Yeah, but I don't think
that's going to happen
in a documentary
about the Holocaust.
They could
show bloopers.
Oh, no.
What is that?
That is Sheldon's
"I'm unhappy and about
to destroy the planet" music.
Come on, let's just go
to your place.
Well, wait, if he's unhappy,
shouldn't we talk to him?
"Shouldn't we talk to him?"
Have you learned nothing
in six years?
You doing okay, sweetie?
There is ominous music playing,
and there is an afghan
over my head.
I don't know where you're from,
but where I'm from,
that means I'm not doing okay.
Want me to make
you some tea?
Tea is for when I'm upset.
I'm not upset.
The university's forcing me
to work with Kripke.
I'm outraged.
So, cocoa?
Yes, cocoa.
Do you have any idea what
it's like to be paired
with someone who's so
incredibly annoying?
Oh, teacher! Me! Me!
See, I did all this great work,
and now he's just going to
come along and ruin it.
I am angrier than ever
and filled with despair.
What beverage
do you make for that?
Oh... no, no, no, I know this.
Uh...
hot apple cider
with cinnamon sticks?
Yes, hot apple cider
with cinnamon sticks!
What the frig, Cooper?
We were
supposed to meet
in my office
a half an hour ago.
And yet,
now you're in my office.
Point: Cooper.
Welcome to the Thunderdome,
Kripke.
We agreed to exchange
copies of our work.
Let me see yours.
Why don't you show me
yours first.
You think I just fell
off the turnip truck?
We exchange at the same time.
How do I know you're not
going to take my ideas
and publish them
as your own?
How do I know you're not
going to do that with mine?
Yeah, because I'm not interested
in getting published
in Mad magazine.
Zingers fly fast
in the Thunderdome, Barry.
Are we going
to do this or not?
Thank you.
So, we read each other's work,
meet again tomorrow?
Fine.
Nice try.
This is blank paper.
And I am sure it's
still more valuable
than whatever's in here.
Cough it up, Cooper.
Very well.
If this one's blank, too,
I'm going to be furious.
Fine.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You!
Always bet on black.
Get that waste of money
out of my face.
It's only a
waste of money
if we don't
play with them.
He's right, dawg.
Please, I'm working.
You know, there is a way
we can get action figures
to look exactly
like us.
Oh, yeah?
How's that?
Two words:
3-D printer.
Wait, maybe it's three words.
No, hang on.
Okay, one word, a letter
and a number and...
maybe a hyphen.
3-D printer.
I have always wanted
a 3-D printer.
Of course you have.
They're an
engineer's dream.
Anything you can design,
a 3-D printer can make
out of plastic.
Yeah, but they're so expensive.
Oh, come on.
You deserve one.
You've worked hard
to find a woman
who makes a lot of money.
Well, the prices
have been coming down.
Oh, true.
They're practically
giving them away.
You know, in exchange for money.
And we can make stuff
we need for work with it.
Prototypes
of my CAD/CAM designs,
specialized tools...
Not to mention
Malibu Koothrappali
and his totally bitchin'
dream house.
We don't need Malibu
Koothrappali's dream house.
Really, smart guy?
Where's he supposed to park
his sweet little Corvette?
The monkey in my tobacco study
has taken to smoking a pipe.
I'm supposed to remove
his brain to examine,
but it's hard because now he
reminds me of my uncle.
You've been
awfully quiet tonight.
Is everything okay?
I'm fine.
All right, well,
how was work today?
Did you exchange your research
with Kripke?
Yes.
Sheldon, what's going on?
I read his research, and...
it's leaps and bounds
ahead of mine.
Which means the mommy
of the smartest physicist
at the university is not
my mommy as I had thought.
It's his mommy.
Sheldon, I wish there was
something I could do
to make you feel better.
May I offer you a consoling hug?
What do we have to lose?
How's that?
I feel like I'm being strangled
by a boa constrictor.
Why'd you stop?
Come on, Sheldon!
We're going to be late!
I can't go in today.
I'm sick.
You're not sick.
You just don't want
to face Kripke.
No, look.
128.
See?
What did you do,
put this in your tea?
Oh, dear.
Now I'm not even smarter
than you.
Sheldon, Kripke's not
smarter than you.
You just got stuck
on a wrong path.
Happened to Einstein.
He got stuck on the unified
field theory for decades.
Oh, don't play
the Einstein card.
His great breakthroughs happened
when no one knew anything.
So everything
was a great breakthrough.
Sheldon Lee Cooper,
I do not have time
for this nonsense.
Now, go put your clothes on,
get in the car,
and lets go to work.
All right, geez.
What a grouch.
How did I do that?
I got to remember
how I did that.
Do you realize, by
owning a 3-D printer,
we are reclaiming
the manufacturing process
and taking jobs back
from sweatshops in China?
I think this thing
was made in China.
Eh, what can you do?
Ooh, I-I think it's done.
It worked!
We printed a whistle.
Amazing.
You realize these things
go for 25 cents a pop
at a party store.
And we made it
in only three hours.
Sounds just like
store-bought.
Okay, give me
a superhero pose,
and I will scan you
into the computer
for your action figure.
Oh, I wish I was
in better shape.
Stop holding
your stomach in.
I'll give you a six-pack
with the computer.
Oh, okay, great.
Now I can look
like Val Kilmer as Batman
instead of Val Kilmer
as he looks today.
All right, you can
suck it in a little bit.
Cooper, we have a problem.
Your work is really not
at a level
I expected it to be.
I know.
Go ahead, mock me.
Just use small words
so I understand.
Don't play dumb
with me.
We both know
what your problem is.
We do?
You have a girlfriend.
So?
So my work would suffer, too,
if I was getting laid
all the time.
Yes.
That is the reason.
My work is suffering
because of...
all the laid I'm getting.
You lucky bastard.
What can I say, you know?
She enjoys my genitals.
I am giving them to her
on a nightly basis.
Okay, stop bragging.
You had some brilliant
insights in here,
but if we're gonna
make this work,
you need to buckle down
and focus.
I'll do what I can.
But it's not going to be easy,
because when I'm with Amy
and our bathing suit areas
mush together...
boy howdy, is it magic
Oh, good,
you're home.
Got a little
surprise for you.
What?
Say hello
to my little friend.
Oh, my God.
That's so cute.
I didn't think there could be
a smaller version of you.
I know, right?
And, thanks
to photographs
and a little
3-D modeling,
here comes the bride.
Oh, Howie,
I love these.
I thought you might.
Were they expensive?
Didn't cost a thing.
I made them myself.
How?
Koothrappali and I
bought a used 3-D printer
for $5,000.
$5,000 for a
couple of dolls?
Are you out
of your mind?
Not just
a couple of dolls.
For as many dolls
as we want.
And whistles.
At any point, did it dawn
on you to talk to me
about spending this
kind of money?
It's kind of
dawning on me now.
I don't believe you!
Howie, we can't afford to waste
money on junk like this.
What are you talking about?
We make plenty
of money.
I make plenty of money!
You make peanuts!
Yes, but we're married now.
That means, when you
get sick,
I take care of you.
And when you make
a bunch of money,
I get to buy stuff.
Sorry if you
don't like it,
but that's how
love works.
No, here's how
You're gonna return
the machine,
or you can print out a
working set of lady parts
and sleep with those.
Oh, my God! Are you
actually thinking about it?
All right, I don't understand.
Why didn't you just
tell Kripke the truth?
Because the truth
made me look bad,
whereas a ridiculous bald-faced
lie makes me look good.
Anyway,
if Kripke asks,
tell him my coitus with Amy
is frequent,
intense and whimsically
inventive.
Is my coitus
whimsically inventive?
That is what I write
on the bathroom walls.
"For a whimsically
inventive time,
call Leonard Hofstadter."
I know you're joking,
but I'd be okay with that.
Yeah.
Sheldon, can I ask you
a question?
Of course.
You ever going to sleep with Amy?
That's awfully personal.
We don't ask Sheldon
things like that.
Maybe you don't; I do.
What's the deal?
Well, word around the university
is I'm giving her sex organs
a proper jostling.
All right, come on,
be serious.
Look, you guys have been
going out a long time.
She would clearly like
to have a physical
relationship with you,
so what are you doing?
All right, we're down
the rabbit hole.
What are you doing?
Well, first of all,
I'm quite fond of Amy.
Then what's
the problem?
Penny...
all my life,
I have been uncomfortable
with the sort
of physical contact
that comes easily
to others--
hand-shaking, hugging,
prostate exams.
But I'm working on it,
you know?
Just recently, I had to put
VapoRub on Amy's chest.
A year ago, that would
have been unthinkable.
Now you know how I feel
when I have to put it on you.
Okay. Hang on.
Are you saying someday
you and Amy might...
actually get physical?
It's a possibility.
Oh, my God!
Sheldon, I know this
wasn't easy for you,
and I'm really glad we could
have this conversation.
Oh, yeah.
Ow!
Are you sure you
want to do this?
Give up your half
of the 3-D printer?
Yes.
And can you please make
that out to Bernadette?
I was taken off
the joint account
until I learn
the value of money.
Wow, that's harsh.
Tell me about it.
Aren't you gonna eat lunch?
Nah, I blew my food allowance
on Pok?mon cards.
Well, the equation
balances,
but it's certainly
not elegant.
Whatever.
You get any last night?
Yes.
Gave it to her good, huh?
No, I gave it to her well.
Now, over here,
I was thinking
the turbulence could be
reduced if we just put...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Was she naked,
or was she wearing lingerie?
I didn't notice.
How could you
not notice?
I was too busy
squishing all the desirable
parts of her body.
Ah, you're killing me, Cooper!
Can we get back to work?
Sure, sure, sure.
You guys ever use any toys?
Toys?
I do have a model rocket
next to my bed.
A rocket?
You're a freak! I love it!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org