What are you drawing
over there?
A hypothetical containment field
for a Frisbee-sized wormhole
that could serve as a portal
to a parallel universe.
Oh, you silly doodlebug.
You know,
a lot of scientists believe
that making contact
with other life-forms
would probably not
end well for us.
It's a Frisbee-sized wormhole,
Leonard.
You can block it with a Frisbee.
Calm down.
Do you expect me
to build this?
I expect you to wipe the pudding
off your chin. Gentlemen.
Have you guys ever noticed
that Sheldon
always disappears every day
at 2:45?
Really?
He probably just goes
to the bathroom.
Actually, no,
he goes to the bathroom
at 8:00 a.m.
with optional follow-ups
at 1:45 and 7:10
on high-fiber Fridays.
It's sad that
you know that.
Oh, that's just the tip
of the sadness iceberg.
I'm looking
at his public calendar.
2:45 to 3:05, nothing.
Yesterday, 2:45 to 3:05,
nothing.
Last week, nothing.
Last month, nothing.
He never has anything booked
during that time.
20 minutes a day,
completely unaccounted for.
We should figure out
where he goes.
Ooh, this is exciting.
Like one of my classic
murder mystery
dinner parties.
Right, the case of
who murdered
three Saturday nights
of my life?
Colonel Koothrapali
in ten
with the olive spread.
It was tapenade
and you guys suck.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 6x08 ?
The 43 Peculiarity
Original Air Date on November 15, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
So, how was work today?
Well, I spent most
of the afternoon growing
isotopically pure crystals
for neutrino detection.
That sounds like fun.
Yeah, it was.
Oh, good, I guessed right.
Who you talking to?
Oh, just this guy
I met at school.
Oh, great.
We're still dating, right?
Relax. He's just a friend.
We're doing
an oral report together.
He's really nice.
I'm sorry, what was that?
I had a little stroke
after "oral."
Would you stop?
Look, he just moved here
from London, okay?
He doesn't really know anybody.
Oh, good, an English accent,
the sexiest accent you can have.
No.
That's not true.
There's French, there's Italian.
No, you're right, it's the best.
Did you tell him
you have a boyfriend?
It didn't come up.
Well, maybe you should tell him.
What am I supposed to say?
Say, "Can't talk right now.
"Hanging with my boyfriend.
England sucks, you suck,
USA number one."
Fine.
"Hanging with my boyfriend.
Talk to you later."
Happy?
Yes. Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
What did he say?
Nothing.
What?
"Did your boyfriend make
you type that?"
I hate this guy.
Don't be like that.
Come on, trust me,
he's hitting on you.
No, he's not.
We're just friends.
Look, is this gonna be
a problem?
Because he's supposed
to come over tomorrow to work.
Really? Here?
If it makes you uncomfortable,
I'll switch partners,
even though
the thing's due next week
and everyone already
has a partner
and I'll probably end up
failing the class.
That'd be great. Thank you.
2:44,
right on schedule.
Hey, Sheldon.
Oh, hello.
Raj and I
are heading over
to the genetics lab to pet
the glow-in-the-dark bunny.
Want to come with us?
No, thank you.
Are you sure? They
turn off the lights,
and it's like a cute
little laser show
that poops all
over the place.
I'm quite sure. Good day.
Well, where
are you going?
Where are you going?
We just told you.
I just told you.
No, you didn't.
Well, it's your word against
mine; see you in court.
Should we follow him?
I don't know, I'm torn.
I want to know
where he's going,
but now I kind of want
to play with the bunny.
Hi, guys.
Hey, Alex, do you know
where your boss just went?
No.
Don't you know
his schedule?
All I know is corduroy
makes too much noise
and I have to go find
"quieter pants."
Come on.
Boy, what I wouldn't give
to get her out of those pants...
and into something
a little more stylish.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This is where
he goes?
What's in there?
I think it's
an old storage room.
What could he be doing in there
every day for 20 minutes?
Well, he's not doing
20-minute abs,
because if he were,
he would have way better abs.
Can you hear anything?
Not yet.
What are you doing?
I'm listening.
Can't you face the
other way and listen?
I can't do anything right
for you, can I?
What the hell
is he up to?
He is kind of a weirdo.
Maybe he's got Leonard Nimoy
chained up in there.
Or Bill Gates.
Or Stephen Hawking.
Why would he chain
up Stephen Hawking?
Howard, please, you can't treat
the man differently
just because he's disabled.
That's not okay.
If you're wondering why
I've been staring
through the peephole,
I'm trying to get a look
at this guy
who's coming over to Penny's.
To be honest,
I didn't know you were here.
It's not a big deal.
He's just in her history class.
They're working
on a project together.
I don't even know why I care.
You know what, I don't care.
You think you don't care.
This is silly.
I have nothing
to worry about.
Oh, I don't know.
Statistically speaking,
I'm sure you have something
to worry about.
What do you mean?
Well, if we assume
your looks are average,
right off the bat,
50% of men on Earth
are more attractive than you.
That's 1.5 billion
handsome lads standing by,
waiting to rain on your parade.
Well, yeah, but this
isn't just about looks.
I'm way above average
in a lot of other things.
Not height, vision, athleticism,
or ability
to digest dairy products.
I'm talking
about important things
like emotional maturity.
You were just spying on your
girlfriend through a peephole.
I liked it better
when you thought I wasn't here.
I'm not saying you don't
have attractive qualities.
Your choice of friends
is impeccable,
you're a good sleeper.
And last but not least,
you buy the grapes I like.
You're a real catch
compared to some snoring guy
with a fridge full
of lousy grapes.
None of this matters.
I trust that Penny cares
about me,
and nothing's gonna happen
with this guy.
Well, unless of course
he's a skilled hypnotist.
What?
While unlikely, it's still
a statistical possibility.
She might be performing
sexual acts with him
and not even know it.
Now you're just being
ridiculous.
Am I?
The mind's
a mysterious thing, Leonard.
He could be having
the time of his life
while she thinks she's
a chicken pecking for corn.
Look at us, sneaking around
in the middle of the night
like a couple
of cat burglars.
I think we're more
like ninjas.
I don't want to be a ninja;
I want to be a cat burglar.
Fine, I'll be a ninja,
you be a cat burglar.
No, we both have to
be the same thing.
Okay, we're ninjas.
Thank you.
But next time, we'll
be cat burglars.
It's locked.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Now, you stand guard,
I'm going to...
It's locked.
Just keep an eye out.
I'll have this open
in a minute.
When did you learn
how to pick locks?
When I was starting to do magic
in junior high,
I thought I could be
an escape artist
like Harry Houdini.
How did that work out?
Pretty good.
I managed to escape friends,
popularity,
and every party thrown
in a 12-mile radius.
There. Ready?
Hold on, hold on.
What?
Sheldon is a very smart man,
and he obviously wants
to keep this a secret.
Yeah, so?
What if it's
booby-trapped?
Don't worry, I'm one
step ahead of him.
Great, what's your pl...
Are we good?
Yeah.
Huh.
Forty-three.
What the hell
does that mean?
I don't know.
The solution to an equation?
Maybe.
It's a prime number.
Encryption systems
are built on prime numbers.
What kind of secret does
Sheldon have to encrypt?
He's always been
very cagey
about what he puts
in his egg salad
to make it so tasty.
It's paprika.
Really?
Well, okay, one mystery solved.
Okay, good night.
Thanks, Cole.
See you at school.
See you.
I'll be right back.
I thought you left
a long time ago.
What's up?
Hey.
You moving into the apartment
on the fifth floor?
No, I was just visiting
a friend.
Oh, cool.
That cute blonde on four?
Yeah. You know her?
I, well,
I see her around.
I like to keep my distance
because her boyfriend
is a pretty scary dude.
Really?
Yeah.
He's ganged up.
She told me
he's a scientist.
That's the name of his gang.
The Scientists.
They are crazy.
Well, thanks for the tip.
No problem, brother.
Stay frosty.
We're still dating, right?
Oh, hello, Dr. Hofstadter.
Hey, Alex,
and call me Leonard.
Dr. Hofstadter is my father.
And my mother.
And my sister.
And our cat.
Although, I'm pretty sure
Dr. Boots Hofstadter's degree
was honorary.
May I join you, Leonard?
Sure.
Thanks.
Hey, Alex,
let me ask you something.
My girlfriend
knows this guy at school.
He's got an English accent.
Ooh, I love English accents.
Yeah, you all do.
Anyway, I feel like
he's hitting on her.
She says he's just being nice
and that I should trust her.
It's probably harmless.
You know how it is.
I'm sure you get hit on
all the time.
Right.
Because girls are always like,
"Ooh, that guy owns
two Star Trek uniforms
"and gets a lot
of ear infections.
I got to get me some of that."
I don't know,
I bet it happens
more than you realize.
Trust me, it doesn't.
You sure?
You're cute, you're funny.
Maybe you're getting hit on,
and you don't even know it.
Really?
I'm pretty sure.
Okay, I got to get back to work.
Thanks for listening.
No problem.
Hope-hope no girls rip my
clothes off on the way.
Come on,
we're smart guys.
We can figure this out.
Forty-three.
What is 43?
Besides my mom's neck size.
It's the atomic number
for technetium.
That stuff's radioactive.
Do you think
he's building a bomb?
It took him two years
to put together
that Lego Death Star;
I'm not worried.
Ooh, this could be something.
43 is the number of calories
in half a cup
of fat-free yogurt.
Why would you know that?
I'm sorry.
We can't all eat whatever
we want and still stay thin.
Wait, in the Hitchhikers
Guide to the Galaxy,
isn't 43 the answer
to the question
of life, the universe,
and everything?
That's 42, dumb-ass.
Hey, hey.
Feelings.
We should stop.
I'm exhausted.
Yeah, me, too.
We've got more
important things to do.
Who cares what
stupid 43 means?
Not me.
Let's go home.
You want
to get something to eat?
Sounds good.
What the balls is 43?!
I have to know!
Hi.
Hey, shouldn't you be out
with your gang,
spray painting equations
on the side of buildings?
Come on, I'm sorry.
I just can't believe
you don't trust me.
I do, of course I do.
Then why did you embarrass me
in front of my friend,
who, by the way,
knew exactly who you were?
Really?
Your picture's on my refrigerator.
Oh.
You know, I'm really starting
to not like this guy.
What is your problem?
Do you use up
all your thinking at work
and then have none left over
for when you get home?
I don't know.
It's hard sometimes.
Everywhere you go,
guys hit on you, even if
I'm standing right there.
And they're all taller than me.
Why is everyone taller
than me?
You know what,
this is all in my head.
It's my problem, not yours.
Leonard, why do you
always do this?
Listen to me,
you're the one I'm with.
You know I love you,
so will you please relax
because you're driving me crazy.
You know that's the first time
you ever said that you love me.
Yeah.
We're just supposed to
pretend it's not a big deal?
That's...
exactly what we're gonna do
because...
you're about to make me cry,
and we both know
if I start crying,
you're gonna start crying.
You're right, you should go.
All right.
She loves me.
"Hey, it's Alex.
"Nice having coffee with you.
"If you want to talk more,
I'm always available.
Smiley face, smiley face."
What a friendly girl.
Okay, picture's up.
Looks like the camera's working.
That's good quality video.
It better be. It's the spare
camera for the Mars rover.
How did you get
your hands on that?
Million dollar camera--
ten dollar lock.
Oh, my God,
here he comes.
This is it.
What the hell
is that thing?
I don't know.
This is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Experimental log.
Wormhole generator test 44.
Wormhole generator test?
The first 43 parallel universes
I've checked proved to be empty.
I see no reason to suspect
universe number 44
will be any different.
Oh, my God!
Holy crap!
Oh! It's eating my face!
Aah! It's eating his face!
I found your Webcam
and replaced the video feed.
You two should be ashamed
of yourselves.
Sheldon, we're really sorry.
Yeah, really sorry.
Sorry?
You may not realize it,
but I have difficulty navigating
certain aspects of daily life.
You know,
understanding sarcasm,
feigning interest in others,
not talking about trains
as much as I want to.
It's exhausting.
Which is why,
for 20 minutes a day,
I like to go down to that room,
turn my mind off
and do what I need to do
to recharge.
But what are you doing in there?
And what does 43 mean?
You don't need to know,
you don't deserve to know,
and you will never know.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Drat.
I'm never going to get
to 43 again.
One, two, three, four...
Rats.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org