I don't know why I avoided
the Harry Potter books
for so long.
These are great.
I just started number six.
That's a good one.
Dumbledore dies in that one.
Yeah, I know,
I didn't see it coming, either.
Why would you say that?
You brought up
the subject.
I contributed an interesting
fact on that subject.
It's called the art
of conversation.
Okay, your turn.
That was a huge spoiler.
Good.
What is wrong with you?
If I did that, you'd bitch
about it for weeks.
Oh, really, Leonard?
Are you going to have
another one of your hissy fits?
Hissy fits?
I have hissy fits?
Yes, and I have a theory why.
Because of
your lactose intolerance,
you switched over to soy milk.
Soy contains
estrogen-mimicking compounds.
I think your morning Cocoa Puffs
are turning you
into a hysterical woman.
You are unbelievable.
I don't know why
I put up with you.
You're controlling,
you're irritating...
There you go again--
nag, nag, nag.
You're only proving my point,
little lady.
You know what?
Screw you, Sheldon.
You are the most annoying person
I have ever met.
What? I'm annoying?
You criticize my behavior
all the time.
"Sheldon, don't talk
about your bowel movements
over breakfast."
"Sheldon, when the president
of the university
"is giving a eulogy
at a funeral,
don't yawn
and point at your watch."
"Sheldon,
don't throw away my shirts
'cause you think they're ugly."
You're impossible.
That's it. I don't...
I don't have to
put up with this.
Actually, I have your signature
on a roommate agreement
that says you do.
Aw.
Here's what I think
of your roommate agreement.
You pick that up right now.
No.
Roommate agreement,
section 27, paragraph 5:
The roommate agreement,
like the American flag,
cannot touch the ground.
I don't care.
I don't have to do
anything you say because...
I don't think I want
to live here anymore.
Where are you going?
To live with Penny and not you,
you crazy bastard.
Crazy bastard?
Yes.
Leonard, wait.
What?
Dobby the elf dies
in book seven.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 6x15 ?
The Spoiler Alert Segmentation
Original Air Date on February 7, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Here you go.
Great. Come on in.
What, you don't say thank you?
It's my suitcase.
I lent it to you two years ago.
Well, then, I should tell you
I broke the wheel
and the handle.
So, is everyone
from Bernadette's company
going to Vegas?
No, just me, her
and a couple of the big wigs.
It's part of a bonus she got.
Cool. Did she discover
a cure for something?
Not exactly.
They spent a ton of
money developing this
dandruff medication
that had the side effect
of horrible anal leakage.
Is there a good
anal leakage?
Anyway, it was
Bernie's idea
to rebrand the stuff as a
cure for constipation.
Way to make lemonade.
You know, from around the
corner where fudge is made.
Hey, I got a favor to ask.
Sure.
My mom's been kind of
an emotional wreck
since that dentist
she was dating dumped her.
Dumped her?
What, did he use a forklift?
Sorry.
There's nothing funny
about morbid obesity.
She's huge. It was funny.
Anyway, I was
just hoping
that maybe you could check in
on her tomorrow night
and make sure she's doing okay.
Dude, I'm a single man.
Saturday night
is my party night.
Really?
What do you got going on?
I don't know,
maybe drive down to Hollywood,
hit a few hot spots,
see if I can get lucky.
Okay, tell me
if this sounds familiar.
You pay $15 to park,
you stand on the sidewalk
for an hour
until you break down
and give the bouncer
20 bucks to let you in.
You push your
way to the bar,
where you drink
an $18 cosmopolitan,
then you stare at a pretty girl
and imagine your perfect life
together.
Your children, grandchildren.
Meanwhile, she leaves
with a guy who claims
he wrote
Beverly Hills Chihuahua.
Then you give up
on anyone ever loving you,
go to Marie Callender's,
buy a pie
and eat it in your car
in the parking lot.
What time should I be
at your mother's?
I told her around 7:00.
I swear, that man is
the most egotistical,
insufferable human
being I have ever met.
Yeah, but you two make
such a cute couple.
Like Burt and Ernie.
You guys even teach me stuff
about words and numbers.
Well, I've had it.
I am done.
I can't... I can't live with him
for one more minute.
Wow. Where are you going to go?
I was thinking
here with you.
Oh.
That a problem?
No, not at all.
No, it's-it's great.
It's terrific. I...
You know, I just can't help
feel bad about Sheldon.
I mean...
how's he going to get by
without you?
Ernie.
He's got Amy now.
Yeah, he does,
but it's not the same.
Why?
Um...
Well, um, all right.
You-you know how in Harry Potter
and the Half-Blood Prince,
Ron didn't abandon Harry
just because
Harry started
dating Ron's sister?
Harry and Ginny
get together?
Sorry.
Spoiler alert.
My point is, as much
as I want to live with you,
I can't do it knowing
how much Sheldon needs you.
Please, the only
thing he needs me for
is to be his whipping boy,
his-his stooge, his doormat.
Well, you know what they say:
if it ain't broke...
Wow.
It sounds to me like you don't
want us to live together.
No. No, no, I do.
I do. It's just...
I mean, it's a really big step.
Is it?
We're together all the time.
Financially,
it makes great sense.
Can you think of one reason
why we shouldn't do this?
Well... um...
I'm just a little thirsty.
Yeah.
I got nothing.
Great. I'll go get my stuff.
Yeah.
Okay, all right,
don't freak out.
You can make this work.
Oh, could you clear off
a shelf for me in the bathroom?
I take a lot of medicine.
Oh, please let
some of it be Xanax.
Are you ready for dessert?
No, thank you, Mrs. Wolowitz.
As it is, I'm going to have
to carry my stomach out of here
like I'm a fireman
rescuing an infant.
Oh, please.
You're a tall glass
of brown water.
Have dessert.
Well, I-I really couldn't.
But, uh, I've had a lovely time
eating your brisket
and hearing about the things
you've had removed
from your body over the years.
Didn't know you could have
a cyst inside another cyst.
The doctor said they were
like Russian nesting dolls.
Well, if you have to go,
how about I put a little
doggie bag together for you?
That would be lovely.
Thank you.
Mrs. Wolowitz, uh...
are you okay?
Don't mind me.
I just cry
when I'm lonely
and have nothing
to live for.
I, uh...
I suppose I could stay
for some dessert.
Great. You like
chocolate chip cheesecake?
Sure.
I'll make one.
One vintage Mr. Mxyzptlk
action figure.
That's Leonard's.
Children's toy.
One Star Trek:
The Next Generation phaser.
That's Leonard's.
Children's toy.
One Game of Thrones collector's
edition Longclaw sword.
Oh... Leonard and I
bought that together.
That's a bit
of an ethical conundrum.
Eh, I'll keep it.
So, uh, what's your plan
moving forward?
Uh, suppose I'll have to find
and cultivate a new roommate.
What a task
that will be.
Do you know how uncivilized
Leonard was when I took him in?
No.
Oh, it took me forever to get
him on a bathroom schedule.
He would just go
whenever the mood struck him.
Like a dog-boy.
Exactly.
What if you could
find a roommate
who was a scientist
and already familiar
and comfortable with your ways?
That would be ideal.
If a person like that existed,
I would sign on,
no further questions asked.
Great. Here I am!
Wait.
Here who is where?
Me.
Aren't I your
perfect roommate?
Um...
Think about it, Sheldon.
I'm not a stranger,
we're intellectually
compatible,
I'm willing to chauffeur
you around town,
and your personality quirks,
which others find abhorrent
or rage-inducing,
I find cute as a button.
What do you think?
Um...
Tell me one reason why this
isn't a fantastic idea.
Um...
See? You can't.
I'm gonna go see
if Leonard's room
is big enough for my water bed.
Um...
Good buddy Leonard.
What do you want?
Hey, good buddy.
So, uh, I was
just talking to Amy,
and she made me realize
that this little dust-up
between you and me
is much ado about nothing.
Is that so?
Yes.
All is forgiven,
so come back home.
I'll make you
some soy hot chocolate,
and then I'll you tell you
about our exciting new
devil-may-care bathroom policy.
Cut to the chase, Sheldon.
Okay. Amy's decided
she wants to move in with me,
so I need you to come back home,
you lovable scamp.
That's a lot of product.
Hey.
What's going on?
Oh, get this:
Suddenly, Sheldon
wants me back
because Amy wants
to move in with him.
Really? Interesting.
Well, too late, pal.
I'm not going anywhere.
Penny and I are very happy
living together.
Isn't that right?
It's like the happiness
won't ever leave
the apartment.
Leonard, please.
You know Amy moving in
marks a level of intimacy
our relationship
isn't ready for.
Yes! That is a real thing.
And it doesn't mean you
don't care about each other;
it just means things
are moving at a pace
you're not comfortable with,
and that's fine.
Well, if he doesn't
want to live with her,
then he should
tell her how he feels.
Well, maybe he doesn't
know how to say it
without hurting
her feelings.
Feelings?
What am I, a hippie
at a love-in? No.
The problem is,
she laid out a series
of logical arguments
that I couldn't refute.
That is the worst,
isn't it?
Yes.
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
I can't help you.
Oh, spoiler alert:
This door's about
to slam in your face.
Oh, there you are.
When do I get a key
to our apartment?
Um...
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hello?
Hey. How'd it go last night
with my mom?
Okay, I guess.
What time did you leave?
Actually, I'm still here.
What? You spent the night?
Yeah. Uh...
after dinner, we watched
a rerun of Rockford Files,
and then she opened a bottle
of, uh, cream sherry,
and the next thing I know,
she was tucking me
into your bed.
You wore my pajamas?
Mm-hmm.
How do you sleep
in these things?
Silk pajamas on satin sheets?
I slid out of the bed,
like, three times.
Rajesh!
You up?
You ready for breakfast?
Oh, boy. Breakfast.
Okay, Raj, listen to me.
You need to get out of there.
But I have a cream sherry
hangover and I smell blintzes.
If you don't leave now,
she'll use food and guilt
to keep you there
for the rest of your life.
Oh, Howard, stop.
Trust me, you're not Jewish.
That's how they get you.
You're being silly.
I can leave whenever I want.
Oh, really? Where are
your clothes and your shoes?
They're on the chair,
right over...
Oy vey.
Hello, home wrecker.
What did I do?
You gave Leonard
somewhere to go.
Thanks to you, Amy's out buying
his and hers bath towels.
Like I'd ever dry myself
with something
that has a possessive pronoun
on it.
Okay.
Listen, the truth is
I don't want him living with me.
Great. Kick him out.
Break his heart.
Everybody wins.
No, I don't want
to break his heart.
I love him.
This is just happening too fast.
You think this is fast?
It's just a matter of time
before I see Amy's leg stubble
in my shower.
Yeah, and I've seen those legs.
You might want
to get some Drano.
Hold on.
If you don't want
to live with Leonard,
why don't you just tell him?
Well, you know how he is.
He's sensitive and emotional.
That's because he drinks
too much soy milk.
Well, I don't know
what else we can do
but tell them the truth.
I suppose there's no choice
but to face the crying,
angry accusations
and the high-pitched wails
of despair.
Yeah.
And who knows
how Amy will react.
Here's some more ice.
Oh, thanks.
What were we thinking?
We should have just done it
the regular way.
Those Chinese acrobats
in Cirque du Soleil
made it look so easy.
Honestly,
if I could bend that far,
what would I need with you?
If you could bend that far,
you'd be doing us both a favor.
Hey, Raj. What's up?
You were right!
I can't get out of here!
You're still
at my mother's?
I'm trapped.
My clothes have been
in the laundry all day,
and she hid my keys.
I think they might be
in her bra,
because she jingles
when she walks.
What do I do?
Hey, you wanted a woman
in your life.
Now you got one.
Come on, Howard, help me.
Rajesh, tatellah,
I ran you a bath.
Oh, my God.
She's not gonna bathe me,
is she?
Gee, I wish I could tell you no.
All right, well,
thanks again for helping me out.
But, Howard...
Should we go back
and rescue him?
It's too late.
We'll see him
at his Bar Mitzvah.
Here you go.
I picked up the Chinese food
just the way Leonard used to.
Is it kung pao chicken?
Yes.
Brown rice, not white rice?
Spicy mustard
from the Korean deli?
Yes. I did good, right?
Yes.
Amy,
are you worried
that us living together
will take the mystery
out of our relationship?
No.
Yeah, why would you?
Oh, and, uh, check this out.
I took the liberty of scripting
a new outgoing voice mail
message for both of us.
"Hello. This is Sheldon."
"And this is Amy."
"We're not home right now."
"'Cause we out
dropping science, son."
"Leave a message."
Beep.
You can't live here.
What?
Why?
Is it the message?
I only used urban slang
to sound tough
so people wouldn't break in.
No.
It's not the message.
Well, what is it, then?
I did everything
just the way you like it.
You did.
Then what the hell, Sheldon?!
We have been going out
for over two years,
and I have been nothing
but patient with you!
I watch your dopey
space movies.
I signed your
ridiculous contract.
I even stopped wearing lip gloss
'cause you said
it made my mouth look
too slippery.
I am the best
girlfriend
you're ever
gonna have.
You give me one good reason
why I can't live here.
It's Penny's fault.
What?
She doesn't want
to live with Leonard,
so he has to come
live here again.
She's the snake in our garden.
She's the reason
we can't be happy.
Hey, Ames.
Yeah.
"Hey, Ames," nothing.
I was all set to move in
with Sheldon, and now I hear
I can't 'cause you don't want
to live with Leonard.
What?
Sheldon, what did you say?
I said the truth.
You don't want to live with
Leonard, and you know it.
Since when don't you want
to live with me?
Oh, don't get all huffy.
You're the one who
decided to move in
without even asking
me if I was ready.
Yeah, I think we should talk
about that.
And since you love
the truth so much,
why don't you tell Amy you
don't want to live with her
instead of
blaming it on me?
I thought we were talking
about the other thing.
You're a coward.
Well, the evidence
does support that.
Come on, Amy,
let's go drink wine
and talk about what jerks
our boyfriends are.
You know what would show them?
I should move in here with you.
Um...
Do you want to...
catch up on some Walking Dead?
Okay.
Have you seen the one
where Lori dies?
No.
Or maybe she doesn't.
Let's find out.
Where you going?
No!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org