Is anyone else troubled by
the Spider-Man theme song?
Why would it trouble you?
It's, like, your third favorite
cartoon theme song.
It is, right behind
? Do do-do do-do,
Inspector Gadget... ?
...and ? Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles ?
? Heroes in a half-shell
? Turtle power!
However, the Spider-Man lyrics
posit that
"Spider-Man, Spider-Man
does whatever a spider can."
Yeah, so?
I can think of many things
Spider-Man can't do
that a spider can.
One: crawl in your ear and die.
Two: legally leave Guatemala
without a passport.
Three: have sex with a spider.
Can we change the subject?
Spiders give me
the jeebie-jeebies.
It's "heebie-jeebies."
I know, but that sounds
anti-Semitic.
Anyway, I was thinking
we could have a little
film festival tonight.
The theme: movies that killed
their franchises.
Oh.
Like Jaws 4, Indiana Jones 4,
Daredevil 1.
Miss Congeniality 2:
Armed and Fabulous.
I mean, you know a movie's bad
when my homegirl Sandy B.
can't save it.
Penny's working tonight;
I'm in.
Not me.
I'm having dinner
with Bernadette and her parents.
Fun. We know how much
you love that.
It's torture.
Especially with her dad.
We have nothing in common.
You know what I like to do
when I'm forced to speak
with those beneath my
intellectual station?
I bring up an
interesting topic,
like the difference between
Spider-Man and spiders.
Thanks, Sheldon.
I'll try that
with my father-in-law.
No, you can't
use that one.
That's mine.
Uh, try this one
for an ice-breaker.
Uh, despite popular
lore, there is no place
in the continental United
States, Alaska or Hawaii
from which one can dig straight
through the center of the earth
and come up in China.
Great, thank you.
Actually, you can't
have that one either.
It's too good. Sorry.
What about you, Sheldon?
Do you have any plans tonight?
Sadly, yes.
Amy's taking me
to a memorial service.
It's for one of
her colleagues
who is of Asian descent, so
my planned conversational gambit
is to casually remark
that no matter how deep
they dig his grave, he'll never
make his way back to China.
That should lighten the mood.
What can I say?
I put the "fun" in funeral.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 6x10 ?
The Fish Guts Displacement
Original Air Date on Decxember 6, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Amy. Amy.
Oh, right, funeral.
Amy.
Hello, Sheldon.
I'm not allowed to wear
my Silver Surfer neck tie,
but you can wear a bathrobe?
I think I'm too sick
to go to the funeral.
You're sick?
You poor kid.
Well, see ya.
Sheldon, aren't you
gonna take care of me?
Me?
No. No, I'm not
that kind of doctor.
But our relationship agreement
clearly states
that when one of us is sick, the
other must take care of them.
Oh, I see the
confusion.
No, the intent
behind that clause
was to force you to take
care of me when I'm ill.
When you're feeling better,
you'll think that's funny.
Never mind. Good night, Sheldon.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Amy. Amy. Amy.
I made a commitment in writing
to comfort you
in times like this.
Additionally, you are
my girlfriend,
and I care about
your well-being.
Thank you, Sheldon.
You're welcome.
Now let's get this over with.
So, how have
you been?
Fine.
Good.
Fine is good.
How you liking retirement?
It's fine.
I'm sensing a theme.
You ever really think about
the Spider-Man theme song?
How's that dinner coming?
I just put it in.
It's gonna be a while.
I like rare chicken.
Let's do this.
You could die.
Death by chicken.
That's a pretty "fowl" way
to go.
Here's another
beer, honey.
Thank you.
So, Mrs. Rostenkowski, you took
that trip to the Grand Canyon.
How was it?
It was good.
Had no idea
you were the chatty one.
102.2.
Exactly what it was
half an hour ago.
It's like you're not even
trying to get better.
Sheldon, you don't get over
the flu in half an hour.
Well, not with that attitude.
I have to say, I'm finding your
bedside manner a little lacking.
I'm sorry.
I just want you to get better
as soon as possible.
And with that goal in mind,
let me ask you a question.
Do you believe in
the placebo effect?
Of course I do.
There have been many studies
proving its validity.
Great.
Now, this may look
like a Tic Tac...
...but it is really a powerful
medication specifically designed
to cure your illness as well as
freshen your breath.
Sheldon, this isn't helping.
Why don't you just let me
get some rest.
How can you sleep?
I'm not done
making you feel better.
I still have to put a
cold rag on your head,
sing to you and apply VapoRub
to your chest.
Y-You want to rub something
on my chest?
Yes.
All over it.
Maybe we should start with that.
Now you're being a
responsible patient.
Now, you may notice
some tingling.
Oh, I'm counting on it.
Oh.
Okay, dig in.
Hold up.
Bless us, O Lord
for these Thy gifts
which we are about to receive
from Thy bounty
through Christ our Lord. Amen.
Took the words
right out of my mouth.
So, Dad, have you done
any fishing lately?
I'm going next weekend.
Oh, you like to fish?
Yes.
Sure. I can hear it
in your voice.
Oh, if he didn't like it,
he wouldn't go.
You know, I hadn't
thought of that.
Help me.
Hey, Dad, maybe you could take
Howard fishing sometime.
Give you guys a chance to get
to know each other better.
No, no.
We know each other
well enough.
He's been talking
my ear off all night.
Howie, I think you'd have fun.
Fine, you can tag along.
Terrific.
My two favorite fellas
gone fishin'.
Well, hang on a
second, Bernie.
Next weekend, we
have that thing.
Whathing?
You know, the thing.
Oh, that thing.
No, I cancelled that thing.
All right, it's settled.
You and I are going fishing.
Great.
Thanks for the help.
I've never even
been fishing.
This is gonna
be a disaster.
If you don't want to look
foolish doing something,
you should practice.
Do you know how many beef
Wellingtons I made by myself
before I invited you guys over?
I'll give you a hint.
You can see them
here, here... and here.
Raj is probably right.
You should get someone
to give you some pointers.
Do either of you guys
know how to fish?
No.
But if you
catch anything,
I know how to steam
it in banana leaves.
Come on, we must know somebody
who can do manly stuff
like this.
S'up?
Step one: worms.
Ew!
Okay, right there,
"ew" is one of the things
you're not gonna want to say
in front of your father-in-law.
It's right up there with "icky"
and "get it away."
Now pick one up.
Really?
You're gonna have to do it
when you're fishing.
Okay.
What are you waiting for?
I don't know, for them
to die of natural causes.
Just pick up a worm
and put him on this hook.
Fine.
There.
I'm no expert,
but I think the hook has
to go through the worm.
Fine.
Sorry, Mr. Worm.
Sherm.
Sherm the Worm.
Hey, don't name him.
Just jab a hook in his face.
You got this, buddy.
Yeah, come on, Howard.
Hook that worm.
You can do it.
That's great.
Cheerleading--
way to man things up.
"And the control group displayed
"significantly fewer
genetic abnormalities.
"But, because of flaws
in the experimental design
"relating to
environment and diet,
they lived
inconclusively ever after."
The end.
That was great.
Rub my chest again.
No.
I need to get you down
for a nap.
For some reason, that VapoRub
gets you all fired up.
How's the poor thing?
Oh, I'm hanging in there.
Thanks for asking.
Okay, Amy,
I brought you some drugs
we were working
on in the lab.
This is proving really
good for congestion,
but there's a slight chance
it can make your tears
burn like acid,
so if you take it--
happy thoughts.
Uh, I'm going to draw
you a soothing bath.
Where's your bath thermometer?
I don't have a bath thermometer.
Fine. Then I'm going to draw you
a nerve-wracking bath
of indeterminate temperature.
This is a really
good expectorant.
Although some
test subjects reported
lactating uncontrollably
when they heard music.
Okay, okay, here's the deal.
I don't need your medicine.
I'm not sick.
I don't understand.
I got better two days ago.
It's just been so nice
having Sheldon take care of me.
So you've just
been lying to him?
See the stuff in my nose?
Rubber cement.
I don't mean to be judgy,
but this is the kind
of thing lunatics do.
All right.
I'll tell him.
Amy, would you
be strong enough
to bathe yourself,
or do you need my help?
I'll tell him tomorrow.
Mama needs a bath.
Now, let's assume,
by some miracle,
you actually catch a fish.
You're going to have to know
how to gut it.
So, what you're
going to do
is you're going to take
your knife,
slice him right up the belly.
You want me to stop?
No, I'm fine.
Keep going.
All right. Now, you
don't want to cut
too deep into its guts,
or the blood will just squirt
all over your face.
Oh, my God.
What is with you guys?
It's not our fault.
Our dads never did anything
like this with us.
What, never?
My dad was an
anthropologist.
The only father-son
time he spent
was with a 2,000-year-old
skeleton of an Etruscan boy.
I hated that kid.
Mine just took me
to his gynecology office.
I got so bored,
I'd put vaginal lubricant
on the bottom of my shoes
and pretend I was ice-skating.
Yeah, well, my quality
father-son time
was spending my adolescence
looking out the window
waiting for my dad
to come back someday.
Yeah, okay, Howard wins.
You know, maybe we didn't
have opportunities like this
when we were growing up,
but right now,
there's a dad that wants
to take you on a fishing trip.
You're right.
I should do this.
Great.
Here you go.
What you're
going to do
is you're going to
stick your thumb
down its throat, grab
the guts and pull.
Here we go.
Oh, look, it's a female.
You can see all the eggs.
? I'm walking on sunshine ?
? Whoa, oh
? And don't it feel good? ?
? Oh, yeah
Oh, Sheldon,
am I glad you're back.
Taking a turn for the worst.
I think I'm going to need
another bath.
I'm surprised to hear that.
See, the other day,
I was concerned
that you weren't recovering,
so while you
were sleeping,
I took a cheek swab
and had it cultured in the lab.
Oh?
I got the results back.
Have you developed any of
the following symptoms?
A growing nose,
or perhaps a warm sensation
in the trouser region?
Also known as
full-blown
"liar, liar, pants on fire."
All right, all right.
But I really was sick
at the beginning.
It's just been so nice
having you take care of me.
It hurts that you
would lie to me, Amy.
I thought our relationship
was based on trust
and a mutual admiration
that skews in my favor.
I feel terrible I did this.
It pains me to say it,
but I think some form
of penalty is in order,
so as to discourage this type
of behavior in the future.
I suppose that's fair.
What do you suggest?
In a perfect world,
I'd lock you
in a stockade in
the public square.
That probably
requires a permit.
I could not be allowed
to go to the opening
of the next Star Trek movie.
Oh, that seems
overly harsh.
You gave in to a
hun weakness.
You didn't kill a man.
You know, it's a
tad old-school,
but my father was not
one to spare the rod
when my brother would
sneak into his truck
and drink his
driving whiskey.
Are you saying
you want to spank me?
I don't want to.
But it looks like you
left me no choice.
That's true.
I've been a very bad girl.
Hi-ho, hi-ho, it's
off to fish we go.
That's what you're wearing?
No good?
The guy at
the sporting goods store
said these are what
fishermen wear.
Maybe in cartoons.
Wish I had known that
before I posted
all those pictures on Facebook.
All right,
let's hit the road.
I wouldn't mind shooting
some ducks in the morning.
Wait, now we're shooting things?
I like using a big shell.
You can't eat them afterwards,
but it's fun
watching them blow up.
Sir, I'm flattered
that you invited me,
and I really want you
to like me,
but...
I don't think this trip
is the way to do it.
And I can't return
these things
if there's chunks
of duck all over them.
So, why'd you
agree to come?
'Cause Bernadette made me.
I tried to back out, too.
My wife said I had to go.
Really?
Your wife makes you do stuff?
You're a big, scary cop.
You're an astronaut,
and your wife
makes you do things,
and she's only four feet tall.
So, what do we do now?
They expect us to go
away for the weekend.
Ah...
There's an Indian casino
near Palm Springs.
You know how to shoot craps?
No, but I'm not a
stranger to dice games.
I was the Temple Beth-El
Hebrew School Yahtzee champion.
Mazel tov.
I'll teach you how to play.
Really?
Thank you, sir.
Call me Mike.
Okay.
Oh, boy,
we're just married
to a couple of
ballbusters, huh, Mike?
That's my wife and daughter
you're talking about.
Great couple of gals.
I wouldn't go that far.
Are you prepared to
receive your punishment?
One second.
I want to put on some music.
Why?
I don't want to disturb
the people next door
while you discipline me.
Very well, then.
Get over my knee.
Let's begin.
Oh, my.
Excuse me.
You're not supposed to be
enjoying this.
Then maybe you should
spank me harder.
Maybe I will.
Ooh!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org