You both know
who we might need
to help deal
with the Darkness.
Castiel: You're Metatron?
The Metatron?
I'm not an archangel,
I'm the scribe of God.
Chuck Shurley?
Castiel:
He's a prophet of the Lord.
I don't know
how prophets are chosen.
I don't want
to be a prophet.
No, you don't at all.
- Obviously, I'm a god.
- You're not a god.
God?!
I'm hoping
that you and I can finish
what I started
a few months ago.
Metatron: You weren't alone
in the beginning.
Your sister
was with you.
Amara: I was the beginning,
and I will be the end.
I will be all that there is.
We're bonded.
You're the one who set me free.
[Glass shatters]
Sam: Our priority is to set
Lucifer loose on Amara.
After we exorcise
Lucifer out of Cass
and put him
into a new vessel.
Useless. Lucifer's hold
on him is too strong.
Archangel plus God power
doesn't trump God's sister.
I think you and I need
to have a nice long chat.
[Screams]
If Amara wipes the slate,
everything is destroyed.
My partner and I
have seen this before, okay?
Wes, Deputy Harris were infected
by something in this fog.
The amulet ... it burns hot
in God's presence.
Metatron: I mean, that's why
you're back, right?
This isn't her story.
It's mine.
What the hell's
going on here, exactly?
I'm happy to...
fill in the blanks,
but maybe
we should go somewhere
where we could actually
sit down.
We're not going anywhere
with you.
Okay, how do we even know
that you're really Chuck
and not just some crazy spell
or manifest...ation.
Kevin?
Guys!
You're looking stressed.
Especially you.
I-It's cool.
Trust Chuck.
Whatever it is
he needs you to do,
he must think
you can handle it.
I always trusted you.
Yeah, that ended well.
How did you ...
Are you okay? Um...
Yeah, I mean, you know,
given the circumstances.
Chuck: Yeah,
I don't mean to interrupt.
Kind of a plateful here.
And, Kevin...
you've been
in the Veil long enough.
It's time
you had an upgrade.
Holy crap.
? Supernatural 11x21 ?
All in the Family
Original Air Date on May 11, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Okay.
So, wow, um, Chuck ...
[Chuckles]
Well, I guess we don't
call you that, huh?
I prefer it.
Okay,
uh, “Chuck” it is.
[Sighs]
I'm sorry.
You're gonna have to, uh,
give Dean and me a moment
to start to process.
We didn't even know
you were around.
I mean, we knew about Chuck,
but we just didn't know about...
Chuck.
I mean, I-I-I was
hoping you were around.
I-I-I prayed and I ...
but I don't know if they
got, uh, lost in the spam or if ...
Sam?
- Yeah?
- Babbling.
Okay.
I'm getting that not
everyone's totally on board.
Here's the thing,
um...Chuck...
And I mean
no disrespect.
Um...
I'm guessing you came back
to help with the Darkness,
and that's great.
That's, you know ...
It's fantastic.
Um, but you've
been gone a ... a...
long, long time.
And there's so much crap
that has gone down
on the Earth
for thousands of years.
I mean, plagues and wars,
slaughters.
And you were,
I don't know,
writing books,
going to fan conventions.
Were you even aware,
o-or did you just tune it out?
I was aware, Dean.
But you did nothing.
And, again, I-I'm not trying
to piss you off.
You know, I don't want to turn
into a pillar of salt.
I actually ...
I didn't do that.
Okay.
People ...
People pray to you.
People build churches
for you.
They fight wars in your name,
and you did nothing.
You're frustrated.
I get it.
Believe me,
I was hands-on ...
Real hands-on for,
wow, ages.
I was so sure
if I kept stepping in,
teaching, punishing,
that these beautiful creatures
that I created...
would grow up.
But it only stayed the same.
And I saw that I needed
to step away
and let my baby find its way.
Being overinvolved
is no longer parenting.
[Sighs]
It's enabling.
But it didn't get
better.
Well, I've been
mulling it over.
And from where I sit,
I think it has.
Well, from where I sit,
it feels like you left us
and you're trying
to justify it.
I know you had
a complicated upbringing, Dean,
but don't confuse me
with your dad.
[Lucifer groans]
[Screams]
[Panting]
[Screaming]
Amara: End your suffering,
Lucifer.
Call out to him.
Beg him to save you.
[Laughs]
Want me to beg Daddy to come
rescue his screw-up of a son?
[Chuckles]
I'm no fan of Pops,
but he did make all of...
you know, everything.
And that's something
that you could never do,
because all you
ever wanted was nothing.
It's not
too inspiring, is it?
because all you
You're strong, Amara.
You may defeat him.
But you will never be him.
You have to understand
this about the Darkness ...
she's relentless,
a force beyond
human comprehension.
It's the only reason
I came off the sidelines.
Must have been great
being her brother, huh?
It was the worst.
Always telling me what to do,
making me do what she wanted.
I mean, you guys
know how that works.
So, where is she?
No freakin' idea, fellas.
She's warded herself
specifically against me.
What have you
come up with?
Zip, and we've been at it
for months.
Well...matter of time.
I've always had faith
in you...
...even if you didn't return
the favor.
Where's the guest room?
I could use a shower.
Uh, it's, um...
just down the hallway ...
the fourth door on the left.
[Clicks tongue]
[Sighs]
Hey, Chuck.
You know that she's got
Lucifer, right?
Uh-huh.
The way we heard it,
um...
last time when you bottled up
the Darkness,
it ... it took more
than just you.
I mean, we heard
that Lucifer was involved.
No.
No?
Lucifer was perhaps
my greatest hope
and my bitterest
disappointment.
Do you think if I could have
trusted him for a moment,
I would have put him
in the Cage?
And I wasn't gonna
mention this,
but thank you so much
for springing him.
That wasn't
really the plan, um...
Now, as bad as he was,
after all this time in prison,
he's probably worse.
And by now, he could have formed
an alliance with Amara.
Not walking
into that trap, guys.
So, no.
Thus spake the Lord.
Amara:
Something's out there.
Lucifer: Hmm, always is.
This is new.
Something's changed.
Maybe Dad picked up
on your latest slaughterfest.
Spoiled brat.
I needed solitude
and he needed a fan club,
so he made all that.
Then when I complained,
he stuffed me
in a hole for eons ...
with your help.
Stop whining.
I don't need this.
[Groans]
?
[Sighs]
Come on, Amara.
Where are you?
Amara:
I've missed you, Dean.
It's been a while
since we've spoken.
I'm aware
my brother has surfaced.
If you should cross paths,
if he should reach out to you,
he should know this ...
Lucifer, his favorite,
isn't doing so well.
Say nothing of the vessel,
your friend Castiel.
By choosing to ignore me,
my brother is allowing
this to happen.
These and...
other things.
I thought
you should know.
[Insects chirping]
[Tires screech, crash]
[Wind howls]
[Indistinct shouting,
screaming]
[Coughing]
[Keyboard keys clacking]
Anything?
Nada.
Yeah, thanks.
- Yeah.
You know, I can't believe
I'm gonna say this,
but, for once, I actually
wish Rowena was here.
I mean, maybe she could
track down Amara.
She's done it before.
Yeah, but you can bet she
and the Book are gonna
stay stashed until
this whole thing is over.
Where's Chuck?
Sleeping in, I guess.
Does God sleep?
I know he takes
really long showers.
Right, and sings, too ...
like, crappy old folk songs.
I had to tell him
to cool it three times.
You told God to cool it?
Yeah, I sleep.
You know, I know this
is a really strange situation and all,
but it's also
really amazing, you know?
I mean, it's God.
[Chuckles]
There's so many things
I want to ask him,
uh, like, uh,
t-the planets, you know?
Why are they round?
Or ears.
I always thought
they were strange.
Okay, fanboy, calm down.
Let's stay focused.
We got to find Lucifer
before it's too late.
Too late?
Amara is ...
she's in my head.
Hey, I didn't ask for it, okay?
She just showed up.
But she's showing me visions
of ... of Lucifer.
By Lucifer, I mean Cass,
and he looks like crap ...
like she's really doing
a number on him.
Shh.
Hey.
Morning.
Is that my robe?
I'm telling you guys,
it's a mistake
to get mixed up
with Lucifer.
Much as it pained me,
I had to walk away.
Too much drama.
Do you have any bacon?
You eat bacon?
Yeah.
Hey, guys,
this just came up.
Looks like that fog, the, um...
Amara fog, uh, hit another town.
And?
And this one wasn't
as lucky as the last one.
Thousands died.
Uh, everybody died.
But, uh,
except for one man.
How'd you miss
that one?
She's baiting me.
I can't respond every time.
I won't be manipulated.
Yeah, but thousands
of people are dead.
Unfortunately.
So find her.
Man: We have
breaking news at this hour
on the most recent
freak weather event.
State police are now confirming
that a mysterious toxic fog
engulfed the town of Lewis,
Oklahoma, late last night.
Reports are also confirmed
there were mass fatalities.
Descriptions of the event
are identical to those
of the fog that overwhelmed
another town in the days ...
?
[Cellphone ringing]
What?
I notice you've been in touched
with Chuck.
Well, I've got some...
information
you're gonna need to know.
Okay, say it.
No.
It's got to be in person ...
something I got to show you.
Professor Redfield.
FBI.
- Call me Donatello.
- Yeah.
I'm named after him.
[Chuckles]
The Mutant Ninja Turtle?
The, uh,
Renaissance sculptor.
Right, of course.
The cops think
I'm a terrorist.
I-I teach chemistry
at the university.
I-I lead a quiet life.
I have a cat!
Had a cat.
Well, we are, uh,
sorry for your loss.
Just a few questions.
Um, other than the fog, did you
notice anything or anyone
that seemed out of place
on the street that night?
It ... It all happened
so fast.
I, uh...
It was like
it came out of nowhere.
We hardly ever get fog,
and never like that.
[Chuckles]
It was horrible.
They were clutching
their throats
like ... like ...
like they were choking.
And...oh.
Their bodies ...
Oh, my God ...
these terrible black streaks.
[Gasping]
And that's when
it happened.
It was like nothing I've ever felt
before in my life. [Screaming]
It was like my head was
exploding, only not with pain ...
with ... with ... with knowledge
and ... and clarity!
Things that I'd never
known before.
Symbols and ... and voices ...
in languages I don't speak!
Then...
horrible...
horrible visions...
of destruction...
and death.
You think I'm crazy.
No, uh, not at all.
Just, uh, you know,
will you give us a moment?
I mean, you get that this is all
sounding familiar, right?
Yeah. Yeah, like when Kevin
found out he was a prophet.
So, what,
this guy's a prophet?
Yeah, but I thought
Crowley rounded up
all the future prophets
and tried to kill them.
Yeah,
but we rescued them
and Donatello
wasn't a part of that,
but, yeah, it's possible
Crowley missed a few.
And, obviously, he had no idea
he was next in line after Kevin.
How would he? He hadn't gotten
hit by the God power yet.
So, Amara's fog ...
could it have been
Amara's God power?
It's still God power.
All right,
I need a coffee.
Yeah.
Um...
am ... am I under arrest?
No, just, um...
want to check out a few more
aspects of your story.
Here we go.
Would you look at this?
Try and read it
a little.
Oh, I can't.
I ... I don't know
anything about it.
“Behold the face of God”"
That came right to me.
Who speaks this language?
- Angels.
Amara:
I need to see you, Dean.
Events are moving swiftly
and everything will change.
I need to meet with you,
but not like this.
Somewhere alone.
Donatello: I can't be a prophet.
I'm an atheist and a chemist!
I-I believe in molecules,
not God.
All right, well, we're pretty
sure that prophets
don't even know
they're in the game
until they've actually been
touched by God, so...
I-I was touched by God?
Or possibly
his sister, Amara.
- He has family?
- Yeah.
She wants him gone so she can
annihilate the universe.
That's the headline.
- What?
And since you might have
a hotline to her,
we're hoping you can
help us find her.
W-Why would you want
to find her?
We got to rescue this guy
she's holding.
- Who is?
- Lucifer, her nephew.
Who's possessing an angel
at the moment.
Yeah.
Oh.
[Door handle rattles]
It's locked.
Yeah, that, too.
Sometimes we keep monsters
in the back.
I ... I ... I can't do this!
- Yeah, you can.
- No, I promise you I can't.
Look, we can't force you to do
this. You've got to want this.
It ... It's like asking me
to believe in Santa Claus.
- Oh, well, actually ...
- Dean, not now.
Okay, look, we ... we're not
asking you to believe
that this is true,
just act like you do.
People do it
all the time.
[Shudders]
What?
I ... I-I don't know.
I ... I think
I'm sensing something.
Something big.
Like Amara?
I don't think so.
Although, how would I know?
[Sighs]
Could it be...
Him?
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
?
Hey, Chuck.
We, uh, found someone.
I think
he's the next prophet.
Neat-o.
Is that my computer?
I've never seen
so much porn.
Not in one sitting.
It's ... I'm gonna...
So, uh, listen.
He ... He's ...
He's a little nutted out
about the whole booga-booga
of it all,
so maybe just dial back
the ... the God stuff.
[Clicks tongue]
[Door opens]
No pants on.
Sam?
- Yeah?
Yeah.
All right, you're safe.
Come on.
[Sighs]
Donatello,
good to see ya.
Sorry about your cat.
You ... You know me?
I made you.
I made all of you, even the ones
who aren't born yet.
Oh, my God.
It's you.
G-Good to meet you, Sir!
Your ... Your celestial
magnificence, your ...
Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
He ... He just kind of
goes by Chuck.
So, we good?
Y'all signed up?
Uh...I-I-I guess you know
that I was an atheist,
until 10 minutes ago.
Is that an issue?
Not for me.
I mean, I believe in me.
But your skepticism is
to be expected.
I did include free will
in the kit. [Chuckles]
[Clicks tongue]
Welcome aboard.
? Don't let the rain come down ?
? Oh, no, don't let the rain
come down ?
? O? no, don't let the rain
Oh, uh, barkeep,
dos margaritas!
Top-shelf tequila please
for my amigos.
Their treat.
All right.
We're here.
Don't try to pull any crap.
And what variety of crap
could I possibly pull?
I've lost my grace.
Look at me.
I got nothing.
Okay, why did you
have to see us?
What's so urgent?
- [Sighs]
So, I, uh, notice you've been
in touch with Chuck.
A.K.A., you know who.
Yeah, yeah.
Is this going anywhere?
Yes, Chuck agreed
to take on Amara.
He said that?
Used those words?
- Pretty much.
Huh.
So, what ...
he's not confronting Amara?
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
He's ... He's going to ...
He's gonna...meet with her.
He's just not gonna
take her down.
He's gonna...
sacrifice himself.
Let her do whatever
she wants with him.
Do you really expect us
to buy this?
No.
Of course not.
Here.
Buy this.
[Thuds]
Ignore the typos,
but read it.
It's in his own words.
It's not an autobiography.
It's a suicide note.
[Child laughing]
You wanted to talk.
This seemed
as good a place as any.
Look at them ...
endlessly optimistic.
The wind blows over his tower,
he rebuilds.
Always gets me.
If that's so,
why are you bailing?
When you see Amara,
you're throwing in the towel?
[Sighs]
Metatron.
Loose lips.
But you think I'm a dick.
Why do you care?
Because before
you went M.I.A...
you did a lot.
Thank you.
And what you call
throwing in the towel,
I call strategy.
How is death by your sister
a strategy?
I know her.
Her beef is with me.
Yeah, but I still don't
understand how ... how dying
is a ...
a blueprint for success.
I don't be dying.
I'll be caged.
I trade myself for...
everything I created.
It goes on.
Okay, well, the, um,
Amara that I know is...
a mountain of ...
of pissed off.
I mean, she spent a ...
a gazillion years in solitary.
The only thing she's thinking
is ... is it's her turn.
And I'll give it to her,
as long as she accepts the deal.
The deal?
What...
She's gonna eliminate you,
and then she's gonna destroy
everything that you've created.
She's told me this
personally.
[Sighs]
You started this.
You started all of this,
but does that give you
the right to end it?
You know, we're not just
some toys you throw away.
I think you owe us
more than that.
If my plan doesn't work,
then humans will step up.
You, Sam,
others that are the chosen
will have to find a way.
It's why
I saved you years ago.
You're the firewall
between light and darkness.
No.
No, I...
Look, give me a ...
a vampire, and I'm good.
But this ...
God's sister?
That is way above
my pay grade.
I...
It...
Bottom line is i-it's you
who has to take her out.
And look,
and then after that,
you know,
get a condo in Cancun.
I don't care!
[Footsteps approaching]
I got you a beer.
I don't know if you drink.
I do now.
Well...
[Sighs]
I don't know...
if Chuck is leaning our way.
You don't know?
If we do get Lucifer
for the added muscle,
then...maybe he'll
play ball.
I thought
they hated each other.
Yeah, they do.
[Door opens]
Wow.
I so miss
being an atheist.
Sam: All right, Metatron.
Make it quick.
Don't touch anything.
Fine.
Dean!
Thanks for inviting me.
Inviting you?
You've been circling
the building all night.
You sent me 200 text messages
with dumbass emojis.
You got three minutes.
Oh.
Donatello!
Pleasure to meet you.
Metatron, scribe of God.
I was there
when you were designed.
I wrote your name on the inside
of the angels' eyelids.
He's freaking me out.
Okay.
You said you wanted to help.
Besides world-class douchery,
what do you have to offer?
Oh, nothing.
I just transcribed the angel
tablet and know all the spells.
And I know
what makes Amara tick.
And I had a relationship
with the big guy for eons.
Shall I keep going?
Ah!
That's mine!
As much as I hate
to admit this...
he kind of has a point.
- I don't know.
- [Scoffs]
You need all the help you
can get ... even douche help.
And since when did you jump
on the God wagon?
You never
used to give a damn.
Well, I didn't ...
at one time.
Now that he's gone all kamikaze,
leaving us with the Darkness,
I...
[Sighs]
I was by his side
since the creation.
He believed in me.
If there's something I can do
to help save him
and his creation,
then...
...uh, it seems like
I should.
?
The plan is to rescue
Lucifer from Amara.
Then he teleports us out
of Amara's hideout
and we convince Chuck
to use him to fight her.
[Chuckles]
[Scoffs]
That's your plan?
Do you even know
where Amara is?
Um, I think I might know
where she is.
I've been getting this vibe.
Uh, it's like a ping
in my cerebral cortex.
Oh, so either Amara
or a stroke.
And how are we supposed to keep
Amara busy while we're...
liberating Lucifer?
?
Thank you for reaching
out to me, Dean.
You said you wanted
to meet.
I missed you.
And the...
sensations you arouse.
I know you feel
the same way.
So...what do we do?
There can be no us.
We should just
walk away.
Then why don't you?
[Sighs]
?
[Engine shuts off]
[Panting]
Oh, goody.
Larry, Curly, Moe.
Search and rescue?
Oh, wow.
It's one
of Dad's favorites.
Your ticket finally
got punched, huh?
It's wacky, isn't it?
One minute,
you're...nobody.
And then ... Shazam ...
you're Joan of Arc.
Let's, uh ... Let's hope
this ends better than that.
All right,
can the small talk.
We're busting you
out of here.
Well, it seems fair
since I wouldn't be here
if you lunatics
hadn't set me up
to be grabbed by Amara.
You're gonna help us
take her down.
If you say no, we'll just leave
you here in Abu Ghraib.
[Chuckles, coughs]
Say no?
You see
what she's done to me?
Do I look like a fan?!
Amara:
This place, this world
hasn't been especially easy
for you.
Why not at least consider
my offer?
This world is flawed.
I will give you that.
But I am not ready to say
goodbye to it just yet.
But one way or the other,
you will.
It's inevitable.
My brother
won't stop me again,
because he can't.
Dean, give up your...
smallness,
your humanity and become
boundless within me.
Eeroh, mahday saytah!
Did you grabbed this
from the steno pool?
You understand you'll be working
with your father.
Is that gonna be
a problem?
[Groans]
That's family.
This is bigger.
So, you'll table
all the old stuff?
What happens in Heaven
stays in Heaven.
Kahtoh, mahday, tayroh!
Metatron,
are we getting any closer?
Dean can't stall forever.
I'm ... I'm ...
I'm narrowing it down.
[Stammering]
You're right.
I am drawn to you.
And it bothers
the hell out of me,
'cause I can't
control it.
Then why fight it?
What you're feeling
is that I am the end
of your struggle.
Something stops you.
Keeps you
from having it all.
Sahboh, taylah!
Oh, oh!
- Yes.
- [Groans]
Where are your thoughts?
Something's different.
Hey, Lucifer, zap us out
of here ... quick!
Oh, no can do.
What do you mean
you can't do it?
Temporarily grounded.
Equipment malfunction.
You've spoken with God.
You've seen him.
You betrayed me.
Guys, I'm ...
I'm feeling her!
She's coming!
All right,
we're out of here.
Okay.
Come on. [Grunts]
[Groans]
All right, Metatron,
come on.
It's okay, Sam.
You go.
What?!
Come on!
I'm serious.
I got this.
?
[Panting]
[Engine revs, tires screech]
The secretary.
You were kidding with that,
weren't you?
He meant well.
Spare the universe.
Spare this.
[Screaming]
[Donatello
muttering indistinctly]
[Tires squeal]
[Engine revving]
You really aren't
worth sparing.
None of you.
[Tires squealing]
What happened?!
[Sam coughs]
Where are we?
[Scoffs]
Home.
[Sighs]
Occasionally,
I do answer a prayer.
[Bottle opens]
[Sighs]
You've changed.
Well, still...
I'm really pretty much
the same.
Still twitchy, huh?
Now, you've met God, Lucifer
and the Darkness.
- You gonna need a spa day.
- [Chuckles]
Better a pair of hookers.
I-I've to sort it all out
to see what comes next.
I don't feel much like
returning to academia and...
I sure as hell can't go back
to being an atheist.
Yeah, I hear you. [Sniffles]
- [Car approaching]
- Thank you...
I guess.
And, uh...
if there is a tomorrow...
Giving your line of work,
I'll probably see you again.
Stay tuned, we may need you.
??
[Sighs]
So Metatron took one for the team.
- Yeah.
- Well, I wouldn't have call that.
[Sighs]
So you won't tell me about it?
I mean Amara obviously figured out
something was going on and...
she gonna rip your head off.
She wants me to be a part of her.
Not metaphorically,
I'm talking litterally.
Forever.
So in other words,
adios.
[Scoffs]
??
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man