Can you really beat her?
I can.
Then yes.
Dean, that's not Cass!
Cat's out.
- Lucifer.
We have had a coward and a fool
at the helm for too long.
I'm still your master.
Did I let you out of that kettle
too soon?
What treasonous thoughts
do you have
brewing in that
little head of yours?
If you thought
you could beat Amara,
you'd be taking the fight
to her.
You're not strong enough.
I may be
a bit under-equipped.
Did you know
the Nazis had a special branch
devoted to archaeology?
What is that,
mon amour?
And they speak of
a super weapon.
Yeah?
What was it?
The Hand of God.
From Men of Letters
to Men of Letters,
I'm fighting a war
in the future.
It's not like your war.
It's big, biblical,
and I need your weapon to win.
Dean's the one
with the link to Amara,
why have I been
trying to spare you?
It's kicked.
Who'd have thought
the Hand of God
would turn out to be
a one-hitter.
This is a barn burner, folks.
Off the ropes.
Picks him up and --
oh, it's a back breaker.
Oh, but only a two count.
The rookie, Shawn Harley, fails
to take “The Hangman” down.
Ooh.
A stinger to the neck.
Are you seriously drunk
right now?
Just shut up
and get ready.
Ooh, and it's a stinger
to the back.
He's going in.
Takes him to the turnbuckle.
Yeah!
Oh, and we know
what's coming next.
Bring it on, baby!
It's all over.
I'm gonna hang his ass.
Oh, yeah, baby.
It's all over now, folks.
We have lift-off.
As Harley
struggling to breathe now.
He's turning blue.
Yeah!
Hey,
has anyone seen my rope?
What the hell?
I almost died out there.
Harley, back off.
You're gonna take
the wino's side? Really?
That's not what this is --
Whatever.
You old-timers like to
stick together, right?
Well, do us a favor --
keep a leash on your boy
or he might get hurt.
?
Hey!
? Supernatural 11x15 ?
Beyond the Mat
Original Air Date on February 24, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey,
have you seen the, um...
Ah. Yeah.
Thanks.
Yeah, bottoms up.
Yeah.
What's with the bag?
Oh.
You remember
Top Notch wrestling?
Yeah.
Those, uh, wrestling shows
dad took us to
when we were kids.
Right.
Came across an obituary
last night.
Larry “The Hangman” Lee
died.
Oh, no.
- Wasn't he, uh --
- He was dad's favorite.
Every time that noose
would come out,
dad would be up
on his feet.
Yeah, that was
one of the few times
I ever saw him
actually happy.
Yeah.
I remember that.
Anyway, the, uh, funeral's
less than a day's drive.
I say
we go pay our respects.
Uh...
Don't you think o-our plates
are a little full?
I mean, it's bad out there,
Dean.
Yeah, Sam.
You think I don't know that?
We've done nothing
but mainline lore for a week, okay?
We've got Jack on another
hand of God and Amara,
and we've got even less Jack
on how to save Cass.
If he wants to be saved.
He does...
Even if
he doesn't know it yet.
- Dean --
- I'm burnt, man.
Okay?
And I need --
we need to get out of here.
Let's go
stretch our legs.
?
Oh, good.
Yes.
Remember, A-B-C --
“always be closing.”
the sooner
you little storm clouds
find me another Hand of God,
the happier I will be.
You want me to be happy,
don't you, Dollface?
Of course, my Lord.
Good answer.
All right.
You're gonna look high,
look low, far and wide.
Search every warehouse,
every farmhouse,
every henhouse, outhouse,
and doghouse.
?
What about you,
little puppy?
You have something
to add?
Nothing, master.
Really?
I would tell you.
I swear.
I believe you.
May I return to my task?
Oh, of course.
Ah, ah.
Just one minor tweak.
Use your tongue.
?
Dude, check it out.
It's “The Scream”
Casey Lyons.
Oh, yeah.
There's
Wrecking Ball Calhoon.
Wow.
The Brooklyn Beast?
What happened to 'em?
They're all...Broken.
Dude. Dude.
Gunnar freakin' Lawless.
Hmm.
Groupie much?
Shut up.
Should I go say hi?
I should go say hi.
I'm gonna go say hi.
I know it's hard.
All right, take care.
Hi, s-sir.
I, uh, saw you --
saw you standing over here
and told my brother that I-I
should come over and say hi,
so I came over
and, uh...
Hi.
Gunnar Lawless.
Oh, I know.
Man,
I-I got to tell you.
I...
Worshiped you,
growing up.
Thanks.
I plan on keeping that hand.
Oh, sorry.
You know, when I was --
when I was 10,
I got my first B&E
from borrowing some family's
pay-per-view
so that I could
watch the cage match
between you
and the Tower of Power.
I'm not sure
how I feel about
contributing to
your juvenile delinquency,
but appreciate it
all the same.
Yeah, uh...
You were robbed, by the way.
You bet your ass I was.
Oh, yes.
Hey.
You're Rio.
Y-you used to manage
Superbomb Sanchez, right?
Oh.
That was a long time ago.
Well, yeah,
b-but you -- you...
You look great.
Sorry. Uh...
Wrong place.
It's just
y-you were my -- my first crush.
Ah. You weren't
one of those guys
that had my poster
above his bed, were you?
What?
No.
Are you still managing?
Oh. Nah.
I call some matches
sometimes,
but I'm mostly
behind the curtain, you know,
booking the shows
and taking care of the guys.
Yeah.
Must be hard to see one go.
Yeah, well...
We spent a lot of time
on the road together.
We're like family,
and lately, I've seen too many
of my boys be put in the dirt.
I knew Hangman
for 25 years.
He was a good man.
Great family.
I just can't believe
he would do this.
Do what?
Kill himself.
Wait.
That wasn't in the obituary.
Ah, the family didn't
want that advertised,
so...
Speaking of which,
if you'll excuse me.
Poor son of a bitch.
Yeah.
You know, uh, word is --
Yeah. I heard.
Hey, you know they're having
a memorial show tonight?
And I know you're itching
to get back, but, uh --
We should go to it.
Really?
Why not?
World's still gonna be screwed
tomorrow, right?
Yeah.
The Brooklyn Beast returns
against Rush
in an epic Iron Man matchup!
All right.
Let me hear you
make some noise.
Are you ready?
You know, I remember
the Top Notch shows being...
Grander, you know?
Top-notch.
Yeah.
Well, you drink enough,
it'll be
just like old times.
Rio.
- You dog.
- Oh, shut up.
Dude, we met at the wake.
She's nice.
Did you tell you used to
have a poster of her
over your bed
when you were a kid?
No.
- Yeah.
- Get this.
Guy at the wake told me they're
only making 25 bucks tonight.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
Now,
that hardly seems worth it.
Yeah, think about that.
Town after town,
putting your ass on the line
for next to nothing?
No money. No glory.
Wow.
You realize you just
literally described our jobs.
Whoa.
Excuse me, fellas.
- It's all right.
- This is gonna be great.
- Yeah.
Got to love some rasslin',
am I right?
Yeah.
?
Beer's cheap,
kid's entertained --
parenting.
Remember, don't tell mom
how many I've had.
Yeah.
Now, that brings me back.
You want to
not try and ruin
one of the nicest things
dad ever did for us, please?
- Ladies and gentlemen...
- Thank you.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
...put your hands together
for Hellrazor!
Almost showtime.
Got a little something
for ya.
?
And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together
for Gunnar Lawless!
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Right?! Right?!
Hey, get up.
Show some respect.
Who's getting it?
Who's getting it, huh?
Oh, oh, remember this?
This is where
he takes a glove off
and gives it to some kid
before the match?
Whoo!
Huh?
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Cool.
Okay.
Maybe next time.
It's all right.
I'm not a child.
It's fine.
Big foot to the face!
Lawless
up on the ropes now.
Get up!
Get up, buddy.
Come on, man.
You can do it, Gunnar.
Get up, buddy.
Come on, man.
Get out of it!
Gunnar!
?
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Up and over!
Oh!
1, 2, 3!
I got to drain the dragon.
Be good.
Oh, but it's all over now,
folks.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
All right,
you guys are good.
Hey, buddy, try to keep
your head up, okay?
Come on. Let's go.
Poor kid.
- Yeah.
- What'd they say?
You're not gonna
believe this.
The body...was marked.
Wow. By what?
What, he get in a tickle fight
with Edward Scissorhands?
Dude.
Look. T-the cuts look
deliberate, you know?
- Ritualistic.
- What, you think this is a case?
You think it's not?
Okay.
What are you thinking?
I don't know.
A-a witch, maybe?
You know what?
I'll head back to the motel,
look into the symbol.
I'll stay here,
shake some trees.
?
Hello?
FBI. I got some questions.
Bueller?
?
Whoo!
Oh, yeah!
Nice moves.
Oh, my God.
A-are you all right?
Yeah, good.
Oh.
Uh...
agent, uh, Roussimoff,
FBI.
Y-you were at the wake,
weren't you?
I was.
Yeah, and then the body dropped,
and back on the clock.
Did you know
the deceased?
Oh,
I-I sold him some tickets.
He had a kid, right?
Yeah.
Wow.
Maybe my boys are right.
Maybe we really are cursed.
Cursed?
Back in Shreveport,
our first stop on the tour,
a maintenance guy found a body
stashed in a dumpster
behind the VFW,
and now this.
Could I get a list
of your whole crew?
Wrestlers, roadies,
anybody that you roll with.
Oh, we use locals for
all the setups and concessions.
I can only afford to
travel my boys.
And where would they be
right now?
Try the nearest bar.
I know
that's where I'll be.
Okay. Thanks.
?
God.
We don't have much time.
I'm getting you
out of here.
Now.
I can't leave.
You can.
You still have friends --
people who want you back...
Who want Lucifer gone.
I don't know
what he's done to you.
I can't imagine,
but you're --
you're not a slave,
a dog.
You're Crowley,
and the Devil should be afraid
of you.
?
Hey.
Dean, right?
Yeah.
You enjoy the show?
The show was great.
Yeah, yeah.
You were great.
After the show, not so much,
but, uh...
Yeah, I heard.
It's a damn shame.
Yeah.
That's, uh, kind of
why I'm here.
Uh...
Kind of buried the lead
on that one, huh?
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
But I hear this isn't the first
murder at a Top Notch show.
It's a rough crowd --
inside the ring and out.
Yeah.
'92.
I'm leaving the ring
and some damn reprobate
goes at me
with a broken beer bottle.
Wow.
A couple years ago,
a, uh, perp
got the drop on me,
decided to take
a chunk of my leg as a keepsake.
See this right here?
Far as I can bend these
thanks to good ol' Jonah Rancid
and all 400 pounds of him
just dropping down on me.
Wow.
Sure thing.
But yet you're still out there,
still doing it.
I've been beat up,
spit on,
stabbed, roughed up,
but I will be damned
if I didn't always get back up.
One thing I learned --
you got to keep on grinding no
matter what's thrown your way.
Damn, you're awesome.
Tell that
to my ex-wives.
Ah.
Give me a sec.
- Hey, what do you got?
- A lot, actually.
Uh, so every stop
on the Top Notch tour,
somebody turned up dead.
It didn't all happen
at the venue,
and most of them
look like accidents,
but they all had the symbol --
Hangman, too.
Well,
I thought he killed himself.
Yeah,
that's what Rio said,
but the cops are treating it
like an open case.
They're thinking,
and I quote,
“It's some kind of
weird satanic crap.”
Awesome.
Yeah, it gets better.
That symbol --
ancient Sumerian.
Said to have the power to
“pluck the spark of life.”
and that means?
Souls, maybe?
So we're talking demon?
It's worth checking out.
Well, Rio says that they use
locals to set up, so...
So it's got to be
one of the wrestlers.
Maybe.
All right.
Just get here.
What are you gonna do?
I'm working on it.
Yo!
Sweetheart!
Hit me again!
Hey, Harley.
Go easy.
I think you've had enough.
Screw off.
Just trying to help.
Like you helped me
in Fort Worth?
What?
You think I don't know
you got me kicked off the card?
You wouldn't job to Crazy D.,
and I couldn't abide by that.
Yeah.
I think
you just can't stand the thought
of me
stealing your thunder.
Kid,
I got no worries about that.
All right.
That's enough.
Get up, old man.
Or do you need
your go-juice?
What?
That's right.
I saw him and his dealer.
Your golden boy's
a freaking junkie.
He's lying.
- Like hell.
- All right, all right.
Harley,
we got two days till Memphis.
Sleep it off.
Gunnar, I'll talk to you
about this tomorrow.
Go.
Hey.
You okay?
Ah, yeah, yeah.
I've been hit harder
by guys a lot tougher.
- Yeah.
- You got it.
Why, uh -- why didn't you
fight back?
I got nothing to prove.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- You okay, boss?
- Yeah.
Just another day, huh?
Well, hey.
Here's, uh --
here's to being the bigger man,
right?
Obliged.
We're gonna need
more shots.
A lot more.
This way.
Uh I wasn't --
she made me.
How did you --
I'm Crowley.
?
Dean?
Dean.
Hey.
Dude, you okay?
Yeah.
Ah.
What happened?
Mostly Tequila...
Cut with holy water.
I bought drinks
for all the wrestlers,
and then, you know,
they're like,
“well,
you got to drink, too.”
Oh, man, they can drink,
especially Rio.
Ugh. I think I heard my liver
screaming at me.
So, did anyone react?
No.
And you got them all?
Uh, except, uh, Harley,
the ultimate douchebag.
He bailed
before I could get to him.
Why is it so bright
in here?
All right.
Let's go find him.
Okay.
Dude!
I'm coming.
?
Harley.
Well, that's not good.
Uh, ya think?
?
My Lord?
That's better.
Now let's go find
the ace up my sleeve.
Hey, check this out.
Come here.
Got something?
Yeah, uh,
security-cam footage.
All right, let's see
if we got anything.
Um, so this is 1:07 am.
Harley heads to his room.
Um...
- Who's...
- No idea.
But, in there for a few minutes,
and that's Harley.
Wow.
He looks knocked out.
Yeah.
Now, let's see.
Lawless?
If Harley is a demon, then how
did Gunnar get the drop on him?
Let's find him
and ask him.
Hey!
Help!
Dude,
what the hell is going on?
Look.
I know I've been a dick,
but I'm sorry, okay?
I took a shot at you.
It was a cheap shot.
It was --
it was a cheap-ass shot.
And I just...
Just don't hurt me.
Please.
It's not my call.
Hello, Shawn.
I'm your new best friend.
Okay, traffic cameras show the
truck heading north on Wilson,
past First and Second,
but it never got to third.
Wait a second.
That's -- that's by the --
yeah.
You want my what?
Forget what I want.
What do you want?
Money? Women? Glory?
A big, shiny belt?
Say the word,
and it's yours.
Because you're a demon?
Businessman.
Dude,
what the hell is --
Eyes on me, champ.
Think about it.
No more crappy motels,
Podunk towns.
You'll have the life
you always wanted --
gumdrops and G-strings
as far as the eye can see.
And all I ask in return
is --
My soul.
And your service.
See, I might
occasionally ask you
to do me a teeny, tiny,
little favor.
What kind of favor?
The kill-somebody kind.
Why me?
Because I like you.
You're brash and driven
and hungry.
Yeah.
I'm looking for
new franchisees.
Why have one
when I can have two?
You did this?
Gunnar's what I like to call
a satisfied customer.
So...
Do we have a deal?
No.
Look, man.
I've never been much for
God or whatever.
I sort of just thought that
when your curtain came down,
that was it.
Night, night.
But if you're a demon,
that means there's a Hell.
And if there's a Hell,
there is a Heaven.
And I'm not giving up
my shot at paradise
for a belt
I can win on my own.
That so?
You're talented, Shawn.
But the human body,
it's just so fragile.
One injury,
one wrong step...
Like, say, if somebody...
severed
your Achilles tendon.
Poof -- you're done.
Duke, no.
You're up.
He's just a kid.
Do it.
What is this?
My personal lockup --
keepsakes, mementos,
things I'd prefer the rabble not
to get their grubby hands on.
Is that you?
Oh, the good old days.
Why are we here?
For this.
The Rod of Aaron --
created by God
on the sixth day
and given to Aaron,
brother of Moses.
I knew it was powerful,
but I had no idea
that it was a...
A Hand of God.
Can I touch it?
With all due respect,
Simmons,
I don't think
you can handle my rod.
I bet I can.
Is it just me, or...
Is it getting
a little phallic in here?
Drop it.
Isn't this a fun surprise?
You really thought
you could double-cross me?
Me?
You know I invented
the double-cross?
Like, literally?
Of course, I couldn't have
orchestrated all of this
without the lovely, talented
Simmons here.
She, um --
she hates you, B-T-Dubs.
Yeah.
I really do.
Yeah, they all do.
Like, every demon in Hell.
Can't really blame them,
can you?
I mean, maybe once you were
the evilest evil that ever...
Eviled --
present company excluded.
But now...
You're nothing but
Dean Winchester's number-one fan.
Sam and Dean.
I got to admit --
after all the stories,
I thought you'd be...
More.
Well,
sorry to disappoint.
It's my fault.
You get your hopes up.
You want an L.A. 10,
but you settle for a Kansas 5.
Life, right?
The name's --
We don't care.
Okay.
Small talk over.
Kill them.
W--
Gunnar, Gunnar, no. Wait.
Dean!
I knew
you were hiding something.
I could see that last spark
of defiance in your eyes.
And rather than
beating it out of you, which --
doable, but messy --
I let you lead me here.
So I'm gonna take this...
...and then
I'm gonna take you.
And, oh, puppy,
you're not gonna like
what comes next.
You looking for this?
You really think
you could double-cross me?
Me?!
I perfected
the double-cross.
Like, literally.
Whew!
So, this is what it feels like
to be God.
Not bad.
Tingly.
So, if this can hurt something
as powerful as the Darkness,
I wonder...
What can it do to you?
Sorry, kid.
I don't want to do this.
Oh, then don't.
You say that
like I got a choice.
That guy out there,
he's a --
He's a demon.
I know.
And I know about Hell
and deals -- all of it.
What's he got over you?
You sold your soul,
didn't you?
10 years ago,
I wanted another shot
at that belt.
50,000 people
screaming my name.
I was desperate and dumb.
But you only had the title
for like a week.
Desperate and dumb.
Okay.
Look, you screwed up,
all right?
Trust me.
I've been there.
But it is never too late
to do the right thing.
You really believe that?
I have to.
You made me bleed
my own blood.
You're out of juice,
huh?
Bollocks.
Does Crowley know
you're doing this?
Crowley's
Lucifer's bitch boy,
which is why
I'm doing this.
Stealing souls?
Building a nest egg.
With the Darkness out
and the Devil running hell,
well, it's kind of every demon
for him/her/shimself.
So why do you need
Lawless?
Well,
I can't be everywhere.
When the g-man's deal came due,
I gave him a choice --
end up hellhound chow
or collect souls for me.
I'm delegating.
That's what
good managers do.
Hey!
Hey, yourself, handsome.
Now, this --
this is my favorite part.
Thanks.
Dean. Hey.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
I'm good.
What?
Hellhounds.
I always wondered
what they'd sound like.
Listen, man.
You, uh...
No.
I've never been
a good man.
I look in the mirror
and I hate
the face looking back at me.
No, I, uh...
I got this coming.
Go on.
Get out.
Now.
Are you okay?
Not even a little bit.
Lawless was a good guy.
He didn't deserve to go out
like that, you know?
Dean, you know what?
He made a bad decision.
We've been there.
Yeah.
Yeah, you, me, now Cass.
Dean, we'll get him back.
We will.
We just got to --
Keep grinding.
No matter how much it hurts,
no matter how hard it gets,
you got to keep grinding.
?
Right.
And that's how
we're gonna win.
And we're gonna win.
We're gonna save Cass,
we're gonna ice the Devil,
and we're gonna
shank the Darkness.
And anyone
that gets in our way,
well, God help them.
Damn right.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man