Oh, I'm sorry.
I always forget.
People can't see me
unless I want them to see me.
[ Loud click ]
? King of Kings ?
God!
Just call me Chuck.
Amara: I'm looking for God.
Do you see what's happening?
All your chosen,
they are suffering!
Show yourself!
Call me Donatello.
Dean:
This guy's a prophet?
He had no idea he was next
in line after Kevin.
How would he? He hadn't gotten
hit by the God power yet.
What about Amara?
She's your sister.
I took responsibility
for her, too.
Locked her away.
So you're just gonna
let Amara win?
How is death by your sister
a strategy?
I know her.
She's gonna eliminate you,
and then she's gonna destroy
everything that you've created.
She's told me this,
personally.
You need all the help
you can get.
The plan is to rescue
Lucifer from Amara.
Then he teleports us out
of Amara's hideout,
and we convince Chuck
to use him to fight her.
And how are we supposed to keep
Amara busy while we're...
liberating Lucifer?
Where are your thoughts?
Something's different.
All right, Metatron,
come on!
It's okay, Sam.
You go. I got this.
The secretary.
Spare the universe.
Spare this.
[ Screaming ]
[ Clicks tongue ]
So, where were you?
That's a...
a long story.
How do you feel?
I healed you.
Mm, yeah,
didn't ask you to.
Son, be reasonable.
Lucifer: One cosmic Band-Aid
on my knee,
and, what, you think
that we're -- we're even now?
Is it time for us
to go play catch in the yard?
[ Door opens ]
Screw you.
Dean: Guys?
Hey.
How's it going in here?
Listen, I know
I've been gone for a while.
I missed
a few million birthdays.
Yeah, and then
the second your apes
send a distress flare --
Boom! -- Daddy's home.
No,
that's not what happened.
Hey,
these apes saved your ass.
He can't hurt you.
Oh, so you're
controlling me now.
No,
it's just a safeguard.
Hey, guys, uh,
Chuck, um...
Lucifer, Dean...
think we can try
and focus here, you know?
End of the world,
common enemy, all that.
The enemy of my enemy
is my friend.
Team Amara.
Go, Amara.
You don't mean that.
You're really
not gonna say it.
He's not gonna say what?
Screw you.
Screw all of you.
[ Sighs ]
Kids, huh?
[ Chuckles ]
? Supernatural 11x22 ?
We Happy Few
Original Air Date on May 18, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ Loud rock music plays ]
[ Banging on door ]
Lucifer!
You know,
at some point in time,
you're gonna have to come out
and -- and talk to...
God.
[ Clears throat ]
This is like the worst episode
of “Full House” ever.
[ Volume decreases ]
Lucifer: If Dad has something
to say to me,
I'll hear it from him.
Until then, I'll be in my room.
It's not your room.
It's my room.
[ Volume increases ]
Whatever.
We can do this.
Lucifer stole the throne.
His authority weakens
the longer he's M.I.A.
The time is ripe for a coup.
That's why I brought you here.
Together,
we can reclaim the throne.
we can make Hell great again.
[ Snickers ]
Of course, I'll need your help
recruiting others.
When the numbers
are in our favor, we'll strike,
and each and every one of you
will have earned
a place at my side.
[ Laughs ]
Told you he'd do this.
“He”?
Do what?
What you always do.
Promise a return
to Hell's former glory --
promises you never
make good on.
How about a rundown
of your recent rule?
First,
you were Rowena's bitch.
Then Dean Winchester's.
Then Amara's,
then Lucifer's.
A few weeks ago, you were
cleaning these floors...
with your tongue.
We could retake Hell,
but why bother?
The world's ending,
and this time...
Hell's ending with it.
[ Door opens ]
Unless you've got a plan
to defeat the Darkness.
Well, then,
this is just more of the same --
King Crowley's
bad dinner theater.
If that's the way you feel,
why did you show?
We wanted to see
the monkey dance...
one last time.
[ Door closes ]
Sam: Talk to him.
Won't do any good.
Why not?
'Cause I can't give him
what he wants.
And what's that?
What everyone wants --
my sister, my children,
you humans --
an apology.
A big, wet “I'm sorry.”
Well, so give it to him.
It's not like he's asking
for a weapon
or for Hell or for Heaven.
He's asking for words.
[ Sighs ] I can't say I'm sorry
if I'm not.
What he wants
an apology for,
I did it for humanity,
for the world.
Look, Lucifer wants what
everybody wants -- Amara gone.
Okay, let's just...give him
a little time to cool off.
Okay, well, I don't know
if you noticed,
but a little time
is not something we have.
The end is freakin' nigh.
[ Thunder crashes ]
[ Insects chirping,
bird calling ]
?
Hmm.
Rowena.
Door not locked.
What all that
astral projection bull for?
We're hardly
on the best terms, Clea.
Before barging in, I just wanted
to check for hex bags
or a --
That.
What you want?
I'm working on a spell.
It requires a second.
A second?
Well,
why don't you ask Charisse
or Melodie or Thomasin?
Oh, yeah,
you torched them all
in one of your
impetuous little fits.
The world's ending, Clea.
[ Thunder rumbles ]
Well, duh.
The end times shouldn't
bother you, though, Row.
You a rat.
Find your way
off any sinking ship.
Damn right.
The spell I'm working on
is Book of the Damned magic,
and it can get us back.
We can buy ourselves
a few more centuries of life.
Turn back
the clock for us...
before the world inevitably
goes bye-bye.
You're scared.
Aye.
I came face-to-face
with the Darkness.
The apocalypse bell's been rung
a few times in our day,
but when I looked inside her,
I saw it.
Not just the end of the world,
Heaven and Hell --
the end of magic.
Greek antiquity...
or no deal.
Middle Ages.
I know,
not the best time to be a witch.
Or a black woman.
And the Greek Age
was better?
I'm a fan of the classics.
I'll make it work.
Deal.
One of you is gonna have to,
uh, go first.
You know what?
Uh, Lucifer, y-you, uh...
you agreed to have a sit-down
if -- if God would show, so...
And, Chuck, you --
you did say you'd talk.
Him first.
I'm the one who's owed
an explanation.
[ Sighs ]
Okay, let's --
let's try “I feel” statements.
Dr. Phil.
Huh?
Sam: Oh, yeah, of course.
Obviously.
I am sorry
that you feel...
that I betrayed you,
that I acted without cause.
I'm sorry that you can't see
you gave me no choice.
I'm good.
You heard that, right?
W-We all know
that you are God, um, but...
maybe could you be
a-a little less...Lordly?
But I am --
I-I'm the Lord.
Wow.
There he goes.
I did what I had to do.
To create the world,
I had to lock Amara away.
And when the Mark
corrupted you
and I saw that you posed
a threat to humankind,
I did the same with you.
No, you betrayed me.
You gave me the Mark
to lock her away,
and when it changed me,
when it did what
the Mark inevitably does...
you threw me away.
No, Son.
The Mark --
You always cast
a jaundiced glance at humans.
The Mark
didn't change you.
It just made you more
of what you already were.
What I was
was your son...
your child.
Why should I put you first
above all others?
Do you have any idea
what it's like to argue
with your father
when your father is God?
Everything is a tautology
with you.
Everything is,
“Because I told you so.”
“It had to be done.”
Pretty sure
that's all fathers.
[ Clears throat ]
Okay.
Fine.
Big picture, as God,
you did what you had to do.
But little picture --
you sucked at being a dad.
Okay, maybe I didn't handle
everything perfectly.
But tell me...
could I have kept humankind safe
with you on the board?
I know about your little bid
to replace me with the angels.
Okay, “New God,” what would you
have done about you?
That is not the point!
I-I can't believe I'm actually
about to say this, but, um...
Lucifer is right.
A-All he wants
is an apology,
a-and you're too concerned
about being right
to -- to give him one.
But apologies aren't always
about being right.
Sometimes
they're just about apologizing.
Yeah, a-and the great thing
about apologies is
you don't have to
mean them.
You know, I-I lie and tell Sam
I'm sorry all the time.
I'm sorry.
See?
That's...
Okay, enough
from the peanut gallery.
[ Grunts ]
[ Sighs ]
What?
What would you have done?
It doesn't matter.
You were my father,
and you forsook me.
I did.
I was supposed to
love all creation equally.
I wasn't supposed
to have favorites.
But you...
You were mine.
I gave you the Mark
because I loved you the most...
because I thought you were
strong enough to bear it.
And when I saw
that I was wrong...
when I watched
my choice...
devour my...
most cherished son...
I hated myself.
And so I punished you.
And I am so sorry.
?
Hey.
So...are we good?
Okay. Great.
So what now?
We trap Amara,
put her back in the box.
Wait, what?
Yeah.
Well, you were right.
She needs to be destroyed.
But I won't kill her.
Why not?
Amara's been caged
for billions of years, but...
you know,
she was always there.
She had to be there --
you know, yin and yang,
you know, uh, dark and light.
English, Chuck.
[ Sighs ]
There's a harmony,
a balance in the universe.
Light needs dark,
dark needs light.
If you blow one of them up,
then, I mean...
It wouldn't be
a good thing.
It'd be really
not a good thing.
Like, end of reality,
not good.
Okay,
so we gift-wrap Amara.
I mean, we got the team
back together, so --
Chuck: Not quite.
We're still a few members short
of the original lineup.
Yeah, first time,
it took the combined strength
of me and my brothers
to weaken Amara before...
Daddy-o finished her off.
Yeah, even then,
it was close.
No, with just the two of us,
we'll lose.
Okay, so, what, we'll need more
group therapy
between you and the archangels
if we want to have a shot?
Well, Michael's in no condition
to fight.
And it's outside of my power
to bring Gabriel
and Raphael back.
But you restored Castiel.
Archangels are different.
They're the stuff
of primordial creation.
Rebuilding them, it's --
it's time we don't have.
All right.
So what do you need to win?
What do you got?
So what do we bring to the table
to make up for archangel power?
We could try
and find more Hands of God.
A little redundant.
Well, what about
Crowley?
Big demon power,
former king of Hell.
He was a player
in his day.
Stealing my moves, Dean?
Let me guess.
You got Lucifer
back in the fold.
He snapped you here.
No, it wasn't Lucifer.
Ah-ah-ah!
It's time to sober up.
You smell like a Dumpster
outside the Liquor Barn.
What's this?
Concern for me?
I appreciate your attempts
at bro-mantic rekindling.
But I think we both agree
that ship has sailed.
That's not
what this is about.
We need your help.
We have the angels.
And here I thought I had made
real inroads with you guys.
You thought wrong,
Serpent.
We loathe you.
We'll always loathe you.
Welp...
I came here to ask
a good-faith favor of you folks,
but as you are...
clearly
less than kindly disposed,
perhaps you'll, uh, lend an ear
to my very own Jiminy Cricket.
Hmm?
?
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hello, brothers.
Sisters.
Castiel?
It's me.
Rowena. I mean, she's a snake,
but she's a powerful witch.
And she's got
the Book of the Damned.
We've got the owl feather
and the yarrow root.
Check and check.
A jaw of pig?
Check.
What are you doing here,
Giant?
Give it!
Not till we've talked.
You walked right into
a powerful coven.
Ah, it takes three
for a coven.
Witch's den...
without a weapon.
I'll turn you into a moose --
an actual moose.
You can't.
Read his aura.
He under
some potent protection.
Never seen that before.
Hear the man out.
Well?
We need you.
Getting these groups to enlist
and then work together,
it's not gonna be easy.
Couldn't you
just compel them?
I invented free will
for a reason.
So we're tying our hands
on principle?
No, you can't make
an effective soldier by force.
They have to choose
this fight.
But they're gonna want to know
they're backing a winner.
So...
[ Chuckles lightly ]
We're gonna play
the God card.
[ Laughs ] God's back.
You've tricked me before,
Samuel.
Why would I believe a word
you say?
It would explain
that aura of protection.
Not no regular magic.
Clea, dear,
is this how it's going to be
with us in Crete?
Even if God's back,
why would I care?
Hello, pagan here.
I serve magic, not God.
Sorry.
Not interested.
I am.
What?
I can't serve both?
Let's hear it from Him.
In good time.
Do I have your support?
I can't even look at you,
Castiel.
You befouled yourself
with the Deceiver.
You know,
every second that I've spent
subordinating myself to Lucifer,
it's been a torment.
It's destroying me,
it's burning through my vessel.
But I would do it
all over again,
because through me,
he and God,
they will defeat
the Darkness.
That's my role in this fight.
It's God's fight.
You can play a part
in that fight, too...
if you join me.
No.
Row, you brought me a plan
to escape.
This here's an opportunity
to fight and win.
She's right.
Nobody's talking to you,
big and tall.
I can enlist others.
Sister witches.
You're mad.
We don't stand a chance
against Amara!
Rowena, honey...
there is a chance.
Game of thrones.
It's musical chairs.
Still...
I wanted it --
to go out
with the crown on my head!
And that's what
you offered them,
a chance
to stroke your ego?
And you wonder why
they said no.
Well, we've got
something better --
a plan.
Now, you can
sit on the sidelines
and watch
the world die...
or you can fight.
You know,
to be king again,
maybe you need to remember
how to be a soldier.
What's the plan?
We assemble
our band of brothers,
hit Amara
with everything we've got.
Then when she's weak...
I finish her off.
So...
a page from
the original playbook.
This time with witches and
demons subbing for archangels.
Exactly.
I still don't like it.
But why trap her
when you can kill her, you know?
I-I mean,
you got to admit,
there's a lot less room for
error if you shoot to kill.
I explained why.
Right,
but why keep her in play?
So she can escape and we can go
through this all over again?
Dean, what is this about?
I -- Nothing.
Am I the only one
thinking rational here?
It's about her.
Sam,
it's about his girlfriend.
Okay.
Shut up.
I mean, think about it.
Dean Winchester meets the
biggest evil in the universe,
and he takes a pass?
Come on.
Now he wants Daddy to do
what he couldn't.
Is he right?
Oh, I'm not getting into it
with him.
Not gonna happen.
Hey, Dean.
Come on, what's good for the
goose is good for the gander.
We opened a vein
for you two.
I tried to kill her.
And it didn't work.
Maybe it didn't work because
you didn't want it to work.
Maybe you didn't want to
kill her.
You want God to kill Amara
because you don't want Amara
to be killed?
Yeah, maybe there's a part of me
that just can't hurt her.
But if she's
already dead...
Then she's already dead.
Right.
Well, that got weird.
Dean...
[ Scoffs ]
...we always sweat this stuff,
these choices.
But, for once,
we have God on our side.
I mean, for once, we can
actually just do things his way.
[ Chuckles lightly ]
That's...
That's a very simple plan.
Simple...
bordering on insane.
It's suicide.
That's right.
Still in?
Let's go.
[ Screaming, grunting ]
[ Coughing ]
Please!
I don't know anything.
I've only been a prophet
for three days!
But you know where he is.
[ Coughing ]
I won't tell you.
You won't have to.
[ Gasping ]
Kansas.
[ Rumbling ]
?
[ Mug shatters ]
Crowley:
I don't hold grudges.
Besides, that dog collar
was a lovely touch,
really made my eyes pop.
Almost wore it here today.
Oh, I'm glad
you're such a good sport.
Hey, Red.
Looking gorgeous
as ever.
Hey, I think a little apology
is in order.
You think you're the first man
to try and kill me?
Hello, Fergus.
Mother.
Hello, my children.
Him?
Rowena. Crowley.
It's good to finally meet you
in person.
Sorry about, well, everything
I've ever done in my life.
Really,
y-you can't have been a fan.
Oh, yeah, I've been quietly
rooting against you both
for some time now.
Although, I can't deny
you're one
of my guilty pleasures.
[ Laughs ]
Oh, God.
All right, no flirting,
and no fighting.
Sam:
Yeah, and no deals.
No talks about
who is owed what
if we survive this.
Nobody likes each other.
It doesn't matter.
We only have
the fight ahead.
Amara's looking for me.
But I'm warded against her,
for now.
The second I drop the warding,
she'll show.
She'll be expecting a fight,
and we'll give it to her.
Shock and awe.
You have your troops
in position?
[ Clears throat ]
Yes, Rowena?
Fabulous plan...God,
but doesn't this strategy
strike anyone
as a wee bit
un-strategic?
Shouldn't we at least try
to catch her off guard?
Is that sequence
set in stone?
Demon, angel, witch power?
Seems to me that
the first response
should come from
the most disposable force.
Lucifer: Right!
Good argument, Doggie.
Demons first, it is.
The weakest
should go first.
Naturally,
that means the witches.
Enough.
Chuck: After that,
it's Lucifer's turn.
Physical attack, one on one.
What about Cass?
Oh, don't worry.
Your pet's safety
is my highest concern.
Trust me,
he's on board.
Once she's been weakened,
I will take the Mark back
from Amara
and use it to seal her away.
You ready?
Yeah.
Wait, what?
God and I talked
about this.
Someone needs to bear
the Mark.
Well, that should be me.
I-I've had it before.
I'm damaged goods.
Exactly.
You've already been tainted.
I can't transfer it to you.
Sam volunteered.
First Cass is making kamikaze
side plans and now you?
You couldn't have
talked to me?
We did talk.
And what happens when the Mark
turns you psycho, then what?
You...lock me up
where I can't hurt anyone.
And you throw away the key.
Sam, no.
Dean, you told me
you couldn't beat Amara,
that it would
have to be me.
Well, this is it --
me.
I'm just saying,
angels can hurt her.
It's worked before.
If you call giving Amara
a mild case
of the pukes working.
We're trying to disorientate her
as much as hurt her.
You underestimate witchcraft,
Fergus, always have.
If anything,
she's inoculated.
Full-scale demon attack.
That's our “X” factor.
[ Lucifer laughs ]
We talked about this.
It's time
to do the smart thing.
So, what am I supposed to do,
just sit by and watch?
No.
We're both in this fight.
You're leading this army.
Oh, you mean babysitting
the bad guys?
[ Chuckles ]
Okay, Sam.
Okay.
God's plan.
?
Rowena: Hello, Amara.
Hello, witch.
How did you find me?
Been inside your head
once before.
Easy enough
to find my way back.
Take it
you're still looking for God?
Well,
I'm with him right now.
Amara: He's here.
Yes.
Right inside.
Our deal holds?
Safe passage
back in time?
I went out on a limb for you --
betrayed God, of all people.
You didn't betray God.
You betrayed me.
I knew this was a trap
the moment you called.
I didn't care.
All I've ever wanted is
a one-on-one with my brother.
And you've just
given it to me.
The question is...
how am I going to
repay you?
Attenuare!
That [scoffs] tickles.
Do you really think the power
of one witch can hurt me?
I'm not just one witch.
Attenuare!
All: Attenuare!
Enough.
[ All screaming ]
[ Panting ]
Points for trying.
[ Thunder crashing,
electricity crackling ]
[ Screaming ]
?
Aah! No!
[ Grunts ]
Get back! No!
[ Screaming ]
No! No! No!
No! [ Grunts ]
?
[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hello, brother.
[ Panting ]
You cheated...
again.
But --
[ Yells ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Groans ]
Ah!
Son.
[ Whimpering ]
I'm sorry.
For this, for everything.
An apology at last.
[ Breathing heavily ]
What's sorry to me?
I spent millions of years
crammed into that cage...
alone...
and afraid, wishing --
begging for death
because of you!
And what was my crime,
brother?
The world
needed to be born!
And you wouldn't let me!
Amara,
you give me no choice.
That's your story.
Not mine.
The real reason
you banished me,
why I couldn't be allowed
to exist...
you couldn't stand it.
No, we were equals.
We weren't
great or powerful,
because we stood
only in relation to each other.
You think you made
the archangels to bring light?
No.
You made them
to create lesser beings,
to make you large,
to make you Lord.
It was ego!
You wanted to be big!
That's true.
[ Breathes heavily ]
But it isn't
the whole truth.
There's a value,
a glory in creation...
that's greater and truer
than my pride or my ego.
Call it grace,
call it being!
Whatever it is,
it didn't come from my hands.
It was there...
waiting to be born.
It just is,
as you and I just were.
Since you've been freed,
I know that you've seen it.
Felt it.
?
It didn't have to be
like this.
I loved you, brother.
[ Exhales heavily ]
[ Chuckles ]
Well...
you've won again.
[ Sighs heavily ]
Finish it.
Kill me.
[ Breathing heavily ]
I'm sorry.
No.
No! No!
[ Grunts ]
I'm so sorry.
No. Not again!
Not ever again!
[ Gasping ]
[ Screams ]
[ Grunts ]
Goodbye, nephew.
Dean: Cass!
[ Grunts ]
Amara:
I'd die a million times
and murder you a million more
before going back there!
Tell me...
if you won't change,
why should I?
Amara, no!
[ Grunting ]
Sorry, brother.
[ Body thuds ]
?
[ Dean grunts ]
No.
Amara, what have you done?
He's dead.
God's dead.
No.
He's dying.
[ Gasping ]
My brother will dim...
and fade away into nothing.
But not until he sees
what comes next.
Not until he watches this world,
everything he created,
everything he loves turn to ash.
?
Welcome to the end.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man