Let us introduce you
to the men of letters.
Rowena: It's a rabid group
of sanctimonious do-gooders.
Dean: It's a secret society.
Peter Jenkins: The last true
beacon of light
in a world gone
topsy-turvy.
Sam: European team-- they were
active during world war ii.
Dean: Inducted in 1939,
part of a small delegation
that was sent to Europe.
We're legacies.
Time travel?
That's a reasonable plan?
What, angels got their hands
on some Deloreans?
How did I get here?
Sam: You tapped the power of
your soul to get here?
Freaking time travel, man.
The Thule society.
Right. They were Nazis.
Dean: Nazi necromancers.
Dark magic, mostly with dead people.
You can kill me, but you will
never kill all the Thule.
Uhh!
Nazi bastards.
Rowena: Lucifer.
Bloody hell. Uhh!
[ Neck snaps ]
[ Grunts ]
Let's chat.
We want
to kill the Darkness.
We need
I've had two shots at Amara,
and I don't think I can.
I got it, Dean.
[ ?dith Piaf's "Non,
Je Ne Regrette Rien" playing ]
Es ist angekommen.
Ja, ich habe eine
militareskorte angefordert.
Naturlich, ich werde den
egenstand zu ihnen bringen.
Bitte,
es ist Mir eine grosse ehre.
Mein fuhrer.
[ Receiver clatters ]
[ French accent ]
The bed is cold.
Liebchen.
What is that, mon amour?
[ Sighs ]
This is why I've come here.
And I thought you occupied
my country to meet me.
Mm-hmm.
You were a bonus,
Delphine.
Mm.
A treasure.
Ma petite collaboratrice.
[ Chuckles ]
But this... [ kisses ]
This is what my country
has been waiting for.
Can I see it?
[ Clicks tongue ]
Naughty Delphine.
Mm.
Bitte.
?
[ Sighs ]
One little peek.
Mm.
Shh.
? Balay?s Les amours ?
? avec leurs tr?molos ?
? balay?s pour toujours ?
[ Unhooks latch ]
[ Kissing ]
? Non ?
[ Inhales deeply ]
Mmm. [ Kissing ]
[ Exhales slowly ]
? Non ?
Alors. C'est vrai.
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Whispers ] Mein liebchen.
? Ni Le bien qu'on m'a fait ?
[ Both chuckling ]
? Tout ca m'est bien ?gal ?
? non ?
Uhh! [ Gurgling ]
I have lived a hard life.
But these months?
Pretending to love a Nazi cochon
like you has been the worst.
But this moment...
[ Continues gurgling ]
Watching you die?
It is the best.
[ Squish ]
[ Choking ]
? Avec toi ?
[ Blade thuds ]
The Men of Letters send
their regards.
? Supernatural 11x14 ?
The Vessel
Original Air Date on February 17, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ coffeepot clatters ]
We're out.
[ Coffeepot thuds ]
There was a half a bag yesterday.
I killed it. Hey...
Did you know the Nazis had
a special branch
devoted to archaeology?
A little early for Nazi trivia,
especially without caffeine.
It was called, uh,
the "Ahnenerbe."
There were sites
all over Germany,
and then as the Nazis
increased their territory,
they started popping up
in -- in Poland,
Finland, uh, North Africa.
Yeah, how is this more important
than our coffee situation?
'Cause I found something.
[ Refrigerator door closes ]
I mean, we need something --
magic,
a-a weapon strong enough
to give us a shot against Amara.
So I've been looking outside
the lore in history,
and I found this --
uh, "The Vichy Memorandums."
They were Nazi communications
that puzzle historians
to this day,
and they speak of
a superweapon obtained
by the Ahnenerbe,
said to be strong enough
to win the war.
Yeah? What was it?
Well, uh, these memos
refer to it as..[ Turns page ]
"The Hand of God."
I mean, that was sort of
a catchall term
for several objects he touched
on earth in biblical times,
but they're believed to contain
traces of his power.
Yeah, well, the Nazis believed
a lot of things.
Dean, Lucifer's caged.
God's M.I.A.
The only beings strong enough
to battle Amara are gone.
If we're gonna fight her,
what better way to arm up
than with an actual dose
of his power?
Okay, so you said the Nazis
got their hands on
one of these, uh..."Hands."
Right.
Well, if it was so powerful
it could win them the war,
why didn't it?
Because they lost it.
En route to Berlin,
it was stolen.
The Nazis searched
high and low for the thief,
but they never found
their prime suspect.
Uh, here.
Delphine Seydoux.
French mistress
to a high-ranking Nazi.
Thought to be
a French traitor
till she killed her German lover
and made off with the weapon.
Allied spy?
French resistance?
That's what the Nazis thought,
but their investigation led them
to a different conclusion --
that she was
"Un Femme de Lettres."
A Woman of Letters.
[ Game noises over tablet ]
[ Fly buzzes ]
[ Demons speak indistinctly ]
Uh, sir?
Would you like to hear
the latest soul numbers?
No, because I don't care.
[ Game noises continue ]
How about an update
on Amara?
[ Pauses game ]
Well, the update is...
Well, that there is no update.
We still haven't found her.
Sir, if I may...
Since you've claimed the throne,
we could use some direction.
Any direction.
We could deploy a force.
Real boots on the ground,
shake the trees to find her.
[ Resumes playing game ]
W-with you leading the charge,
of course.
We have had a coward and a fool
at the helm for too long.
[ Muffled groans ]
Perhaps it's time to...
Doggie wants to speak.
[ Gate rattling ]
[ Scraping ]
[ Chains rattle ]
[ Exhales ]
How dare you.
The impudence.
The lack of humility.
That's no way to talk
to your master...
Lucifer.
That's a good doggie.
Who knew the Men of Letters had
European chapters?
Maybe it wasn't
an entire chapter.
Just some assets, you know?
Yeah, and letting women join
way back in the '40s?
I just never
got the impression
that they were so big
on gender equality.
You know, it's right there
in the name.
Well, it was World War II.
Kind of an all-hands-on-deck
situation, you know?
Yeah, Rosie the riveter.
Hmm. Cool.
Here you go.
This report was written by
Clifford Henshaw,
a bunker-based Man of Letters,
back in 1943.
It's the right era.
[ Book thuds ]
But it's in French.
[ Scanner whirring ]
Well?
Hey.
[ Door closes ]
So it's definitely about
Delphine.
Her name's at the top
of every page.
And check this out.
[ Bottle thuds ]
They're transcriptions
from transatlantic cables
between Clifford
and Delphine.
What do they say?
Uh, give me a second.
[ Sighs ] Web translation's
kind of buggy.
Seriously?
Dude, it's, like, noon.
Uh, well, you drank
all the coffee,
so what am I supposed to drink? Water?
[ Scoffs ]
[ Bottle thuds, laptop chirps ]
Look at this.
They were making arrangements
to get the artifact
out of Europe to keep it safe.
Uh, Henshaw pulled
some strings
with a Man of Letters
in the O.S.S.
to requisition an active
U.S. submarine to transport
Delphine and the weapon
back to the states.
Back to here.
Wait, the bunker?
Yeah.
So it's been here
the whole time?
Uh...
[ Typing ]
No. Never arrived.
Uh, the U.S.S. Bluefin
came under German attack
midway through its trip across
the Atlantic.
The sub was sunk.
[ Taps key ]
The ship and its contents
haven't been recovered
to this day.
Great. It's lost.
[ Clears throat ]
Or is it?
Well, yeah, I'd say so.
I mean,
tides took the wreckage.
Submersibles have been trying
to locate it for years.
I mean, if James Cameron
and his "Avatar" billions
can't find it...
Yeah, but...
We have something that
James Cameron doesn't have.
[ Wheels rattle, doors open ]
[ Rattling continues ]
[ Rattling stops ]
[ Sighs deeply ]
That's all of it?
[ Spear clanks ]
Yes, sir.
The requested weaponry
from your crypts.
Does it...Please you?
Spare me.
[ Departing footsteps ]
How are your wounds, doggie?
[ Doors close ]
They are...
[ Clicks tongue ]
No less than I deserve.
[ Winces ]
Aww. [ Chuckles ]
You're scared of your master.
[ Clicks tongue ]
That's a good doggie.
[ Chains rattle ]
Aah!
But it's an act.
I broke you, but, um...
[ Inhales deeply ]
Yep, I can still smell it.
You've got that delectable
little whiff of defiance.
You're just playing, huh?
Waiting for your moment
to retake the throne.
[ Clicks tongue ]
Am I right?
Yes, sir.
[ Chains rattle ]
Well, then...
Tell me, uh,
once and future...
[ Chuckles ] King of Hell,
you've been watching
my rule.
What treasonous thoughts
do you have
brewing in that little head
of yours, huh?
[ Thud, chains rattle ]
What are you really thinking?
Hmm?
The truth, sir?
Yeah.
?
You're not strong enough.
You've had your weapons
delivered.
You realize
they won't be enough.
If you thought
you could beat Amara,
you'd be taking the fight
to her,
right now.
[ Inhales sharply ]
You're a clever
little doggie.
You're right.
At the moment, I-I may be
a bit underequipped.
Maybe defeating Amara was
a bit more of a team effort
than I led certain people
to believe.
You know, all that said...
[ Chains rattle ]
I'm still your master.
Did I let you out
of that kennel too soon?
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Whispers ] No.
[ Ring ]
[ Exhales ]
[ Whispers ] No barking.
[ Ring ]
[ Normal voice ] It's showtime.
Hello, Dean.
There were several
God-touched objects,
but it never occurred to me
that any had survived the flood,
let alone the 20th Century.
Do you think we can use it
against Amara?
It's perfect.
I can get you back there.
Without wings?
Cass, you can't even teleport.
Time travel's is a...
It's a whole different system.
[ Snaps fingers ]
Told ya.
So, uh,
these the last coordinates?
That's the Bluefin's last
transmission to shore, yeah.
All right.
Wait a second.
Cass, aren't there still risks
with time travel?
[ Papers rustle ]
I mean, aren't there consequences that --
[ pounds tabletop ]
Sam...
This is the ideal scenario.
What?
That sub's a tin can floating
in the middle of the ocean,
doomed to go down.
You can't really mess
with history at 20,000 leagues.
So we get in, get the weapon,
get out. It's a milk run.
Well, t-that's not
a-a very good plan.
Well, if things get
out of hand,
then Cass'll just zap me
right back.
You?
You're not going.
I beg your pardon?
You need to stay here.
Stay here?
Just in case
things go sideways,
somebody needs
to be left standing
to take care
of the Darkness.
We can't risk us both,
and at the moment,
I'm the least valuable player.
You both know
that I can't kill Amara,
so the least I could do
is get the thing
that we need so that you can.
So you expect me to sit here
and ride the pine
while you and Cass
go play Jules Verne?
Yes. No. Uh, who?
I won't let him
out of my sight.
[ Sighs ]
You'll stay by his side
the entire time?
I will.
Sam...
Let me do this.
Okay? I need to do this.
Be safe.
When am I not?
[ Scoffs ]
Let's do this, Cass.
?
[ Sighs deeply ]
Bon voyage.
[ Whoosh ]
?
[ Engines whirring ]
[ Man snoring ]
[ Whispers ] Cass?
[ Metal rattling ]
[ Metallic thumping ]
[ Whispers ] Cass?
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Door creaks ]
See, I enlisted
to sink German ships.
You're up.
[ Towel smacks ]
[ Man sighs ]
Let's go. Vacation's over.
Now we got zip running patrols
in the bay.
Now captain's got us going
the wrong direction?
To run some mystery mission
for some broad?
Tell me how that
makes sense.
I wouldn't worry about it.
Get some rest.
You know I can't rest.
[ Footsteps passing ]
?
[ Metal clanks ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Door opens, closes ]
[ Water sloshing ]
Cass?
Why...
Wait a second.
Where's Dean?
We made the leap.
He got on. I didn't.
What?
[ Sighs heavily ]
I couldn't make it past
the hull.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
1996?
Uhh!
Where's Delphine?
Where's the broad?
I-I-I don't know
what you're talking about.
Someone must have warded
the ship.
Delphine. It has to be.
I mean, she's protecting
the weapon, right?
[ Suit rustling ]
Cass.
Just go back to their last port
before she boarded,
leave a message
so Dean knows.
Where?
Where would Dean see it that
the crew wouldn't?
He's as likely
to find the warding
as he is any message
I'd leave.
Then send me.
You got Dean past the hull.
Right.
We'll double-down on what
screwed us the first time.
You're really bringing
your "A" ideas today.
I can't believe I lost it.
[ Sighs ]
Him. Mm.
Can't believe I lost Dean.
Well, it's up to him now
to find and clear the warding.
No. We can help.
There's got to be something
in -- in -- in magic
or angel lore.
You know, some way to clear
the sigils from the outside.
Cass...
Don't worry.
We'll bring him back.
[ Book thuds ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Man: Look out.
Coming through.
Uh...Sir.
When can I smoke?
When it's your turn,
I'll let you know.
Surely some of you boys take
breaks in the engine room?
Captain wants you stayed put.
Let me guess. He fears
I would distract his men?
Does not want a skirt
roaming the decks?
Give me the light.
But, ma'am, uh...
You're wearing pants.
[ Chuckles ]
Rich, ain't it?
Frog's sittin' pretty
like Queen of Sheba,
getting room service
in the wardroom,
and I can't even gripe 'cause...
Well, you seen that dame?
The gams on her?
[ Whistles ]
Yeah. Yeah, she's a hottie.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, those gams, huh?
Who are you?
Delphine...
You might find this
hard to believe, but --
[ grunting ]
[ Groans ]
Not a soul on this ship
knows my name,
so I repeat, who are you?
Coming through!
Man: Hey!
Excuse me, sir.
I'm a friend
of Clifford Henshaw.
I'm a Man of Letters.
[ Footsteps approach ]
That's him.
That's the guy. Captain.
Sit down.
Okay, I'm --
[ thud ]
He took my clothes,
and he hog-tied me
in the head, this guy.
What should we do with him, captain?
Search him.
All right, all right.
That's... [ grunts ]
?
Petey, this yours?
What the hell is this?
It's a phone.
Right. A phone in your pocket.
Petey: Next thing
this guy's gonna tell us
is he's from space.
Yeah, or the future.
[ Both chuckle ]
I-I am.
?
Captain James Dearborn?
My name is Dean Winchester,
and I am on a mission
from the future,
the details of which
I am not at liberty to discuss.
But know this --
within the hour,
a German destroyer will find
and attack this submarine,
and you will go down.
Okay, you've said your piece.
Let me tell you what I think.
Captain...
I think you're a soldier
that's gone A.W.O.L.
You've hopped a ride home,
and this cockeyed story
is some loony attempt
to keep your cover as a civvie.
That, or you're a spy.
Deciding which? I'll leave that
to the court martial.
I need to speak
with this man alone.
Not a chance.
Captain, there are things,
things about this mission
that you don't know.
Flash Gordon here
will remain under guard
until we reach the shore.
Gladly.
[ Scoffs ] What if we don't
reach shore? What if he's right?
The odds of a German attack
from a surface ship,
this far west,
hunting down a lone submarine?
Captain?
Sonar's picked up a surface ship
on a steady bearing, closing.
Understood.
Harris, back to your station.
Giraldi, watch our guest.
Petey: Yes, sir.
The Germans,
they've come for it.
Delphine, the warding
on the hull? The sigil?
That's not like any
I've seen.
[ Man speaking indistinctly ]
You're certain of the identification?
Yes, sir.
Uh, 36B German destroyer,
3,000 yards in closing.
Bearing 0-9-0.
Clear the bridge.
Clear the bridge!
My mentor
in the men of letters,
he taught me the symbol
before he died.
World Series, 1944.
Go.
Um...
You're from the future.
Tell me, who won?
Um, the, uh, the Rangers.
The Rangers?
He believed it would keep me
and the artifact safe
on our journey...
Who are the Rangers?
...from supernatural
interference.
And angelic interference.
Angels? They are not real.
Who are the Rangers?
Look, kid, I don't follow
baseball, okay?
Yeah, and angels are real.
In fact, one of them
is my ride off this ship.
Now look, the warding that you
put up to block the magic,
it must've blocked him, too.
I cleared the one.
If there's any more,
we gotta clear those, too.
Otherwise, I'm stuck here.
Okay, then.
The next president.
Delphine, you wanted the weapon
to be at a Men of Letters
safe house, right?
I'm from the bunker.
That's how I knew how
to find you,
from your communication
with Henshaw.
Now if you clear the way,
I can get it there for you.
And that's why you came,
to protect the object,
the weapon?
You gonna answer my question?
Eisenhower, okay?
No. Uh...Truman.
Now would you please
shut up?
No.
This sub is going down.
But the allies do win.
But from Man of Letters
to Man of Letters?
I'm fighting a war
in the future.
It's not like your war.
It's big.
Biblical, end-is-nigh big.
And I need your weapon
to win.
That is why I came.
But we all die?
?
Me, the girl,
the rest of the crew?
I'm just trying
to get your story clear.
Yes.
Look, I know
it's a lot to ask,
especially from
a complete stranger.
You're not a stranger.
"Man of Letters
to Man of Letters."
I trust you.
[ Water splashes ]
Hatch secure.
Alter course to 2-7-0.
Take us down to 60 feet.
Alter course to 2-7-0!
Altering course to 2-7-0.
Open front port.
Dive, dive, dive!
Dive! Dive!
[ Alarm blaring ]
[ Lightning crackling,
rain pouring ]
[ Thunderclap ]
Wait a second.
I think I have something.
"The spell of gathering."
It's an incantation used
to "focus the power of
celestial beings" -- angels --
"against all drawn forms
of evasion."
This spell was designed
to clear all mystical
or occult blockages.
I mean, this is
highly theoretical magic.
It's never been used before,
but it sounds like it could work.
Do you have the ingredients?
Uh... [ mutters ]
[ Sighs ]
All but one.
[ Scoffs ]
That's why it's never
been used before.
It requires the power
of an archangel.
[ Closes book ]
[ Groans ]
[ Sighs deeply ]
Well, Sam,
we may as well try.
[ Scoffs ]
We don't have time
for long shots, Cass.
Even at full power,
you're not strong enough.
[ Exhales ]
?
[ Lid creang ]
That's the hand of God?
Doesn't look like much.
No, I suppose it doesn't.
It must have been more
impressive in its complete form.
The Ark of the Covenant.
Oh, so full-on "Raiders."
That's...
Okay.
Don't touch it bare-handed.
Its power is potent
and unstable.
No mortal can survive long
with direct contact.
[ Closes latch ]
I'll remove the warding.
I'll be back.
[ Chuckles ] Promise.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Definitely not you.
Okay.
When?
When what?
When do we win?
Months, years, decades?
Got a lot of friends
and family on other ships,
in other branches.
I want to know
what their chances are.
Years.
1945.
You believe me?
I read a lot
of Flash Gordon.
1,500 yards.
We are not shaking him.
Battle stations.
Sir, respectfully,
our orders were to go home,
not engage.
X.O., do not make me
repeat myself.
Battle stations!
Aye, aye, sir!
[ Switches click ]
General quarters, battle stations.
[ Over P.A. ] General quarters,
man your battle stations.
All hands, man your battle stations.
Okay, let's go!
Let's go, boys! Let's go!
Come on! Come on!
Go!
Okay! Okay!
Let's go! Let's go!
Keep it going!
Keep it going! Go.
He said get a move on!
Get a move on! [ Scraping ]
Get to it! Get to it!
Everyone in positions!
Stand by
to load tube number 8.
?
Load aft torpedoes.
[ All speak indistinctly ]
[ Whirring ]
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
Harris, open the rear door.
Opening door.
Go! Clear!
Easy. Ease it down.
?
[ Groans ]
[ Clank ]
We're secured!
Flood the tube.
Flooding.
[ Wheel squeaks ]
Ready to fire.
800 yards and closing.
Torpedoes loaded.
Line us up for a bow shot.
Line up for a bow shot.
Lining up for a bow shot.
[ Switch clicks ]
Locked.
In position, ready to fire.
?
[ Knobs clicking ]
Captain, uh, I-I've lost
his position.
What?
He's gone.
How is it possible
to lose a 3,000-ton warship
from 800 yards?
[ Knobs clicking ]
Find him!
[ Switches click,
wheel squeaks ]
[ Sonar pinging loudly ]
Aah!
30 yards, sir!
He's right on top of us!
How?!
Flood negative!
Take us down to max depth
and rig for silent running!
Silent running!
[ Both grunt ]
[ Engines muffle ]
[ Clanking in distance ]
What's happening?
[ Whispers ] Shh! Shh!
[ Clanking stops ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Whispers ]
Leveling out at 300, sir.
[ Panting ]
[ Buttons snap ]
Kill me.
Wait.
You can't do that.
?
[ Whispers ] Kill me.
Splashes.
Depth charge.
I don't have to kill you,
okay?
I can just cut it.
It'll work.
Not with this.
It's spell-bound --
to my blood, my heart.
Its power lives and dies
with me.
Do it.
[ Thud ]
?
[ Explosions ]
[ All grunting ]
[ Shouts indistinctly ]
[ Explosion ]
[ All shout ]
[ Panting ]
Midshipman down!
We need a medic!
[ Crunch ]
Hey.
Cass, what is that?
It's
your spell of gathering.
Are you nuts?
[ Clank ]
You're not strong enough, Cass.
You could get hurt.
You find a better option?
Well...No,
but without a serious boost
to your angel power,
that spell won't even work.
My strength may surprise you.
[ Continues chopping ]
Wait a second.
I remember Bobby told me,
when you needed strength
to retrieve us from the past,
you used him to power up.
You -- you touched his soul.
Right?
That's right. I did that.
But that -- that, uh, procedure
it can be fatal.
[ Bowl clanks ]
Use my soul.
That way, maybe you'll have
enough power to wield the spell.
That isn't necessary.
It's worth the risk.
Cass, Dean needs our help.
I trust you.
[ Laughing ]
What?
Oh, it's ju-- I don't --
I don't need you anymore.
I mean, Dean's the one
with the link to Amara.
Why have I been trying
to spare you?
I mean, maybe it's because
you're like the girl who kept
turning me down at the prom.
[ Grunts, groans ]
I will touch your soul,
just because you asked
so nicely.
And I'll use your spell
to blast through the warding
and retrieve Dean
and the, uh...Hand of God.
And then
when Dean comes back
and he finds this place
decorated with your guts,
I will tell him the truth,
Sam.
I'll just say, "Dean" --
[ imitating Castiel's
gruff voice ] "Dean...
"He knew the risks.
He wouldn't take 'no'
for an answer."
Lucifer.
In the flesh.
?
[ Crackling, whooshing ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Screams ]
[ Crackling,inhooshing
continues ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Groans ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Hello, Castiel.
[ Grunts ]
Medic!
Come on!
Damage report?
Battery room is flooded.
Hull's breached.
We're dead in the water.
[ Exhales heavily ]
Ship's locked
in position above us.
Man: [ Over radio ]
American submarine.
Captain...
The Germans are sending
a message.
American submarine.
Sir, it's not for you.
[ Lock disengages, door creaks ]
Petey: Watch your head.
[ Door creaks, clanks ]
Go ahead.
[ Switches clicks ]
Hello, mein liebchen.
It is not possible.
I killed you.
A little advice, Delphine.
If you want a friend
of the Thule to stay dead,
burn the body.
A word for the captain.
You may have noticed
you are up against a warship
and a crew possessing,
let us say,
extraordinary abilities.
And you have taken damage
that you cannot recover from.
So I offer you a choice --
surface now, relinquish
the girl and her cargo,
and I can assure you
and your men
the highest of P.O.W. treatment.
Or you can protect her,
and we will depth charge
you and your boat
right into the seabed
and recover the cargo ourselves.
You have three minutes
to surrender.
I don't expect you
to understand, but this cargo,
the Germans can't have it.
[ Exhales ]
You need to believe me.
Our orders were to protect you
and your cargo.
We wouldn't even consider
a surrender.
You had better reconsider.
Killing me is your only way off
this ship.
Maybe not.
Teach me how to use it.
It's the power of God.
Maybe I can use it to save you,
save the sub.
And your war?
I want to help you now.
Two minutes, Captain.
You save the ship,
get us to the surface,
and then what?
The power of God
will consume you,
and you'll have merely
brought the weapon
closer to the Nazis' grasp.
[ Sighs ]
We are supposed to die.
Let us do it with a purpose.
How long can you keep
the boat steady?
Not long. And once they resume
their attack --
Give me every second you can.
Delphine, what are you doing?
One minute.
I'm going to get you home.
And I'm going to get
you and your men
your first German ship.
[ Groans ]
[ Grunts ] No, no.
Sam.
Sam, it's me.
Cass? [ Groans ] Why?
I wanted to be of service
to the fight.
And only Lucifer
can beat her.
You chose this?
You have to fight, Cass.
Eject him now!
I can't.
It's taking all my strength
to keep him from killing you.
And besides, we need him.
No, Cass, we don't.
We'll find another way
to stop Amara.
[ Breathing heavily ]
We need him to save Dean.
You can't time travel.
Only Lucifer can.
How fast is your ride back?
Fast.
Good.
It's time!
[ Inhales deeply,
exhales slowly ]
[ Explosions ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Humming ]
[ Whoosh ]
God help us all.
[ Humming continues ]
[ Panel explodes ]
Aah!
[ Crewman over radio
speaks indistinctly ] Isolate that panel!
[ Electricity crackling ]
What is this?!
Aah!
[ Explosions ]
[ Alarm ringing ]
Fire in the control room!
[ Whoosh ]
[ Shouts indistinctly ]
Torpedoes are taking water! We need...
[ Extinguisher hissing ]
[ Shouts indistinctly ]
[ Explosion ]
Electrical!
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Dean.
That's not Cass!
Cat's out.
[ Grunting ]
Mm! I feel a burden lifted.
[ Groans ] You know,
this whole "deep cover" thing,
it just wasn't -- it wasn't
terribly well thought out.
Donning this...This Cass mask?
This grim face of
angelic constipation?
Just ugh.
And then teaming up
with you two? I mean...
[ Blade clicks ]
I thought you boys
were insufferable as
mortal enemies.
[ Inhales sharply ]
But working with you?
Ugh. That's the soul crusher.
[ Whoosh ]
[ Groans, grunts ]
Why the faces, boys?
You should be cheering.
We have a common enemy.
With this,
she will be no problem.
I mean... [chuckles]
I will have killed you both
by then, but still...
Come on.
No.
No!
?
It's kicked.
[ Exhales deeply ] Well...
Who'd have thought
the Hand of God
would turn out to be
a one-hitter?
[ Thud ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Screams ]
[ Sigil sizzles ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
?
[ Water lapping ]
So...
[ Clears throat ]
Cass.
Yeah.
[ Sighs deeply ]
Yeah, what do we do?
What else?
We hunt Lucifer,
trap the bastard,
and save Cass.
Like I said,
Lucifer may
be in control now,
but Cass may not come back
willingly.
I mean, he chose it.
No.
No, not possible.
Hales sharply ]
So how'd you get through today?
I mean, what did you do?
Nothing.
Sam, they...
I was just a witness.
Do you want to talk
about it?
No.
No. Story for another day.
?
Hey, the, uh...
The German ship
that sank the Bluefin,
what happened to it?
It went down.
Unlike the sub,
its wreckage was found.
Um, there was a giant hole
that'd been ripped through
the entire thing.
Something must have hit
the fuel tanks and exploded.
But it burned. Sank.
?dith Piaf:
? non, rien de rien ?
? non, je Ne regrette rien ?
? ni Le bien qu'on m'a fait ?
? ni Le mal
tout ca m'est bien ?gal ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man