I'm Sheriff Donna Hanscum.
My husband Doug left me
last year
'cause he said I loved
cookie dough milkshakes
more than him.
You deserve better.
Donna.
Doug.
Well, aren't you
looking good? Huh?
I lost six pounds.
Hey, you're a quarter
of the way there!
Doug seems like kind of a dick.
You ever think
there are things out there,
things that don't end up
in the police blotter?
What I think I saw
were teeth.
You think I'm crazy?
Not at all.
Sheriff Cuse is a vampire.
She just pulled out a machete.
Donna saw his teeth.
What the cuss?! A vampire?
Ha!
[ Thud ]
They can't hurt you. They can't hurt you.
[ Laughing maniacally ]
If it bleeds, you can kill it.
This isn't about your, uh,
your clown thing, is it?
Sam: What? No.
[ Cackles ]
What in the world
did they do to you?
[ Grunting ]
I think I've been
having visions.
It's just images. I mean,
more of a feeling, really.
I mean, maybe these visions
are coming from God.
Whoa.
I mean, Dean, the first one
happened after I prayed.
You prayed? When was this?
Back in the hospital.
What did you pray about?
I guess I was just looking
for answers, you know?
When was the last time
God answered
any one of our prayers?
Man on TV: This is their
second drive in overtime,
with both teams having
possessed the ball.
The next score wins.
Mm.
Man: Every play becomes...
Oh! [ Sighs ]
Man: 1st and 10
from the 32-yard line.
8:21 in O.T...
Stan!
Can you take out the trash?
[ Sighs ] He is running left.
Ohh! He gets...
Stinks to high heaven.
[ Lowered voice ]
It's your cooking that stinks.
[ Dish thuds ]
What was that, honey?
Nothing, dear.
2nd and...
The game's in O.T., can't it wait?
...backs him into center,
slowly defends...
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Crowd cheering ]
[ Groans ]
[ Men speaking indistinctly ]
[ Door creaks ]
[ Men continue
speaking indistinctly ]
[ Door creaks ]
[ Rattling and clinking ]
[ Lid bangs ]
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Rattling and clinking ]
[ Door creaks open ]
Hey, hon, bring me another brewski.
[ Door closes ]
[ Refrigerator door opens,
bottles clink ]
[ Refrigerator door closes ]
He's flushed out of the pocket.
Hey, thanks, babe.
He's got a man open...
[ Gasps ]
Throws...
And it's caught by...
[ Cheering, whistle blows ]
[ Glass shatters ]
Uhh!
Don't need possum traps, huh?
[ Lid bangs, glass clinks ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Squishing ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Screams ]
? Supernatural 11x07 ?
Plush
Original Air Date on November 18, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
So, uh...
on the off chance that you're
actually listening, uh...
Uh, I gotta be real honest.
The visions aren't making
a whole lot of sense to me.
Truth is...
I don't know what's what.
Please.
[ Exhales sharply ]
What are you trying to say?
[ Exhales ]
Really?
I mean, really?
You ever hear of privacy?
Hey, you want privacy,
close your door.
Thought we talked
about this.
Yeah, we did, Dean.
But why is it so hard to believe
that God could be sending me
visions about the darkness?
You kidding me?
He didn't feel the need
to show up for the Apocalypse.
Why would he give
a crap now?
I don't know. Maybe because
she's his sister?
What do you wanna do? Sit back?
Ignore him? Do nothing?
No, that's -- that's not
what I'm saying.
I'm saying,
don't count on God.
Okay? Count on us.
Right.
Oh, this is everything
Cass dug up in Gaza,
every last bit
of prebiblical lore.
Hmm.
Half of it I couldn't read.
It's in Aramaic.
And the other half...
[ Cell phone rings ]
Nada.
[ Ring ]
Not a single mention
of the darkness, so...
[ Ring ]
Well, I'll be damned.
[ Cell phone beeps ]
Huh?
Donna, what's shakin'?
[ Lowered voice ]
Fat sucker Donna?
What do you mean
"Killer bunny"?
[ Turns off engine ]
[ Whispers ] Sheriff. Hey.
[ Gasps ]
Oh! You two are a sight
for sore eyes!
[ Grunts ]
Mmm!
What, are you working
all 10,000 lakes now?
This isn't usually
your beat.
Just Larsen County, what with
the cutbacks and all.
For the most part, it's been
tater tots and lemon drops,
except for this doozy.
I mean, when you get a call
about a killer Easter bunny,
you don't know what to think.
Well, you think crazy.
Guy's real strong, too.
Lashed out
at several officers.
Took a whole team
just to get him into custody.
But that's not
the weirdest part --
bunny head won't come off.
What do you mean?
Tried everything
short of a chainsaw,
but it's really stuck.
I mean, who knows?
Could be nothing.
Guy could just have a big melon
like my Uncle Wally.
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
But ever since I've seen
what goes bump in the night...
[ Whispers ] I'm not taking
any chances.
You did the right thing,
for sure.
Maybe.
I'm just still not 100% sure
this is our kind of case.
But if, uh,
you got a wild hare...
See what I did there?
[ Laughs, claps hands ]
It's good to see you two!
Who you got there, Sheriff?
[ Clears throat ]
Gentlemen,
this is Officer Stover.
He's lead on the case.
Agents Elliott and Savage.
Huh. Nice to meet ya.
And please, call me Doug.
[ Clears throat ]
These two fine fellas
will be helping out
with the old hippity hop.
Oh. We're gonna need it.
And not that Sheriff Hanscum
isn't doing a bang-up job.
We're lucky to have her.
[ Clears throat ]
Well, I better get
back to it.
[ Telephone ringing ]
Uh-huh.
What?
Hey, it's none
of our business,
but it looks like
somebody might have a crush.
I was born at night, Dean.
Not last night.
[ Chuckles ]
What's the deal?
He seems nice.
He is!
But he's a cop...
named Doug.
I mean, clearly,
I have a type,
but no, thank you, ma'am.
Won't be once bitten,
twice Doug'd.
[ Chuckles ]
All right,
where's the wascally wabbit?
?
Sam: Any witnesses?
Yeah, vic's wife --
Fran Hinkle.
Poor thing thought
she was next,
but the bunny just up
and walked out the door.
You I.D. him yet?
Nope.
No wallet. No cell.
Ran his prints,
but no prior record.
Couldn't even get our hands
on him long enough
to check for any
identifying marks.
Only thing we do know --
he's Caucasian,
roughly 18 to 25.
And terrifying.
[ Knock on door ]
Clive's on the line.
Said it's an emergency.
Just shoot a hoot
if you need me.
Doug: You need anything?
Crullers?
Donna: Not right now.
[ Speaks indistinctly ]
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
What's up, Doc?
Be easier all around
if you just talk to us.
Careful.
Yeah.
So what happened, pal? Hmm?
What, you dropped
too much Molly?
Super glue your mask
to your head,
get paranoid, stab a guy?
Hoo. I've been there.
Let me guess, Rog.
You were framed!
[ Chuckles ]
What?
Dean!
Ah! I-I got it. I got it.
[ Grunts ]
[ Bars rattle ]
Ah!
[ Grunts ]
It's not a demon.
[ Strained voice ] He is strong.
All right. Whoo.
[ Both grunting ]
"Kylie Forever."
That'll work.
Better be her.
Last Kylie on the list.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Car doors creak ]
[ Dog barking in distance ]
Excuse me. Kylie Jennings?
Yes?
You know this rabbit?
You found him.
Who is he?
Mike Hooks.
He's my boyfriend.
Okay, well, you have any idea
why your boyfriend
would stab somebody?
[ Chuckles ] Wait. What?
How would Mike know
Stan Hinkle?
Who?
The victim.
Okay, hold on. This...
This makes no sense.
Why would Mike stab
a complete stranger? I mean...
Oh, God.
What?
I don't know.
I thought it was nothing,
but he was acting
really weird yesterday.
Weird how?
Well, after class, we went
to this thrift shop.
We needed to buy costumes
for a party off-campus.
And Mike found this
super creepy bunny mask.
I mean, it -- it grossed me out,
which he just loved.
But as soon as he put it on...
That's when the weird started?
Yeah. He just...
Stared at me.
At first, I thought that
he was just messing around,
but then he walked out
without paying.
He left his cell
at the register,
so I had no way
of reaching him, and...
Look, Mike's, like,
the sweetest, okay?
But I'm telling you,
as soon as he put that mask on,
it's like he was
a completely different person.
[ Sighs deeply ]
You really think the hospital
can get this puppy off?
Two words -- bone saw.
Yeah, let's see here...
What?
Lady cops can't handle
the heavy liftin'?
I didn't mean that...
I just figured...
We shot him full
of tranquilizers.
Dead weight.
I didn't want you
to hurt yourself.
"Hurt myself"?
I do crossfit.
Just gotta engage the core
and lift with the knees.
[ Strained voice ]
Watch and learn.
[ Grunts, clears throat ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
Oh!
[ Panting ] Little help
would be nice!
Okay, yeah.
[ Both groaning ]
[ Cell phone rings ]
Yeah. Oh, hold up.
Oh! [ Grunts ]
[ Ring ]
[ Beep ]
Those FBI boys.
Hiya, Dean.
Whoa.
Whoa!
[ Grunts ] Aah!
[ Gunshots ]
[ Thud ]
Oh!
[ Panting ]
[ Cocks gun ]
?
You okay?
No, not really.
A 19-year-old kid is dead.
[ Train whistle blows ]
That's not on you or Doug.
He was just doing his job.
[ Train whistle blows ]
I know, but...
That kid was innocent.
I mean,
if the mask was cursed,
then he was just a puppet,
right?
He was victim, too.
No one else dies.
[ Matches rattle ]
Not like this.
[ Whoosh ]
?
[ Exhales slowly ]
Come on.
[ Exhales sharply ]
That's good.
Come on, one more.
[ Exhales slowly ]
Good.
[ Exhales deeply ]
Nice job, Buckner. All your
hard work's gonna pay off.
You think so, Coach?
I know so.
Any scout would be a damn fool
not to snatch you up.
Just lay off the H.G.H.
You might have to pee
in a cup.
[ Chuckles ]
I'll be next door
if you need another spot.
[ Five Finger Death Punch's
"Hell To Pay" playing ]
[ Dumbbells clank ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
? Feels like
I'm running in place ?
? a past I can't erase ?
? I'm breaking,
breaking apart ?
? I know they're after me ?
? it's like I'm fading
each day ?
? they took it all away ?
[ Exhaling sharply ]
? Left nothing,
nothing but scars ?
? they make it hard
to breathe ?
[ Bells jingle ]
[ Continues exhaling sharply ]
Need another spot?
[ Bells jingle ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Dumbbells thud ]
Aah!
Uhh!
[ Bells jingle ]
Woman over radio: Are you over
at the high school? Come in.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Man over radio:
Yeah, I'm here now.
Donna: Good news --
coach is still alive.
Bad news -- he's in a coma,
so we're not
out of the woods yet.
Two masked psychos
in two days.
I mean,
what are the chances?
[ Police radio chatter ]
[ Clears throat ]
My guess? Copycat killer.
Damn social media.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Uh...
Okay?
Yeah.
You know, did you guys
talk to the kid yet?
Be my guest.
Thanks.
Hi.
Agents Elliott and Savage.
Brock Buckner.
Well, um, Brock,
what did you see?
Not much, man. I mean,
I was just hammering my bi's,
gettin' all swole,
and next thing I know,
coach Evans is getting
his ass kicked by the mascot.
And who is the mascot?
Why would I know?
I'm the quarterback.
Besides,
his mask wouldn't come off.
I couldn't believe
how strong he was either.
I mean, for a scrawny dude,
he was as strong as me,
and I hold
the state bench record.
Oh, yeah?
What do you bench?
Four plates.
On each side.
Oh. That's...
Okay, so other than the, uh,
mask not coming off
and the Jester hulking out,
did you notice
anything else unusual?
What do you mean?
Uh, power surges?
Temperature fluctuations?
Uh, the weight room
did get really cold.
[ Radio chatter continues ]
Thanks.
[ EMF detector whirring ]
Hmm.
Well...
[ Powers down ]
Ain't a cursed object.
[ Sighs ]
Ghost possession.
Oh, for jeez.
Ghosts can possess people?
Yeah. So, uh, Ghosts 101 --
somebody's spirit can attach
itself to an object
or a bunch of objects
left behind.
In this case, masks.
Right, so whoever possesses
the object...
Gets possessed.
But if we can't get the mask,
how the heck do ya
unpossess someone?
Everything has a weakness,
even ghosts.
They hate iron and salt.
So all we gotta do is
spook the spook
with a little salt and, uh,
maybe we could pry it off.
My diet secret.
One bite of dessert
and then I dump salt on it.
Kills the craving.
And that works?
You betcha.
On everything except...
[ Whispers ] salted caramel.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, that's cute.
But I was thinking
something a little bit more like this.
[ Bag thuds ]
You said no one else
was dying.
Salt pellets.
[ Cocks shotgun ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Bells jingle ]
What's going on?
Poor thing doesn't deserve
to be locked up.
So let her go.
No one saw her face, right?
Yeah, he was a drifter,
overpowered you, escaped.
Well, there's some
female empowerment for ya.
[ Sighs ]
Don't worry, hon.
Just gonna ask you
a few questions,
then you're free to go.
I am?
Scout's honor.
You remember attacking
Coach Evans?
No, I swear.
I went to pick up
the new mascot costume,
went to try it on,
and the next thing I know...
[ Inhales sharply ]
I'm in jail.
Did you even know him?
He was my P.E. coach
last semester.
I mean, he was kind of
a hard-ass, but...
That doesn't mean
that I wanted him dead.
Michelle, where did you get
the costume?
Was it a thrift store?
No, someone donated it
to the school.
Do you know who?
Sam: Rita Johnson?
Yeah, who's askin'?
Got a few questions
we want to ask you
about a case in town.
Who is it, Mom?
Um, Max, why don't you go back
and finish your homework?
Why are the police here?
Hey there, fella.
You ever see a real cop car?
I mean, if it's okay
with your mom.
Yeah.
[ Whispers ] Yeah.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
You can talk
on the police radio.
Really?
It's pretty simple to figure out.
Max: Cool.
Mind if we come inside?
[ Donna speaks indistinctly ]
[ Sighs ]
The costumes belonged
to my brother Chester.
He was a kids' party performer
before he passed.
Ah.
And, um, how did --
how did Chester die?
Uh, my brother suffered
from depression.
He took his own life
a couple months back.
Jumped off a bridge.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Max begged me
to keep the costumes.
He loved them.
He loved his uncle.
I mean, he lived with us,
so they were really close.
But they made me sad,
so I donated them
to the local high school,
the theater company.
Thrift shop?
Yeah, places like that.
Can I ask
where Chester's buried?
He's not. He was cremated.
Would you mind making
a list of his costumes?
As many as you can remember?
Sure. But what does this
have to do with your case?
That's what we're trying
to figure out.
Uh, one more question.
Did Chester have a falling out
with Stan Hinkle or Phil Evans?
Um, or anyone
for that matter?
What do you mean?
Did he, um,
did he have any unfinished
business with anyone?
No, not that I can think of.
I mean, I don't even --
I don't think Chester
even knew those guys.
I remember
Chester's suicide.
Real sad.
So now that we know
he's the ghost,
how do we stop him?
Well, usually you gotta
burn their bones,
but he was cremated.
So we're up poop's creek
without a paddle?
Mm.
Not exactly.
I mean, looks like he's tied
to the costumes,
which means the only way
to stop him is to burn them.
Then we're already
ahead of the game.
I had Doug go to the high school
and collect the costumes.
Great.
[ Paper crinkles ]
Here is a list of the rest.
Think you and Doug
can round 'em up?
Yeah. You betcha.
Now we just gotta
figure out
what Chester's beef was
with the vics.
Ghosts come back
for something personal.
Usually, it's revenge.
All right, drop me off
at the hospital.
I'll check on the coach.
I'll see if I can find
Stan's widow. Let's go.
[ Door creaks ]
[ Ventilator whirring ]
[ Calliope music playing ]
[ Slices, splatters ]
[ Monitor beeping rapidly ]
[ Monitor emitting
continuous tone ]
[ Bell dings ]
[ Muzak playing ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Elevator whirring ]
[ Bell dings ]
?
[ Grunting ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Bell dings ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Breathing deeply ]
?
Who the hell are you?
[ Bell dings ]
[ Wheels rattling ]
You get a story out of Bozo?
Yeah, uh, name is
Steve Buress.
60 years old, retired G.P.
Apparently, he was playing
dress-up with his grandson,
and the next thing
he knew, he...
Doesn't even know
how he got to the hospital.
[ Telephone ringing
in distance ]
He "escape," too?
Yeah.
[ Sighs ]
I'm so losing my job.
I was on my way to Woodbury
to pick up a Woodpecker costume.
Then I got the call
about the coach.
Yeah. This time...
Killer clown.
Already put out an A.P.B.
What the heck is going on
in this doggone town?
Told ya. Copycat killers.
So this is a-a copycat
of a copycat?
Come on, Doug.
It's not that hard to wrap
your noggin around, is it?
Whatever you say, Sheriff.
I'm gonna go get
the Woodpecker.
What's the deal? Why don't you
cut the guy a break?
I mean, I wouldn't be buying
what you're selling either.
I don't have time
for insubordination.
Or is it maybe that you're
treating new Doug like old Doug
and not even
giving him a chance?
You know what I think?
You need to mind
your own beeswax.
We have a case to solve.
?
Phil and Stan
were college roommates.
Knew each other
since they were 18.
They were like brothers.
Out of all these years
of friendship,
did, uh, your husband
or the coach ever know a guy
by the name of
Chester Johnson?
He was
a children's performer.
Yeah. They knew.
Ugh. I can't even
say his name.
He makes me sick.
[ Sighs ] I know you shouldn't
speak ill of the dead,
but I have nothing nice
to say about that man.
Killer clown?
You're serious?
No, Dean, I'm joking.
Because clowns are
really funny to me.
Did you take care of it?
Yeah.
What about you? Anything?
Yeah, turns out
that Stan and the coach
were besties from way back
who accused Chester of crossing
the line with their kids.
Oh. Wow.
Yeah.
But they didn't wanna
go to the cops
'cause they didn't wanna
embarrass their kids.
So they decided to track down
Chester themselves.
They went to his house
and got Rita instead.
So she lied?
Chester did know the vics?
Apparently.
So Fran said that
Rita told them to screw off.
And...Well, before they had
a chance to confront him,
he killed himself.
So suicide led to
a vengeful spirit.
I mean, it's not like
we haven't seen it before.
Or maybe it wasn't suicide.
[ Door creaks ]
Hey, uh, Max, right?
Is, uh, is your mom home?
Not yet.
Okay.
Um, I just needed to ask her
a few more questions.
Uh... [ clicks tongue ]
Um...
I-I guess you can
wait inside.
Okay.
[ Door creaks ]
[ Lock clicks ]
Hey. Poker?
I can show you
a move or two.
Magic trick.
Something my uncle taught me.
Ah. Yeah, you were
pretty close to him, huh?
Yeah.
He was cool. I miss him.
He sounds like a good guy.
He was.
What those men said about him
wasn't true.
[ Door creaks ] I don't appreciate you
talking to my son
when I am not home.
[ Door closes ]
Hey, we were just trading some
card tricks, that's all.
What are you even doing here?
I told you everything I know.
Okay, honey, go to your room.
[ Door opens and closes ]
Look, we know
that the coach and Stan
confronted you about Chester.
That is none of
your damn business.
It has nothing to do
with any of this.
Those men were murdered.
And whether or not you believe
it, your brother is connected.
How? Chester is dead.
Killed himself.
You sure about that?
Oh!
Look, we need to know
the truth.
People's lives are
at stake here.
Yeah. Maybe yours.
Maybe Max's.
Okay. [ Sighs ]
Okay.
A couple of months ago,
Stan and the coach came by.
They said that Chester
was with their kids,
did something...
inappropriate.
I got defensive. I mean...
Chester was sweet,
like a dad to Max.
So I told them to get lost.
If they had a problem
with Chester,
they could go to the cops.
But they didn't.
They didn't have any evidence.
But then,
I started to have my doubts.
I mean, as much as I wanted
to defend my brother...
What they said really...
Got under my skin.
Chester was always a little...
Off.
Only got along with kids.
That's why he became
a party performer.
I spent my whole life
sticking up for my brother.
But what if I couldn't see him
for who he really was?
[ Voice breaks ]
And he and Max were so close.
[ Whispers ] I mean...
What if he was hurting him,
and I didn't know?
Chester was my brother, but...
Max is my son.
So you wanted
to protect him?
How could I look
the other way?
I had to suck it up
and face my biggest fear.
If not me, then who?
But I should've talked to him.
I just should've gone
to him first.
Instead...
I called Stan back.
And he said that
they would take care of it.
So one day when Chester
was working,
I told them where he was.
[ Whistling ]
Going somewhere?
[ Keys jangle ]
Yeah. Home.
I don't think so.
No. Hey!
Hey! Help! Help!
They promised me that they
weren't gonna hurt Chester.
They were just gonna
scare him a little bit.
And I thought, you know,
maybe a good scare..,
maybe that's all he needed.
[ Screaming ]
Stop! Stop, please!
Stop! Why are you doing this?!
You know why, sicko!
Leave our kids alone!
I've never hurt your kids
or anyone's kids!
I love kids!
Yeah, we know!
Oh! Oh!
Let me go. Let me go!
Stop it! We're not gonna --
let me go!
Stop it! We won't --
Oh, let me go!
Stop it! Stop it!
[ Screams ]
They didn't mean to kill him.
They -- they said...
That it was an accident.
But I wasn't there, so I didn't
know what to believe.
[ Gasping ]
[ Birds calling ]
And I wanted to go to the cops
and explain what happened,
but Stan said that
we'd all go to jail.
And I couldn't do that to Max.
[ Voice breaking ]
He already lost his father
and his uncle.
And he...
He couldn't lose me, too.
So I...didn't say anything.
Fear cripples you.
It makes you do nothing.
Or worse...
[ Crying ] It makes you do
something that you regret.
[ Sniffles ]
I should've trusted
my brother.
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Cell phone rings ]
[ Sniffles ]
[ Ring, beep ]
Hi. How's it going?
Tracked down
every last costume.
You didn't happen to see
a-a deer head by chance,
did you?
Deer head?
Oh, my God.
That wasn't on the list.
Uhh! [ Groans ]
Max?
[ Whispers ] Max? Max?
Uhh! Aah!
[ Glass shatters ]
Max? Max! [ Grunts ]
[ Strained voice ]
Max. Max, no!
What are you doing? M-Max!
[ Grunts ]
[ Whoosh ]
Max?
[ Groans ]
[ Voice breaks ]
Mom, what's happening?
Oh!
Hey! Burn it now!
Yeah.
?
[ Panting ]
Come with me.
[ Whoosh ]
[ Growls ]
[ Grunts ]
Uhh! [ Groans ]
Okay. Whatever you do,
stay inside this circle.
I don't understand.
Ghosts.
You wanna know
how this ties to your brother?
Cause and effect.
Wrongful death
spawns a vengeful spirit.
Chester.
Uhh! Aah!
[ Glass shatters ]
Uncle Chester, no!
[ Grunts ]
[ Growling ]
[ Groans and gasps ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Panting ]
Sam: All right,
I think it's, uh,
time we gotta get out of here.
Here's hoping something
less murderous
brings you back
to Minnesota,
like Prince
or cheese curd fest.
You had me at "curd."
[ Laughs ]
I-I don't know
how you two do this,
day in, day out.
Figuring out
who's possessed, who isn't.
Your life's one big poop storm,
isn't it?
Spoken like a true hunter.
Really?
Hunter?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, with three cases
under your belt,
I think you earned it.
Yay!
[ Grunts ]
Okay. [ Clears throat ]
Yeah.
Mmm!
[ Pats back ]
There we go.
[ Laughs ]
Thank you.
Bye.
So... [ sighs ]
[ Door creaks ]
Been a crazy couple of days.
[ Door closes ]
Darn tootin'.
[ Chuckles ]
But you've been great.
I really appreciate
all your hard work.
And, uh...
[ Clears throat ]
Sorry if I was
a little tough on ya.
You mean you treating me
like a punching bag?
[ Chuckles ]
It's okay. Really.
I got baggage, too, Donna.
Everyone does.
You know, if it makes you
feel any better,
you can call me by
my middle name...
Lonnie.
Mnh.
[ Laughs ]
I think "Doug" will do
just fine.
Okay. [ Chuckles ]
[ Engine purring ]
I keep praying to God
because if it is God --
and I know you think it isn't,
but if it is --
then he's showing me something
I don't know what to do with.
What?
The cage.
Lucifer's cage?
Yeah.
What if he's telling me
I have to go back?
What if he's saying
that's where the answer is
to beating the Darkness?
Sam, no. No, okay.
I don't know if these visions
are coming from God
or PBS or what.
But we've been down
that road.
Anything having to do with that
cage is -- it -- it's suicide.
And you of all people
know that.
[ Sighs ]
So, no.
Just...Not gonna happen.
Okay.
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man