Dean: We are not the only
hunters on the planet.
[ Blade clangs ]
Hunters. So trusting.
Listen, I have seen more than
my share of monsters.
And I mean real monsters,
bad monsters.
Oh, Lucifer.
Dear nephew,
my, how you've changed.
[ Whooshing ]
I think you and I need to have
a nice, long chat.
[ Whoosh ]
[ Grunts ]
Uhh!
You may be the one thing
in all of creation
that He still cares about,
the one thing
that could finally
make him show himself.
[ Screaming ]
[ Creek trickling ]
Jesse:
It finally happened.
Matty: What? You didn't get
detention this week?
Me and Jackie, we kissed.
Okay, can I stop hearing about
him every two minutes now?
"You think he likes me?"
"Jackie looked at me.
I-I think he looked at me."
He definitely likes me.
Jesse, you know
you gotta be careful, right?
I'm not an idiot.
Yeah, I know,
but it's not just
Ned and Charlie and those dicks
who'll stomp your head in.
I mean, everybody at school
and in town...
they won't leave you alone.
Okay.
I wish we were gone
already.
Can't you lie and say
you're 18 and get a fake ID?
California's expensive,
okay?
We just gotta save
some more money.
You can sell
your collection.
I will, okay?
When it's time.
I can get at least $900
for the Buffalo nickel
and another $400
for the double eagle.
That's a lot.
Look, Jess...
As soon as I turn 18,
I promise,
we're gonna get out of here,
okay?
Can I see it?
Yeah.
[ Cooler clatters ]
Come on. Here.
Gotta go get that
early morning bite, right?
Hang on. I gotta pee.
[ Tackle box clatters ]
[ Rattling and buzzing ]
[ Birds calling ]
[ Rustling ]
Matty?
[ Rattling and buzzing ]
Jesse! Aah!
Matty!
[ Rattling and buzzing ]
Jesse! Aah!
Jesse! Jesse!
[ Grunts ] Aah!
Matty!
Matty! Matty!
?
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Rattling and buzzing
continues ]
? Supernatural 11x19 ?
The Chitters
Original Air Date on April 27, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
?
[ Utensil clinks ]
Dude, you even move
since last night?
Sleeping is the new smoking.
What? No, it's not.
It's sitting.
Sitting is the new smoking.
That can't be right.
Dean, we'll find Cass, okay?
He's stronger than he looks.
You know, we gambled with Cass,
and now Amara has him.
For a reason,
which means he's still alive.
I've been with Amara.
Her beef is with the big guys --
with God, with Lucifer.
The small fries,
even an angel like Cass,
doesn't even register.
And if it meant hurting Lucifer,
killing Cass would mean
nothing to her.
It's been a week.
We've still got no leads.
You think
I don't know that?
So... [ Sighs ]
[ Utensil clinks ]
So we get back out there.
We get back to work.
We keep moving. We keep working.
We'll catch a break on Cass.
We have to. It's -- it's karma.
You know, karma's been
kicking us in the teeth lately.
Yeah. [ Sighs ]
So...
[ Bowl thuds ]
...let's kick it back.
Here. Check this out.
Libby Strauss.
Uh, went missing
near Gunnison, Colorado.
Now Libby's friend claimed
she was carried off
by a mutant creature
with green eyes.
Demon?
That's what I thought,
but it gets better.
The friend chased after 'em
and she found Libby,
only it wasn't Libby anymore
because now she, too,
is a green-eyed mutant.
Demon swap suits?
Only one way to find out.
?
[ Tires squeal, engine revs ]
Dean: How many missing
do you have?
Six, all in the last 48 hours.
They're disappearing one by one.
Okay, uh, let's start with
Libby Strauss.
I understand that she was
from out of town.
Uh, she and a friend were
visiting from Tucson.
Libby was
the first reported missing.
But all the rest have
been local?
All residents.
You got any leads?
The only eyewitness I have
is the friend.
Not the most reliable source.
Why is that?
She and Libby were on
the last legs
of their cannabis tasting tour.
Fumes still coming off the girl
when I questioned her.
A trippin' trip.
[ Chuckles ]
Have you had anything odd like
this happen around here before?
[ Sighs ] 27 years ago.
About a dozen residents
went missing.
27 years before that,
another 8 disappeared.
All within the same time frame?
Couple days?
Same time of year, too.
And how far back
do the disappearances go?
That's it. The town's only been
here since the '50s.
It was all virgin forest
till they found coal here.
So then how do people explain
the missing?
Mostly they don't.
People come and go
in this town.
I've only been here
two years, myself.
There are some old-timers
with their theories.
Such as?
Town's built on
an Indian burial ground.
Forest folk are pissed
because we stole their coal.
And what's your take?
We're a small town.
People get bored,
they get fed up, they leave.
Once a few get free,
it's like a jail break.
Encourages the others.
Every 27 years like
clockwork?
Honestly, I-I'm just focused on
the missing
that I have right now.
You're welcome to take a look
at the files,
talk to the witness.
[ Inhales deeply ]
I've got panicked residents
I need to talk down.
Right. Sure.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
What the hell
is going on here?
No idea.
Whatever it is, it's moved in.
[ Door closes ]
Or keeps coming back
for seconds.
[ Inhales deeply ] All right,
I'll go check the reports
on the other missing.
Oh.
I guess that leaves me
Ganja Girl.
[ Water trickling] You're gonna say
I was hallucinating.
The weed was laced with PCP
or something.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
It's okay, Cori, just -- just...
tell me what you remember.
And nothing is too strange
or weird to mention.
The thing that took Libby
was naked and pale.
Except for the eyes.
I swear to God, they flashed
green for a second.
And it didn't have any hair.
Anywhere.
It was shaped like a man.
Or was it a woman?
Was it a man or a woman?
It didn't have a...
A penis?
It didn't have anything.
What, you're saying it was
junkless?
Completely.
Okay, uh...
anything else unusual
you can remember?
Sounds? Smells?
Definitely sound.
When I found Libby,
she was just
standing there...
shivering, shaking.
It was creepy.
[ Rattling and buzzing ]
[ Breathing shakily ]
Libby?
What happened?
[ Hisses and growls ]
[ Screams ]
It wasn't Libby.
I don't know what it was.
The buzzing...
was coming from her body?
We heard the same sound
right before that thing
jumped out at us.
Green eyes, buzzing.
Weed alone doesn't conjure up
that kind of scenario.
[ Inhales deeply ]
Isn't that right, Sam?
Dude, I was 18.
Sinner.
It was college.
It was probably oregano
anyways.
Rebel.
You're an idiot.
Look,
I'm coming up empty also.
Uh, nothing on Junkless
or the green-eyed shaker.
So we think Junkless
turned Libby?
Hold up.
We're not actually gonna go with
"Junkless" on this, are we?
Eh.
Dude, that's a new low,
even for us.
Well, something happened.
You got the eyes, the buzzing.
Yeah, I know you're right.
That can't be a coincidence.
Uh, here, I found this.
The, uh, the sheriff
who was here in '89, Cochran.
Those are his notes.
There's no mention of buzzing.
But he seemed to be closing in
on some of the missing,
and then his notes, they just
kind of abruptly stop.
He take a flyer, too?
No. He remained sheriff
for a few more months.
He ended up resigning and, uh,
then he fell off the radar.
I asked around the station,
but that was a few sheriffs ago.
So...
Nothing?
The dispatcher said she thought
he moved to Florida,
but that was a dead end.
Kind of like this case.
Yeah.
[ Telephone rings in distance ]
Wait a second.
[ Papers rustle ]
Most of the witnesses
in '89 and '62,
they're all dead
or they've moved away,
but there does seem to be
one holdout from the '89 case.
Etta Fraser.
Let's go talk to Etta.
Your husband was one of
the people who disappeared
in 1989.
Oh, my second husband.
Barely that. [ Chuckles ]
Pete only stuck around
a couple months.
So he left voluntarily?
Oh. [ Chuckles ]
Pete was volunteering himself
all over the place.
Right before he disappeared,
people saw Pete diddling
two different women in public,
separate occasions.
You mean they actually
saw him in the act?
What does "diddling" mean
to you?
Uh, Pete was never a showman,
but apparently, Doris Kagen
and Missy Petersen
brought out the hog in him.
Doris and Melissa --
uh, Missy --
they disappeared that year, too.
Oh, yeah. Surprise, surprise.
I'd bet my mortgage
Pete ran off with one of 'em.
But you reported him
as missing.
Well, he didn't come home
for three days.
I thought he was
dead in a ditch somewhere.
We didn't find out about
the women for a long time after.
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Sniffs ] Is that...
is that white sage?
Mm. Yeah,
you know your herbs.
You, uh, planning on
taking a trip?
Uh, yeah. I'm going to stay
with my sister a few weeks.
For any reason?
You're gonna think
it's real out there.
Well, you'd be surprised
at the kind of crazy we hear.
Well...
when Pete went missing, and we
found out about the women,
my grandma said
that he "got the chitters."
According to her,
once a generation
around the spring equinox,
people in town start going nuts,
having orgies,
copulating in the woods.
And then they disappear,
never to be heard from again.
Well, that's certainly
one explanation for Pete.
[ Chuckles ]
I never really, um,
believed what she said, but...
now people are
disappearing again.
She always said burn sage
to protect yourself.
Hmm. So why did she call it
"the chitters"?
Oh, that was the word
Gran used
to describe the sound
coming from the woods
when the orgies were
happening.
Yeah, kind of a buzzing,
rattling.
Did your Gran ever mention
something about, uh, green eyes?
Oh, yeah.
Gran said that if you got
the chitters,
you get so revved up
with lust
that your eyes would shine
like emeralds.
?
Uh...
So we got spring equinox.
Which was yesterday.
Orgies, buzzing green-eyed freaks.
[ Dog barks ]
Sounds like a rager.
All right, let's pick up a six-pack.
Just six?
Oh, whatever.
Let's hit the books.
[ Dog barking ]
[ Siren wailing in distance ]
Just don't be a wuss.
It's faster this way.
And it smells like a urinal,
but whatevs.
[ Rattling and buzzing ]
Whoa.
[ Woman moans ]
[ Rattling growl ]
[ Hisses ]
[ Screams ]
Come on!
[ Rattling and buzzing ]
[ Both scream ]
[ Screams ]
[ Boy screaming, man growling ]
[ Siren wailing ]
We ran, and then another one
with green eyes
came from nowhere.
It was Coach Hollister.
Grant Hollister?
He attacked us.
He had these teeth
that were pointed.
He ripped into Cliff.
I could hear him screaming,
but...I ran.
[ Crying ]
He killed Cliff.
Did you, by chance,
recognize the couple?
It was one of
the Deaver brothers --
the tall one --
and Mrs. Limoski.
You're sure about this?
Did you see anybody else?
I couldn't see their faces,
but I'm pretty sure
there was more of them
down the alley, past the couple.
I-I could see them
moving around.
The, uh, the couple that --
that was...going at it,
would you say this was a...
orgy-like situation?
I've...never seen an orgy.
No?
Enough.
Excuse us a second.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Telephone rings ]
[ Train whistle blowing
in distance ]
I got a dead kid
minus a chunk out of his neck
and all the people that girl
ID'ed are missing.
Were missing.
Yeah, now they're all having
sex with each other.
Then there's that.
Putting aside the fact
that Rob the fireman
is screwing the librarian,
and I am friends
with his pregnant wife,
now I've got two witnesses
claiming they saw...what?
I don't even know. Aliens?
Attacking people.
Yeah.
What is this?
Spanish Fly gone bad?
Well, I can honestly say this is
a new one for us.
I gotta go contact
the families.
[ Mouths word ] Right.
[ Sighs ]
So we have confirmed
orgy-ish behavior.
Yeah, just like Etta's husband.
What, the chitters?
Well, we should go check
the crime scene. [ Cellphone rings, beeps ]
Agent Lewis.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey.
Cori, calm down.
Where exactly?
All right, I'm on my way.
[ Beep ]
Ganja Girl's
pretty hysterical.
Says she just saw her friend
walking in the woods.
She's too freaked out
to go, so...
You go. I'll grab the alley.
Great.
[ Sighs heavily ]
?
[ Rattling and buzzing ]
Libby?
[ Rattling and buzzing stop ]
Hey, Libby, there's a whole lot
of people looking for you.
[ Hisses ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Head thuds ]
Uhh!
[ Panting ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Squishing ]
You hurt?
No, I'm -- I'm --
I'm good. Thanks.
[ Grunts ]
Jesse, I think it's dead.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Just making sure.
Who the hell are you guys?
You wouldn't believe us.
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Blues music playing ]
[ Bottles thud,
pool balls clack ]
So how long have you guys
been hunting?
Together? About seven years.
And we've heard
of the Winchesters,
but we also heard you bit it
a couple years ago.
Ah, that's a long, ugly,
ugly story.
Hey.
Sam, hey. Uh, Jesse and Cesar.
You guys are hunters, right?
Yeah.
I'm surprised we never ran into you.
Well, we're mostly in Mexico.
Sometimes we make a run
over into Texas.
Nice. Uh, nothing in the alley,
by the way.
Thanks.
[ Bottle thuds ]
You guys have any idea
what we're hunting?
They're called Bisaan.
It's a kind of cicada spirit.
We couldn't find any lore
on 'em.
They're rare,
at least in America.
People think that
they originated in Malaysia
in the forests there.
[ Door opens ]
So what are they doing here?
What they always do.
[ Door closes ]
Every 27 years, they come up
from underground,
they mate like crazy
for a few days.
That generation dies off,
and the whole cycle
goes on repeat.
So they're reproducing?
But we're -- we're dealing
with townsfolk here.
I mean, they didn't just crawl
out of a hole a few days ago.
This is what surfaces.
Bisaan can't reproduce
on their own,
so they take over a human body
to do the deed.
They enter through the mouth,
like a hermit crab
climbing into a shell.
Only they don't care
that the shell's not empty.
Well, that explains Junkless.
What about the buzzing?
It's how they communicate.
It's a mating call.
And you, um...
kill them by taking off
their heads, I see.
Seems to do the trick.
How do you guys know
so much about these things?
?
One of them took my brother
27 years ago.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
I'm sorry to hear that.
I've been waiting years
to come back
and have this shot at them.
So I hope you understand,
I'm gonna ask you two to take
a step back from this one.
Well, catch us up.
Where have you guys been?
In the woods,
where the action is,
looking for their burrow
and saving your ass.
[ Exhales ]
What?
Well, one of the reasons we've
been holed up in the trees
is because Jesse hates the town
and everyone in it.
Because they're ignorant
and useless.
They didn't believe me
27 years ago,
they're not gonna start now.
It's boneheaded not to be
following leads in town.
Hey, nobody's stopping you
from talking to
the whole box of crackers.
Ah, you guys fight just like
brothers. [ Chuckles ]
Almost as bad as us.
[ Chuckles ]
Well...
it's more like
an old married couple.
[ Chuckles ] That's...
Oh. So...
Yeah.
Okay. That's...
[ Bottle thuds ]
What's it like settling down
with a hunter?
Smelly, dirty.
Twice the worrying
about getting ganked.
Huh.
Jesse, you're from here.
Do you know anything about
the sheriff, Cochran,
who worked the case
back in '89?
That son of a bitch
was incompetent.
He shut himself away
years ago.
Do you know where he is?
Turned tail,
ran off into the hills
couple towns over.
Lives like a hermit.
Can you take us there?
It seems like he was honing in
on some of the missing.
We need to find the burrow.
Jess.
We've been beating around
the woods for two days.
That's where they are.
You saw the tracks.
I can keep searching on my own.
We're losing.
Why don't I go with you?
We'll start where --
where I got jumped.
Okay.
?
How long do we have
before these things are gone?
We gotta find
the burrow tonight.
By tomorrow, the Bisaan will be
underground, dying.
Won't be able to find them
or their eggs.
And Jesse will wait another
27 years.
Well, there's four of us now.
We'll smoke
those sons of bitches.
Yeah. It'll eat him alive
if we don't.
It's hard to watch someone
go through that, isn't it?
[ Exhales ] Yeah.
I never had a brother
or a sister,
but I've seen it
over and over,
when someone loses someone
when they're young.
It never heals over.
No, it doesn't.
And the insane thing is,
how many hunters
have you seen over the years
get their revenge?
A few.
Yeah. Me, too.
And they are never fixed,
are they?
No, I guess not.
But you gotta help him
get that revenge anyway.
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Thunder rumbling ]
?
I must've stumbled around
searching for Matty,
10, 20 minutes.
[ Sighs ] I was
shaking and panicking.
Told myself I had to focus,
find him,
and I did.
Those green eyes
staring at me.
It wasn't human.
I took off,
didn't look back.
You never saw him again
after that?
Everybody in town,
including my mom,
thought some pervert
had taken him.
She was falling apart,
crying.
Why didn't I remember
what the guy looked like?
Why was I making up
this lie?
She still live here?
Moved as soon as she could.
Still thinks I should've
done something.
Saved him. Everybody did.
They couldn't accept
that your brother
was taken by a monster, huh?
They couldn't accept
a lot of things.
But Matty did.
He was a great brother.
?
[ Low rattling and buzzing ]
[ Branch snaps ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Hisses ]
[ Groans ] Ah!
You good?
Go!
[ Groans, Pants ]
[ Owl hoots ]
I don't care
if you're FBI or not.
It was 30 years ago.
I don't remember a damn thing.
[ Inhales deeply ]
Except we never found them.
Yeah, well, one of them
was a 16-year-old boy,
and that was my brother.
A lot of folks lost family
that year.
And you didn't help
a damn one of them, did you?
Jesse...
Mr. Cochran,
we're here because more people
have gone missing.
The same MO.
No.
No, it's done.
It's done.
[ Rustling ]
[ Groans ]
Cesar?
You lost it?
No. No, I followed it.
I saw where it went.
I think I found the burrow.
[ Exhales ] Thank God.
I think that's why
he attacked you.
He was being protective.
Of what?
The females, the burrow.
Oh, that makes sense. Must be
laying their eggs by now.
You gonna be all right?
Yeah. Where are we headed?
It's a hike.
That's okay.
I tried to call Sam.
There's no service.
Do you think
the whole brood's there?
If we're lucky.
[ Sighs deeply ] Let's go.
All right.
[ Squeaks ]
[ Squeaks, water stops ]
Okay, I'll tell you what.
Leave me your card,
and if anything
comes back to me, I'll call.
Mr. Cochran,
you don't own a phone.
Look, we're not asking
for a lot.
Just please tell us
what you know.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
I couldn't find them.
So that's on me.
[ Sighs heavily ]
I never recovered from it.
I...I...
So I bought this little slice
of heaven and made my peace.
I wish you all better luck.
Joe...please.
I was 12 when my brother
got taken.
I never got over
what I lost that day,
the one person in the whole
world I loved the most.
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Okay, I'm only gonna say this
once. It's time for you to go.
Listen, we know what took
Jesse's brother,
and what took all
the townspeople then and now.
You know, Jesse was only a kid
at the time,
but he was telling the truth.
What took these people
was not human.
How do you know?
It's what we do.
I saw one of the creatures
today.
[ Inhales sharply ]
I knew she was something.
I didn't know what.
I tracked one of those things
down in '89.
It was sick and dying.
I...
I followed it back
to its -- it's lair, I guess.
[ Voice breaks ]
My daughter was there.
[ Crying ]
Couple of days before that, she
had left to go back to school.
I... [ Exhales sharply ]
I don't know what happened.
But she was one of them.
[ Inhales shakily ]
Wait a second. You never
reported her as missing.
[ Sniffles ]
I knew where she was.
[ Inhales deeply,
exhales sharply ]
All the missing people were...
scattered all around, dead.
[ Sniffles ]
I think she and that other thing
had killed them.
I tried...
I tried talking to her,
but she attacked me
like some kind of rabid wolf.
[ Sniffles ]
Teeth like thorns.
I killed her.
You son of a bitch.
You knew the whole time!
You knew where they were
when everybody was suffering.
I was suffering, too!
Jesse. Hey, hey.
Hold on. Hold on.
You think anybody would've
believed me?! Monsters?
You told me
I was making it up!
We could've told people
together, found those things.
They were already dying.
All the missing people
were dead.
No.
You didn't wanna say that
your kid was one of them --
a monster --
and that you...
Hey.
...killed her.
Jesse.
You killed her.
Jesse, stop. Stop.
What did you do?
What, did you just erase her
from your life?
Pretend that she just
went away somewhere?
[ Crying ]
Yeah, better to bury it.
All of it.
[ Exhales shakily ]
We just let
the townspeople think
their loved ones
had run off for a...
big, bright life.
Where was she?
Where did you find her?
[ Inhales sharply ]
By Taylor Creek.
The old Donnelly mine.
[ Sniffles ]
Come on.
[ Exhales shakily ]
[ Foliage rustles ]
?
[ Wood cracks ]
[ Boards clatter ]
?
[ Low rattling ]
[ Squishing sounds ]
[ Low rattling and buzzing ]
[ Hisses ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Grunts ]
Uhh!
[ Growls ]
Oh! [ Groans ]
[ Machete clangs ]
[ Squish ]
[ Hisses ]
Uhh!
[ Head thuds ]
[ Hissing ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Shovel clangs ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Shovel clanking ]
[ Head thuds ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Panting ] Oh.
I hate it
when I lose my blade.
Yeah. You could've
jumped in anytime.
[ Shovel thuds ]
[ Groans ]
[ Shovel clatters ]
What is this place?
[ Low rattling ]
It's a maternity ward/
subway station.
That hole --
I think that's a tunnel.
That's gotta go topside
eventually.
Mothers are already dead.
Males weren't protecting them.
They were protecting the eggs.
They must gestate inside
for years till they hatch.
Yeah, well, these aren't.
I got about 5 gallons
of gasoline in the car.
I'll go pull her around.
[ Vehicle approaching ]
[ Engine turns off ]
You guys find the burrow?
Where are they?
Dean: They're in the mine.
Don't worry.
They won't be coming back out.
We just gotta take care
of the eggs.
You okay?
Hell, yeah.
It's finally over.
You wanna finish them off?
[ Gasoline sloshes ]
Let's give him a minute.
Jesse: Aw, jeez.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Hey, bro.
[ Crying ]
We found Matty.
[ Whispers ] Oh, jeez.
[ Inhales shakily ]
Oh, god.
[ Exhales sharply ]
We'll give him
a proper burial.
[ Sniffles ]
What about the others?
[ Continues crying ]
Don't worry. We'll, uh...
[ Gasoline sloshes ]
we'll take care of it.
?
[ Birds cawing ]
Sam: You know...
[ Exhales sharply ]
whenever you and dad
used to leave me to go hunting
and I -- and I wouldn't hear
from y'all for a while, I, um,
I was always sure
that some vamp or rugaru
or take your pick...
I always figured
one of them finally got ya.
I tried to think
of what to do,
you know,
the next step to take.
I was just lost.
We came back, though, every time.
[ Wood clattering ]
Yeah.
And look at Jesse. I mean,
he turned out all right.
They're a good team.
Come on.
They are.
I was thinking,
maybe they could
give us a hand with Amara,
you know, with Cass.
Fresh eyes.
Could use
the extra muscle, too.
Yeah.
[ Match strikes ]
[ Flames whoosh ]
You did it.
We did it.
Thank you.
?
[ Flames whoosh ]
You know, it's a good thing
you guys had
that fire extinguisher.
Yeah, for a second there,
I thought the whole mine was
gonna go up in flames.
Yeah, you loved it.
Like 27 birthdays
and Christmases
all in one fireball.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, you're awfully upbeat
for a guy who spent
half the night in a cave.
That's because we had a deal.
When we finished this hunt,
if we caught 'em,
we hang up our spurs.
Nice.
Unless your hides
need saving.
No.
No, we're all set.
So, uh, what's freedom
look like?
Nice little spread
in New Mexico.
We've been paying on it
for years.
Set foot on it about...
twice?
Gonna raise horses.
And if that goes bust,
Jesse used to be an EMT.
Oh, so now I'm supporting
your ass?
[ Chuckles ]
It's time to start living.
Couldn't do it, huh?
No, didn't feel right.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
Two hunters who make it
to the finish line?
Yeah, you leave that alone.
[ Engine starts, revs ]
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man