- Werewolf?
- Their organs was ripped clean out.
- Hearts consumed.
- Everyone here's a wolf?
We don't use the “W” word
around here.
Dean: Break some hearts,
then you eat 'em.
- Lucifer?
- Bloody hell.
Donning this...Cass mask?
Hello, Dean.
Just ugh.
Dean, we'll get him back.
We're gonna save Cass,
we're gonna ice the devil,
and we're gonna
shank the Darkness.
-Damn right.
-Reapers?
People are still dying,
souls to collect.
You kill everyone whose number's up.
I have a list.
Death
is nothing to fear.
What, you got some kind of
death wish or something?
You're the one who's always wanted
to go out blaze of glory style.
- Why are you dead?
- Tessa, I need a favor.
I couldn't live
with you dead.
It's your time to go,
Dean.
Now, if it's the last thing
I do, I'm gonna save you.
- Name's Billie.
- The reaper Billie?
My brother says
you want to kill us.
No.
I'm just gonna make sure
that when you die...
[ Grunting ]
...you stay dead.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Snarls ]
[ Grunting ]
? Supernatural 11x17 ?
Red Meat
Original Air Date on March 30, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
How's it going
over there?
Same.
Hmm.
And you, anything?
Yeah, I-I think so.
Yeah?
On Amara, Lucifer,
Hand of God?
No, no, it's a --
it's a case.
Werewolves looks like.
Um, a pattern of
missing campers --
five
in the last three months.
So they got lost.
Well, that's what the rangers
thought, too,
until a couple days ago,
when they found a body --
Let me guess --
minus a heart.
Yeah. Now, they're calling it
an animal attack, but...
All right, well, we make a call
and we put somebody on it.
Yeah, but...
[ Sighs ]
We'll get him back.
How?
I-I don't know.
But we'll figure it out.
Meantime, we got to
get out of here.
Clear our heads.
I mean, this is a case.
Let's do what we do.
L-Let's work it.
[ Grunts ]
Baby,
you still with me?
All right, all right.
Hey, Dean, they, uh...
Okay, just hold tight,
you two, okay?
All right, listen, we got to get
that bullet out of there, okay?
- [ Grunts ]
- This is gonna hurt like hell.
Oh.
[ Grunting ]
Here, might need that.
[ Grunts ]
Okay, okay.
All right.
Almost got it. Almost got it.
Right there.
Come on, come on!
Okay, there we go.
There we go.
Look at that, huh?
Hey!
Well, you know what?
We got to keep that one.
That one's gonna be
a little memento.
We'll laugh about it
some other time.
Guys?
She ain't doing so good.
I got it.
- Here.
- Thanks.
The one he killed,
he's got the key.
Good. Okay.
W-What were they?
Werewolves.
Told you
they were monsters.
That's right, baby.
You called it.
I thought werewolves
needed nighttime,
a full moon?
We've been here for days.
These guys,
they can change any time.
Yeah, that's 'cause
they were probably purebloods.
And they
can change any time.
Any time they want.
Those wrists --
Those wrists are infected.
We got to get something on them,
okay?
Corbin: Okay.
[ Groans ]
How we doing?
How we doing, huh?
- You good, you good?
- [ Panting ]
All right, keep pressure on it.
Keep pressure.
Here you go.
Wrap those up.
Is there a landline
in here?
You don't have
a cellphone?
There's no service
for miles.
I had a signal back at the car
a couple miles back.
Okay, listen to me.
I'm gonna go for a signal,
okay?
We're gonna get you to
a real doctor.
You're gonna be just fine.
Yeah, no, I know.
Okay.
You and me,
hitching the national parks.
Best honeymoon ever,
right?
Are you okay?
I thought yesterday...
Just a couple scratches.
Hey, we're coming!
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, we can't stay here,
not with the others
still out there.
Others?
Okay, listen,
my brother's been shot.
He can't stay here alone.
Yeah, I'm fine.
[ Grunts ]
- Sam, hey.
- I'm fine.
Hey, hey, hey, let me help.
Yeah, right here.
Okay, guess we're going.
Let's go. Go.
Whew! [ Sighs ]
Rose: You know, I used to
be good with faces,
but it's my age
and the number of folks
that come through this place.
I seem to have lost the knack,
so...
These days, everybody under 40
looks the same to me.
I'm sorry.
All right, look...
we know we're in
the right place.
I've tried all the big
landmarks outside of the park --
the police station,
the -- the --
the fleabag motel
we're staying in, this bar.
Yeah, well, we're running out of
things to interrogate,
unless you want to go outside,
start talking to the trees.
Right.
All right,
let's call it a night.
- [ Clears throat ]
- Right.
Grab the check.
You know, we can go to
Park Services in the morning,
talk to the rangers.
You know
what I was thinking?
You boys should check out
one of the easement cabins.
It's private property
within the park.
It's just held onto
for tax purposes,
so campers stumble on them
and they can hole up in there
for weeks.
Some of your missing
could be in one of them.
Do you mind, um, showing us
about where they are?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Right about there.
Well, that is a big help.
That's great.
Thank you.
No problem.
Thanks.
Careful.
Anything?
[ Cellphone beeping ]
No, nothing yet.
The sun's gonna be up
pretty soon.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come on.
Okay.
[ Grunts ]
I told you that roadhouse chili
was a bad idea.
Yeah.
Guys, over here.
Hey, look at that.
Okay.
All right, see if you can find
a-a radio or a phone.
[ Grunts ]
Anything?
No, it's dead.
[ Sighs ]
[ Phone receiver slams ]
I got matches over here.
I'm gonna light those up.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Okay?
Yeah.
Corbin: Hey.
Hey, we got to keep moving.
Those of us who --
who can.
- What did you say?
- I -- Look.
Hey, Michelle's real sick,
but she's got a chance.
Him --
he's slowing us down.
- And if they find us --
- We saved you, okay?
We saved both of you.
It's three lives
versus one.
Dean, stop!
Dean...
he's right.
You guys need to -- to go.
Move.
Go find help,
come back for me.
No, Sam! No!
I'm gonna go outside,
I'm gonna find some wood,
gonna build you a litter,
and we are going to carry him
the rest of the way.
It's only
a couple of miles.
?
[ Sighs ]
I thought
we trained you boys up right.
I warned you
they were coming,
all but served them up to you
on a platter.
Now what?
Well...
we're burned here.
So clean up their mess
and we'll get gone.
[ Sighs ]
?
Get off me!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
[ Grunts ]
Guys?
Go find Dean.
Get out of here.
Hey, please.
Go.
You got to go.
He won't leave you.
And we won't last out there
without him.
Wait, what?
[ Grunting ]
I'm sorry.
[ Panting ]
Corbin?
Is...
Is he...
Dead.
?
[ Door opens ]
We got to go.
Sam?
Sammy?
What happened?
I-I-I don't know.
He just went.
No.
Sammy?
[ Vehicle approaches ]
Sammy.
No, no, no.
It's them.
?
Let 'em come.
No. What?
He wants to stay.
No, you can't!
Hey, hey, you stay, you fight,
you die.
And so do we.
Look...he's gone.
I'm sorry, but he's gone.
Help us.
Please.
?
I'm gonna come back for you,
okay?
I promise.
Okay.
Let's go.
?
[ Rose gasps ]
Damn it!
All right, so, I think
if we head in that way,
should be about a four-mile trek
to the cabin.
You know, we always talk about
taking a break, going camping.
This could be like camping.
It could be fun.
Yeah, which part?
Hmm?
Freezing our nuts off
in the middle of the woods
on a thin lead?
Yeah, that part.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, come on.
Okay. [ Sighs ]
[ Birds chirping ]
Hey,
what happened back there?
[ Cellphone beeping ]
Talk to me.
I saved us.
Look,
you're hurt bad and...
And I love you,
Michelle.
I can't lose you.
I did what I had to do.
[ Vehicle approaches ]
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Hey!
Hey! Wait!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Right here, right here!
Okay.
Come on, guys.
Okay, here we go.
- Geez.
- Come on.
What'd you all get into?
She needs medical attention
right away.
- Hey, hold up.
- No, no, just take care of them.
I got to get back to my car,
back to my brother.
Hey, first,
everyone is gonna settle down
and tell me
what the hell is going on.
Officer,
I don't have the time.
Hey, hey, hey!
You'll make time.
[ Grunts ]
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Groans ]
Dr. Kessler: Don't try
to move if you can help it.
You got a couple broken ribs
I haven't tended to yet.
That,
and what is probably...
a nasty concussion.
[ Groans ]
Hey, do us both a favor.
Get some rest.
Mm.
Then his brother...
his brother just died.
And we ran.
The bad guys,
they're still out there.
Monsters.
Werewolves.
We don't know
what their deal was.
Only what
that guy told us.
“That guy” saved us,
and so did his brother.
Thank you for your time.
Your wife's been through
a lot.
I'll give a call
to the rangers,
have them check out the cabin
and the station,
then I'll let you know
what they find.
Okay.
Michelle...
we made it.
Okay,
your wife is stable now.
Time for me to
get a look at you.
I'm fine.
I'll be the judge.
No.
Really, I'm -- I'm good.
Have a seat on the bed.
?
What did this?
How do you feel?
I feel, uh...
...good.
[ Ringing ]
Come on, Charlie, pick up.
Come on.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Grunts ]
Hi.
Hey.
Can -- Can I...
Sure.
I-I just wanted to see
how you were doing.
And to tell you Th...
I'm sorry.
You saved our lives
and...
Well,
my mom used to say, um...
I didn't believe her then,
but I-I think I do now.
She used to say...
death --
it's not the end.
Dean?
- I, uh...
- What are you doing?
I need to...
I need to talk to a --
Well, I wouldn't call it
a friend, more like a...
scary, crazy
death machine.
Werewolves aren't
the only monsters out there.
How exactly do you talk to
an evil, scary death machine?
Easy.
I die.
What?
Look, if you don't...
If you want to leave,
I get it.
But if you want
to help me...
I'm looking for
pretty much anything
with “barbital”
in the name.
?
Yeah.
This will work?
It has to.
?
[ Gasps ]
[ Coughs ]
[ Grunts ]
Okay.
After I do this,
go get the doc
and tell her to, um...
Tell her to bring me back,
if she can.
If not...
no hard feelings, okay?
You don't have to do this.
Yeah, I do.
[ Grunting ]
[ Groans ]
Dean?
[ Screams ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Panting ]
[ Vehicle approaching ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
Go around that side.
How do you feel?
[ Heart beating ]
?
Dean?
[ Grunting ]
Dean!
Oh!
Dean?
?
[ Gasps ]
Michelle: It's in here.
What did he take?
Damn it.
Uh, grab me naloxone.
It's the little bottle, middle
shelf, and a bag of saline.
We need to run a line.
Damn it.
Hold him down.
- Hold him!
- I'm trying!
?
[ Breathing raggedly ]
[ Floorboards creaking ]
[ Sniffs ]
- Help!
- Holy hell.
Help us!
Put me on my back.
It's easier to find a vein.
No.
Roll him over.
[ Grunting ]
Michelle: I got him.
-Hmm.
-Well, it took you long enough.
Dean Winchester.
What's with
the freeze-frame?
Just savoring this.
Though I have to say of all
the ways I thought you'd go --
heart attack, some fang,
choking on a burger
while binge-watching
“Charles in Charge”...
Well,
that was peak Baio.
Point is, never took you
for the suicide type.
Doesn't fit
your whole martyr thing.
So...
'Sup?
We need to talk
about Sam.
What about Sam?
I need him back.
- Back?
- Stop playing.
Look, you've got him,
I need him. Let's make a deal.
Pass.
Really?
Just like that?
Just like that.
You know, the Darkness
is out there...
and the world
is gonna burn.
And once she gets started,
that's the end of everything,
including you.
Now, Sam's the only one
who can stop it.
Hmm.
How's that?
That's what I thought.
It's cute, though.
You pretending you're trying to
save Sam for the greater good,
when we both know
you're doing it for you.
You can't lose him.
But even if Sammy could win
the title bout...
the answer
would still be “no.”
The answer
will always be “no.”
Game's over, Dean.
No more second chances.
No more extra lives.
Time to say bye-bye to Luigi,
Mario.
I'm asking you...
I'm begging you, please.
Bring him back.
Bring him back
and take me instead.
I'm not here
to bargain with you, kid.
I'm here to reap you.
And the kicker is...
Sam's not dead.
But you are.
Or will be, soon enough.
[ Gasping ]
Pulse is fading.
Throw me that cardio tray.
- But how?
- Trust me.
If the big “W” bit it,
I'd get a call.
Come along now, Dean.
It's time.
Dr. Kessler: Okay.
The empty...
it's waiting.
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
Turn him on his side.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Okay.
[ Coughing ]
?
[ Grunts ]
[ Clattering ]
[ Knife plunges ]
[ Body thuds ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
He's alive.
- He?
- Sam?
Oh, thank God.
Yeah, not so much.
I need a -- I need a car.
No.
No, not a chance.
Look, pal,
I'm not asking.
Hey, look, psycho,
I got you for stealing
and consuming a felony's worth
of Schedule IV drugs,
plus assaulting
a police officer.
You ain't going nowhere.
Sedate him.
No.
Can we have a word outside,
please?
[ Panting ]
[ Door closes ]
?
More drugs is the last thing
he needs.
He could die -- again.
Fine,
just keep your eye on him.
I'm gonna call over to
White Bird,
get some backup in here.
[ Engine shuts off,
door alarm chiming ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Chuckles ]
[ Groans ]
[ Dialing ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
Sammy?
Dean, yeah.
Oh, God.
I -- What happened?
Where are you?
I'm, uh,
at the Urgent Care on 54.
Is Cor--
[ Static ]
Sammy?
Is Corbin with you?
Sam?!
Dean!
[ Cellphone beeping ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Engine starts ]
[ Man groaning ]
Hello?
You okay?
?
[ Gasps ]
I really am.
[ Screams ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
?
Are you okay?
What was that?
What happened?
- I don't know.
- [ Grunts ]
[ Screams ]
[ Body thuds ]
Corbin?
Hey, baby.
Please,
don't be scared of me.
I didn't want this.
Okay, any of this,
but...
it's happened
and it feels so...
You'll see.
[ Whimpering ]
We'll be together.
No. Please.
- Forever.
- No!
[ Screams ]
Run!
[ Gunshot ]
No! No!
It took you long enough.
[ Grunts ]
Hey.
How you doing?
How's your brother?
The doc says that, um...
Well,
when Corbin choked him,
um,
Sam's body went into shock
and his breathing,
his heartbeat
slowed down
to almost nothing.
So he was, uh --
he was just mostly dead.
But he'll be okay.
Must be nice.
?
That wasn't...
Corbin wasn't a killer.
I know.
He did it for me.
Michelle,
this is gonna be very hard.
But you will be okay.
And, eventually...
eventually
you'll get back to normal.
[ Sighs ]
No, I won't.
?
They said I could leave...
[sighs] an hour ago.
But...
where am I
even supposed to go?
After everything
we survived together...
I watched
the man I love die.
There's no normal
after that.
So, that's it, huh?
Two quarts O-neg,
and you're good to go.
[ Sighs ]
How is she?
Ooh.
She's strong.
She'll be all right.
Those stitches gonna hold?
Oh, yeah --
uh, professional grade.
Couple days of antibiotics
and some bed rest,
and I'm, uh,
back to normal.
[ Groans ]
[ Sighs ]
Hey,
so, what did you do?
When you thought
I was dead?
What did you do?
Thought about redecorating
your room,
you know, putting in a Jacuzzi,
a nice disco ball --
really class up the joint.
Right, seriously.
What, I, uh...
I knew you weren't dead.
Right.
I knew.
[ Engine starts ]
?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man