Dean: We did this, Sam.
We broke it, we bought it.
Sam: I unleashed a force on this
world that could destroy it.
All I know is that
we set her free,
and we're gonna put her back
there no matter what it takes.
[ "Changing Tracks" plays ]
? Blowin' Cold in Chicago ?
? the sun has the blues,
and it just won't shine ?
Aah!
? The riffs
that really move me ?
Ohh!
Aah!
? Make the hours
and the minutes mark time ?
[ Grunts ]
Aah!
? Took the blacktop to Texas ?
aah!
? Stevie Ray was on my mind ?
Ohhh!
? Knelt down at the crossroads ?
? can't get the devil
off my mind ?
In order to create the world,
God,
he had to betray the Darkness --
his sister.
[ Music continues ]
Dean: What was that?
Amara: The future.
We're bonded.
You're the one
who set me free.
No, that was an accident.
It was destiny.
I can't be resisted.
There's this cage in Hell,
and it's where
they keep Lucifer,
and I've been in it,
and I think God
wants me to go back.
He's so Alpha.
It wasn't God
inside your head, Sam.
It was me.
He's never been with you.
It was always just me.
I guess I am your only hope.
It's never gonna happen.
Settle in there, buddy.
? Godspeed
and help from below ?
[ "Has Anybody Seen
Kris Kringle?" Plays ]
[ Fire crackling ]
Boy, oh, boy.
[ Wrapping paper tearing ]
? Has anybody seen
Kris Kringle? ?
? It's getting mighty close
to Christmas day ?
Mom!
Mom, I got a Sam!
? And I haven't heard
a single ?
? little "Merry Christmas"
jingle ?
Good for you, dearie.
? That's coming from
his reindeer or his sleigh ?
[ Sighs ]
[ Pound at door ]
? Has anybody seen
Kris Kringle? ?
[ Pounding ]
[ Crash! ]
? I really hope he isn't fast asleep ?
Santa!
? he may need someone to mind him ?
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Merry Christmas!
? if we don't get to find him ?
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
? an awful lot of kids are gonna weep ?
What'd you bring me?
Oh, let's see what Santa got
for you today.
? Well, Mrs. Kringle called
this mornin' ?
[ Laughing ]
? She said that Kris says
everything's okay ?
[ Laughing ]
[ Groans ]
O it's time for celebratin' ?
? she said that Kris says everything's okay ?
? Kris Kringle isn't waitin' ?
? it's gonna be
a happy Christmas day ?
But...
I was a good boy.
[ Groans ]
[ Thud ]
[ Music continues ]
Really, Rowena.
This is what
you dream about?
It's more of a recurring
nightmare, actually.
These don't come off.
I've been having this dream
for months,
but you --
you're new.
Who are you?
Yeah, sorry,
my manners are a bit rusty.
[ Music continues ]
? Supernatural 11x10 ?
The Devil in the Details
Original Air Date on January 20, 2016
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You.
[ Thunder crashing ]
[ Chuckles ]
The visions.
Everything.
It was all you.
Impressive, right?
And Rowena?
Did as she was told.
Groupies --
they're always so eager.
So you did all of that
just to...
To what?
Jump my bones?
Literally.
Well, you wasted
your time, then.
'Cause, see,
I know how this ends.
Oh, do you, now?
Yeah.
You'll taunt me,
and you'll torture me,
and I'll say no,
and eventually,
sooner than you think,
my brother's gonna walk through
that door and kick your ass.
[ Laughs ]
Dean?
You're betting on Dean?
I always have.
[ Chuckles, sighs ]
Oh, Sam,
you got me all wrong.
Ha. Yeah,
I doubt that.
Oh, no. I-I'm not here
to torture ya.
I mean, I could.
I could inflict pain
like you can't even imagine.
I could inflict such
delicious, perfect pain.
But that was so
five years ago.
No, I'm not gonna harm
a glorious little hair
on that
glorious little head.
Then, what do you want?
To make you an offer
you can't refuse.
You see, Sam, you need me.
And I'm gonna prove it
to you.
Recognize it?
What?
We're in a memory, Sam.
One of the few good ones
from your childhood.
By the way, I thought
I had daddy issues, but you?
Wow.
Anyway,
I think you recognize
the dashing young beanpole
over there.
That's me.
You're dead.
Please, Fergus,
enough with idle threats.
[ Gasps ]
You betrayed me --
in my kingdom.
Not yours, his!
Hell is his!
I'm his.
So hurt me, and what do you
think he'll do to you?
Lucifer will never
get out of that cell.
[ Gasping ]
Are you willing to stake
your life on that?
[ Gasping ]
On Sam Winchester?!
[ Gasps ]
[ Coughing ]
How long?
How long have you
been working for him?
Not long.
Lucifer came to me
in a dream.
Not that kind of dream.
So, you're just gonna let the
big, strong man boss you around?
Whatever happened to
the super-duper awesome coven?
#girlpower?
Lucifer's no man.
He's perfection.
Why do you think
I let your droogs find me?
Lucifer has a plan,
and --
And he's the devil.
You say that
like it's a bad thing.
Oh, I'm a bad thing.
He's a worse thing.
The last time Lucifer
went topside,
do you know
what he wanted?
Death for you, for me, and
every human, and every demon.
He's changed.
Oh, yes, of course.
All he needed was the love
of a horrible woman.
[ Scoffs ]
So, and you're doing
all this, why?
Out of the goodness
of your heart?
Don't be daft.
After Lucifer stops
the Darkness,
he'll ascend to his throne
in heaven,
and I'll be by his side,
a loyal follower.
A queen?
Like it or not,
you know I'm right.
Lucifer fought the Darkness
before, and he won.
So, unless you've got
the almighty
in your back pocket,
I suggest you sit down,
shut up,
and let him work.
[ Bird calling ]
[ Ringing ]
Dean: Hey, Sam can't talk 'cause
he's waxing, like, everything,
but leave a message and --
Sam: Dude, what are you doing
with my phone?
Dean. Come on.
[ Beep ]
Call me -- now.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Beeps ]
[ Ringing ]
Crowley: Thank you for phoning
Crowley, king of Hell.
For demon deals, press 1.
To report a sighting of that
ginger whore, Rowena, press 2.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Engine idling ]
[ Coughing, spitting ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunts, coughs ]
Castiel: Dean.
I came as soon as you called.
Are you all right?
Cass?
[ Coughing ]
[ Grunting ]
You're not all right.
Obviously.
Ugh, what's wrong with me?
Oh. What are you doing?
What are you --
Stick out your tongue.
What?
Ah, are we done?
No, I...
Let me take
your temperature.
No,
that's not gonna happen.
[ Coughs ]
How far are we
from the event?
You mean the Angel nuke?
Yeah.
Ground zero's about
a mile down that way.
Okay, that explains it.
You're suffering
from smiting sickness.
[ Sighs ]
That's a thing?
Yeah.
The Angels,
what they did,
it released a tremendous
amount of energy,
and there's fallout,
so this whole area is poisoned.
You can heal me, right?
No, I can't,
and the closer you get
to the blast site,
the worse your sickness
will become.
How worse?
The last time there was
a smiting of this magnitude,
lot's wife turned to salt.
Awesome.
All right, Dean,
you need to go back.
Uh, no.
[ Grunts ]
No, no, we got to --
we got to go see if it worked,
see if Amara
is alive or dead.
We don't.
The fallout doesn't affect
Angels. I'll go in alone.
[ Gagging ]
Okay, yeah, it's --
it's probably better that way.
I'll take a drive.
I'll go check on Sam.
Right.
Good.
Hey, Cass?
If it did work,
and she is dead...
Bring her body out.
And if she's not?
Run.
[ Groans ]
So, the Aztec priests,
they thought if they
didn't sacrifice people,
the whole world would end,
so they built
all of these temples.
The most amazing ones
are in Mexico City.
Young woman:
Have you seen them?
Last year, my dad took
me and my brother
on a trip to Mexico.
On vacation?
Kind of a working vacation.
[ Both chuckle ]
Have you ever heard
of a Chupacabra?
[ Chuckling ] No.
Okay, good.
[ Chuckles ]
Look at that, Sam.
A simple girl
from a one-stop-light town,
and you, the worldly,
handsome-ish Sam Winchester.
No, she didn't stand a chance.
You remember?
Yeah.
Why are you --
Here. Shh, shh, shh.
This is the best part.
Sam...
You know I didn't bring you
here to study, right?
You didn't?
No.
I-I mean, I just think that
you're smart and funny and cute.
So, I mean,
if you want to make out...
Boom! That's it.
That's what I'm talking about
right there, man.
Kissing?
No, Sam.
This is the Sam Winchester
that I remember.
Bold, decisive,
a solid "B"
on the tongue action.
What is this about?
You used to be a hero,
Sam.
Hell, you beat me.
Now?
[ Sighs ]
I don't know.
I look at you -- I don't
even recognize you anymore.
Sam!
Sammy!
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
You son of a bitch.
Miss you, too, puddin'.
Where are you?
Where's Sam?
Ah, there's a bit
of a hiccup.
Your brother's in Hell
with Lucifer.
Stull cemetery.
Bingo.
Where the title fight
went down.
Hey, ass-butt!
[ Glass shatters ]
[ Screaming ]
Ass-butt?
I-I-I-I still don't get that.
Look, I appreciate the stroll
down memory lane, but --
Sam, have I ever told you
how much I respect you?
What?
Oh, don't get me wrong.
I don't like you.
I've never liked you.
You're --
you're sort of prissy.
But in this moment,
when you stood toe-to-toe
with me and won,
I got to say,
you had balls, kid.
It's okay, Dean.
It's gonna be okay.
[ Breathing shakily ]
I got him.
You were willing to do
the hard thing
if it meant
saving the world.
[ Wind howling ]
No!
[ Both grunting ]
[ Both screaming ]
That's not you anymore.
You've gone soft, Sammy.
[ Rustling ]
Oh!
Who are you?
Ambriel.
I work in birth/death
statistics in Heaven.
I-I'm an --
I'm an angel.
Yeah, I know.
And you're Castiel?
I've heard stories
about you.
Why are you here?
Same reason you are.
Heaven wants to know if
the Darkness has been destroyed?
Pretty much.
And they sent you?
Are you gonna kill me?
Is that what they say,
that I kill angels?
Well, that's
the nicest thing they say.
Maybe we can work together,
so no one murders anyone?
Right.
Fine.
Okay, so I've searched
the east end of the forest.
Nothing weird.
Really?
You know it is
the middle of the afternoon.
So...?
So...
Why is it dark?
Excellent question.
[ Beep ]
Hey, Cass, I know
you're fighting the good fight
right now,
but I need you at 3rd and Pine,
Kenesaw, Nebraska.
'Cause, uh,
I'm going to Hell.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Siren wails in distance ]
Password.
Crowley sent me, all right?
Just open up.
Password.
Really?
? Camptown ladies
sing this song ?
? Doo dah, doo dah ?
? Camptown racetrack
five miles long ?
? Oh, the doo-dah day ?
All right, just let me in.
Nice work, Bieber.
Funny for a demon.
Not a demon.
Name's Billie.
The reaper Billie?
My brother says
you want to kill us.
No.
I'm just gonna make sure that
when you die, you stay dead.
Subtle difference.
So what,
you work for Crowley?
With, not for.
It's strange days,
Winchester.
Times like this...
It doesn't hurt to have
the King owe you a favor.
For the limey.
What is it?
You'll see.
Whatever.
All right, just get me
to where I need to go.
That's the plan.
[ Whooshing ]
Billie: Watch your step.
It's a long way down.
[ Doors clank ]
Thought about what
you're gonna say to him?
Amelia: I've thought about it,
and I've thought about it.
I still don't know.
Here's where it all changed, Sammy.
It's just all
so surreal.
This is the worst thing
you've ever done.
Does he know they told you
he was killed in action?
Really?
After the Leviathans,
when your brother was trapped
in Purgatory,
you were here with a girl
and a dog.
You didn't even bother
trying to find him.
You know what? Not that I
have to defend myself to you,
but Dean and I promised we
wouldn't look for each other.
Right, and if he never
came back, you'd be fine.
But he did,
so you're not.
Whatever happened
to the Sam Winchester
who was bold, decisive,
and ready to sacrifice
for the greater good?
Right here.
And so why did you let Dean
talk you out of closing
the Gates of Hell?
'Cause the old Sam never
would've done that, not ever.
I didn't --
No, wait, here's my personal favorite
is you doing every stupid thing
you could to cure the Mark,
even after you knew
it would go bad.
My brother was dying.
Yes, and you'd do anything
to save him,
and he'd do anything
to save you,
and that is the problem.
Because of this,
you're so overcome by guilt
that you can't stand
to lose Dean again,
and he could never
lose you.
And so instead of choosing
the world,
you choose each other,
no matter how many
innocent people die.
You're gonna lecture me
about hurting people? You?
You know I'm right, Sam.
You know it.
And I know that if you're
gonna beat the Darkness,
you have to be ready
to die.
You have to be ready to watch
the people you love die.
A long time ago, you could've
fought the good fight, kid,
but not anymore.
You can't win this one, Sam.
You're just not strong enough.
And you are?
Hey, snapping necks and cashing
checks -- that's what I do.
Rowena:
Isn't this nice?
Spending quality time.
Your tea is ready.
[ Liquid pouring ]
Finally.
That does sound lovely.
How do you take it?
Both:
Honey and a splash of milk.
Like mother, like son.
Excuse me.
I need to go vomit.
Hurry back, dear.
I never wanted this, you know,
to be hated by my own kind.
I never --
OH, no,
I don't hate you, Castiel.
Thank you.
I mean,
we have a lot in common.
Our names rhyme,
and that's a big one.
I look good
in a trench coat, too.
And we're both
expendable.
Excuse me?
Uh, well, that's why
we're here, right?
I'm a number cruncher,
and -- and you --
like I said,
I've heard the stories.
You help,
but Sam and Dean Winchester
are the real heroes.
So, if the Darkness is
still alive, and she's pissed,
and she kills us,
no big loss.
So, sure, maybe
we're not super important,
but we do the job.
You know?
I think there's nobility
in that.
Coming?
I'll catch up.
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
Welcome to hell.
Where's Sam?
Oh, don't worry about Sam.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Have you met me?
I mean,
Lucifer needs the moose.
He's not gonna kill him --
probably.
You versus the devil?
Trust me, there's easier ways
of committing suicide.
We need to focus
on Rowena.
Okay, great,
let's kill her.
Ah, easier said than done,
I'm afraid,
and we need mother to slam
the devil back in his hole.
Well, is she gonna
play ball?
She doesn't have a choice.
[ Lock clicks ]
It's called
a Witchcatcher.
Most of them were destroyed
after the inquisition,
but, uh,
Billie came through.
Yeah, she's a peach.
What does it do?
Oh, you're gonna love this.
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Dramatic music plays ]
Ambriel.
[ Wind howling ]
Castiel.
Amara.
What did you do to her?
I consumed her.
Her Grace, her spark,
her memories -- everything.
She...
Oh, she really hit the spot.
Seriously?
I mean, Heaven brought
the thunder,
and it barely even scratched
my paint job,
but you
and a shiny knife?
Sure,
that's gonna work.
You think
I'm afraid to die?
I know you are.
You reek of fear
and self-loathing.
[ Grunts ]
Ooh. Scary.
[ Grunting ]
She's right, you know.
You are expendable...
and weak.
And why God took
a special interest in you,
I'll never understand.
My brother always did have
horrible taste in men.
Just do it.
Blue eyes...
You aren't even
worth the effort.
And, no offense,
but you look a bit used up.
Plus...
I have a job for you.
[ Screams ]
[ Inhales sharply ]
[ Panting ]
[ Whoosh ]
[ Screams ]
[ Panting ]
Hey.
[ Cup clatters ]
How's Dean?
Pardon?
Little tip, love.
The next time you go about
making secret plans,
check your pockets.
I need to go vomit.
Hurry back, dear.
You heard.
Everything.
Not that it matters.
What does that mean,
big boy?
A little tip, mother.
Never accept a cup of tea
from someone who loathes you.
[ Laughs ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Gasping, retching ]
Get this bloody thing
off of me!
Oh, I would, but this bloody
thing makes you my slave.
[ Scoffs ]
Hop on one foot.
Please, Fergus.
I don't know what kind
of Oedipal fifty shades
you think you're playing at,
but if you think for a second...
Bollocks.
All right,
let's do this.
Lucifer: Now, Sam...
I know this is a lot
to take in,
so if you need to
[Clears throat]
Take some time and noodle on it,
that's cool.
But, uh,
the world is ending,
clock ticking and such
[Chuckles] if you follow me.
What do you want me
to say?
A little word, uh, starts
with "Y," ends in "e-s".
Okay,
you don't like me.
[ Sighs ]
I get it. I get it.
Sometimes I don't like me,
either.
But Gabriel and Raphael
are dead.
God went out for a pack
of smokes and never came back.
And Michael?
Well, let's just say
prison life hasn't really
agreed with Michael.
These days, he's usually
sitting in a corner,
singing show tunes
and...touching himself.
So you're it?
[ Laughs ]
I'm it!
And, hey...
I-I'm not the good guy.
We -- we both know
I'm not,
but, uh, the Darkness?
She's the end
of everything.
But I can beat her.
We can beat her.
You and me.
Together.
So, come on, Sam.
Make the right choice.
The big sacrifice
one more time, man.
Sam.
It's time to save
the world, man.
No.
So this spell is supposed
to slam Lucifer back in the box.
How long's
this gonna take?
About five minutes.
Unless Sam says yes.
And if he does?
If Lucifer finds a vessel,
he'll be anchored to Earth.
The incantation won't work.
And then we're screwed.
[ Footsteps ]
I'm sorry, my Lord.
I tried to --
Cass?
Oh, good,
the Angel's here.
What's happened?
Amara, she's --
she's alive.
She --
she sent this message.
Crowley:
"I am coming"?
Is that a threat?
[ Breathes heavily ]
Or a promise?
What do you mean, no?
You heard me.
Okay, now, Sam,
I got to tell you,
this is selfish, man.
Everything that --
You are done.
It's over.
And you know what?
You talk a good game.
You do.
Hell, you almost had me sold
a few times,
but then I thought,
what if you're right?
What if you're telling
the truth?
What --
what if you can beat her?
I can.
Even though, last time,
it took you
plus three other archangels.
Oh, yeah,
and capital "G," God.
Oh, okay, what,
you mean the dead weight?
But let's say you gank her.
Then what?
I move to L.A.,
solve crimes.
Wrong.
Then you go about starting
the Apocalypse again
because you're an old dog,
and that's your old trick.
Hey, first off,
you don't know that.
Second, even if I did,
that's better
than what she has planned.
Is it? Really?
Because
this is what I think.
I think that whoever wins,
you or the Darkness,
everyone else loses.
So, no.
My answer is no.
[ Laughs ] This isn't 'cause of Dean
or -- or the past.
This is about me
having faith in my friends,
having faith in my family.
We will find a way.
[ Thunder crashing ]
I'm ready to die.
And I'm ready to watch
people I love die.
But I'm not ready
to be your bitch.
Okay.
Plan "B."
[ Sam grunting ]
Sam?!
Don't!
Hey, ass-butt!
Dean.
Uh, the other one.
Welcome to the party.
[ Panting ]
Scared?
Not even a little.
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Moments like this,
it's all about ambience.
[ Snaps fingers ]
? Heaven ?
? must be missin' an angel ?
? missin' one angel, child ?
? 'cause you're here with me
right now ?
I can beat the Darkness.
Me, only me.
[ Grunts ]
Hey.
? Your love is heavenly, baby ?
who are these two?
They're a couple of apes.
? heavenly to me, baby ?
You know I'm right, Castiel.
You know it.
You want to play that way?
? Your kiss ?
We can't win.
We don't have to win.
? Filled with tenderness ?
We' can settle this in a few minutes.
? I want all -- ?
[ Suspenseful music plays ]
[ Grunting ]
You hit like a human.
All right, Sam.
I'm gonna make this
real easy for you.
You say the magic word...
...or your brother dies,
And we both know
you won't let that happen.
[ Grunts ]
[ Spits ]
Anan avar kavak!
So? Last words?
[ Panting ]
You're welcome.
Anyone?
Bite me.
I can make her do that.
So, what now?
About the Darkness?
No clue.
We'll figure it out.
Or die screaming.
This has been a horrible
train wreck, so we're done.
Team-up over.
What about her?
She stays.
The rest of you lot,
get the hell out of Hell.
[ Thunder crashing ]
[ Horn honking in distance ]
You all right?
I think so.
I will be.
Want me
to give you a lift?
No, you two go on ahead.
I'll catch up.
Okay.
[ Grunts ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Horn honks in distance ]
[ Car door opens ]
[ Grunts ]
Is he all right?
Tough day.
Yeah,
tell me about it.
You good?
[ Sighs ]
I don't know.
I mean, what if Lucifer
was telling the truth?
You know, what if he's the --
No, dude.
Darkness is bad.
Her and the Devil?
That's a nightmare.
Mother?
Why do you hate me?
I hate you because
when I look into your eyes,
I see the woman I used to be,
before magic,
before the coven,
when I was nothing but Rowena,
the Tanner's daughter.
A pale, scared, little girl
who smelled of filth and death.
I hate you...
Because
when you were born,
your father said
he loved me.
Then he went back to his
grand wife and his grand house
whilst I lay pathetic
and half-dead on a straw mat,
my thighs slick
with blood.
I hate you...
Because if I didn't...
I'd love you.
But love --
love is weakness.
And I'll never be weak again.
[ Door clanks opens ]
Castiel.
Guess again.
No.
Last words?
Can you really beat her?
I can.
Then, yes.
Lucifer.
I'm back, baby!
[ Sighs ]
It can't be.
You finished the spell.
But if he was already
in another vessel...
Loophole.
Bloody hell.
Ah, ah!
Ooh.
Rowena.
My liege.
You know...
What you've done for me,
I'll never forget it.
'Twas my honor.
Yes.
It was.
You deserve a reward.
Or some little token...
of my affection.
I thank you.
Oh.
Just one teensy,
tiny little question.
Can anyone else
open the cage?
Just me.
Good.
[ Neck snaps ]
[ Sighs ]
Okay.
Let's chat.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man