Those things from purgatory.
Uh...Leviathan.
They're like
shapeshifters only a lot
only a lot more
into eating folk.
And they bleed black goo.
Mr. Singer. I believe
you know Sheriff Mills.
It's Dick frigging Roman.
Who the hell
is Dick frigging Roman?
I'm gonna eat you, Bob.
Yes.
Bobby! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Go! Go!
Hey, Bobby, your hat.
Oh, God. Bobby?!
Hold on!
What, did you come here
to finish the job?
We're coming for you,
and not just to hurt you --
to kill you.
Bobby, um, hey.
Thanks...for everything.
Idjits.
Bobby? Hey!
All right, let's do this.
Move fast.
Wait, wait, wait.
What's the plan exactly?
Don't die.
He's heading downtown.
All right, you take the street.
I'll take the alley.
I'll meet you
in the middle.
Son of a...
Dean?
Dean?!
? Supernatural 7x12 ?
Time After Time After Time
Original Air Date on January 13, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Don't give me
that dirty-diaper look.
I ain't calling you.
Hello?
Sam, it's Jody Mills.
I wake you?
The sheriff?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, I mean, uh --
Listen, I got something that
smells like you boys.
A body turned up
in Canton, Ohio.
Local P.D.'s trying to bury
the story and the body.
Okay, um, so, uh,
what's up with the body?
Well, when it went missing,
it was a perfectly normal grad
student named Charles Durbin.
When it turned up,
the thing was mummified
minus the wrapping.
This is actually
the second body found like this
in the last couple weeks.
Sound like a song
you boys tap to?
Yeah, yeah,
that's, that's um...
that's
our kind of number.
Hey, question --
how does a sheriff
in Sioux Falls
get wind of a case in Ohio?
I'm just that nosy.
Look, after everything I've been
through with you boys and...
with Bobby, you know,
something like this pops up
on the wire, it catches my ear.
What can I say?
Well, we'll look into it.
Thanks, Sheriff.
- Call me after, okay?
- Yeah.
That was Sheriff Mills.
She caught us one.
Oh, I feel bad.
We didn't get her anything.
I can't believe
I'm about to say this
but I hope you're watching
cartoon smut,
'cause reading Dick Roman crap
over and over again
is just self-punishment.
It's called anime,
and it's an art form.
Well, this looks nice.
Check around back?
And one un-rancid bedroom.
Define semi-functioning,
and do not use the words
"hole in the floor."
How does paper
beat a rock?
It's stupid.
Kids playing hide-and-seek
found the body.
Wow. Very King Tut.
Yeah, so, this is where
the eyewitness
to the assault lives,
but the cops are calling him
an unreliable witness.
Because?
Let's find out.
Special Agent Smith.
This is, uh,
No relation.
Whoa.
Do you mind if we,
uh...
My mom's sleeping in there.
S-so, how can I...?
Oh, we, uh -- we had a few
questions about the incident
you witnessed in the alley.
You just gonna laugh at my story
like the rest of the suits?
We're not gonna
laugh at you.
All right, well,
I'm on the steps...
medicating...
when I hear fighting.
So I look.
There's my neighbor Durbin,
and some dude
dressed like my grandpa's
got him by the neck,
right?
What do you he looks like
your grandpa?
Uh...
Snappy shoes, suit,
one of those, um,
Justin Timberlake hats.
Y-you mean a --
a fedora?
Aha!
Did you see anything else?
This red, like, energy
passed through Durbin
to hat guy.
Even my watch stopped.
Durbs...
He aged before my eyes.
He looked like a raisin.
Well, we believe you.
Oh.
Thanks for your help.
Thank you,
officer -- officers.
Yep. Nothing that turns a dude
into a crypt keeper.
You?
Uh, well, greater Canton
turns out kind of a hot spot
for weird dead bodies.
Hmm. You don't say.
Yeah. News archives.
They're not exactly reporting,
uh, mummifies.
But still -- 1928,
three deaths cited as
spontaneous combustion.
Bodies "shriveled despite
no signs of fire."
Little stretch, but okay.
'74, three bodies found
with leathery decay.
Uh, '57, three more --
severe dehydration.
This time one made
the front page.
Girl named Terry Cervantes
found a corpse near her church.
Any pattern here
other than the location?
Random vics,
random years.
But they seem to drop
in threes.
That's two down,
one to go.
All right,
let me drive for a sec.
What, are you gonna look up
more anime,
or are you
strictly into Dick now?
Hmm.
- Are those local feeds?
- Yeah.
How did you do that
so fast?
A little tutorial
from Frank.
Don't worry. We'll pretend
this never happened.
Now, mummy numero dos
was found at the Gas n' Sip
near Main Street, correct?
Yeah.
All right, well, here's all
the cameras around that store.
You need to teach me
that trick.
Hey, check it out --
Timberlake.
Wait a sec.
You can't let me bask in the
glory for one second, can you?
Shut up.
Look.
He hasn't aged a day,
has he?
All right, well, if he's been
popping up for decades now,
then somebody's bound to know
who he is, right?
Is there any chance that, uh,
Terry's still local?
You know it's so pretty
in the spring.
Everything's blooming.
That's why I walked home
that way --
to see the flowers.
Instead, I found that body.
I still have no idea what could
have done that to a person.
Do you recognize
that man?
Yeah.
I mean, he lived
on my parents' street.
Mr. Snider.
Where'd you say
your parents live?
So, what exactly
is this thing?
Some sort of vampire
who got too sucky?
Nope.
Coroner's reports said
there was blood in both bodies.
300-year-old blood,
but blood.
Dude, dude.
Uh, fedora dude.
All right,
let's do this.
Let's move fast.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's the plan here, exactly?
Don't die.
All right, you take the street.
I'll take the alley.
I'll meet you
in the middle.
Son of a...
Hey!
Hey, you!
Drop the gun!
Put it down!
All right.
- Okay, can I just --
- Don't.
Listen to me.
Hey, if you tell me you're from
the Bureau one more time,
I'm gonna
air you out myself.
Got it?
"No signal."
Are you some
kind of Jerry spy?
Jerry who?
And a terrible one at that.
This badge was issued
68 years from now.
Ace work,
kraut-muncher.
'44?
I'm stuck in 1944?!
We're all stuck in 1944,
ya bunny.
Take a powder.
Yes, sir.
Look I don't even like
frigging Sauerkraut, okay,
so you can
just skip the --
What happened in the alley?
And paint me a real picture.
All right, well,
I'm "12 monkey'ed" no matter
what I say, so here goes.
I was chasing this dude. Uh,
I'd just seen him mummify a guy.
Yeah.
So, I jumped him.
He lights up red.
Poof, we're in 1944.
Tell me more
about the red light.
Are you
seriously asking --
You want out of this jail,
you're gonna tell me
everything you can
about that man
and the so-called light.
Okay.
I saw it,
and then we were here.
Would you say that, uh...
It was all around you
or that more that it came
from inside this fella?
You believe me.
Are you...?
You're a hunter.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Demons,
ghosts, shifters.
Hey,
I've killed 'em all.
And you're the same.
Just 68 years
before me, huh?
And your name is...?
Dean...Winchester.
Ness.
Eliot Ness.
Dean?
No. Why?
Where's Dean?
The thing that's been
mummifying people
took him in a frigging ball
of light and disappeared.
You guys get that a lot?
Yeah,
more than most people.
Well, I got you
into this, so --
No, no, no, you didn't.
A-all you did was just --
Shut up, Sam.
How I can help?
Well, um...
How do you feel about driving
and lifting boxes?
I-I got to tell you,
I mean, "Untouchables" is, like,
one of my most
favorite movies ever.
What?
I must have seen that thing,
like, 50 times.
"Seen it?"
What, like, I'm in the --
Oh, yeah, yeah! You don't even know!
Oh, you are -- pbht!
Look, hey, wait, wait, wait.
Let's just...Slow it down.
Okay?
Now, time travel.
Is that something you find
up a lot of sleeves
in the future or...?
No, no, no. It's, uh,
not normally on the menu.
Trust me.
I'm as surprised as you are
that I'm here.
So we're hunting
the same thing,
just in different
centuries?
Two bodies.
A few days apart
just a little over a month ago.
One witness said that she saw
an assailant light up red
after sucking the life
out of a man.
Awesome.
How does that
fill you with awe?
Look, Dean, this thing,
it kills --
- In threes.
But you already know that.
He's two down.
You're coming with me.
We've got to get this thing
before it grabs the last one.
Okay, so, so, wait, uh...
Does...Does this mean
that I'm an Untouchable now?
It means we got to get you
into some new clothes.
You look like
some kind of bindle stiff.
Stiff your
br-- bin-- what?
Hey.
What's the rumpus,
Eliot?
Ezra Moore.
Dean Winchester.
Hey.
Who's he?
Some farmer clown?
He's, uh,
from the future.
Yeah.
Gas costs four bucks.
You can get cheese
out of a spray can.
And...the President,
he's a black guy.
I could go on.
Paint me impressed.
I assume you need
some clothes.
Come on.
Hey, let me, uh --
let me help you with those.
No, I got these.
You go get the other 20
in my truck.
Seriously?
Yeah.
I think Bobby may have had
a slight hoarding issue.
I could barely get the door open
on that storage locker.
And, um, I'm pretty sure
something's alive
in at least three
of those boxes.
Awesome.
"Awesome"?
You some religious kook?
No, he just
likes saying that.
So, spill already.
What bucket of syrup
did you two idjits step into?
Something funny,
sweetheart?
No, you, uh...
You just kind of
remind me of someone.
Okay, Ezra...
We need your help.
It seems we're hunting
a time traveler.
Delightful.
Got it.
Looks like fedora man,
1968.
Is that a -- is that
a ring on his finger?
Um...
Yeah.
I know that symbol.
It's the infinite hourglass.
That's the symbol
I saw on his ring.
- Yeah, that's the mark of Chronos.
- Who?
The God of time.
That's crazy.
The thing is,
with the Old Gods,
once upon a time they were
just short of invincible.
But a lot of their mojo
from worshippers,
from people feeding them.
These days, not so much.
Right, they're not
what they used to be.
But they make up
for lack of power
with being twice as pissed
and a lot more hands-on.
Okay.
So why's this God
killing people?
Could be he's killing folks
for his time juice.
All right, well,
how the hell
am I gonna
ride him back to 2012?
Well, you could
let him grab you,
if you don't mind him
using you for gasoline.
So, how do we
get Dean back?
How do we even find
this Chronos?
Best stab?
We find a way
to summon a God.
Look, let's just stick with
what we know.
Ezra, see if you can
find something in all this junk
that will kill a God.
No trouble at all.
Come in a few hours,
see what I can scrounge up.
You said you fellas
found his house?
Well, let's go see
if it's been built yet.
And then let's kill
that bastard, because that --
Is the Chicago way.
"The Chicago way?"
Who talks like that?
Sean Connery.
Come on.
Never watch that movie again.
- It looks empty.
- You got a lock pick?
Sure.
Take a look around.
Where's he getting all
the lettuce to support this?
He's using
the "biff strategy."
Using what?
He's -- Chronos is betting
on races
he already knows
the outcome of.
Look at this.
He's spent a lot
of time in '44.
Yeah.
What's L.Y.?
It's not a what. It's a who.
Lester young.
He lays bets for a lot of
the flunkies in town.
Let's say we go
pay him a visit.
Hey! W-whoa!
Hey! Hey!
Easy with the jacket!
Yeah, I ain't talking.
I'm no stoolie.
I learned it
from watching you.
Look, you seem like
a swell guy, Lester.
And I want to help you out.
I do, but my partner here?
He just back from the war.
And he's spent the last
two years
kicking in Nazi skulls.
If he doesn't kick in
a skull every couple days,
he gets real touchy.
Lester.
That a German name?
Hey, okay, okay.
There's no need
to snap your cap.
W-who you looking for?
Fella by the name
of Snider.
What, that guy?
I mean,
bum never missed a bet,
but he gave me
the heebie-jeebies,
so I cut him off.
Where would you meet him
for the payoff?
T-the Early Bird!
It's a dive on Haggerty.
Practically lives in the joint.
That's it! Damn it.
Okay, yours sounds better.
You first.
It says here that people
could summon Chronos
"to compel him to tell them
their futures."
And I've got the spell
to do it right here.
So why the "damn it"?
'Cause calling Chronos
isn't the problem.
It's making sure we summon him
when Dean is right there...
Literally with his hands
on the guy,
so he can surf him back.
That's not automatic?
No, it's more like we need to
get the time on their end right
to the exact second.
Or we get an angry God
but no big brother?
And he's trapped there
forever.
"Fine, you ass.
You win for once. Enjoy. R."
Who's "R"?
Rufus, a family friend.
Wonder what they
were betting over?
Well, whatever it was,
Rufus sure was a sore loser.
Yeah.
It's weird, huh?
It's like their life's
a big puzzle.
You just keep finding
pieces of it
scattered
all over the place.
We should drink this.
He'd want us to.
Am I wrong?
It'd be rude not to.
That's him.
Kind of puny for a God.
Thought you were, uh --
thought you were Mr. Boy Scout.
Why do you think I went after
Capone in the first place?
The guy had the best hooch
in Chicago.
So, now, w-who died in your life
and made you a hunter?
Who died?
Nobody died,
you morbid son of a bitch.
I started doing this
'cause vampires were turning
folks in Cleveland.
And you got the bug.
That's when
I got the bug.
Sometimes you just want to
punch through the red tape
with a silver bullet.
Yeah, hunting sets me free.
Isn't that why you hunt?
I used to do it 'cause
that's what my family did.
Hmm.
But they just seem
to keep dying.
To tell you the truth,
I don't know why I'm doing
much of anything anymore.
Boo-hoo.
Cry me a river, ya Nancy.
Tell me, are all hunters
as soft as you in the future?
Everybody loses everybody.
And then one day, boom.
Your number's up, but at least
you're making a difference.
So enjoy it while it lasts,
kid,
'cause hunting's
the only clarity
you're gonna find
in this life.
And that makes you
luckier than most.
Hello, nurse.
Hey.
Sweet merciful awesome.
Well, everything's
coming up us, kid.
Talk to me.
I am.
The owner of the house,
Miss Lila Taylor, age 20,
lives alone.
Take the car, head back to Ezra,
see what she's got.
I'm gonna stay here
and keep my peepers
on the Sheik and the Sheba.
That's it?
That is a 1,000-year-old
olive carved by vestal virgins
and dipped in the blood of --
you don't want to know.
Pulling this together
wasn't easy.
You and Ness both owe me,
smoothie.
You can have whatever you want
soon as we gank this thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Take your twig, wise guy.
Well, now,
how's it work?
Well...
You stick this end
in his heart.
Miss,
he has you for supper.
Make sense?
Wait, if I --
if I kill Chronos...
I'm stuck here.
You just now realized?
Oh, come on.
1944 ain't so bad.
Yeah, I could head over
to Europe,
punch Hitler in the neck.
Oh, there's lots of ways
to pass the time, sugar.
That's for luck.
'Cause I'm lucky.
Thanks.
"Back to the Future III."
I need to borrow
some paper.
Mr. Ness I presume?
You know, I stopped by
the police station
to take care of that hunter
who rode me here.
I heard you took him
out of jail.
I thought
I might see you again.
Ethan?
There you are.
Can't take the trash out
without the trash silly.
Sorry, honey.
I don't know
where I left my head.
Be right there.
Sweetie, I want you
to pack a bag.
Excuse me?
Well, you're always asking me
where I go.
Come with me tonight.
Is...is everything okay?
Yeah,
everything's perfect.
You're perfect.
I just need you
to pack a bag
and I'll explain why
on the way, okay?
- But the diner --
- Forget about them!
We'll call them tomorrow,
okay?
Just go. Pack.
Jackpot.
Can I help you, son?
Yes, sir. I am, uh,
Special Agent Costner
with the, uh, Department
of Homeland Termite Invasion.
- Termites?
- Yes, sir.
There's been an outbreak
all over this area,
and I just want to do
an inspection,
make sure that the, uh,
perimeter's secure.
Yes. Yes, of course.
Um, you'd better come in.
Okay.
Is everything okay
up here?
What?!
Oh, yeah -- no!
No, no.
Not to worry, because
I'm going to install something
that will protect this house
forever.
Yeah.
You are toast.
I'll keep pushing.
You go get some shut-eye.
Uh, that's okay.
I can, uh...
Do I have to use
my mom voice?
All right.
You asked for it.
Young man --
"Sammy, turns out
Snider is Chronos."
Wait, this is from Dean?
How --
Just read.
"I rode him to 1944.
"Am working with Eliot Ness --
yes, that one.
"Tracked down Chronos.
"He's banging some chick
named Lila Taylor,
"and we got a weapon.
We're going after him.
Take care of yourself, Sam."
Look at the top.
November 5, '44.
So, now we know the exact date
Dean had hands on Chronos.
All we need
is the exact time.
Which we get how?
Hoping, we ask someone
who was there.
Miss Lila Taylor?
Oh, can you get
"The Sullivan Show"?
I want to watch
that Frankie Valli.
Um, actually,
we're with the police.
Oh. Is Michael
in trouble again?
I told him not to read
those comic books.
Uh, no, no, no, no.
He's, uh -- he's fine.
We'd wanted to ask you
some questions about this man.
Ethan.
That's Ethan.
Do you remember the last time
you saw Ethan?
Of course.
November 1944 --
the night the clocks stopped.
Th-the clocks stopped?
11:34.
Every clock in the house.
Ma'am, can you tell us anything
else you remember?
Ethan...
Said awful things.
And then...
And then he strangled
that poor man.
What poor man?
Two policemen came
to arrest Ethan.
Ma'am,
was this one of them?
Ethan choked the life
out of that man.
Ness!
Ethan!
Let's talk.
Here, break this.
Please don't hurt her.
Ethan,
what's happening?
Yeah, Ethan.
What the hell?
Lila, I'm sorry,
but, you just --
everything I said to you
is true--
Oh, he might have left out
a few details.
He tell you he's a monster
who jumps through time?
I'm a God!
Look, I'm not a monster.
Listen.
I'm the opposite.
Well, don't forget
to tell her about
all the people you murdered
along the way, boy scout.
What?
It's not like that.
I do it for you, Lila.
I don't understand.
Well, he's not as strong
as he used to be.
Isn't that right, Ethan?
Now you got to
suck people dry.
Wild guess -- it takes
three kills to juice you up.
Sacrifices.
Three sacrifices,
and I can control
when and where I land.
But once I get there,
it's never for long
before I'm tossed
through time again.
That's my life, Lila.
And all I want
is to get back here.
Because you just love
the clean Canton air?
Because I love her!
Because I lived the worst
existence you can imagine,
and then I found you.
After you killed Tyler Crosby
and Cathy Porter?
Lila here was gonna be
victim number three.
Am I right?
Don't act like you never
killed a soul
before you met her, pal.
Something tells me you used to
kill three saps
just for
a change of scenery.
Yes, I did.
Back down.
I-I used to wander,
but now I have you.
I knew Cathy.
She used to come into the diner
every day.
Lila, please.
You are a monster.
No, Lila, please!
O khrone parakaloumen
se thespizein
hemin khronon
ton mellonta.
No!
Hey, Untouchable!
Dean!
Hey!
No!
You!
Destroyed everything!
Hey, Chronos?!
Was that
the best you got?
You want to know
your future?
I know your future.
It's covered
in thick black ooze.
It's everywhere.
They're everywhere.
Enjoy oblivion.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==