You can't stop any of us.
We can't be killed,
you stupid little chewtoys.
These things are smarter
than you.
You don't have a clue
how to kill 'em
or slow 'em down, and
your plan is what,
go right at 'em?
We've been
a little busy.
Hunting Leviathan.
You met dick yet?
I'd sooner swim through
hot garbage than shake hands
with a bottom-feeding
mutation like you.
I'd never work with you,
Crowley.
I hate the bastard.
Squash 'em all.
You need to see a fella
named Frank Devereaux.
Bobby Singer sent us.
Or not. Who?
We just need you to get us
further off the grid,
but keep us
on the board.
Wipe all your old aliases.
Change your phones
on a very frequent
non-schedule schedule,
you understand?
You can't just
look me in the face
and tell me you're fine.
- You want me to be honest?
- Yeah.
I don't like lying to you.
You know,
it doesn't feel right.
So, yeah, you got me there.
I been climbing walls.
I know how that is.
Good night, sweetie.
This is Nature Sounds'
"Sounds of Nature,"
Volume 4, "Soothing Seas."
What the hell?
Leanne!
Stay away.
? Supernatural 7x09 ?
How to Win Friends and Influence Monsters
Original Air Date on November 18, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Did you strip enough wire?
Yes, I stripped
enough wire.
All right.
See? Told you.
Well, isn't this cozy?
Yeah.
Well, Motel 6 just ain't
leaving the light on anymore.
Well, I'm taking page
out of Frank Devereaux's Bible
on this.
Everybody's out
to get you --
paranoia is just
plain common sense.
Weeks, guys. Weeks.
We've been living
with cold showers,
cold Hot Pockets,
cold freaking everything.
I mean, this is the bottom
that we're living in.
You guys get that, right?
How many big mouths
are out there,
running card traces,
like Chet,
or hunting us down
God knows what ways?
No, now's not the time
to be laying our bed rolls out
on the grid.
Not if we can help it.
That's just great.
This is stupid.
Our quality of life
is crap.
We got Purgatory's
least wanted everywhere,
and we're on our third
"The World's Screwed" issue
in, what, three years?
We've steered the bus away
from the cliff twice already.
Someone's got to do it.
What if the bus
wants to go over the cliff?
You think the world
wants to end?
I think that
if we didn't take its belt
and all its pens away
each year
that, yeah,
the whole enchilada
would have offed
itself already.
Stop trying to wrestle
with the big picture, son.
You're gonna hurt your head.
So, what's the guff?
Well, uh, there have been
a rash of sightings
all over the southern
pine barrens --
a strange, fast-moving,
human-like creature.
Locals even have
a name for it.
The Jersey Devil?
I thought that was just
local tall-tale crap.
The area's history
of sightings
goes back
more than two centuries.
Some accounts gave it bat wings,
others horns,
a...a tail.
And, uh, oh, yeah,
a horse's head.
The sketch looks more like
a Chewbacca head.
Sounds kind of mixed-up.
Yeah, kind of like it should be
fighting a Japanese robot.
Well, mixed-up or not,
it sounds like it might
just have a body count.
"Camping high season
harshed by human burrito"?
Yeah.
Something hung a camper
up in a tree,
then ate him alive right
through his sleeping bag.
His wife
hasn't been seen, either.
Plus, there have been
four other missing persons
reported in
the last three weeks.
State troopers -- get this --
are saying it's a rogue bear.
Yeah, of course,
when was the last time
you saw a bear string up
its own pi?ata?
Something's out there
in the woods.
Hey, we're going honest to
goodness wilderness hunting.
I haven't used my .30-30
in a while.
Okay, Davey Crockett,
well, safari's gonna have
to wait till tomorrow
and after
our suit-and-tie dance.
We'll make sure this is not just
some backwoods crackhead
who likes to roll glampers.
What the hell's
a glamper?
Sam?
High-end camper.
TV, A.C., Wi-Fi.
Back to nature,
zero inconvenience.
That's idiotic.
Yeah.
Some people just don't
know how to live.
So, Ranger Evans --
oh, uh,
you can call me Rick.
Ranger Rick.
Uh, you were the one who found
Mitchell Rayburn, correct?
The human burrito.
State police have it down
as a bear attack.
Yeah, I read
what the state police says.
That was no rogue brown.
Apparently, some others
reported seeing something
a little,
you know, weirder.
You know,
I've been a ranger for 12 years.
Tell you the truth,
we have no idea
what's out there.
Big.
Lot of trees and whatnot.
Tell you this, though.
You got to respect
mother nature.
You respect her,
or she's gonna string you up,
and she'll eat your ass
right through the Gore-Tex.
So you're thinking
it's mother nature?
See, me and Phil,
we've been finding, uh,
something's leftovers
for weeks --
deer remains, badger,
missing pets.
Who's Phil?
Assistant Chief Ranger.
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen Phil
in a couple of days.
He's supposed to call
from whatever station
he's checking off.
But you think maybe
your assistant chief ranger
might be missing?
I should probably
report that.
Oh. Excuse us.
Well, you, uh...
Enjoy your lunch...
Ranger Rick.
So?
Well, I took a look
at the cadaver --
what's left of it.
Not a happy camper.
Don't have any stats
on a Jersey Devil,
but the bite radius
on the vic's wounds --
it's too small
for a Leviathan.
And he's still got a ventricle
and some change,
so I doubt
we're talking werewolf.
And a wendigo
don't leave no scraps.
Hmm. Lunch?
Starving.
Hey! Uh, Brandon.
We grab a booth?
Hey, uh, douchewad,
a hostess will seat you.
Do I look like
a freaking hostess?
Do you want
to look like a hostess?
That didn't really make sense,
what you...said.
What was that?
I sure hope we don't get
Brandon's section.
Sidewinder soup and salad combo
goes to big bird.
TDK slammer to Ken Doll.
And a little heart-smart
for creepy uncle.
What is your problem?
You are my problem!
Oh, Brandon's got his flare
all up in a bunch.
Yeah.
There goes his 18%.
Anyway,
the chief ranger --
I don't think he believes
in the Jersey Devil.
Oh, by the way, did he seem
a little, uh, stoned to you?
Ranger Rick? Yeah.
Definitely growing his own
on the back 40
and smoking
all the profits.
He did seem to think
that there was something --
Oh,
that is good sandwich.
What the hell
did you get?
New pepperjack
Turducken Slammer --
limited time only.
Bunch of birds shoved up
inside each other.
Shouldn't play God
like that.
Hey, don't look at me sideways
from that --
that Chinese chicken geezer
salad there, okay?
This is awesome.
Like the perfect storm of
your top-three edible birds.
All right, anyways, um...
The ranger did seem to think
there was something
out in Wharton Forest.
Well, then I'd say
it's safari time.
Look at her!
You're telling me she's not fat?
No, no. Up yours, Mike.
Shove it right up yours!
Well, anyway, back to bigger
and better things.
Couple of bucks.
Head-butting
over turf probably.
Pretty sure
the other fella won.
I guess I forgot.
Before you were a hunter,
you were actually a...hunter.
Yeah, well, we shot our dinner
when I was a kid.
You used to take us hunting.
Remember?
Dad had a case,
he'd just dump us on you.
Shoot,
you must have taught us
most of the outdoor tracking
we know.
Yeah, what I could get
to stick.
I never could get
you little grubs
to pull a trigger
on a single deer.
Talking about Bambi,
man.
You don't shoot Bambi,
jackass.
You shoot Bambi's mother.
Well,
looks like we found Phil.
Special agents.
Listen, I got your call.
But I'm not sure I got
what you were saying.
Hey.
I think we found Phil.
That's what I said.
Uh, I should probably
call this in.
Yeah, yeah.
Solid move, Rick.
Uh, this is Ranger Evans
up at Acher's Point. Come in.
Uh, repeat.
This is Chief Ranger Evans.
I have a situation
out at Acher's Point.
Ranger,
I think we've got company.
Yeah? Who's that?
Ranger!
Ranger Evans!
It's got him
up in the trees.
- Lights off.
- What?
Wait, Bobby, you think
that's really a good idea?
Shut up, shut off,
and listen.
Damn thing is eating Rick.
Man, I liked Rick.
Wow.
Nice shot, Bobby.
Seriously.
We all got our gifts.
What about the rest
of Ranger Rick?
Ranger called in his 10-20.
His own will find him.
We got crap to do.
Built like a supermodel,
but the thing was strong.
That's for damn sure.
Carried a full-grown man
up a tree in nothing flat.
But it only took one bullet
to bring it down.
And not even a silver bullet,
just a bullet-bullet.
Whew!
First one
must have just stunned it.
All right, well, let's check
its hulk pants for some I.D.
Oh, that is just gonna
ruin the leather.
Are you feeling okay?
Yeah, I feel great.
Gerald Browder,
uh, lived here in town, 5'9",
brown hair and blue eyes...
235 pounds.
Whoa.
Well, apparently,
he's lost a little pudge.
Maybe it's a-a lap-band
side effect.
What the hell?
I think we better have a look
under Gerald's hood.
God!
Its organs are swimming
in the stuff.
You guys getting hungry?
I'm hungry.
What's that?
His stomach.
For a guy on a diet,
Gerry here packed it in
pretty good.
That's human right there.
That's fresh Rick.
Let's see.
Plus...
Pine cone?
Pack of gum
in the wrapper.
That's -- that's older.
Maybe like a --
maybe Ranger Phil or the camper.
What's that?
Looks like a --
yeah, that's a --
that's a cat's head.
A glamper or two
is one thing,
but you got to be damn hungry
to eat a cat's head.
Mm-hmm.
Well, lookit here.
I'm no Dr. Oz, but...
I think
that's his adrenal glands.
Okay. And?
Meant to be the size
of hotel bar soap...
And bright orange.
Ooh.
All right, that might help
explain the strength.
Um, but whatever this thing is,
it's not the Jersey Devil,
but it sure as hell
ain't Gerald Browder anymore.
Okay, guys, seriously.
It's time for dinner?
Gerald Browder, 35,
self-employed.
Air-conditioning
repairman.
Missing person
number three.
Disappeared
eight days ago.
Well, that explains
all the people
who got eaten
in the last eight days.
Yeah.
Question is,
what happened to him?
Dean.
Uh, so,
what do you think?
I'm not that worried
about it.
Excuse me?
That's funny, right?
I could give two shakes
of a rat's ass.
Is that right?
Do rats shake their ass,
or is it something else?
Eh.
Give me that.
Whoa, whoa! Why?!
There's some funky chicken in
the TDK Slammer, ain't there?
Yeah.
This is stupid.
My sandwich
didn't do anything.
I don't know what you think
you're gonna find.
There's something wrong
with you, Dean.
Are you kidding?
I'm fine!
I --
I actually feel great.
The best I've felt
in a couple months.
Cass? Black goo?
I don't even care anymore.
And you know
what's even better?
I don't care
that I don't care.
I just want
my damn slammer back.
Dude,
you are completely stoned,
just like
Ranger Rick was.
Just like the dinner rush
back at Biggerson's.
And everybody's loving
the Turducken.
I think you pissed off
my sandwich.
That -- that's in me?
O-only half of it.
Does that snot
look familiar?
Okay, so whatever turned
Gerry Browder into a pumpkin head...
And is currently turning Dean
into an idiot --
I'm right here.
Right here.
Is in the Turducken Slammer
at Biggerson's.
Yeah.
It's in the meat.
If I wasn't so chilled out
right now, I would puke.
How's he doing?
He's sleeping it off.
Tryptophan coma.
So,
you think he's okay?
Yeah, he's all right.
Good.
So you don't worry
about him?
What do you mean?
Before the turducken?
Yeah. Yeah,
I kind of mean more like, uh...
More like
ever since my head broke...
And we lost Cass.
I mean,
you ever feel like he's --
he's going through
the same motions
but he's not the same Dean,
you know?
How could he be?
Right, yeah,
but what if --
What if what, Sam?
You know,
you worry about him.
All he does
is worry about you.
Who's left to live
their own life here?
The two of you --
aren't you full up
just playing snuffleupagus
with the devil
all the live long?
I don't know, Bobby.
Seeing Lucifer's fine with me.
Come again?
Look,
I'm not saying it's fun.
I mean,
to be honest with you,
I kind of see it
as the best-case scenario.
I mean...
At least all my crazy's
under one umbrella, you know?
I kind of know
what I'm dealing with.
A lot of people
got it worse.
You always were one deep
little son of a bitch.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here we go.
Well, I guess
we follow him.
That's weird, right?
I mean, national franchise
like Biggerson's
getting meat from a place
that looks like it wholesales
Hong Kong knockoffs.
Okay. Yeah.
It's a little weird.
All right, well,
I guess we wait
till they close up shop,
go take a look around?
Hang on.
No.
Edgar.
Leviathans.
Son of a bitch.
What the hell
is going on?
Put him with the others,
if you don't mind.
Edgar. Follow me.
I've been so busy
with this experiment,
I didn't even realize
you were back.
It's, uh, big stuff.
I'm back
because of the experiment.
What's happening?
You said you were
refining the formula.
Yes. Absolutely.
And it's going great.
The absorption rate is up
in lower concentrations.
But it didn't solve our little
issue with adverse reactions.
Well, no.
Not 100%.
Burn them.
What?
But they represent
crucial test data.
Where the additive formula
went wrong,
where my initial
projections failed.
Dick is coming.
Burn them.
There's nothing happening
back here at all.
Yeah, okay, Sam.
Well,
they're pretty dug in,
so why don't you finish circling
and head on back?
How's your head?
Well, I think the slammer's
pretty much wore off.
In between that
and the 20 cups of coffee,
I'm nicely tense
and alarmed.
I wasn't talking
about that.
Oh, Bobby, don't --
don't go all Sigmund Freud
on me right now, okay?
I just got drugged
by a sandwich.
I want to talk
about your new party line.
Party line?
What are you talking about?
I don't even vote.
"The world's
a suicide case.
We save it,
it just steals more pills"?
Bobby, I'm here, okay?
I'm on the case.
What's the problem?
I've seen a lot of hunters
live and die.
You're starting to talk like
one of the dead ones, Dean.
No, I'm talking
the way a person talks
when they've had it,
when they can't figure out
why they used to think
all this mattered.
Oh, you poor, sorry...
You're not a person.
Thanks.
Come on, now.
You tried to hang it up
and be a person
with Lisa and Ben.
And now here you are
with a mean old coot
and a van full of guns.
That ain't
person behavior, son.
You're a hunter,
meaning you're whatever the job
you're doing today.
Now, you get a case
of the Anne Sextons,
something's gonna
come up behind you
and rip
your fool head off.
Now, you find your reasons
to get back in the game.
I don't care if it's love
or spite or a $10 bet.
I've been to enough funerals.
I mean it.
You die before me,
and I'll kill you.
We need to scrape
some money together,
get you a condo
or something.
Hey.
Something's up.
Well, I'll be a squirrel
in a skirt.
It's Dick frigging Roman.
What? Who the hell
is Dick frigging Roman?
Billionaire Dick Roman,
seen here at
a recent press conference,
has been on the
corporate-takeover warpath
in the last several months
and shows no signs of relenting.
I believe in good old
American values,
like unlimited growth.
But it's like I always say --
if you want to win,
then you got to be the shark.
And a shark's got to eat.
Well, that's a great question.
Yes, we have made
new acquisitions.
I don't believe
in hostile takeovers.
I believe in merging...
and coming out on top.
Whether at the helm of
his America's cup-winning yacht
or one of his
Fortune 500 companies,
Roman has never shied away
from the spotlight.
Roman's record-breaking series
of motivational seminars,
"When in Rome," have outsold
every other money-making program
on the market.
A vocal member of the NRA
and a steadfast supporter
of the second amendment,
Roman has started attracting
some conservative
political attention, as well.
Roman is ruthless,
but good-looking.
I think he'll make
a great candidate.
Another great question.
No, I am not running for
political office at this time.
But I do have
a number-one bestseller.
Holy crap.
What the hell is that?
That's one of the top 50
most powerful men
in America, Dean.
Says here top 35
as of last month.
Now it's all
making sense.
Remember when Crowley kept
going on about hating Dick?
I thought he was just
being general. Pfft!
Well,
if the Leviathan got to him,
then that means they're playing
on a much bigger board
than we were thinking.
So what, then? I mean,
we can't exactly outgun them.
No, but we got
the drop on them.
Means we got a chance
to figure out
what these guys
are really doing here.
Whoa.
Where'd you get that mother?
It's on loan from
Frank's big brother collection.
It'll pick up
vocal vibrations
from window glass
at half a mile.
Well, it's time to find out
what these ugly bastards
are up to.
[ Rossini's "William Tell
Overture: Call to Cows" plays ]
The patient is put
under general anesthesia.
The eye is immobilized,
then a scalpel is used
to sever the optic nerve.
The food additive
that I've introduced
into the Turducken has a
near-100% rate of effectiveness.
Once the subject tries it,
they crave more
within a few hours.
With the very first dose,
it starts to work on their DNA,
slowing their metabolism,
causing weight gain,
and dampening
their emotional range,
which makes them
perfectly complacent.
As you can see,
they have yet to notice that
grandma is no longer with us.
True, if you leave out
a cooked patty
for more than an hour,
it reverts back
to a somewhat, uh,
unappealing state,
but I have yet to have a case
of leftovers.
You know what I love?
I mean, besides handball
and a really crisp Chardonnay.
I love progress.
And I know that progress comes
from collaboration,
which is what makes moments
like this so thrilling.
I am so glad
to hear you say that.
Now, what can you tell me
about your failures?
Hmm? My...
The ones that went off
the rails
after they ate
your little treats.
I, um...
They're, uh...
- They've been very instructive.
- No.
See, I asked
for complacency.
Not complacency
and a 0.03% margin of
hyperadrenalized cannibalism.
I will have this
under control.
"Camping high season
harshed by human burrito"?
Have I ever mentioned
how I feel
about our little forays
making the papers?
But, again,
collaboration.
Progress.
I want to turn
this little mistake
into a big fat
teachable moment.
Will you help me
with that?
Well...Yes.
Of course.
Our side's still dead,
Bobby.
Anything with you?
Same here.
I got -- hold on.
Yeah, I got movement --
my side, second floor,
meeting room.
And I'll reschedule
with the Senator
for lunch Tuesday.
You can deal with the
archdiocese in the afternoon.
Fine.
Dick, please,
let me explain to you
what our program
has to offer.
No. Let me explain why we're
shutting your program down.
We're shutting it down?
No, you can't --
I'm shutting it down
because of the one golden rule.
Do you know it?
Yes.
"Don't make the papers."
And I promise that --
No, the golden rule is
there's no such thing
as monsters.
Anything stirs their little pots
to the contrary --
very bad for our plans.
So, how can I use
your mistake
to communicate this
to all your coworkers?
Listen, sir,
I will do anything.
I will give anything
to make this right.
I know you will.
You're bibbing me?
Do you know what you can
give us, doctor?
Your example.
What's happening now?
Wait.
Now, Doc.
It's time.
Now I have officially
seen it all.
Bobby, what is it?
He's making the doctor
eat himself.
What?
He's --
They got him.
Dean, there are at least
four Leviathans out there.
We don't even know how
to kill one.
Well,
it'll be quite a shock
when we walk in through
the front door, won't it?
We'll have the jet
on standby at O'Hare.
Thursday morning, you close on
the land acquisition in Gleason.
Fine.
And this came
this afternoon.
- Sotheby's.
- Outstanding!
Thank you, Susan.
Oh, and, Susan?
Hmm?
Uh, tuh-tuh.
No, you're not tied up.
Why waste the effort?
We both know that
you're not gonna get past me.
How's your head?
So you got Dick Roman.
We can have
whoever we want.
We could have you,
for example.
If you were
worth the effort.
Oh, you're hurting
my feelings.
Well,
it's a hard world, Bob.
It's an us-eat-dog world.
What do you got there?
Winning bid at auction.
Beautiful.
Known for
their peerless sighting.
I imagine
you appreciate guns.
I'd appreciate one
right about now.
Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo.
But I mean the machine,
the idea.
Just one of your species'
most inspired inventions.
I mean it. I really think
you guys have spunk.
You're like a planet
of just the cutest little
engines that could.
But...
Like the late, great, actual
Dick Roman used to say
to the whores he'd kick out
of the presidential suite...
...Cute don't quite
hack it, sugar.
Oh, let's just
cut to the chase.
I clearly ain't worth the extra
time I'm getting here.
I'm gonna eat you, Bob.
Yes.
But I like
my meals prepared.
Besides, holding on to you
could pay big dividends.
I bet your friends are on their
way to rescue the damsel.
Nah,
they're too smart.
They know
they don't have the numbers.
It'd be suicide.
I've run my race.
Could die worse.
I'd stay in the chair.
Okay, sons of bitches.
See what you're up to now.
You're coming with me.
Sam...
That is not how we communicate
from a place of yes.
That was bracing.
Where'd you kids
find this stuff?
Hey!
That's mine.
Go! Go!
Would you stop it
with that stuff?
Damn it, where's Bobby?
Bobby! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Go! Go!
Son of a bitch!
I'm glad you got in.
He almost took
your freaking head off.
Hey, Bobby, your hat.
Bobby?
Oh, God. Bobby?!
Bobby?!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==