We think it may have been
an Alpha.
An Alpha, like...?
Like all monsters come from somewhere.
Bag me a live Alpha.
The first of your species.
The very first.
Prison full of monsters --
can't just leave them,
can't let them go.
I understand.
Geothrive is part
of Roman Enterprises.
Dick's funding
an archaeological dig...
Factory in Saudi Arabia...
Fishery in Jakarta...
A research center --
it's everywhere.
It's all tied together,
Dean.
He's not in control.
That was
vengeful-spirit crap.
But it's still Bobby.
Well,
what the hell are you?
I'm a...
K-Kevin Tran.
I'm in advanced placement.
He's a Prophet
of the Lord.
And that's the word of God?
One of them, yes.
- Well, what's it say, then?
- It's about Leviathan.
Does it say anything
about how to kill them?
Leviathan cannot be slain
but by a bone
of a righteous mortal
washed in the three bloods
of the fallen.
It says we need to start with
the blood of a fallen angel.
Always happy to bleed
for the Winchesters.
Hello, Kevin.
Thanks, Phil.
And now we turn our attention
to agriculture,
where an unlikely personality
has now come on to the scene
in a major way.
Richard Roman,
a C.E.O. whose company
dominates the defense
and aviation sectors,
not to mention being a giant
in the motivational-speaking
world.
What can I say, Gloria?
I'm a multitasker.
Clearly.
And now you've recently
purchased controlling stock
in Sucrocorp --
among the world's
leading manufacturers
in high-fructose
corn syrup.
It's a pleasure to have you
with us, Richard.
Please. "Dick."
So, tell us, Dick,
why the recent fascination
with big foods?
Well, it's no secret
we all love to eat,
but now Sucrocorp will focus
on eating well.
Help me connect the dots.
How will pumping sweeteners
into our system
make us healthier?
One word -- purity.
We're dialing back
the additives
to deliver the highest quality
all-American product
you people deserve.
America
is for go-getters,
folks who get off their butts
and make it happen.
And we need you just
as healthy as you can be.
Which is why we are diving
whole hog
into what keeps Americans
living longer...
and tasting better.
You do, of course,
mean to say
the food
will be tasting better.
That's exactly what I mean.
? Supernatural 7x22 ?
There Will Be Blood
Original Air Date on May 11, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Your 11:00 a.m. is waiting
in the conference room.
Thank you, Susan.
Susan...
Are we still looking
for a rep in Mainstream Media?
- Yes, we are.
- Wunderbar.
Put a "replace order"
on Gloria there.
And with the corpse?
Call Chef Fieri.
I feel like barbecue.
Kevin. Dick.
I'm very excited
to meet you.
You nervous?
Don't be.
I'm your biggest fan.
I brought you a present.
What's that say, Kev?
I don't know.
Cute.
Edgar?
Easy, Edgar.
Don't scare the boy.
You know, I've checked,
Kevin.
Number one in your class,
winner of the Chad Kennedy
top young scientist prize --
all that on top of being
Keeper of the Word.
You're a clever
young man.
I'm confident you'll make
the right choice here.
But I see this is
a negotiation.
Well, I will sweeten...
the pot.
What is it?
My sources tell me
you're applying to Princeton.
Letter of recommendation
like that from a man like me --
done.
I can't do it.
I admire
your gumption, kid.
But I still think there's
some wiggle room here.
I tell you what --
let's kick it up a notch.
See if I can't
change your mind.
Edgar,
that live feed up yet?
Of course.
Ma?
Mom?!
Well, I think this negotiation
is concluded.
You drive
a hard bargain, kid.
Okay, man, I have read this
more times
than the Playboy I found
in dad's duffel.
Anna Nicole?
Anna Nicole.
Oh, the good --
they die young, huh?
Look, we can read this
till our eyes bleed.
This ain't getting
any clearer.
Okay.
Then what does it mean?
Uh
Cut off the head,
and the body will flounder.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well, I think we both agree
that the head is Dick. Right?
Right.
So, bottom line is,
we go grab the stuff,
and we mix ourselves
a weapon.
End of story.
Look, I'm all
for killing Dick.
I'm just saying,
what then?
I mean, what about the rest
of the Leviathan?
What, are they gonna
just...drop dead?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Maybe?
"Maybe" is good enough
for you right now?
- One problem at a time, all right?
- Okay.
But it's not a crazy idea
to try and figure out
what the catch is
before we go crashing
the gate.
Maybe this is the catch.
God's not telling us
every detail.
You know?
The word is from God.
I don't know how much better
it's gonna get.
Hey, Bobby.
How you feeling?
Stronger than ever.
Now, while you two
have been chasing your tails,
I've been thinking
on that weapon.
Wait a second. Don't you think you
should be saving your strength?
For what?
I'm just saying you might want
to slow down. You don't look so hot.
I'm in the veil.
My Brad Pitt days
are over.
Now, the kid says
that the only way
to kill Leviathan
is with a bone washed in the
three bloods of the fallen.
It's got to be from a human
as light and good
as the Leviathan are hungry
and dark.
Yeah.
Good luck with that.
The rest is doable,
and doable now.
You've already got
the fallen angel blood.
Now, next up is blood
from the ruler
of fallen humanity.
Now, the best I can tell,
that's Crowley.
Numero tres is the father
of fallen beasts.
Which means...?
You got to bleed an Alpha.
But they're all dead.
I mean, every one we found,
we rounded up for Crowley,
and then Cass
whammied them all.
Well, then, make this
Cass' problem, too.
Cass ain't exactly in the
problem-solving mode, Bobby.
Then Crowley!
All right, I get it.
I get it.
Do you?!
I'm just sayin'.
I have faith that you boys
will figure it out.
Relax. I'm fine.
Just got a little
carried away.
Here at Sucrocorp,
your well-being is
our number-one priority.
Sucrocorp...
Little F.Y.I.
Bobby's officing out of the John
these days.
Uh...awkward.
Yeah, you're telling me.
He does have some ideas
about the weapon, though.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, uh, he may be
just in time.
"Roman acquires..."
What's Sucrocorp?
They make food additives,
namely high-fructose
corn syrup.
That crap is in -- well, it's in
just about everything --
um, soda, sauces, bread.
Don't say "pie."
Definitely pie.
Bastards.
So now what?
Roman's moved past
restaurants?
And into grocery stores,
Gas n' Sips, vending machines.
What can we do about it?
Short of going Al Qaeda
on their trucks and plants,
there's nothing we can do
about it.
Like I said, uh,
Bobby's got some ideas.
Et ad congregandum
eos coram me.
Hello, boys.
That's some bracing prose you're
putting down there, Kevin.
You all done?
You've done well. Princeton
will be lucky to have you.
What about my mom?
Make the call.
Release her.
But stress the consequences
of talking.
Kevin, I'm gonna request
the pleasure of your company
a tad longer.
You, on the other hand,
I need to drop in
on an old friend.
So, that's what all
the "rumble, rumble" was about.
Who translated it for you?
Never mind. You gonna give us
the blood or not?
Happily.
But not quite yet.
I'm all for chopping Dick,
but I can't have you
running around
with a vial of my blood,
now, can I?
You know the sheer number
of nefarious spells
my enemies can use
that blood for?
- Well, then when?
- Last.
After you've got
all the other components.
Most difficult, the angel part,
I'm assuming.
Given your role
in their little apocalypse,
I can't imagine
the choirboys upstairs
are wetting their vestments
to do you -- what's the word? --
a solid...
Unless, of course, you have
an angel up your sleeve.
Well, that'd be convenient,
but, uh, no.
Don't worry about it.
We'll get the angel blood
one way or another.
We just need you to be ready
next time we call.
Fine.
Oh, here's a tip.
I have it on good authority
there's one Alpha
still among us.
Whose authority?
Mine.
Wily character,
that Alpha vampire.
Somehow made good
his prison break
before Cass went nuclear
on the place.
And you know this how?
Keep your friends close,
your enemies, blah blah.
Needless to say,
I keep tabs.
He moves around quite a bit.
But I have an inkling
I know where to start
the Easter-egg hunt.
Happy trails.
Okay.
Where, jackass?!
Hoople, North Dakota.
Piece of paper
would have worked.
Hey.
He seem angry?
Angry?
Of course he's angry.
If you were Bobby,
wouldn't you be?
But was he showing signs
of fatigue,
like -- like fritzing?
No, actually,
it was just the opposite.
He said he never
felt stronger.
That's what
I was afraid of.
The stronger he gets,
the closer he comes to going
full vengeful spirit.
That's reality.
We need to talk about
what we're going to do with him.
- Do with him?
- Yeah.
Three weeks ago, you were
talking how this could work.
And now you want to go Kevorkian
on his ass?
I'm just saying
that the lore
doesn't have a single
real-life example
of Casper
the friendly ghost.
It's all basically poltergeists
until a hunter comes along...
Yeah, well,
the lore sucks.
I'm talking pure hatred,
Dean.
No humanity.
I mean, he could...kill...
possess people.
I mean, Bobby could burn
this friggin' building down.
Look, if he goes off the rails --
Hey.
What?
Check out that guy
over there.
He seem a little
out of it to you?
I-I don't know.
Maybe.
What about Paula Deen
over here?
Yeah, they --
they look like...
...like those
Turducken people.
It's starting.
It's the corn syrup.
Everything in the store
is laced with it.
Everything?
Hey, man, I'm gonna go
into toxic shock, okay?
I-I...I need my road food.
That's what Roman
is banking on.
Hey.
This one says "natural."
T-that means it's safe. Right?
I hate to break it to you,
but corn syrup is natural,
technically.
Well, then what the hell
are we supposed to eat?
It's totally dark.
I can't see inside.
Well, should we wait
for daylight?
Hell no,
we're not waiting.
I'll scout it.
See if we need to bring in
the big guns.
I don't know.
Look, Bobby...
Okay.
Place is clear.
But there's something
you're gonna want to see.
Careful.
You know a way to kill vamps
with battery acid?
Only way I know
is beheading.
Well, something
didn't agree with them.
Hey.
Check out that wall.
Something seem weird
to you?
Yeah, see if you can find a switch
or a lever or something.
Don't need one.
Hey.
Dean. Machete.
Look.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Okay? No fangs.
See?
We just want to talk.
I was 8.
My mom left me at the playground
while she ran to the store.
A man approached me
and said I was
the prettiest girl there.
And I've been living
with these...
things...ever since.
At least until now.
Do you have any idea why?
I'm one of
his special girls.
All the others,
it was their job
to make sure I was ready
for the Alpha,
whenever he came.
Wash me...
give me my I.V. bags
every day.
It's my only food.
So my blood's pure.
They've been doing this
for, what, 12 years?
Virgins are a delicacy.
He always has
at least one of us on hand.
Well, don't worry, okay?
We're gonna get you back
to your mother.
Think she remembers me?
Of course she does.
Don't you remember her?
These, uh...
these guys --
they, uh, friends of yours?
They take care of the Alpha
when he's here.
Or did.
What happened to them?
A week ago,
they came back
from what they said
was an easy hunt.
Three humans just came,
didn't put up any fight.
But when they started
on them,
the vampires screamed
in pain.
The ones who ate
died immediately.
And the ones who didn't?
There was only one.
When he saw what happened,
he moved to animals.
He's out hunting
as we speak.
Never heard of vamps
being allergic to humans before.
You think maybe
it's the corn syrup?
I mean, think about it.
The Gas n' Sip was lousy
with stoners.
All ripe for the picking.
She did say
it was an easy hunt.
Do you know where
the Alpha is now?
I don't know.
Maybe.
He has a place he goes
when something's wrong.
He calls it his retreat.
What is that?
That's, uh,
that's Sam's douche tracker.
Helps us find the Alpha.
All we need's an address.
I don't know.
But I remember things
that maybe can help.
That's okay.
Just do the best you can.
Finally.
I'd run out of magazines.
Quick question.
Where's your boss?
Let's try that again.
- Where is he?
- Go to hell.
No. My neighborhood
is worse than that.
Missoula, Montana.
Was that so hard?
I can't do this, man.
I can't live
on rabbit food.
I'm -- I'm a warrior.
Dean, you'll be fine.
You don't know that.
So what's next
on the list?
Well, if we're bum-rushing
the Alpha,
then we're gonna need
dead man's blood,
which means a morgue.
Or...
Or what?
Dude, forget the morgue.
We are swimming
in vamp poison.
Excuse me, sir.
Hi.
We, uh,
we're with the...
Red Cross?
See, we have
an emergency shortage.
And we're gonna need
you to...
You're not getting a word
I'm saying, are you?
Hey.
Hold out your arm.
We need your blood.
Dude.
All right, Sam.
Tap the keg.
Here?
Yeah, Sam, look around.
It's friggin' Woodstock. Everybody's
hopped up on the brown acid.
We don't need
the song and dance.
Give him a little prick.
That hurts.
This is for Hurricane Katrina,
you said?
Yes.
Yes, I did.
So, look...
When we get there...
Yeah?
Bobby's gonna have
to hang back.
Do you disagree?
He ain't gonna like it.
I mean, he helped us
in getting Emily.
Look, I'm team Bobby, too.
Okay?
But there's a reason we left him
in the car with Emily. You know that.
The more action he sees,
the more chance he gets
to spin out.
All right, fine.
So, we'll keep him
off the front lines,
and he can just, you know,
keep calm and carry on, right?
And if he can't?
[ War's "Why Can't We Be
Friends?" Plays ]
? Why can't we be friends? ?
When they hauled you off
to vamp camp,
do you remember how long
the drive was?
We left at night.
Got in before dawn.
So, six, seven hours?
I think so, yes.
Do you remember
any highways?
No. We only
took back roads.
Okay. So, figure they averaged
45 miles per --
Couldn't have been more
than 300 miles.
Right.
What direction
were you going?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
Em, you're doing great.
Um...is there anything else
you remember?
Bells.
As we pulled up,
I heard these loud bells.
It was still dark out?
You thinking church?
No, that's too early.
It could have been
a monastery.
Monks get up at 4:00 a.m.
to pray.
Ugh. Can't get laid.
Can't sleep in.
A friggin' tragedy.
Okay, so, Alpha's camping
next to a, uh, monkey house.
How many do we got
in range?
Looks like one.
Just outside...
This is where he took me.
Are you sure?
What now?
We'll get you
someplace safe.
Circle back and ginsu
these leeches.
...but she couldn't get it.
Yes, the famous
Fleur-de-lis mansion.
$125 million estate...
All right, here we go.
10 ccs of vamptonite.
It's a thing.
What's a Kardashian?
Oh, that's...
just another bloodsucker.
No, it --
it's...a joke.
Here.
If we're not back
by dawn,
call this number,
Jody Mills.
She's a friend.
She'll take care of you.
Here, use this phone.
You gotta hang here.
For your own good.
Capiche?
Sam?
Thank you.
You bet.
It was the wind.
Chill out, Bobby.
We'll be back soon.
Well, he didn't take that
very well.
How'd you think
he was gonna take it?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
And the pitch...
Bass is leaning in
for the sign -- he's ready.
Enters the stretch...
And here's the pitch --
again, way, way inside.
He's having some trouble
out there.
The national weather report.
High tides and heavy surf
battering the coast
of North Carolina today.
Force-40 winds
and heavy rain...
Hi, daddy.
Why, you little schemer.
No, I'm close by.
Sending you a present.
And that's Dick Roman.
Yesterday I introduced you
to this rising star
in American business.
In this hour,
we'll go behind the scenes
and answer the question
everyone's been asking
for months --
what makes Dick so hard
to beat?
You son of a bitch.
Well, this time of day,
most of them would be
catching z's.
They won't know
what hit them.
Hey. You with me?
Yeah.
But...
Are you sure you just
want to charge in there,
machetes blazing?
Last time,
it took a dozen hunters
to take down the Alpha.
And most of them
didn't make it out.
Yeah, well,
you got a better idea?
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
Dean.
Maybe we're too late.
Sam!
You know,
where I'm from,
you have to bite and claw
your way to the top.
Once you get there,
trust me,
the view's incredible.
Okay, Dean's birthday.
Sam's birthday.
Damn it!
Son of a bitch.
Everything okay in there?
- My birthday.
Hello?
I need your help.
Get away from me.
Listen,
I need out of here.
Please!
Just need you a little while.
Just till I get the bastard.
The Winchesters.
I'm intrigued.
Emily.
Hi, Sam.
Wow.
For a girl raised
in a basement,
you're a hell of an actress.
You were gonna hurt
my daddy.
Hmm.
Wow.
You get a trophy
in Stockholm Syndrome.
I'm sorry to burst
your bubble, but...
we weren't.
Sam here had
a better idea.
We're here to talk.
That's it.
Now that my guys have taken
your blades
and your syringes
of tainted blood.
Is that what you mean?
Well, we...
figured you might hold
a grudge.
And why would I?
Because you captured me,
tortured me,
sold me to
the king of Hell?
That was more our grandpa.
Ugh.
Thank you.
That was awesome.
I'm going to
peel off your faces
- and drink you slowly.
- Just listen.
You need us.
Oh, yes.
I am thirsty!
The plague!
We know what it is!
What do you know
about Leviathan?
A bit.
You know they're poisoning
the food supply?
Roman didn't mention that
when we met for dinner
last fall.
We made lots of plans.
We are on excellent terms,
he and I.
You sure about that?
Did he mention
that he was going to...
Maui wowie
the human population?
Oh, of course.
He said grabbing a snack
would be easier than ever.
He said you'd all live together,
didn't he?
You really believe him?
You think your children
are dying by accident?
There is pesticide
in the formula!
It suits you to think so.
You need me on your side.
Look, we're not the ones
burning from the inside out.
Think about it.
Whatever deal he made with you
was crap!
- Trust us!
- Why are you telling me this?
Because we can stop Dick.
Stop all of it.
We just...
We need your blood --
for the weapon.
So now you want to prevent
the extermination
of the vampire race.
No.
But it beats going down
with you.
Allan, darling...
come.
Well, the creep
gets creepier.
- What's wrong?
- Edgar's here.
Wow,
what a funny coincidence.
All right, we need soap,
uh, cleanser,
anything with borax in it.
We need knives.
Put them in the study.
Wait. No, no, no.
- No, wait.
- Word of advice, boys.
You do not live through
centuries of fire and ice
and continental divide...
by jumping to conclusions.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're making a mistake!
Listen! Wait!
Never hurts to get
the story first.
Hey. Hey!
Edgar.
I would've whipped you
up a meal.
Please, sit.
I'm dying to know
why you're here.
I think you know.
And how is that?
I smell Sam
and Dean Winchester.
Anything?
Nothing.
You think Edgar's here
for the same reason we are?
I mean, look,
if they figured out
that we're here to get
Alpha blood for a weapon...
I think
any way you slice it,
you got Pac Man and True Blood
in the same room,
and that's bad news.
I mean, he's not stupid.
Why the hell do you think
he locked us in here?
Dean, we're his enemy.
I mean, they're like
monster cousins or something.
Who would you give the benefit
of the doubt to?
You know what? Maybe the Sucro
is poisoning the vamps on accident.
Maybe they'll fix it.
I think you got the oldest
monster on earth
thinking he can hold his own
because he always has.
Edgar's gonna
eat him alive.
Yeah.
Hey.
You think you could pick a lock
with this?
But, Dean...
We gave up
all our vamptonite.
Did we?
Do you want the boys?
Yes?
You're welcome to them.
I'll have them sent out.
How kind of you.
Oh, Edgar...
You do know why Sam and Dean
are here, don't you?
They insist that you're
exterminating us,
and I thought, well,
that's...impossible.
Must be a mistake.
You're right.
Of course.
Wow.
Vamptonite.
Friggin' vamptonite.
All right, we need knives.
There's got to be a prep room
or a kitchen somewhere. Come on.
Here's what I don't
understand, Edgar.
You are aware
that your little additive
has side effects, yes?
Dick warned you
there might be kinks.
Yes. He also said
he'd be in touch.
My children are in a panic.
You don't call,
you don't write,
you don't send cookies.
Where exactly on the list
is fixing our plague?
My dear friend...
...nowhere.
We want you to burn like
the little roaches you are.
Roman said if I kept quiet,
I would get my reward.
And now you get to lay down
and die.
Nothing personal.
Our additive kills
the wolves, too...
the shifters, and those
disgusting little things
that eat corpses.
Anything with a taste
for human.
Except us.
Mankind's a limited resource,
after all.
There are seven billion...
of them.
Only seven.
- We come from you.
- Barely.
I am the son of Eve!
A pathetic mutt.
Hardly one of us.
I knew Eve,
and honestly...
your mommy was a whore.
Don't squirm.
I need every last drop.
Hey!
Grab a glass.
We're juicing this freak.
No!
Stay back!
Leave her alone.
She's been through
quite enough.
Now, that's rich...
coming from the guy
who took her off the swing-set.
Do you want to do
this fight?
Or do you want my blood?
For taking care of Edgar.
Now go.
What about the little boy?
Are you joking?
Do we look like
we're joking?
How many other kids
you got in here, you freak?
At the moment, just him.
Emily...
help Allan with his coat.
He's leaving
with Sam and Dean.
Now, take it.
What?
No "thank you"?
Oh, right, right.
Your flesh is crawling.
All you really want to do
is kill me now.
You hate having to wait
and come back and try again.
Pretty much.
I wouldn't leave that head
too close to that body
for too long.
See you next season.
Looking forward to it.
Let's never do that again.
Cops thought
we took that kid.
Long as he gets back
to his folks,
I don't care
what they thought.
We had to jump out
a freakin' window, man.
Bobby.
Bobby?!
Dean?
He's gone.
I'm getting trace bits of EMF,
but it's fading fast.
And Bobby's probably been gone
three or four hours.
He's got the flask, Dean.
How the hell are we supposed
to track him?
Look,
I hate to say this...
Well, then don't.
He's gone.
How could he do this...
Now?
I mean, we've got half
the freakin' weapon,
we're almost there.
It's not him.
I mean, he's not thinking.
So, what, we just keep going
while he's out there like this?
Do we have
any other option?
I mean, it's what
he'd want us to do. Right?
Yeah.
Yeah, him and Frank
and Cass,
if his marbles
were in the bag.
It's a good thing we got Crowley
in our corner. Right?
Seeing as how it all
comes down to him.
What could possibly
go wrong?
Hello...
...Dick.
Mr. Crowley,
we have so much
to talk about.
Take a seat.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==