- Hello.
- Bobby singer?
My surgeon is a monster
please get your ass here to,
sioux falls general hospital.
They're like
shapeshifters,
only a lot more
into eatin' folk.
And...Nothing
can kill 'em.
Anything else?
Yep.
They bleed black goo.
Hi, Dean.
The spell only lasts
for a few days.
The stuff you don't talk about
doesn't just go away.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about whatever
you're not telling me about!
We're good. Right?
We're good.
You sure about this?
Trust me.
Good morning...
Megan.
That is a really,
really pretty dress.
Oh!
Thank you.
It's vintage.
Well, it looks new
on you.
Aren't you sweet, sir?
Call me Dean.
How can I help you today,
Dean?
Um, well, I don't actually
have an account at this bank,
but I was wondering
if there was any way...
I could get change
for that?
I think I can make
an exception...
Just for you.
Thanks.
How do you want it, Dean?
Well, I'm gonna have
to take a rain check...
And all your money.
Hands in the air!
Your money's insured,
so no heroes, okay?
You ready?
Yep.
? Supernatural 7x06 ?
Slash Fiction
Original Air Date on October 28, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Okay, Chet.
Let's see how you like a little
fruit of the poison tree.
Isn't that just
a legal expression?
You're gonna wish it was.
Hmm.
Oaky.
Similar finish
to holy water,
not as bitter
as rock salt.
And how are my two
favorite meat-sicles?
Is he still sucking air?
Greatest hits
didn't do the trick.
I'm down to B-sides
and deep cuts.
Well, you better figure out
something quick.
That whammy that witch dude
put on him
is only gonna last
for a few days.
He gets his spinach back,
we're gonna end up having
to drop a car on him
just to stop him.
Actually...
Edgar walked away
from that car.
He's fine.
Well, he is a little pissed
at you, but--
Oh. You didn't know?
Why don't you shut
your caketrap?
Ooh.
Bobby...
You've been using all this stuff
and he still won't talk?
Huddle over, coach?
How'd you find us?
It was easy.
I used pattern-recognition
software
and a basic heuristic algorithm
to track your known aliases.
Great.
Just what we need --
a Mensa monster.
All right.
Let's just start
with the start.
Where'd you get
our aliases?
From your trench-coated friend,
obviously.
When we were all nestled in
at Camp Cass,
kind of got
the full download.
That's just how we do.
So why are you
talking to us, Chet?
You're not dumb.
Why you spilling
state secrets?
'Cause I'm not scared of you.
You can't stop me.
You can't stop any of us.
We can't be killed,
you stupid little chewtoys.
You are aware that I'm the least
of your concerns, right?
Oh.
You haven't watched the news
today, have you?
The two men, who up until
today were presumed dead,
locked the doors
and opened fire,
leaving no survivors.
Sam and Dean Winchester
are now the subjects
of a manhunt throughout
the state of California.
Busy morning, you two?
Those sons of bitches
xeroxed us.
But I don't
understand how.
I don't know.
Maybe one of 'em
touched you at the hospital.
It was the hair!
Not too hard to lift some DNA
out of a motel
shower drain, guys!
You can copy people
like that?
Awesome.
Well, what is their plan,
exactly?
Squeeze us.
Turn us into the most wanted men
in America.
All right.
Well, that settles it.
We find these ass monkeys,
and we kill them ourselves.
Wait a sec.
Every form of law enforcement
in the country
has seen your ugly mugs
this morning.
Exactly. So what's the point
in trying to hide?
Better than sticking
your fool neck out.
These things are smarter
than you.
Geez, Bobby,
don't sugarcoat it.
You don't have a clue
how to kill 'em
or slow 'em down,
and your plan is, what?
Go right at 'em?
Genius.
They're wearing our faces,
Bobby. This is personal.
I'm with Dean here.
Well,
if you're gonna be stupid,
you might as well be smart
about it.
You need to see a fella
named Frank Devereaux.
Who's he?
He's a jackass
and a lunatic,
but he owes me one,
from back in Port Huron.
In the meantime,
I'll keep working
on Chatty Cathy here,
see if I can figure out
what makes him die.
The usual?
Rhymes with sing-songs.
You guys
sell protein bars?
Yeah.
But it's in --
it's in the back, though.
Just, uh,
give me a second.
Sure. Thanks.
Pretty sure
the cashier just made me.
Drive.
Hell.
Thanks.
Special Agent Morris.
This is Special Agent Valente.
Gentlemen.
These Winchester boys
are keeping busy, I hear.
What is this,
some type of psycho road trip?
The second bank,
plus that convenience store?
Couple of days ago,
they were dead.
We know about
what you know.
Excuse me.
Actual serial killers.
Crime spree means paperwork.
Lots of it.
Which you'll be doing.
We gotta go.
Winchesters spotted
at a Gas n' Sip.
It's about a thousand miles
from here.
That's fast.
Must have flown.
That or Batmobile.
You sure this is
the right place?
Yeah.
Frank, you in there?
Frank?
Frank, anybody here?
Hello?
Anybody home?
Well, well.
Spider caught some flies.
Well, I'll be darned.
Psycho Butch and Sundance.
You're on CNN right now.
No, no,
t-that's not us.
I know. Can't be.
Unless you had a teleporter.
Do you have a teleporter?
No...Sir.
We don't.
Well, my condolences
on the doppelgangers.
Now, who sent you?
NSA? The Feeb?
March of Dimes?
Uh, Bobby Singer sent us.
Or not. Who?
H-he said
you could help.
He said you owed him,
from Port Huron.
Guy saves your life one time,
and, what, you owe him
the rest of yours?
That's usually
how it works, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I know that Bobby's
into that magic hooey,
but truth is,
the government have been
cloning people for years.
Guess it was just your turn
in the barrel.
- Well, actually --
- Forget it. He's rolling.
Yours have been
busy beavers.
You're number two
on the most wanted list.
Quickest climb up the charts
since Donna Summer.
So, what do you think
we should do?
Cuba's nice
this time of year.
No, we're not hiding.
Is he always this stupid?
Look, we got to stick around
and kick a couple asses.
So, we just need you to get us
further off the grid,
but keep us on the board.
Well, first thing we got to do
is wipe all your old aliases.
No more rock shoutouts.
It's Tom and John Smith
from now on.
And no plastic.
Cash only.
And change your phones
on a very frequent
non-schedule schedule,
you understand?
Oh, and try to stay out of view
of the 200 million cameras
that the government
has access to, 'kay?
200 million?
Big Brother,
he has many eyeballs,
my friend.
You see a place
that even looks like
it can afford security,
you just
ease on down the road.
This...
This is your laptop,
right?
Yeah. That's mine.
What -- gee -- hey --
what are you --
what was that?!
Uh...
Thank you, I guess.
No problem.
You owe me five grand, cash.
- What?
Unless you wanna go
comparison shop at the mall,
sweet cheeks.
Say hi to the cops for me.
Okay.
Let's blue steel you up
some new I.D.,
Mr. and Mr. Smith.
Whoo!
Do it again!
Come on, do it again!
So you're just gonna touch me
in the morning,
then just walk away?
Are you still talkin'?
Aren't you sick
of this yet?
You bleed.
Black...snot, sure,
but you bleed, you can die.
Sure, sport,
whatever you say.
Try the acid again,
why don't you?
Poor sap.
You're stumped.
Give it a rest, mouthy.
How long
you think these'll hold
once the spell wears off,
hmm?
Tick tock, old man.
I'm gonna really enjoy
eating you,
right down to that hat.
I said shut up.
And then I'm gonna
eat everyone...
you ever said hello to.
Hot damn.
Well, that's somethin'.
I marked all the towns
your stunt doubles hit
so you can see
the pattern.
All right, great.
Um, so,
what is the pattern?
No clue, man.
I can't see it.
Seems random.
Little tip from a pro --
there is no such thing
as a random series
of robbery murders
by your evil twins.
Well, have yourself some uppers
and look at that some more.
Good luck.
Thanks, Frank.
For what?
Sending you to your death?
Your doubles want to be
on "candid camera,"
put you
in the line of fire.
Now, I'd lay low,
'cause I love life
and its infinite mysteries.
But you two want to be dumb,
that's fine.
At least have the common sense
to ditch your car.
Uh, excuse me.
What?
Your doublemints --
they're using a car
just like the one outside.
What the...
What the hell
are you doing here?
You're all charm, Bobby.
So my therapist
keeps telling me.
How'd you find me?
I'm a cop, remember?
You gonna invite me in?
Well,
you may not want me to.
I got one of the big mouths
downstairs.
So I won't go downstairs.
Mm.
I, uh...
I wanted to come
thank you.
Thank me?
Well, yeah...
Seeing as they were
fresh out of
"thanks for saving me from
liver-eating surgeon" cards
at the store.
Oh, that.
Just doing my job,
which nobody pays me for.
Right.
How you doing, Bobby?
I'm fine.
Every day is a gift.
Your house
just burned down.
As you can see,
I got a roof over me.
Bobby!
Let someone be nice to you
for five minutes?
Okay.
But not too nice.
I can't be going soft.
'Course not.
I can cook.
Ish. You know?
Why don't you
let me make you something?
Maybe put this new place
of yours in some kind of order.
Come on.
I owe you that much.
Okay.
Thanks, sheriff.
Jody.
Did you think
it would be that easy?
No.
But it's a start.
Ugh.
You okay?
You know, it's bad enough
that they're ganking people,
wearing our mugs,
but now this?
Have us driving around
in this...caboodle
while Baby's on lockdown.
It's temporary, Dean.
Nobody puts Baby
in a corner.
Y-you know
that's a line from --
Swayze movie.
Swayze always gets a pass!
Right.
Uh, well, you want some tunes
or something?
Here.
? And what would you say
if I called on you now ?
? and said that
I  can't hold on? ?
- Sorry, man, I-I...
- Just leave it.
Probably gonna be
the only thing on.
? There's no easy way,
it gets harder each day ?
? please love me
or I'll be gone ?
? I'll be gone ?
? I'm all out of love ?
? I'm so lost without you ?
? I know you were right ?
? believing for so long ?
? I'm all out of love ?
? what am I without you? ?
? I can't be too late to say
that I was so wrong ?
? oh ?
? what are you thinking of? ?
? what are you -- ?
- Dean.
- What?
Jericho --
the lady in white.
Blackwater -- wendigo.
Lake Manitoc --
the kid in the lake.
They're hitting towns
we've worked jobs in.
In order.
Since the day I left Stanford
with you.
So, what,
they want us to find them?
Well,
one way to find out --
next case would be
in...St. Louis.
Perfect.
Connor's Diner.
Best burgers
in St. Louis.
Oh, I deserve something good
in my life right now.
You know,
he has one of these every day.
And in his heart,
he thinks they're almost
as good as sex.
This...
is disgusting.
Dead plants
with creamy goo.
It's like eating
self-righteousness.
I mean,
you tell me which is worse.
I mean, honestly, I just...
You know what?
I can't stand the guy.
Talk about a hero complex.
And he doesn't have
relationships.
No, he has applications
for sainthood.
Oh, and he thinks
he's funny.
He thinks
he's a damn comedian.
Who has two thumbs and
full-blown bats in the belfry?
I'm serious.
It's nothing but Satan-vision
on the inside.
I mean, how he's walking around
in a jacket
with detachable arms
is beyond me.
You know, I had a brother
with this many issues once.
- Yeah?
- Know what I did?
- Hmm?
- I ate him.
Of course you did.
How are these guys
even a threat?
Boss says they gotta go,
they gotta go.
Right.
Idea.
You wanna trade?
I mean, I'll take chuckles
over schizo.
No, I like this one's
hair better.
You can stay
in the big one.
All right. In that case,
let's turn up the heat.
The sooner I get out of this
and into something more stable,
the better.
Hold on.
Hey, kid. Hey.
Why don't you fire up
the camera on that thing?
Point it over here.
Shall we?
All right, everybody be cool!
This is a robbery!
Anybody moves,
and I'll execute
every last one of you!
Choppin' their heads off
won't kill 'em,
but it'll slow 'em down
pretty good.
Till they fuse back up,
anyhow.
Well, that's something,
I guess.
I mean, assuming we can even
get close to them.
Believe me, I don't want you
walking right up to 'em, either.
I'm still looking for something
you can shoot at 'em.
Good times.
All right, thanks, Bobby.
Hey, you take mayo,
right, Bobby?
You got a chick
over there?
What?
No.
Are you even working,
Richard Gere?
Shut up, you idjit.
Where are you boys
off to next?
Uh, St. Louis.
That's where we --
It's too late.
They hit St. Louis.
Pumpkin-and-Honeybunny'd
a diner there.
Connor's Diner?
Yeah.
How'd you know?
Lucky guess.
All right,
so much for that.
I guess we're off to...
To Ankeny, Iowa.
Call us if you get
anything else.
You got it.
Special Agents Morris,
Valente.
You were first
on the scene?
Unfortunately.
Wanna tell us
what happened?
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Keep that up!
I didn't say
you could put that down!
I want the whole world to know
what Sam and Dean Winchester
are capable of.
That all of 'em?
All but one.
No, please, no.
Well,
goodnight, St. Louis.
You've been
a wonderful crowd.
Grab your socks and hose,
Iowa,
'cause we're
headed to you next.
We need to alert --
Federal, state, local --
I'm on it.
Ooh.
Does this skin
make me look fat?
Balls.
It's pretty dark in here.
High-school dropout.
A drunk like your daddy
before you.
Oh. You and dad.
Now, that's a can
of scorpions.
Your favorite singer
is Joni frickin' Mitchell?
Oh, Bobby.
You are 10 pounds of sad
in a 5-pound bag.
Sam, Sam. Hold up.
Don't move.
Oh, no.
This is all sorts
of wrong.
Those are nice wheels.
Tell you what,
when this is over,
I'm stealing those rims.
Tell the kids I said hi.
Yeah.
Bobby,
we got eyes on them.
What?
It's like looking
at a funhouse mirror.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
All right, well,
tell me you got something.
Otherwise, we're gonna
have to get in close.
Look,
just hang back for now.
It's too late.
We gotta --
hang on.
Hands in the air!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Big misunderstanding.
Look, the guys you want --
shut up!
They're right there.
Shut up!
Drop the phone.
Put your hands in the air.
Dean?
Dean!
You know the thing
about you, Bobby...
Save it.
I already know me,
handsome.
You got
the gruff thing down.
Seen more death
than an electric chair.
Ready to die
with your boots on.
But, you know,
deep down inside...
you're no cynic.
You still hope.
You even got a thing
for that lady upstairs.
Tiny part of you thinks,
maybe...
after this is all done,
you and miss sheriff can make
your own little cabin
in the woods.
That's hilarious.
You're not getting any older
than tomorrow, Bobby.
Why do you bother?
You a Browning fan?
Come again?
Robert Browning.
Poet.
You got that name rattling
around up there
with the rest of my thoughts
and feelings?
It's kind of hard
to sift through
all the drunken
blackouts, but --
"A man's reach
should exceed his grasp."
I like that.
That's actually lovely.
Browning?
After I eat you,
I'm definitely gonna hit
the library.
What the hell is that?
Get it off.
Get it off!
Get it off!!
Get it off of me!
Get it off me!
Oh, sorry.
Little snafu here.
Mm!
Okay, wasn't expecting
that reaction.
What the hell
was in that bucket?
Look,
you're making a mistake.
The real killers
are back at the diner, okay?
Is that the best
you can do?
I want my phone call.
Oh, there'll be a call,
to the FBI.
Take him
to cell number one.
Take that one
to the interview room.
Once they're separate
and secure,
you boys call it a night.
You're making a mistake!
What, did you guys
forget something or what?
Hey. I have a right
to my phone call.
A right?
You killed how many people
last couple days,
and you want me to hop-to
on your rights?
I didn't --
please --
just give me one --
one phone call.
Boys?
Bobby, we got popped.
Okay.
I'll be there as soon as --
No, no, there's no time.
Look, we saw them...
They saw us.
So, we are coming
to get us.
You read me?
Tell me
you got something.
There's a chemical --
sodium borate.
Okay, let me get Mr. Wizard
on speed dial.
No, no,
it ain't as weird as it sounds.
It's found in industrial
cleaners and soaps
and laundry powder.
Just look for anything
with the word borax on it.
You want me to "Desperate Housewife"
these mothers?
No, just trust me.
It burns 'em bad enough
to slow 'em down.
So get the strongest
you can find. Hear me?
Borax. Burns.
Got it.
Then douse 'em,
then get close,
and then chop the heads off.
Got it.
And keep
the heads separate!
Bobby, you're a genius.
Thanks. I --
what'd you do that for?
Borax?
Decapitation?
What kind of sickos are you
and your friends?
Hey, you listen to me.
If you don't go get
every ounce,
every drop of
whatever that stuff is
in this place right now...
We're all gonna die!
Well, you're crazier
than I thought.
Hey!
What are you doing?
What is your problem?
We don't have time for lunch
right now.
I was hungry.
Later. Let's go.
What is it?
What happened?
I...It's just...
I don't know
what I just saw.
Let me out of here.
Okay, you listen to me,
and we'll live.
All right, keep your head down,
get to the supply closet.
Get anything that says borax
on it -- bring it here.
Now. Go.
Dean!
I'm not your brother.
But I am Dean adjacent.
Sorry.
Sammy.
Not Sammy.
I just want to let you know
how much I've really grown
to hate
you and your brother
since we've been wearing you.
I just don't get it.
You could be anything.
You're strong.
You're uninhibited.
You're smart enough,
believe it or not.
But you're so caught up
in being good
and taking care
of each other.
What do you care?
Because it pisses me off!
You're wasting
a perfectly good opportunity
to subjugate the weak.
Cute. Really think you can
get close enough to use it?
Not until you're burning.
Here's the deal.
Dean...
...thinks you're nutballs.
He thinks you're off
your game.
You gonna kill me,
or is this some sort of
"play with your food" bull?
All right.
You know, I guess that's why
Dean never told you
that he killed Amy.
There it is.
The look on your face.
That is priceless!
That's what
I've been waiting for.
Now I can eat you.
'Cause, you see,
I like my meat
a little bitter.
Well, that felt good.
So...
the FBI is on the way.
Yeah, listen,
about that...
whatever I can do...
Especially if it involves lying
about everything I just saw.
Good.
I was hoping you could help us
kind of...be dead.
You know, quote unquote.
Yeah.
Yeah, I should be able
to swing that.
All right.
Come on,
let's grab a mop.
Sammy? You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Let's go.
That's when I got the drop
on them
and shot them both.
You did good, sheriff.
Here's the files.
Cause of death --
multiple gunshot wounds.
I fingerprinted them first,
of course,
for your records.
Mind if we take a look
at the bodies?
Their bodies were sent to
the funeral home for cremation,
as per their living wills
and religious requirements.
Wow.
That must be
some kind of record.
They died last night.
You can contact
the funeral home.
They might still have
the bodies.
As you know,
once we do the autopsy,
we're obliged to release --
You had the bodies
destroyed?
What kind of
backwater operation is this?
Hey! Easy.
Forget about it.
No bodies,
no paperwork, right?
Someone once told me
that was a good thing.
The good news still stands.
This case is closed.
Sam and Dean Winchester
are dead.
The Winchester crime spree has
come to a violent end in Iowa,
where they were gunned down.
That should take the heat off.
For now.
Thanks, Jody.
Couldn't have done it
without you.
Anytime you need me
to spill something else,
you give me a call.
Actually,
there is one more thing.
Don't open it.
Even if it starts talking.
Especially
if it starts talking.
When you cross over
Underhill Bridge,
just toss it
in the drink.
If you'll excuse me,
I, um...I got a body
to bury in cement.
Dad, seriously?
Lying to the FBI,
incinerating bodies,
and this stuff?
What the hell is it?
'Cause it sure
isn't blood.
You're right about that,
sweetie.
It's much more than blood.
I can explain.
Don't bother.
It's valente.
Yes, sir, I'm with them now.
Well, unfortunately,
their heads are...
missing.
Huh.
But the actual Winchesters
are dead, yes?
No, sir.
They're in the wind.
So, all that brainpower,
all those resources,
and those two field mice
are still on my to-do list?
I'm sorry, sir.
We could grab some more DNA
and double them again.
I like
where your head's at,
but sometimes
less is more.
Those boys coming back
from the dead again
starts to strain
credulity,
even for the American media,
am I right?
Yes, sir.
I like
a subtler approach.
Back to the vision board
on this one.
Of course.
Just secure the bodies
and get back to the FBI,
and we'll give this Winchester
situation a good think.
Definitely.
Thanks, sir.
And, Valente?
Next time,
call me with a win.
For your sake.
Please don't make me
bib you.
Yes, sir.
I'm craving a latte.
You mind running
across the street
before we hit the trail?
Decaf,
two pumps of vanilla,
and grab yourself whatever
you want -- my treat.
Mr. Roman.
I felt it was time
we met in person.
I'm Crowley.
I run hell.
Yes, yes. Of course.
I agree, 100%.
High time we met.
A token.
You shouldn't have.
I love a muffin.
100% organic baby uvulas --
gluten free.
So considerate.
I'll cut to the chase,
Mr. Roman.
Please. Dick.
Dick.
You and I control
large interests
that I feel strongly
could meld,
to the benefit of all.
You think?
I know.
Straight talk --
we should be friends,
you and I.
Why?
Why in the world
would we be?
Well,
I brought you here...
Dick.
I found the way to open
the door to Purgatory.
To steal every last soul,
you mean.
You and that angel friend
of yours.
Don't roofie me
and call it romance.
I think you've
got me wrong.
Now it's your turn
to listen.
I'd sooner swim through
hot garbage
than shake hands
with a bottom-feeding
mutation like you.
You demons are ugly, lazy,
gold-digging whores.
You're less than humans,
and they're not good
for much
till you dip 'em
in garlic sauce.
I'd never work with you,
Crowley.
In fact, if I wasn't busy
with better things,
I might actively wipe your kind
from the face of the Universe.
And you'd deserve it.
Are we clear?
Keep the muffins.
Are you sure you want to dump
these things?
I'm thinking they might actually
come in handy down the road.
What do you think?
Hey.
What? What is it?
Talk.
Nothing.
Well, that's convincing.
Did monster-us
give you the jeebs, huh?
'Cause I gotta be honest --
I ain't looking in the mirror
for -- for a while myself.
Okay.
You really want to know
what's wrong?
Yeah.
Yeah, you know my motto --
here to help.
"Here to help."
Kind of like
you helped Amy?
Listen, Sam...
Don't --
don't lie to me again.
No, don't even talk to me.
Yeah, I can't.
You know what, Dean?
I can't.
You can't what?
I can't talk to you
right now!
Dean, I can't even be around you
Okay, so --
I think you should just
go on without me.
Go.
All right.
Sorry, Sam.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==