[ Reo Speedwagon's
"Ridin' the Storm Out" plays ]
Who the hell --
Leviathan!
? Ridin' the storm out ?
? waiting for the fallout
? on a full-moon night in
the Rocky Mountain winter ?
? wine bottle's low
stay the hell away
from me.
Your world is whatever
I want it to be, understand?
Leave me alone!
Whoa! Whoa!
You want to know the truth?
You got away.
We got you out, Sammy.
This is real.
You need to see a fella
named Frank Devereaux.
Bobby Singer sent us.
? Watching the full moon
crossing the range ?
You can't stop any of us.
We can't be killed.
These things are smarter
than you.
You don't have a clue
how to kill 'em
or slow 'em down,
and your plan is, what?
Go right at 'em?
Hello, boys.
Years of demons
nipping at your heels,
haven't seen one for months. Wonder why?
We've been busy.
Hunting Leviathan --
yes, I know.
You met that dick yet?
We should be friends,
you and I.
I'd never work with you,
Crowley.
Okay, you sons of bitches.
Let's see what you're up to.
Go! Go!
He's not gonna die.
It's one bullet.
He's gonna be fine
because he's always fine.
So maybe I'm not real,
but I'm not going anywhere, Sam.
His eyes are open.
Bobby?
Hey.
Idjits.
Bobby?
Thank you.
Sure.
You've been here a couple nights
in a row now.
What can I say?
I like the ambience.
Get you anything else?
No, thanks.
Thanks.
Keep safe out there.
Hey, there.
You lost?
What?
- Excuse me...
- Ooh-hoo.
You're looking a little
cabo wabo, there.
No. No, I'm fine.
No. You're not.
I slipped a little special sauce
into your coffee
while you were watching
the skirt.
You do know we're venomous,
right?
Looks like I didn't dose you
quite hard enough.
That's okay.
There's more
where that came from.
That's for the crappy tip.
? Supernatural 7x11 ?
Adventures in Babysitting
Original Air Date on January 6, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Dean, you know, um...
...I wonder if -- if we...
I mean, should we
be telling people?
I mean, people he knew.
How long ago did I give Frank
these numbers?
It's been a few weeks,
right?
What, is he nuts,
or is he just being rude?
Probably both.
Dean, I-I got
to ask you a question.
Unless, of course,
something happened to him.
He can't get to the phone because a
Leviathan ate his face.
Yeah,
also a possibility.
We should go check
on him.
Dean, do you want to call
Bobby's people or not?
W-why is that our job?
Because who else
is gonna do it?
I'm not calling anybody.
If you want to,
you go right ahead.
I don't want to call anybody.
You kidding me?
Well, I'm not getting it.
Hello?
Is Bobby Singer there?
Uh, no.
He's, uh...
I-I-it's not,
but I'm a friend of his.
My dad asked me to call
Bobby Singer specifically.
He's...Not here,
but, look, if you need s--
Who was it?
Just some kid.
For Bobby?
Girl scout cookies?
I think maybe...
Maybe a-a hunter's kid?
I mean, she sounded
pretty scared.
You know, I have a caller I.D.
Maybe we should go find her.
We can check on her.
What about Frank?
Well, Dean, I think we should
go find this girl first.
Sam, Frank's been working
on the numbers
that Bobby spent
his last breath on,
and you want to
back-burner that?
Fine. You go
check out girl scout.
I'll find Frank.
Fine. But you know what?
On one condition --
if Frank is just
spinning his wheels,
then you bail out on crazy
and come meet me.
And thanks for drinking
my entire beer.
I didn't touch your beer.
Mine's right there.
You probably drank it
without noticing.
Right.
Hello?
Um, we...spoke
on the phone earlier?
Hi.
Uh...I'm Sam.
You sounded like
you needed help,
and I was in the area.
How'd you find me?
Your dad is in
Bobby's address book.
So where is he?
Bobby?
He, uh...
He's passed away.
Look, um --
Krissy.
I get it.
You don't let strangers in.
But if your dad said
you could trust Bobby,
then you can
trust me, too.
Just so you know,
911's on speed-dial.
One button.
Yeah, sure.
Note taken.
So...
...you're a salesman,
too?
Yep.
So your dad's on the road
right now?
Been gone a while?
He usually calls
every night.
How long has it been?
Five days.
It's just you and him,
huh?
I know how that is.
Look, um...
Sometimes on the road,
crap happens.
So I'll help you
track him down.
Really?
'Course.
Did he happen to say
where he was going?
Said he had a couple leads
near Dodge City.
And does he have a desk
or something
where he keeps his stuff?
Do you mind
making some coffee?
Thanks.
Krissy.
Hey, listen, so I think I got
an idea where to start.
So I'm gonna go.
Um...Can I borrow this?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Here.
Here's a number,
in case you don't hear from me
in the next couple days.
Don't worry.
I promise I'll check in.
Don't say that.
That's what my dad said.
This can't be good.
Well...Hi.
Frank...
We're amongst
friends here.
Okay, acquaintances.
That's just what a Leviathan
would say.
Frank.
I'm not a Leviathan.
Oh, sure.
You're not a Leviathan.
Dick Roman's
not a Leviathan.
Gwyneth Paltrow
is not a Leviathan.
Yeah?
Trust me.
Okay.
You know what, Frank?
I think you've been doing
a little too much research.
They're anywhere, anyone.
Who's to say
this ain't the day
they come for old Frank
who knew too much?
They bleed black goo,
right?
You want to see
what I bleed?
Oh! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Let's take the guns
out of it, okay?
Okay.
See?
Red-blooded American.
Now...
Your turn.
Oh! Whoa.
Look, I'm obviously not --
Fair's fair, douchebag.
Yeah.
I'm glad we could share
that together.
Grab your gun,
come with me.
For God's sake,
don't make any noise.
Why the downsize?
You!
"Hey, Frank, go dig up some dirt
on Richard Roman."
That night, I was burned off
every I.P. I had.
Ears on my phones,
eyes on my house...
Wait -- Dick's got people
watching you?
Do I look like I know?
You think it's easy to see
this deep into what's real
and also be bipolar
with delusional ideation?
There is no pill for
my situation, sweetiepop,
so, yeah, best guess --
the bigmouths are onto me.
Next question.
All right. Well, what's the word
on the bigmouths?
Their tentacles are everywhere.
I-I'm looking at bankers,
military high-ups...
This is why
you didn't call me back.
Hey, cut me some slack.
You called me
like four days ago.
I called you
four weeks ago, Frank.
What? No.
Really?
Days, weeks --
quit busting my chops.
What, are you kidding me?
You cool your heels,
Buster Brown.
Frank, I paid you 15 grand
for this.
- Yeah, I get that --
- No, you don't get that!
Dick Roman is every card
in my hit deck.
You understand that?
Those numbers, they got
something to do with him, okay?
Bobby died
for those numbers.
Look,
I'm sorry about Bobby.
I really am.
You know, this one
time, we were in Fresno,
and we got stuck --
No. No, no, no.
I'm not gonna play
"this one time with Bobby" crap,
all right?
I'm not gonna get all warm
and fuzzy
with somebody else
who barely knew him.
Just trying to make
friendly conversation.
This is not a friendship, Frank.
I'm paying you!
Hey.
You know what you need?
A little LSD,
a little shiatsu --
I'm out of here.
Hey, you want to know
what those numbers are?
Bupkes.
They're not lottery numbers,
license --
I know that, Frank.
Thank you.
Which leaves us
little else to do
but probability generate.
Come again?
You run most
reasonable possibilities
for a levi-related
five-digit number
written by a dying drunk,
you come up flat.
Know what you start
to wonder?
"Hey, maybe I'm missing
a number."
Well, how do you figure?
Oh, I don't know.
Because Bobby was dying
of brain trauma.
I just had a tickle
there was a reason
nothing was popping out
at us,
so I set up a program
to run possibilities
for six numbers,
seven, eight.
But good news.
Good news.
Never had to go past six,
because this...
...my little lamb,
is coordinates.
Are you sure?
To what?
A field in Wisconsin.
No.
No, Bobby didn't
give us coordinates
to some patch of weeds
in cheeseville.
No, he gave you coordinates
to a parcel
recently purchased
by Willman, Inc.,
a subsidiary of...
...Richard Roman
Enterprises.
So what do we do?
Stay away.
Or, if we're stupid...
We go there
and set up surveillance.
Matthew Havlena --
found in a ditch
off the interstate.
Cause of death?
Missing five pints of blood
can't have helped.
Puncture wounds --
femoral arteries
and carotid.
So, what?
Some kind of animal attack?
Or a vampire.
Huh. That...usually gets
at least a chuckle.
Find Frank?
- Yeah. Those numbers?
- Coordinates.
Dick bought some land.
We're headed there now.
Wait, wait, wait.
- You're just gonna drive right up to --
- Relax.
It's a field,
not the death star.
Dick's at
a T.E.D. Conference.
It's all over
The Huffington Post.
Wait, wait, wait.
Since when do you read?
Know your enemy, Sam.
What's going on
with the girl?
I don't think she even knows
her dad's in the life.
So far, I got three
missing truckers
and one blood-free body.
Good times.
All right, well,
keep me posted.
Got the equipment arranged.
Come and get your costume on.
We can scoot.
"Costume"?
What?
What the hell's so special
about this place?
I love a mystery.
Now get up
in that cherry picker
and act like
you're fixing something.
I don't know how
to drive that thing.
You think I do?
Well, why do I got to be
the sap that --
this one says "manager."
That one says "technician."
Sometime this month?
Yah!
Whoo!
Come on down, Tarzan!
What?!
We need to move.
They got this place
wired up the wazoo.
They're watching us
right now?
Nah, nah, they're just watching
Cheech and Ed from ma bell.
You know, it's gonna be
a little difficult
to set up surveillance
if there's,
uh, surveillance
everywhere.
Right. So we need to tap
into theirs instead.
All right, now what?
You look horrific.
When was the last time
you really slept a night?
Let's just work,
all right?
This is it.
We watch the screens.
I can take
the first shift.
You're no use
if you can't even...
Keep your eyes open.
Dean, hey.
So I think this guy
was hunting a Vetala.
Dad took one down
back in the day.
Silver knife to the heart,
twist, they're done.
He says they're maladjusted
loner types --
like to knock a guy out,
drag him home, feed slow.
So, if Krissy's dad
got grabbed,
there's a chance
he might still be alive.
It'd be nice to get this girl's
dad back home to her, you know?
All right,
I could use your help.
Call me.
Excuse me.
Your manager said that you might
be able to help me.
Sure.
What can I do for you?
You ever see this man?
I...might have served him
the other day.
I think he may have
gone to...
talk to that girl
out there.
Thanks.
Hey!
Can I talk to you
for a second, uh...
Sally?
You ever see this man?
You sure?
It's not safe here.
Somewhere private.
Something's happening
around here.
I'm afraid I'll be next.
Tell me what you saw.
I don't know what I saw.
Sally, run!
Ohh!
How long was I out?
'Bout 36 hours.
What?
Why didn't you wake me?
Not your butler.
Come see this.
What?
This is where
it gets good.
Frank,
you need to get out more.
Not that.
Check out Sarah Palin.
Who is she?
Amanda Willer.
Surprise, surprise --
works for Richard Roman.
What was she doing?
Being a naughty,
bossy little girl.
Well, I hate to ask for that
in the non-porno version.
They're surveying.
They're getting ready
to build something.
- Build what?
- Exactly.
"What?"
No idea.
Well,
how do we find out?
We watch.
Patience, grasshopper.
Yeah, patience and me
aren't exactly on terms.
Well, then go out
and kill something
or whatever you kids do
to blow off steam.
What, you don't like
my suggestion?
I don't think
you're in a position
to be giving suggestions,
all right?
I think you're one tinfoil hat
away from a rubber room.
Did I mention
you look awful?
Yes.
Maybe because
somebody I cared about
just got shot in the head.
And this is like shoving a rock
up a hill.
And -- screw you.
Here's my advice
you didn't ask for -- quit.
What?!
You want to keep going?
I want Dick Roman
on a spit.
But you're gonna drive yourself
into the ground first.
Good plan.
I'm not gonna quit.
It's not even an option.
I'm not gonna walk out
on my brother.
Okay, then, fine.
Do what I did.
- What?
- Go native?
Stock up on C rations?
No, cupcake.
What I did when I was 26
and came home to find my wife
and two kids
gutted on the floor.
Decide to be fine till the end
of the week.
Make yourself smile
because you're alive
and that's your job.
Then do it again
the next week.
So fake it?
I call it
being professional.
Do it right,
with a smile,
or don't do it.
Dean, hey.
So I think this guy
was hunting a Vetala.
Dad took one down
back in the day.
No, no, no.
Sam, that's not right.
What's the guff?
...says they're maladjusted
loner types --
like to knock a guy out,
drag him home --
Sam.
No. Who's this?
Who's this?
Sam told me to call
if I didn't hear anything
back from him.
That ringing
in your ears --
it's from the venom.
Venom?
Yeah.
They hit you with some kind
of knockout juice.
You seem to be handling this
pretty well.
Yeah. Well, um...
I was out there
looking for you.
Lee Chambers?
I'm a friend
of Bobby Singer's.
Krissy called.
She -- she's fine.
She is.
She's just worried about you.
So how do we
get out of here?
They'll be back
pretty quick here.
Just the two of them?
Yeah, they're a tag team.
One of them
knocks you out.
The other one dumps your rig
or your ride
or whatever
miles down the road.
It's a pretty nice system
they got.
They've been draining you.
Yeah.
They tap you three, four times,
you're dead.
And let me tell you
You can't see...
You can't walk.
I thought they'd kill me
right off,
but they don't have to.
They got nothing
to worry about.
How many times
they fed on you?
Three.
Did Sam tell you
where he was going?
That's what I'm trying
to figure out.
What did you tell him?
Uh...He checked
my dad's room.
There?
Yeah.
Look,
I really don't have time
to hold your hand here,
so --
What are you saying?
I'm saying go wait
in the living room.
Your dad may not
want you to know
every single thing
about him.
Where is it?
You mean everything about
the job my dad was working?
Sam said you didn't know.
Sam seemed competent,
so I figured, fine --
I'll do what my dad
always tells me to.
"Be a regular kid,
don't say anything,
"stay out of
the line of fire.
Let the adults
work it out."
So much for that.
All right.
Hand it over.
Okay? I have had
a long, long week.
All right, I get it.
You're a tough kid.
But I'm trying to get Sam
and your dad back.
My dad left,
and he didn't come back.
Sam left,
I give you the info, you leave,
you don't come back.
I'm coming back.
I'm coming with you.
N-no. No.
Hell, no.
I'm coming!
Or you're not going.
Ow!
Now hand it over.
I can't.
I burned it.
You what?
But lucky for you,
I memorized it all first.
Hey, I have a question.
All right,
here's the deal.
I'm a fun guy.
I'm actually awesome.
Okay?
But right now,
I'm not in the mood.
I'm neck deep
in some serious crap,
and if this wasn't
an emergency,
I would drop your ass off
at the nearest mall.
What serious crap?
Revenge crap, all right?
Now shut up.
Eat a cookie or something.
One thing doesn't
make sense, though.
My dad's
a pretty great hunter,
and your brother's the size
of a car, so...
So how'd this thing
get 'em both?
Vetalas usually hunt
in pairs.
Sam and your dad
both assumed
it was one thing
hunting solo.
Why'd they think that?
Because they had
the wrong info.
Or, best available.
Our dad took down a loner
years ago.
Sam has his journal.
Your dad must've been going
on the same facts.
And you know different
'cause...?
Because I hunted one
that turned out to be two
a couple years back.
And you never told Sam?
Wow, thanks.
How 'bout sharing that
with the rest of the class
so we don't all
get killed?
Sam was away at Stanford,
smartass.
Sam went to college?
I thought you said your dad
was a hunter.
He was.
We were.
Sam quit,
went to college.
You could, too, you know --
go to college.
Be a hunter/pediatrician.
Hunter day
at the all-you-can-eat.
How's everyone feeling?
Good?
Strong silent.
Fine.
I don't need much entertainment
with my meal.
Hey, Sally,
uh, did I tell you
about the Vetalas
I took down in Utah?
Yeah.
You remind me of them.
Except they were
so much...younger.
I tied 'em up.
Not because I had to.
More so...
I could take my time.
- You're lying.
- No.
I just want you to know
how much I enjoyed cutting up your sisters.
Shut up!
Aah! Ohh!
You ever actually work
with your dad?
Sure. 'Course.
No, I mean work,
not shoot cans in the woods.
I mean,
I help all the time.
So, no.
Well, right about now,
your stomach should be
pretty knotted up.
Not really.
Look, maybe this was a lot
harder for you
when you were my age.
Oh, you think
you're a good actress.
You're not.
What are you
talking about?
Well,
I hate to break it to you,
but it's all over your face --
you're scared.
Quit treating me
like I'm some girl.
I've been prepping for this
my entire life.
Training's one thing.
Doing --
whole nother beast.
Wow. You really
scared me straight.
Thanks, Dean.
Why is that waitress
getting into that truck?
I'm not explaining
the R-rated crap to you.
The front of the truck,
not the back, Dean.
All right.
What century is this?
No one fist-bumps
anymore.
Come on. Give it up.
Good work.
You're a dweeb.
What the hell?
I got an idea.
How 'bout you stay here?
Oh, you jackass.
Yeah, well,
I'm the jackass
who ain't bringing a kid
in there, period.
Why?
I can do everything
you can do.
I'll bring them back.
Trust me.
Please,
they're probably dead.
You don't know that.
It's been days.
Probably just
a pile of meat.
I've seen it.
People die, Dean.
I watched my mom
get torn to shreds.
Let me go in there
and kill them.
No.
Sorry.
You're such a hypocrite.
How come you get to do it
and I don't?
Because I'm the grown-up!
Give it to me.
What?
Your lock pick.
I will frisk you.
Thank you.
Good thing we picked up
a new one.
This one's
about tapped out.
You want to
finish him together?
Sure.
Not so fast.
Dad, hold on --
I got you!
Krissy, no!
Let her go...
Or little miss sunshine here
gets it.
What were you thinking,
bringing her here?
Now drop the knife!
She's just a child.
Let her go.
Yeah, I don't think
we'll be letting anyone go.
Daddy...
It's okay, baby.
Everything's
gonna be fine.
All right.
Enough with the family bonding.
It's time for you
to shut up.
Daddy, no!
Dean!
He can't help you.
No one can.
I guess I'll have
to help myself, then.
Bad actress, huh?
Yeah, I take it back.
Yeah, I was hoping
you'd stop by.
I wanted to thank you.
It's no problem.
No, you saved my life.
Krissy's, too.
Actually, uh
she kind of saved ours.
Don't thank us.
Quit.
Your daughter's
14 years old.
She's already a hunter
with a kill under her belt.
I'm not trying
to be a dick,
but what do you think that does
to her life span?
She could still be
a regular kid.
You know,
I got into this for a reason.
I know.
Your family.
That's the same reason
you should get out now.
I can't.
You ever know anyone
who left the life?
No.
They all get killed first.
Well, uh...
We should probably
let you get some rest.
Yeah.
Dean!
Thanks for saying bye,
asshat.
Oh, what?
Now you're sentimental?
No.
Just wanted to tell you
that you're kind of amusing
for an old man.
How'd you get out
of them cuffs, anyway?
Girl's got to have
her secrets.
Bobby pin.
You know, you could've
gotten yourself killed.
I saved your bacon.
My point stands.
But yes.
So...
Guess I'm retiring --
one and done.
Really?
How you feel about that?
Who knows?
Maybe I'll go to Stanford
like Sam.
We're so lame.
Yeah, we are.
Take care of yourself.
You know what?
Good for them.
Yeah.
It's nice to walk away
from someone
and feel like
they could be okay.
How about you? How you doing?
You all right?
No.
I'm definitely not.
But, you know,
I mean, I think, maybe...
I just want to work.
Should I even ask?
I'm fine.
"Fine," meaning...?
You're right.
We should just...
Work, right?
And figure out a way
to kick Dick Roman's ass.
Well, hey, we are
the professionals.
[ Traffic's
"Dear Mr. Fantasy" plays ]
? Dear Mr. Fantasy,
play us a tune ?
? something to make us
all happy ?
? do anything ?
? take us out of this gloom ?
? sing a song, play guitar ?
? make it snappy ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==