Sam:
These are curse boxes.
They're supposed to keep
the evil mojo in, right?
Kind of like the pandora deal?
Yeah.
They're built to contain
the power of the cursed object.
Sam, Frank's been
working on the numbers
that Bobby spent
his last breath on.
It's coordinates.
To what?
A field in Wisconsin.
Recently purchased
by Willman, Inc.,
a subsidiary of...
If you want to win,
then you got to be the shark.
And a shark's got to eat.
...Richard Roman
Enterprises.
They're getting ready
to build something.
- Build what?
- Exactly. What?
Sam: I'm a grade-a freak.
But I'm managing it.
Something's definitely
different now, isn't it?
You let me in.
Shut up.
He said "shut up" to me.
So you think you can use
your little tricks
to banish me again,
like that? No.
I do believe I've got you,
bunk buddy.
No Irina again.
Guess she's too famous for us.
No, she just...
[European accent]
Vants to be alone.
[ Both chuckle ]
[ Door closes ]
Irina. A little late
for practice, no?
Never too late.
Practice
makes perfect...
If you have
the talent.
[ Door opens ]
[ Tchaikovsky's "Swan's Theme"
plays ]
? Supernatural 7x16 ?
Out With the Old
Original Air Date on March 16, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
So, Dick's funding
an archaeological dig?
Well, unless Dick's
actually digging himself,
I'm not sure I know
what to do with that, Frank.
Or the factory
in Saudi Arabia,
or the fishery
in Jakarta.
None of this
is helping, Frank.
Explain how Western to Southeast
Asia is too wide a net.
You know, I could be
in Tromso right now.
Zero Leviathan activity
in tromso.
Where the hell
is Tromso?
Norway, you moron.
By the way, they opened
another Biggerson in Butte.
Yeah, well,
we're not in Montana.
Oh, you know where Butte is.
That's encouraging.
So, where are you?
We're in Oregon.
No.
I got nothing
in Oregon.
Wisconsin, Frank.
What about it?
The coordinates --
Bobby's coordinates.
Bobby...
Oh! Right.
Yeah, no. I got nothing.
I got no activity.
Well, work on it.
Hey. When did you
become the boss of me?
You don't like
what I'm doing,
you can stick it
right up your Montana.
All right, all right, all right.
Take it easy, Frank.
Oh, and another thing --
[ Beep ]
Frank? Hello?
Fr--
he's a crazy
son of a bitch.
Frank?
You know, having a cranky
total paranoid
as your go-to guy --
that's -- it's...
I don't know
what it is.
What, are you going for,
like, the Guinness record
of caffeine consumption?
That's like your fifth
this morning.
Yeah, well,
every time I close my eyes,
Lucifer is yelling
into my head.
It's like I let him in once,
now I can't get rid of him.
You know
he's not actually...
Yeah.
Yeah, no. I know.
Uh, try telling that to the
volume control inside my brain.
Well, did you try
the hand thing?
Yeah.
Anyway, long as I'm awake,
check it out.
They're saying drugs,
but read between the lines.
Sounds like she danced
her own feet off.
Might be
our kind of thing.
Dancers.
They are toe shoes
full of crazy.
[ Chuckles ]
You -- and you
would know this how?
I saw "Black Swan."
Twice.
Hot tutu-on-tutu action?
Come on, Sam.
What's wrong with you?
Wow.
The depths of your
[Sighs]
Anyway, it's in Portland,
a couple hours away.
What do you think?
Yeah, dancers. Why not?
Maybe you'll get some sleep
on the way.
[ Scoffs ]
Yeah, maybe.
[ Engine rumbling ]
[ Tires screech ]
So, the usual --
no emf, no sulfur, no hex junk.
If there's no more dancers
to interview on this trip,
it could be a bust.
Although I hear they have
good coffee in Portland.
Dude, that's Seattle.
Oh, let's just
get the drill over with.
[ Clears throat ]
Hi.
Yeah?
Uh, we'd like to see
the crime-scene photos from
the Irina Koganzon case, please.
And you would be...
Oh.
[ Clears throat ]
Give me a minute.
Take your time.
No, you can't
touch those, honey.
Those are
for daddy's work.
Daddy...
I have to go pee.
Sweetie, you know
where the little girls' room is.
Yeah,
I'd call that weird.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
[ Whispering continues ]
[ Crackling ]
Hey, there.
How you doing?
Okay. What can I do
for you fellas?
Well, we need to see
the shoes
that were involved
in the ballet dancer's death.
Didn't figure that would be
an FBI deal.
But sure.
Yeah, right here.
Damn it, Tracy.
Who's Tracy?
My daughter.
She loves ballet.
Hey,
take those shoes off.
Dean, get the shoes!
I'm trying!
[ Both grunting ]
Come on, Dean!
I'm trying!
I got it!
I got it.
Okay.
[ Both breathing heavily ]
I'm going with
cursed object.
You think?!
You okay?
[ Police radio chatter ]
Next stop --
out with the old.
I suppose it's too much
to hope that these shoes
are the only thing in that store
that we have to worry about.
Oh, what a dreamer
you are.
[ Police radio chatter ]
Dean: Hey.
Didn't we put those
in the trunk?
H-how did they --
Cursed object, Sam.
Do they...Look like they're...
Your size?
Shut up.
Wait, a-are you --
getting the strong urge
to Prince Siegfried myself
into oblivion?
Yes.
You really did see
"Black Swan."
Well, it was nice
seeing you, Mr. Marshall.
Please call me if you have
any questions about the offer.
I'll let you know.
I don't think
he's gonna sell.
Thinking is not
your strong suit, George.
George?
The door.
Dean: Hello?
Hey, did you
sell these?
Uh, yeah.
Where did you
get them?
Uh, m-my m-mother had them
in that box.
I don't understand.
What's happening?
[ Soft piano music plays,
indistinct whispering ]
This, in here?
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Geez!
[ Music, whispering stop ]
[ Sighs ]
You okay there,
Baryshnikov?
Yeah.
Yeah,
I'm "pas de done."
Scott: Okay, if it's not
too much trouble,
do you mind telling me, uh,
what's -- what's going on?
What's your name?
Uh, Scott --
uh, Scott Freeman.
You said these were
your mother's?
Where'd she get them?
I don't know.
I found them in the back.
I got it.
Now, where
is your mother?
Well, she's, uh...
She passed away
last week.
[ Sighs ]
I'm sorry to hear that.
Scott, listen.
These shoes...
Just some personal stuff
she collected.
I'm trying to get rid
of it all.
All?
Is there more like this?
Dean: Sam.
Scott, what was
in those boxes?
[ Knife chopping ]
[ Kettle whistles ]
[ Indistinct whispering ]
[ Sizzling ]
Okay, what the hell
kind of FBI guys are you?
The kind that are trying to fix
the mess you started.
Now where'd your mom
get these?
I don't know.
I found them in her safe.
Sam: Did it ever occur to you
that these things
might be locked in that safe
for a reason?
No, I just thought
it was some of the junk
that she had collected
over the years.
Like, I knew she was into
some weird stuff,
but I never thought that
she would be, like --
Yeah, well,
think again, okay?
'Cause this "junk"
is killing people.
What? Like, how can that be?
Look, Scott.
We're gonna need to know exactly
what you sold out of that safe
and names and addresses
of who you sold it to.
All right,
what do we got?
She bought
a tea kettle.
Tea kettle?
Yeah.
Hey, with enough curse mojo,
you can turn a freaking pencil
into a weapon
of mass destruction.
Good times.
[ Clattering ]
Better call this in.
Hello, yeah.
I'd like to report an accident
at 23 Gorham Road.
My name?
Uh...
Bruce Hornsby.
All right.
Who's next on the list?
[ Clears throat ]
We got a, uh, gramophone
sold to Brenda Gluck,
413 River Street,
and a vintage
gentlemen's magazine
sold to Peter Yankit,
27 Johnson Lane.
Really?
Yeah.
All right,
we'd better split up.
Why don't you
take the gramophone?
I'll handle
the old rag.
I wouldn't really "handle" it
if I were you.
Remember those shoes?
Yeah,
how could I forget?
You know, I wonder
how old porn kills you.
[ Scoffs ] Pretty sure
you don't want to know.
Yeah, you're probably right.
All right. Let's do this.
Yep.
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Static ]
[ Up-tempo piano music playing ]
I'm gonna run these upstairs.
Be right back.
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Music continues ]
Deep voice:
Psst. Timmy. Timmy.
Psh-wsh-wsh-wsh-wsh...
Psst. Timmy.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
Timmy.
[ Bicycle bell rings ]
[ Music continues ]
Aaah!
Where's the gramophone?
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hey. That's mine.
[ Sighs ]
Kid, this would be
a really good time
for a lesson
in gratitude.
Lucky for you,
I'm too tired.
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Beep ]
Hey.
Dean: Hey.
Got the porn.
Just in time, too.
What was he doing?
Uh, like you said,
you don't want to know.
Where you at?
I just got
the gramophone.
I'm across town.
I'll head your way.
[ Beep ]
So my mom wasn't just
some whack job.
All this stuff is real?
Yep.
Well, now I-I really
feel like crap.
How come?
Well I kept pushing her
to sell the store.
She kept saying no,
and I kept pushing her,
you know, telling her
how much money she'd make.
You think
you changed her mind?
I don't know.
You know, this real-estate lady
kept coming around,
and then one day,
just like that, mom says okay.
Then she had
that accident,
never even
got to enjoy the money.
How soon after?
The next day.
The n--
how did she die?
Car crash.
You know, I keep thinking,
if I hadn't pushed her, then...
Hey, a little tip.
Feeling guilty
ain't gonna bring 'em back.
Best you can do
is live your life
the way that you think
would make her proud.
Or at least not
embarrass the crap out of her.
[ Sighs ]
Oh, uh...
You know
the drill, right?
Don't touch anything
in those boxes.
In fact, don't even
go near the safe.
Once we get it all boxed up,
we'll get a U-Haul
and get everything out of here.
Believe me, I --
I got it.
You know, Mr. Marshall,
the block won't be the same.
Most of your neighbors
have already sold.
Now, I've prepared
an analysis report for you.
George?
Not this one, George.
Mr. Marshall's.
[ Sighs ]
[ Laughs ]
Hard to find good help
these days.
Anyway, as you can see,
our offer is more than generous.
Seems that way.
And with
that generous offer,
you can pretty much go wherever
and do whatever you please.
You can
get on with your life.
You know, Miss Bicklebee,
I came here tonight
with every intention
of selling.
But what you just said,
about getting on with my life --
that store is my life.
I can't sell.
Look, we all feel
attached to our past,
but it's the future that's
the real adventure, and --
[ chuckling ]
Sorry, not sellin'.
And I ain't buyin' that crap
either, lady.
Well, if that's your decision,
what can I say?
I wish you the best of luck
with the rest of your life...
What little there is
left of it.
[ Crackling ]
See?
As promised...
On the dotted line.
What?
Well...
Maybe you were a little
quick on the trigger?
First the woman at
the antique shop, and now this.
I mean, you know
that Mr. Roman
doesn't like us calling
attention to ourselves...
So, what should I do
with the body?
There.
That's the attitude.
Okay.
Take Mr. Marshall
and his stinky cigar home
and put them in bed.
Oh. And, George?
Make sure
the cigar is lit.
There goes Mr. Marshall.
Should've quit smoking.
Can be hazardous
to your health.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Coughs ]
Do you know
how many assistants I've had
since taking this body,
George?
Maybe three?
Five.
I leave it to your imagination
what happened to the first four.
Was something wrong
with the brew?
You tell me.
What did I ask for?
A hot cup of coffee.
That's right.
Got the coffee part.
But did I say "hot,"
or, I don't know,
"tepid"?
Four, George.
Just saying.
So go to that nice barista
on Main
and get me a Grande non-fat
no-whip white mocha,
one pump sugar-free,
double-shot espresso, 'kay?
Sure.
Um, t-that's
all the way across town.
I won't be back till 9:00.
Okay. See you at 8:45.
[ Rock music plays ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Radio shuts off ]
Hey, what's up?
I'm on my way.
Yeah, not sure we're taking
the safe out of town just yet.
[ Coffee pours ]
Thanks.
Um, so, it turns out
that mama hoarder
didn't just die
and leave the store to Scott.
She didn't?
No, listen to this.
The lady spends 40 years trying
to keep that place, right?
Then one day
she wakes up and sells.
Next day,
drives her car off a cliff.
[ Yawning ] So, uh...
What, you think
somebody cut her brakes
or something?
No, I think the world is
full of hilarious coincidences.
Oh, and
there's this new company --
never even tasted
real estate,
just gobbled up
a huge chunk of Main Street.
Now, I could be
off the deep end here,
but doesn't that
seem weird to you?
Sam?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Yeah,
sounds good. Keep me posted.
Sounds good?
Are you all right?
Sleep deprivation
is an "enhanced interrogation
technique"?
Yeah.
[ Sighs ]
Trust me, it's torture.
[ Beep ]
Son of a bitch.
[ Sighs ]
[ Ringing ]
This better be good.
Frank, hey, I don't mean to
double-dip in your crazy sauce.
No offense.
None taken, fudge pop.
But I think
I found something.
My silence
is your cue, Dean.
All right, so,
there's this new company
that's buying up a whole bunch
of mom-'n'-pops in Portland,
but I hit a firewall when
I tried to access its site.
Think you can crack it?
Can a dog play poker?
I don't...
The answer is yes.
What's the company name?
Uh, Geothrive, Inc.
[ Tires screech ]
[ Horn honks ]
[ Horn blares ]
[ Tires screech ]
Wait!
I said one pump sugar-free,
not two.
Extra pump's
on the house.
That's very nice, but my boss
is gonna be able to tell, okay,
so please
just make me a new one.
[ Sighs ]
There's people in line,
and I'm here all alone, so...
Enjoy the free pump.
How 'bout
make me a new one?
How 'bout you eat me?
Don't tempt me.
You're lucky I'm late.
So lucky.
Next.
Can I get a, uh,
a-a triple red-eye, please?
It's your funeral.
[ Sighs ]
Joyce: What are you
talking about, George?
Where's my coffee?
I am seriously
not kidding.
And you're sure
it's him?
Of course I'm sure.
Sam Winchester
is going into
that antique shop
we just bought.
Y-you think
they're here for us?
No. Trust me.
If the Winchesters were here
for us, we'd know.
I am going to enjoy this.
Enjoy?
Enjoy what, George?
Well...Eating him is pretty much
what I was thinking.
What?!
No!
No?
Come back to the office.
Now.
We have a chain of command
here, George.
You see a Winchester,
you don't eat him.
You tell me,
and I eat him.
What do you think,
I'm gonna tell Dick,
"I think he ate him,
but I didn't see it"?
What, I'm supposed to
vouch for you, George?
Like you're not one dumb move
away from a bibbing already?
Come on.
But I --
Oh, no!
- But --
- No!
Hoo!
[ Scoffs ]
Ugh!
Two pumps.
Really, George?
[ Sighs ]
Frank,
tell me you got something.
No, I'm calling with
the Lakers-Celtics score.
What?
'Course I got something.
I figured out
why you hit that firewall.
My silence
is your cue, Frank.
[ Chuckling ]
Oh, touch?.
So, you were trying to access
the Geothrive internal site,
and the reason
why you couldn't
is 'cause
if you dig down deep,
it's all Dick.
Yeah, well,
that'd be helpful
if you didn't say that
about everything.
Yeah, except I'm operating
on hard fact now, wise-ass.
So you're tellin' me that
Geothrive is part of Roman, Inc.?
It's a conglomerate within a
subsidiary within a conglomerate.
It's all
tied together, Dean.
So, what, Leviathans
are Walmart-ing mom-'n'-pops?
And bingo was his name-o.
Ahh!
So, we've got a big ol' field
in Wisconsin
and a bunch of friggin' shops
in Portland?
What the hell
are they up to?
Beats me.
All I know is it's corporate
and smelly as the day is long.
If I were you,
I'd get out of Dodge, pronto.
People are dying here,
Frank.
Sure, every second.
Check the obesity stats.
That town
ain't nothin' special.
Well, we're not
done here, okay,
and, hey, we might
get some answers.
Fine.
Call me
if you don't die.
[ Beep ]
So?
Well, that'll work.
Um, how's it going?
[ Inhales sharply ] I just
got off the phone with Frank.
Apparently, we have a bit of
a Leviathan issue in this town.
Leviathan, here?
Yeah.
We're lookin' at a big, old
giant nesting doll of Dick,
as far
as property sales go.
Hey, you hearing me?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry.
Okay, you know what?
Enough with the insomnia crap.
All right, Pacino?
You need to crash.
I'll keep working. You find a motel
and get some sleep. Okay?
It doesn't matter
what I do, Dean.
Lucifer will not
shut up.
Even now?
He's singing
"Stairway to Heaven" right now.
Good song.
Not 50 times in a row.
Hm.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Hey, Scott.
Please, Sam.
Y-you got to help me.
What's happening?
I looked in
one of my mom's old mirrors,
and now I want to rip
my face off!
I think it was cursed.
All right, hold tight.
We're on our way.
Let me guess.
He touched something
he was not supposed to.
'Course he did.
[ Groans ]
Was, uh...
Was that okay?
Well, not exactly
Oscar-worthy, but...
...I was convinced.
Not that it matters,
because you don't have
any more lines.
Now what?
[ Sighs ]
Now we wait for meal service.
So...
One more body we're gonna
have to spirity, huh?
Actually, no.
As you so helpfully
pointed out earlier,
Dick doesn't like
making the papers.
Right,
so what's the plan?
Well, we can't have Scott here
running his mouth.
Loose lips,
yada, yada, yada.
We will kill him.
But that doesn't mean anyone
ever has to notice he's dead.
Pack your bags,
Georgie.
You are turning into
one Scott Freeman
for the next, oh,
30-some-odd years.
Right, Scotty?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Chuckles, gasps ]
[ Bells jingle ]
[ Door slams ]
So much
for the cursed mirror.
Sam and Dean.
It is such a pleasure
to make your acquaintances.
Now, just so you can
put names to the faces
that will be eating you,
I'm Joyce,
and this is my assistant,
George.
Dean:
Oh, you're the --
you're the lady
from the real-estate signs.
Yes.
You like my photo?
Oh, you might want to lay off
the whitening strips.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, Dean.
I am gonna enjoy
picking you out of my teeth.
There's a bucket of that stuff
that you love throwing at us
right there.
Dunk me,
before she sees.
Joyce: Agh!
Ugh!
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Gurgling ]
The sword.
The sword!
[ Gasps ]
Thanks.
[ Sighs ]
Okay, I get that these things
mean business, you know,
but I can't just, like,
uproot my life.
[ Sighs ]
Sure you can.
It's not as hard
as you'd think.
Look, Scott.
These big mouths don't like
to leave loose ends.
So don't you look back
till you get someplace
where you don't speak
the language.
All right. I'm going.
Hey, thank you,
I guess.
Don't mention it.
[ Bells jingle ]
[ Door closes ]
One minute.
That's how long you have to
explain to us why you helped us.
Because I am dying to know
what that bitch tastes like.
Wait, let me get this straight.
You want to eat your boss?
You got a better way
to make her stay dead?
So, what? So now
you're on our side or something?
Yeah.
No.
But if Joyce is alive,
then I spend the rest of my life
cleaning her messes.
Or worse, I get eaten.
Or bibbed.
[ Shudders ]
So, thanks...
for chopping
her head off for me.
Taking her on solo -- yikes.
[ Chuckles ]
So, really, thanks
for the assist there.
And, of course,
you're welcome...
For saving you...
Before she ripped into your ass
like a Christmas present.
[ Clicks tongue ]
Win-win, right?
So [Clears throat]
How 'bout that head?
Yeah, not gonna happen,
Georgie.
Now...
What the hell is Dick Roman
building in Wisconsin?
I don't know.
I barely know
where Wisconsin is.
I'm a West-Coast
representative.
You gonna
keep killing people
who don't sign
on the dotted line?
All right,
take it easy.
Mmm.
Killing people
isn't part of the agenda.
Joyce just kept
getting impatient.
You got nothing to worry about
with me.
Don't you get it?
You guys are freaking out
about the wrong thing.
Oh, you think?
A couple
of real-estate deals?
Come on.
Big picture, guys.
Y-you think
it's just here?
It's everywhere.
And it's a lot more ambitious
than this little project.
My advice -- keep your heads
down and stay down.
Listen to me,
you gooey son of a bitch.
You're gonna tell us
what you're building here,
or I'm gonna wash
your mouth out with soap.
Well, I was hoping
we could play nice.
But if you must know...
...it's going to be
a research center.
Research for what?
Disease.
This, gentlemen, is where
we are going to cure cancer.
Wait. That doesn't
make any sense.
I mean, why would Dick Roman
want to cure cancer?
'Cause we're only here
to help.
[ Sighs ]
Monsters cure cancer.
A sentence
I never thought I'd say.
Why does it
make me so nervous?
Yeah, I hear you.
So, what do we do now?
You are gonna
sleep on it --
all the way to Frank's.
Capiche?
I wish I could.
Did you get any sleep
last night?
Yeah.
Yeah. A little.
I-I don't know.
Well, we'll find you
a soft-rock station.
Always knocks you
right out.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Creedence Clearwater Revival's
"Bad Moon Rising" plays ]
? I see a bad moon rising
? I see trouble on the way
? I see
earthquakes and lightning ?
? I see a bad time today
? don't go 'round tonight
? well, it's bound
to take your life ?
? there's a bad moon
on the rise ?
? I hear hurricanes a-blowin'
Frank!
Deveraux!
? I know
the end is comin' soon ?
What the hell
is he doing in there?
Frank!
Don't shoot!
We're coming in!
? Don't go 'round tonight
[ glass shatters ]
? well, it's bound to take your life ?
? there's a bad moon
on the rise ?
? all right
Not good.
? There's a bad moon
on the rise ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==