You look horrific. When was the
last time you really slept a night?
Let's just work,
all right?
Killer clown. I know
what you're thinking, Sam.
"Why did it
have to be clowns?"
Give me a break.
You didn't think
I remembered, did you?
Come on,
you still bust out crying
whenever you see Ronald McDonald
on the television.
At least I'm not afraid
of flying.
Planes crash.
And apparently clowns kill.
It's okay.
They can't hurt you.
"If it bleeds, you can kill it."
Yeah.
? Supernatural 7x14 ?
Plucky Pennywhistle's Magical Menagerie
Original Air Date on February 10, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Hello?
Ye--
"I am the eggman."
Seriously, Frank,
pay phones?
I mean, come on.
I'm getting the clap off
this thing just touching it.
Fred Savage? Really?
Yeah, no, I know,
big mouths are everywhere.
Uh, well, since you asked,
some actual intel on the
Dick Roman guy would be nice.
Fine.
All right.
Yeah, good looking out.
I hope he finds
something quick.
This whole protocol du jour thing's
really creeping my cheese.
So, we got dick on Dick?
That's a vivid way
of putting it.
You find anything on Wonder Woman?
No.
And there probably won't be.
They are definitely gone.
But I might have found
something over in Kansas.
All right,
well, let's do it.
But, uh, a few simple rules,
okay? No babies.
In fact, no baby mamas.
No bars.
No booze --
no hot chicks of any kind.
Wait, wait, wait.
Did you just say --
Hey. You spawn
a monster baby,
see how quick you want
to dive back in the pool.
Ohh.
Those are not the fun kind
of hickeys.
You're -- you're saying
an octopus did this?
Not just any octopus.
Based on welt diameter,
enteroctopus dofleini.
And for those of us who skipped
the enteroctopus class?
Giant pacific octopus.
How giant we talking, Doc?
Approximately 30 feet.
I mean, aren't...
giant octopi rare around here?
Yet here we are.
All right,
so what happens?
Guy comes home,
cracks a beer,
and gets...suckered
to death?
Obviously, this was some kind
of freak fetish attack.
Someone created
those hickey marks,
then bled the man out.
That bite look
a little vamp-y to you?
Yeah, no question.
So what are we
looking for?
An octovamp?
A vamptopus?
That's crazy even for us,
right?
It does push the envelope.
Let's go chat up
the widow.
We're very sorry
for your loss, ma'am.
Mrs. Harper, we know
this is, uh, bad timing.
But we just have a few
routine questions
that we need to ask you --
is that okay?
Yeah.
Did the house
feel any different lately?
Different...?
Anything strange.
Cold spots.
Uh, did you smell
anything weird?
Maybe sulfury?
No. Not that
I can remember.
Okay, we're just ticking
all the boxes here.
Um, what about any skeletons
in your husband's closet?
- Skeletons?
- What do you mean?
Can you think of anybody
who would want to do him harm?
A colleague,
an old flame.
The tiniest detail
could really help.
You want to know
what he was up to lately?
Ask Stacey.
She was here
the night he died.
Um...Stacey?
Our nanny.
Any other questions?
No, that's...
Thank you.
You've been a big help.
Really appreciate
the hospitality, ma'am.
Mom, dad, nanny --
boy, that is a love triangle
right out of casa erotica.
'Course, in those,
the jealous wife
tends to channel her feelings
more productively.
The only thing I can't wrap
my mind around is --
What, how wife lady
summoned an octovamp?
More like "why?"
I mean,
kind of impractical, right?
Yeah.
All right, one of us needs to go
talk to the naughty nanny.
The other one stay here,
shake down the place
when the wife leaves --
see what
we're dealing with.
All right.
I'm on the nanny.
No, I'm on the nanny.
I thought you said
no hot chicks.
We don't know
that she's hot.
Now, uh,
how would you describe
your relationship
with the deceased?
I don't know.
Normal, I guess.
Normal?
Well, I mostly dealt
with Debra.
There was nothing going on,
if that's what you mean.
Debra said that you were at
the house late the night that...
That Brian died.
Yeah.
Brian was working late,
so I stayed with Kelly.
She was pretty upset.
Why's that?
Well, it was her birthday.
We had a party
at Plucky's.
Plucky's.
Why does that sound familiar?
Plucky Pennywhistle's
Magical Menagerie?
Pizza chain for kids.
Actually, more
for lazy parents.
Anyway, her dad showed up
for five minutes,
then he went back to work.
And, of course,
her mom was out of town.
This stupid kid told Kelly her
folks didn't really love her.
She freaked.
I was calming her down
for hours.
Uh, did you...notice anything
weird at the house?
Weird like...?
Anything.
Even a bad feeling.
No, nothing like that.
Actually, Kelly does have
a weird thing about closets.
But it's just kid stuff.
Try me.
She thinks there's a monster
in her closet.
It drives everyone crazy.
Hey, we talked
to the wrong person.
What?
Yeah, forget the mom.
Talk to the daughter.
She's mad at her dad
for ditching her birthday.
So, what do you think?
A birthday wish gone wrong,
something like that?
I don't know.
It could be.
I got a 20
on her right now.
Can you get to her without
tripping the AMBER Alert?
I'll try.
All right,
see what you can find out.
Whatcha working on there?
I know who you are.
- You do?
- Mm-hmm.
You're the guy
that talked to my mom.
That's right. I did.
Kelly!
Something wrong?
My mom will get mad
if I talk to you.
Um...How come?
Because of what I told
the police.
And what did you tell
the police?
I told them that I tried
to warn my dad.
That the monster
would get him.
Kelly. Come here!
Now!
Kelly!
Aah!
Ugh!
"If it bleeds,
you can kill it."
Huh.
Hey. Um...
Okay, so,
the horse I get.
The hoofprints,
the jumping over the fence.
But, uh,
what ran him through?
Best thing I could tell you
is something big.
So, what, like a lance?
It's sad.
Lady's got to pull
her friggin' 8-year-old
out of school
and tell him his dad's dead.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Agent Jones, FBI.
I'm sorry.
I-I really need to go.
Okay. Uh,
just one quick question,
if you don't mind.
Um, was yesterday
your son's birthday?
Billy's birthday? No.
Why would you ask that?
Nothing. Never mind.
Oh. But...
His father did take him
to a friend's
birthday party yesterday.
Hey.
Hey. You remember a chain
called Plucky Pennywhistle's?
No.
Really? Could have swore
you loved those places.
No, dude, I hated them.
Uh, you would dump me
and go trolling for chicks.
It's not like I left you
in jail.
I mean, those places
are supposed to be fun.
Fun?
Uh, they're lame.
And they smell like puke.
And the ice cream
is all grainy.
All right, don't have
one of your episodes, okay?
I'm just saying I hit
a dead end with this whole
wishes-gone-wild thing,
but both kids
were at Plucky's day of.
Look, why don't you go
check out the local Plucky's
and ask
about this Billy kid?
Look, man,
w-why don't I just...
Why don't I just
wait for you to get back?
No can do, Hermano.
I'm on my way
to talk to little Billy.
Why -- why -- why don't I talk
to Billy...Right now?
Wait, wait, wait.
This isn't about your, uh,
your clown thing, is it?
What?!
No!
Sammy?
No.
Yeah, what in the world
did they do to you?
All right, you know what?
Never mind.
Just know that 99.99%
of all clowns
can't hurt you.
Okay?
And if it bleeds,
you can kill it.
"If it bleeds, you can kill it."
I'm too old for this.
Welcome to Plucky's,
where all your dreams
are good.
Could you just,
uh, maybe...
Just get the manager
for me?
Okay.
I just need you to stay sane
for three more hours.
Okay? Here.
Finish your homework.
Like I can concentrate
in here.
Real beauties, huh?
We rotate them out
once a week.
Kids love having their art
on the wall.
"Draw your worst fear"?
I know.
But we don't post
the truly evil stuff --
just the standard crap
like sharks and ghosts.
Jean Holiday,
shift manager.
Johnson, FBI.
So
tell me --
why even ask the kids to draw
creepy stuff to begin with?
It's just an exercise...
Some pop psychologist
came up with.
Plus, the owner's obsessed
with "aiding children's
development."
So, the place mat
is a safe way
to get kids to talk
about their fears.
You know, we get them
to sketch it in a little box,
and -- voil?! --
Plucky magically transforms it
into rainbows and candy.
Personally, I think
it's a load of hooey,
but they say that
if these fears run wild,
then it affects kids
long into their adulthood.
Yeah, I've -- I've --
I've heard that.
Um...So, I don't know
if you'll remember,
but there was a kid
in here yesterday
named Billy Pogue
for a party?
Oh, the conniption kid.
Conniption?
He -- he had --
No, no, no, not him.
He was fine. It was his dad.
He pulls the kid away
before cake and presents,
and I guess the kid asked to
stay for another five minutes.
The dad pulls
a full-frontal douchebag,
starts screaming.
Just embarrassed
for the kid.
Hey. Hey.
Hey!
You a cop?
Uh, yeah.
I'm a Fed.
Uh, what are you
investigating?
Couple of crazy deaths.
Why, is there something
you want to share?
Look -- not now.
Too many eyes.
Come back after closing.
Hey.
So, what's the lowdown
with trauma town?
I can tell you this much.
Neither vic was up
for parent of the year.
Kelly's dad skipped
her birthday,
and Billy's dad pulled one
of those Dick Parent scenes
that makes
everyone cringe.
What the hell are these?
Kid therapy.
Um, you draw
your worst nightmare --
poof! --
Plucky fixes it.
Um, they hang them up
on this big wall.
Well,
can't argue with this.
Leprechauns are deadly.
Okay, so, Kelly draws
a monster,
and then that goes after
her father?
That's what we're saying?
Well, here's the thing.
They label those.
And guess which two
were missing.
Well, name tag was there --
no place mat.
Little miss octovamp.
Yeah. And...
- Billy.
- So...
Somehow, whatever he drew
came to life
and killed his dad,
riding a horse.
Close, but no Seabiscuit.
See, I went and had
a little chat with Billy.
And he drew me this.
Wait.
So now unicorns are evil?
- Yeah.
- Obviously.
Great.
Well, now the question is,
how did a Unicorn come off
a sketch and kill Billy's dad?
How's any of this
happening?
Well, that's it for me.
Guess I'll head out.
Uh, one more thing.
Some kid puked
in the ball pit.
It's gonna need
a full sanitization.
Do that,
and then you can clock out.
Aah!
Ah!
Hold on one second
there, guys.
All right.
Uh, thank you.
So?
The manager found the body
in the ball pit.
Blood everywhere.
Cops have a theory?
Yeah, they think
the ball washer did it.
The what?
The...ball washer.
The ball --
Look at this.
Thank you, gentlemen.
That's a shark bite.
Yeah.
And, uh,
judging from the radius,
I'd say a 20-footer,
at least.
"Shark Week," man.
How do you not watch that?
Whole week of sharks.
Omar Cooper.
How much you want to bet
little Omar here
was scared of sharks?
And Saul the janitor
is connected how?
I mean, he's not related
to Omar.
No. But Saul had something
he wanted to tell me.
So this isn't about ganking
some dickweed parent.
More like, uh,
silencing a whistle-blower?
Great, so whatever
we're looking for
can literally fire off
childhood fears at will.
Wow. Watch out
for evil lunch ladies.
All right.
Let's comb this place.
Seriously.
Dractopus.
Seabiscuit the impaler.
Land shark -- what's next?
Okay, Tyler, that's it.
You got to take the bus
from here.
But I thought --
I can't. I'm sorry.
I'm late.
Here.
Stay out of trouble.
Whee!
Aah!
Ohh.
Ow!
Maybe...Tulpa?
No, killing's are
too spread out.
True.
Um...Angel?
It's a little imaginative
for the God squad,
don't you think?
All right. So...What?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm tapped out.
Well, whatever it is,
at least we know
where it is.
Plucky's!
That's where the victims
are getting picked up.
Yeah, but we swept the place
last night, and nada.
I can go back.
Go to the employees,
maybe dig up some dirt.
What good's that gonna do?
They think you're a Fed.
The one guy who was gonna rat,
he got Bruce'd.
If anybody knows anything,
they're not gonna tell you.
All right. Yep.
That's the plan.
I'll go back...
Play bad cop,
really lean into them.
And...?
And...when I'm done,
then you watch them.
So if somebody freaks out,
then that's our creep.
Or he'll lead us closer,
and you can track him.
Well, what's my cover?
I don't know.
Just hang back.
Act normal.
Yeah, yeah. Guy in his 30s
hanging out at Plucky's alone --
that's normal.
That's not pervy at all.
So, it doesn't matter
what people say.
We've roped it off.
I've notified the powers
that be. Everyone's aware.
Just no one goes in the...
Hi.
Agent.
I bet I know
why you're here.
How's business?
Turns out not even
grim flippin' death
can slow down
the birthday fun.
Oh.
We roped off the ball pit,
though,
until corporate
can get here.
I just can't believe
the machine fritzed
and did Saul in
like that.
Yeah,
that makes two of us.
I'm gonna need to talk
to some of your employees.
Like who?
Like you.
Howdy, friend.
Giant slinky.
Would have killed for one
of those when I was a kid.
How much?
1,000 tickets.
American dinero. How much?
Oh, we don't take cash here
at Plucky Pennywhistle's.
Only tickets won through
hard work and determination.
You mainlined
the kool-aid, huh?
It's double-ticket Tuesday
if you play skeeball.
Howdy, friend!
So, where were you
last night?
Well, here.
Obviously.
I found him.
But I was by the cash register
the whole time.
There's a security camera
pointed right at the counter.
- The cops already looked at it.
- Uh-huh.
And you heard nothing?
I heard the ball blaster.
I didn't hear him.
If I did, I would have
run in, of course.
Yeah, right, right.
So that's your excuse.
My what?
Look, I know
I'm new to this job, but I'm --
What?
- How new?
- Couple weeks.
I just got promoted.
Hmm.
So, uh, was there a lot
of competition for the gig?
I guess.
It comes with benefits.
The bosses had us
all write essays
about how we would
do our best for the kids,
and they picked me.
Don't be shocked,
but I actually did two semesters
at college, so...
I'm not in any kind
of trouble, am I?
I don't know.
Why don't you tell me?
Look, I know I'm not perfect,
but I'm trying.
And, I mean, it's not as if
I'd ever do anything illegal.
Sure you wouldn't.
Special Agent?
Wow!
I want you to know, sir,
that I really appreciate
what you do, and --
Quiet.
Hey!
Stop cheating!
You heard him.
Knock it off!
Jackass. Jackass.
Tyler, soup's on.
- But, mom, I don't want --
- Just eat it.
But it sucks!
Hey, why don't you cut her
some slack?
What do you care?
Because I've been
where you are.
Your mom made you camp at
a stupid Plucky's after school?
Y-- no.
No, but my dad,
he...hauled me places.
Besides,
she's working a tough gig.
You know?
She's exhausted.
You should take pity
on the old.
And, hey, free grub.
That stuff tastes
like butt.
What?
Come on,
it can't be that bad.
Let's see here.
Ah.
That is butt.
You scared of robots?
They have laser eyes.
Yes.
Howdy, friend!
What's your name?
Hi.
Lose the head.
Why'd you do it?
Do...What?
I think you know.
I...
I got rights.
You can't --
I'm the federal
government, pal.
- I can do whatever I want.
- Okay. I'll talk.
Dean!
Hey! Hey! Come here!
Hey!
If this is about the meth lab
that fireballed up in Butte,
it wasn't me.
Okay, it was my brother,
but, um, we got
the same fingerprints, and...
Please. This is
the best job I ever had.
All right, look, uh...
Cliff.
You're not using
kids' nightmares
to smoke people,
are you, Cliff?
I don't...think so.
Get up.
What's going on?
All right, cards up.
Yeah, we don't care that you,
you know, broke bad or whatever.
But there is some seriously
weird going on in there.
You mean the sub-basement.
This place
has a sub-basement?
Sure.
Door's out back.
Easy to miss
if you don't know.
What's in there?
Alls I know is...
Me and Saul used to come in
after hours sometimes and...
You ever shroom
in a ball pit?
Not that I...would,
agents.
It was Saul.
Just Saul. All alone.
Anyway...
Sometimes we'd hear, like,
spooky stuff,
through the vents...
Coming up
from the boiler room.
Okay, kiddo.
Let's go.
But somebody stole it!
So, draw another one!
Okay?
We gotta go.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
That place mat
sucked anyway.
Dean. What?
What is it?
While you were out
being Dirty Harry,
uh, Tyler's mom
got pissy with him,
and now
his place mat's missing.
So, what do you think?
I think the bitchy mom
plus, uh, sad kid
plus place mat
with something nuts
written on it...
equals wacky corpse.
So you think she's next
on the list?
All right, I'll tail them
just to be safe. You --
check the boiler room.
I know.
Right.
Oh. Oh.
Uh, Dean, hey, uh,
any idea what he drew?
- Robot.
- Robot?
Yeah, about the size
of a house.
Shoots destructo beams
out of its eyes.
At least
I'll see it coming.
Yeah.
Now, that's perfectly normal.
Drop it.
Drop it!
Mm-hmm.
Now kick it over.
Some pretty heavy hoodoo
you got here.
I gotta say,
as far as I know,
none of these things,
uh, can poop out a Unicorn.
There's power in fear.
And when a child draws
what he's afraid of,
a little of that mojo
ends up on the page.
So, what, you toss it
in the fire,
and some bed-wetter's
horror show comes to life?
I got to get something
off the parent, too.
Something they own.
That bit gets tricky.
Well, it hasn't seemed
to slow you down.
I'm just doing
what I need to!
Okay. Okay.
I get it. Okay?
No drawing...
No Iron Giant!
Oh, that b-word
is still on the list!
But not tonight.
Bigger fish.
What, are you gonna shoot me,
Howard?
You really want a body
on your hands?!
- Blood everywhere?!
- You shut up!
'Cause I got lots of ways
to take care of bullies.
Don't you worry.
Like that FBI guy.
He's your pal, right?
I saw you chase
Cliff down.
Five minutes ago,
his business card was torched.
Along with something
from my...
personal collection.
I-I-I picked it out
real special for him, too.
Soon as I saw him,
I noticed.
He was staring
at every little Plucky
like it was gonna stab him
or something.
Guy's got a real thing
about clowns.
Well, hey, these are,
uh, really nice dolls.
Did you paint
them yourself?
Oh.
Uh, friggin' Plucky.
Plucky helps kids.
It's all I ever
wanted to do.
And when the management slot
opened up, I...
But they passed me over.
Shocker.
No, I told them,
"No one cares more than me."
But suits never listen.
So, I'm doing it my way.
So let me
get this straight.
You didn't get
the good parking space,
so you start
dropping bodies?
Those parents
were horrible.
They deserved
what they got.
What about Saul?
Saul had a big mouth!
Some guy hits on
the babysitter,
all of a sudden
he's the world's worst dad?
A good parent
puts his kids first.
And having a little girl
watch her pop get ganked
by the closet monster --
that's putting her first?
In the long run,
they'll all be better off.
You think so?
Really?
I would have been.
So, your brother.
What'd you do to him?
It's not my fault!
It's theirs!
Looks to me
like he drowned.
I was screaming...
But my folks...
They didn't listen.
They never listened.
It was an accident.
They let him die!
Ohh!
Yeah!
I'll bet you still
have nightmares.
In fact, I'll bet you haven't
been in the water since.
Shut up!
Because you're afraid.
No!!
It wasn't my fault.
I'm sorry.
Let's roll.
Go ahead. Say it.
I'm sorry.
You look like you got attacked
by some PCP-crazed strippers.
Dude, one of them sprayed me
with seltzer from his flower.
I'm s-- whew.
What?
Nothing.
Carry on.
Ohh.
That's...
Sam...
I'm sorry for...
psychologically scarring you.
Which time?
Shut up. Seriously.
You know, me ditching you
when we were kids,
that was a dick move.
You know,
the whole clown thing...
You know what, man?
Honestly...
Getting my ass kicked
by those juggalos tonight was...
It was therapeutic.
- You faced your fear.
- Exactly.
And now what else could a clown
possibly ever do to me?
- I feel good.
- Well, congrats.
By the way,
to celebrate...
What?
- No!
- Yes.
Did you win this?
We earned that.
Ha ha!
Hey. I got you a little
something, too, actually.
What? You said
you were over it.
You can think
of it as a...
clown phobia
sobriety chip.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==