There's a new leader.
arising in the West.
Hi Dean.
It's me, Lilith.
I don't think
I like you anymore.
Aah!
I'm gonna put up a barrier
inside your mind.
Don't scratch the wall.
Maybe I'm not real,
but I'm not going anywhere, Sam.
Sam! Unh!
Aren't you full up
just playing snuffleupagus
with the devil
all the livelong?
I don't know, Bobby.
Seeing Lucifer's fine with me.
At least all my crazy's
under one umbrella.
Ms. Havelock,
you shouldn't have come.
I needed to see it
for myself --
after all that tracking,
all those hours we spent.
I mean, it's one thing to
study them in books. It's...
Do I smell menopause?
Well, if it isn't
the Wiccan bitch of the west.
Ms. Havelock, I know you're the
one that helped them find me.
My God...
Not in time
to save our big girl here,
but still,
you get a merit badge.
They caught you,
you son of a bitch!
No more murders!
And you're going back
to hell.
Oh, Nora, Nora...
I'm gonna scoop you out
like a pumpkin.
You know that?
Yeah, your, uh,
scooping days are over, Gomer.
All you got to worry about
now...
Is us.
You ain't the first demon we've
tracked down on this safari.
That's right.
As a matter of fact, I think
you put us over half a dozen.
Looking for Lilith
in all the wrong places.
Well, you're gonna help us
with that.
If things
are about to get messy,
maybe you should meet the owner
of this fleshy temple...
A puppy of a man.
You'll like him.
Jeffrey?
Jeffrey, is that you?
No.
You have to stop him.
We will.
We're going to, okay?
We're gonna send that Demon
back to hell.
Okay.
Please don't hurt me.
Jeffrey,
before we can let him go...
Look, the Demon knows where we
can find more of his kind, okay?
See, we're hunting them --
all of them.
He's not gonna give up
his rolodex easy.
Jeffrey, we're gonna have to
cut in to him.
That means you.
Oh, the things he made me do
to those women.
Whatever you have to do...
You have to do it.
Please
just stop this evil piece of...
And on and on and on.
Frankly, he can get tedious
with this whole
"good and evil" thing.
You know,
you were right.
I like Jeffrey.
He's a decent guy.
In fact, he just signed off
on his temple.
Uh...
Ohh!
Unh!
She's got other lieutenants.
We already know that.
We want names.
Unh! Ohh!
All right! All right!
His name is Merrick!
I swear!
You'll find him
in New Orleans!
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus,
omnis satanica potestas,
omnis incursio infernalis!
? Supernatural 7x15 ?
Repo Man
Original Air Date on February 17, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Jeffrey?
Jeffrey, you awake?
Hey, you passed out.
You're in shock.
He's -- he's gone?
We exorcised him.
Try not to move, okay?
We're almost to the hospital.
Your...
Your brother?
My brother stayed back to clean
us out of that crime scene.
There's no reason to go down
for a Demon's murders.
You know what I mean?
All right.
All right, take it easy.
All right, you're good
to make it from here, right?
Okay, Jeffrey, no demon talk
in the E.R., you understand me?
You were mugged.
Okay.
Uh, um, uh, thank you.
"Classified server"?
Got to be Devereaux,
right?
Hello?
Thank God.
Frank, Frank,
what do you got for me?
It's nice.
Kind of like a men's room
with beds.
Hmm, avocado grime.
Takes years to build up
a patina like this.
What do you mean
you can't find him?
It's Dick Roman.
Turn on CNN.
Didn't you see him at that, uh,
press conference in Phoenix?
The bastard's everywhere.
You sure?
No, I-I-I don't.
I don't care
that they've infiltrated
the luxury-boat industry,
Frank.
Great. Call Kanye.
Frank's still stumped
on Roman?
Yeah.
All right,
let's do this.
Okay, um,
look at the victim profiles --
same age, same hair color,
body type.
The ritual mutilations
line up exactly.
Who down there would've
let our demon out of the can?
He squealed on his superiors.
We made sure of that.
I mean, he should be down under
until, uh, trumpet day.
But two women killed in the last
two weeks, same parts missing,
I mean,
same old hunting grounds, even.
All right, well,
we can take a swing at it.
But you know it's all about
the Leviathans now, okay?
They're the ones
we need to be hunting.
Yeah, but, no --
I mean, not right now.
This one's ours, Dean.
It's unfinished business,
apparently.
All right.
- This is unit 32.
- Repeat, we've got another one.
That's a 187.
Female, Caucasian, maybe late
30s, at the Henley Auto-Wash.
Unit 32,
assistance is en route.
Got a real mess here,
dispatch.
You know, every time we do this,
I wonder if today's the day.
We walk up, flash our tin
to a bunch of chompers
pretending to be policemen.
I hear you.
Thought you guys
might show up.
It's the drummer boys,
agents, uh, Bonham...
and Watts, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
Uh, it's a pleasure to see you
again, Detective...
- Sutton.
- You know what? Pardon me.
Uh, what was it --
Detective...
Sutton.
Oh, no problemo --
Detective Sutton.
Sutton.
Sutton, yeah. Hi.
Sad to say,
case looks to be open again.
Are you sure?
Same tools.
Same cuts.
Same crazy.
Makes sense.
I mean, we didn't catch the
critter last time, did we?
And no suspects?
Same as before.
Very thorough.
Cold-blooded.
Thank you, Detective.
Anytime.
Hey.
Sulfur.
Damn it.
Better go check
on Havelock.
This is it.
Wiccansweb.com.
Internet mail order.
White magic only
herbs and talismans.
You sure about that?
Careful, it's still drying.
I have a friend
at the sheriff's office.
I know about
all the new murders.
I'm doing what I can
to protect myself.
I'm also translating
some very old banishments.
Wow, uh, these are --
these are good.
Thanks.
Got an affinity.
But back then,
that night in that farmhouse,
I was in over my head.
I know that now, believe me. I
will leave all that to the pros.
Well,
you helped track it down.
I mean,
it was some solid legwork.
When it came down to it,
all I really knew
was somebody
who knew somebody
who knew the right number
to call.
And your number is not working,
by the way.
Right, we, uh, we've had
some  technical
difficulties -- phone issues.
It's a monster problem,
really.
So, uh, you haven't
had any contact?
With the Demon?
No, thank God.
I have one or two things
to finish in town,
and then I'm leaving.
Good choice.
Have you found
Jeffrey yet?
Who?
The man
who the demon possessed.
The one
you almost beat to death.
Yeah, Jeffrey.
That poor bastard.
Some demons tend to be
sentimental, don't they?
Always go back to the same host
if they can.
It's a start.
I want to talk about Cinemax.
We're grown men.
We pay rent.
Why can't we get Cinemax?
Skinemax.
The halfway program advisers
have already weighed in on that.
Fine, fine.
- Bringing it up in group is not gon--
- I said fine!
Jeffrey,
you have something pretty big
going down later this morning.
That's right, I guess.
Um, I'm picking her up today.
I'm getting a dog --
a rescue.
I had to get her spayed
and shots and stuff,
but they said she's ready.
Jeffrey and I talked about this.
He understands that
pet ownership is a privilege,
not a right.
He's gonna have to
show the whole house
that he can handle
the responsibility.
And that's what it's all about,
right, Alan?
Handling it.
You okay there?
Huh?
Surgery's a bucket of laughs,
huh?
You look good.
I'm sorry for the cone of shame,
but we got to
keep these stitches in.
Okay. Okay.
Come on. Come on.
- Hey!
Oh!
Jeffrey?
Okay. Look, it's okay.
You're okay, you're okay.
Sorry.
Just had to make sure.
Make sure of what --
that I peed my pants today?
Aw, you scared my dog.
Uh, we did not want to
do that.
Listen, Jeff, we got to,
uh, we got to talk.
Well, this is, uh...
I know what it is.
Look, I know it must've been,
um, hard.
Do you even listen
to yourself?
Oh, don't bother.
What do you guys want from me?
Well, um, we're pretty sure
the demon that possessed you...
Is back.
What?
What do you mean?
You exorcised him, right?
He's -- he's supposed to be
in Hell.
Jeffrey, look,
please just calm down.
Just have a seat, please.
I don't understand.
Three more women have been
murdered over the past two weeks.
No, no.
Same vic profiles,
same forensics,
crime scene
dusted with sulfur.
We've got to assume
that it's him.
But we're here now, okay?
So if he comes after you,
we'll nail him
just like we did last time.
What was her name?
What?
The last one he killed.
Uh, Anna?
Anna Paxton.
Marjorie Willis.
She's the next one on the list.
List? What list?
The demon used to recite it all
the time, like a grocery list.
He burned it in my head --
the names of all the women
he was gonna kill.
He already had
his victims chosen?
And put in a line
in an order.
Wait. Why?
Demons aren't usually into the
obsessive serial-killer crap.
You know, they're more
just kind of all-around evil.
Why would he do this?
He said it was his job.
Jeffrey, did your,
uh, guests sign in?
I'm really sorry, Alan.
They're friends of mine from
my days back at the Post Office.
I didn't know
they were coming.
So, what do you think?
I think we really helped mess
this poor son of a bitch up.
Look at him.
He's got a state-assigned dad.
Okay, just get them to sign in
when they sign out.
Uh, Jeffrey,
look, I'm gonna go,
uh, I'm gonna go find Marjorie
Willis, keep her on watch, okay?
Don't worry.
I'm gonna stay here
just in case.
You're right.
We just don't read anymore.
Marjorie Willis.
Librarian,
indoor gardening enthusiast,
our Demon's
next organ donor.
Come on, Sam, talk to me.
It's been months.
When you left me at the E.R.,
I had three smashed fingers,
five teeth out, a broken wrist,
nose, cheekbone, collarbone.
I had to get 160 stitches.
Mugged.
The doctor on duty
said it looked like
I got caught
in the Spanish Inquisition.
And we're the good guys.
They patched me up, mostly.
But I lost my job,
my health insurance.
I just started to drink
and drift, and I got lost.
Had some kind of
mental break.
And I started to talk...
about what happened.
Aw, man. Never tell.
Never...Never.
I know that now,
believe me.
So, let me guess.
Drunk tank to psych eval
to 72-hour forced hold
to a nice long stay at
an institution of their choice.
Yes.
It's happened
to friends of mine.
For a long time,
I didn't care.
The truth was more important
than where I was.
I was in no shape to cope
with the outside world.
Well, hey, you got out,
you know?
Holding it together.
And now the demon is back.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, man.
I mean it --
about all of it, you know?
You saved my life.
I owe you for it.
I know that.
I owe a lot of people
for getting even this far.
I...
Crap.
What?
If he isn't already circling
the next woman, Marjorie,
than I-I think I might know
where he is.
He had this special place
where he kept souvenirs
where he nested.
Why didn't you tell us this?
I didn't want to go.
You don't have to go.
We'll handle it.
I do. I have to.
"Average annual rainfall --
Hackberry, Texas"...
Come on, Sam,
pay attention to me.
I'm bored.
Civil war buff?
Damn it -- no service.
Good girl. You stay.
Here's some jerky.
Stay.
Thing's not gonna pee in here,
is it?
Um, I don't know.
So, he'd get you this far, and then
he'd shut your lights out, yeah?
For some reason, he was very
secretive about this place.
But after a while,
he'd only really sort of cover
my eyes when we walked in.
Okay, you think
you can get us back there?
Right here in my
discontinued periodicals.
Oh.
Oh, that's it.
Red door
down the hallway.
Yeah, there is.
This must be it.
All right, stay over here.
Okay?
You just stay here.
Don't move.
What the hell?
Hey.
Hey, all right.
We're gonna
get you out of here.
Hey, hey, I'm not gonna
hurt you, okay?
But you got to stay still.
I'm pretty sure this guy's the
boring sort of chubby chaser.
Leave your name, number,
and nightmare at the tone.
Dean, where are you?
I'm scoping zero out here.
Not a good sign.
Hmm.
Surprised you haven't
picked up on that yet.
It's right...
There in the coroner's report.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
In this latest round
of killings, our big girls
had traces of heavy
tranquilizers in their blood.
Yeah, but our Demon's
strong enough
to make fat Betty
do whatever he wants to, right?
So, why does he need
the tranqs?
Think he's got a bad back?
Yeah,
whatever is going on here,
you know that Demon's
not coming back to kill anybody.
This is Special Agent Smith.
Please leave your name, number --
Oh, no. That's every cellphone
Dean's got.
One of them should've picked up,
right?
Big brother's probably dead.
Shut up.
He said "shut up" to me.
That's what I'm talking about,
Sam -- real interaction again.
I miss that.
The rapier wit,
the wittier rape.
Come on.
I'll be good.
I'll even help you solve
your little Nancy Drew mystery
or whatever.
No note.
Hmm,
a cellphone scrambler.
But, Luci, those are illegal.
Think, Sam.
Maybe this has something to do
with Dean's telephone blackout.
Hmm.
Latin --
not suspicious at all.
I've never seen
this spell before.
No. But you've seen
this type.
Demon summoning -- why?
Why? To summon a demon,
jackass.
Start looking at who.
Okay, what do you mean?
Look at the page.
You know this handwriting.
I know this handwriting.
Ohh!
Iay, caramba!
Imi cabeza!
Nora, stop it!
Calm down!
What is this?
Why did Jeffrey have a demon
summoning in your handwriting?
Everything's happening the way
he said, the way he planned it.
- What plan?!
- You can't help --
you can't change it.
Hit her.
Nora,
tell me what is going on.
Sam, shake her up.
She knows what happened to Dean.
Get this stupid cow to focus,
will you?
Nora, listen to me!
Whatever it is, you should be a
lot more scared of me right now
because I'm 2 inches away from
you, and I can make you talk.
Do you understand me?
It's my son.
He has my son!
What were you thinking?
I mean, why would you even
help bring back a demon
in the first place?
Not the demon.
Jeffrey!
Jeffrey?
Good. You're up.
What happened?
What's going on?
No one asked you
to get involved,
to save me,
to save anyone.
What?
Did you ever think that maybe
I loved being possessed?
Did you?
I loved the connection,
the power.
And I loved him.
Love of my life, actually.
Oh, you got to be
kidding me.
He liberated me --
started me
on my true life mission.
So you're the one with the thing
for all those women.
Aren't you, Jeffrey?
You're a serial killer.
I was nothing
before he found me --
a shadow too scared to do
what I was brought here to do.
Too timid to live up
to my true potential.
So, what happened --
redheaded mommy make you
stuff birds, put on dresses?
You shouldn't trivialize
other people's pain.
So, demon comes along,
rides co-pilot in your skull...
Teaches you how to kill.
The list...
That's yours.
For years,
it was just a game I would play.
Every time I'd walk by
one of them in the street
or see one
on my mail route...
There's a sound
that comes from their brains.
You know that?
Only I can hear it, like
an evil, little steam whistle.
Every time I saw one,
I'd follow her,
take down her address.
But I was never
gonna do anything,
not till he came along.
He's the one who saved me.
And you sent him to Hell.
I kept tabs on Jeffrey
after the exorcism.
I even sent him
care packages in the hospital,
but he never responded.
And then not long ago,
he came to me.
He seemed healthy, put together,
except he wanted to know
if there was a way
to summon the demon back.
He said he'd been doing
some research.
It was mostly nonsense, but he
was convinced it was possible.
You really knocked the cork out
of her piehole.
I sent him away.
I told him
to get some more help.
The next day
He called me.
He put my son on the phone.
He had taken him
from his dorm room.
I gave him everything --
the ritual, the sigils.
But he kept my boy.
And then he sent me this.
My baby's ear.
He cut it off
because the ritual didn't work.
Well...
That demon gave up
some serious state secrets --
would've gone
into big lockdown now.
Not so easy to bring him back up.
Jeffrey didn't care.
He told me to find out
what went wrong or else.
Finally, I found
a summoning spell
that would work for sure.
And that's when he said
I had another job to do.
Which was what?
When you came, I was supposed to
send you to Jeffrey.
He left a trail of bodies
to make sure of it.
"Blood of the exorcist"?
Strongest summoning
I've ever seen.
Requires the blood of the
exorcist who banished him --
your brother.
You see?
It is all part
of Jeffrey's plan.
Yeah. Well...New plan.
Tracking spell --
Bavarian, Egyptian.
I don't care --
dealer's choice.
Use the flesh of the body
to find the body and Dean.
Do you want the ear
or the kid?
You're giving me the chills.
I like to think
I know you pretty well.
Yeah, how do you figure?
I watched you torture an
innocent man to get out a demon.
Pretty charged situation...
Revealing.
You guys talked about a lot,
showed a lot of character.
God...
You were so desperate
to fix the world back then.
It kills you...
That people
keep getting hurt...
And you just can't stop it.
Or I should say it's killed you,
shouldn't I?
You know what?
Screw you.
- Hey.
- I was there.
I was depressed, Dean,
because he was gone.
I was a wreck,
an emotional shell, a drunk.
I was suicidal.
I don't usually endorse suicide,
but, man, what stopped you?
It was Alan --
at the house.
You're kidding me.
He's a really good
rehab therapist.
Really helped me focus
on my goals, my attitude.
I have to say,
I really benefited
from the whole program.
Yeah.
A life well-lived
comes from the structured
pursuit of meaningful happiness.
I realized I was nothing
without my demon.
Then I decided
I have to get him back.
I'll be right back.
Hey, there, honey.
Come on.
It's a bitch of a recipe,
I must admit.
No.
Oh,
you sick son of a bitch.
Hello, Jeffrey.
Dean Winchester.
As I live and breathe...
Again.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
What are you doing?
I'm thanking you,
Jeffrey.
What are you doing with
this half-dead piece of crap?
Come into me.
We had a very special time
together, didn't we, Jeffrey?
It warms my heart to see you
haven't forgotten what I taught you.
You built on it.
You captured a Winchester.
You, Jeffrey...My pupil.
I don't want to be your pupil.
I want to be yours.
But I'm done with you.
My work is finished.
You can do everything now,
all on your beautiful own.
No.
No?
Oh!
Unh!
We don't do "no."
Remember, Jeffrey?
Keep sawing away at your ropes,
Penelope Pitstop.
We can dance standing up
if you want.
So,
is this what you do --
find postal workers,
make 'em go postal?
I talent scout.
That's all.
Looking for the next generation
of superstars...
Before they get to hell,
like Jeffrey here.
He had all the raw material...
Just bubbling in there.
All I had to do
was loosen the lid on his jar,
show him
some practical know-how.
Yeah, what about the kid?
This one?
I don't think.
Not much to work with.
No natural gift.
I'll probably burn this meat off
on my way to Vegas.
You've got to be kidding me!
You let go of my son!
Where do you keep coming from?
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus.
He'll be back, you know.
Back in black.
Go to hell.
Omnis congregatio
et secta diabolica, ergo,
Draco maledicte,
ecclesiam tuam,
secura tibi facias libertate
servire, te rogamus, audi nos!
Oh!
Mom?
I got you.
I got you, baby.
Oh, God.
So, Jeffrey was just pretending
to be the victim.
Way back in that farmhouse
during the exorcism,
h-he was just...acting.
He was a psychopath,
Sam.
That's what they do
all the time, is act.
Act like they're normal,
act like they're not
balls-to-the-wall crazy.
You going to sleep?
Damn straight. Screw consciousness --
that's what I say.
No, no, Sam.
No nap for you, Sammy.
Oh, come on,
don't do that.
Let's talk, Sam.
I always enjoyed
our special little chats.
Don't you want to talk?
Yeah, look at that.
Something's definitely different
now, isn't it?
You let me in.
You wanted me, partner.
So you think you can use
your little tricks
to banish me again
like that? No.
I do believe I've got you,
bunk buddy.
Got my finger wiggling around
in your brainpan.
Come on, Sammy!
Come on!
Say it with me now.
Good morning, Vietnam!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==