Mr. Singer...
...your time's up.
Bobby! Bobby!
Idjits.
Bobby? Hey!
You really want
to get stuck...
turning into some ghost?
I know what I'm doing,
Rufus.
You're thinking
you can help those boys.
But how many spirits you meet
in their right mind?
What's it gonna be --
stay or go?
I'm concerned that Bobby
might be haunting you.
I've already tried
contacting Bobby.
Without me?
If he was there,
I'd have told you.
We burned him, Dean.
The blade was across the room,
and then it was in my hand.
My beer drank itself.
That page magically appeared
on the bed.
Bobby's book fell down,
and out popped the number
of the guy who found Cass.
It's not Bobby!
It could be.
- No, it couldn't be!
- Why not?
Because we want it to be.
Regular people -- they see ones
they lost everywhere, too.
Yeah, freakin' ghosts.
Or they just
miss them a lot.
If it was Bobby,
he would let us know.
Balls!
All right, here we go.
You know...
even though the world
is going to crap,
there's one thing
that I can always count on --
these things tasting the same
in every drive-through
in every state
in our great nation.
Mmm.
Annie.
Hey, Dean.
A nice surprise.
How you been?
Oh, I'm still kicking.
So, good, I guess.
Heard about Bobby.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. Us too.
What's up?
Well, I got
some of his old books.
I thought
maybe you'd want them.
Yeah. Sure.
Where you at?
Bodega Bay.
Crow's Nest Inn.
- You working?
- Always.
You guys anywhere nearby?
- Near enough.
- Cool.
Why don't we meet
at the Pier Front
Restaurant -- lunch?
- 1:00?
- Yeah. Bye.
We shouldn't be here.
Yeah. I know.
Cops?
You shouldn't have
come here.
? Supernatural 7x19 ?
Of Grave Importance
Original Air Date on April 20, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Hey, get this.
Dick Roman is funding
another archaeological dig.
Guy moves more dirt
than "The Drudge Report."
Well, anything
on what he's digging for?
Don't you think
I would have led with that?
Annie's not usually
this late, is she?
No, never.
She's totally compulsive.
I'll try her cell.
You know, uh, you know she
and Bobby had a thing, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I knew that.
Really?
Yeah.
Kind of a foxhole thing --
very Hemingway.
Huh.
She and I kind of went Hemingway
this one time, too.
All right, well...
that happens.
What, you too?
Look, it was
a  while back.
We ended up
on the same case.
She was stressed.
I-I-I...
I didn't...have a soul.
That's a lot of foxholes.
She's not answering.
Well, here's to ghosts
that aren't there.
You sound
kind of disappointed.
Ah, it's better this way.
I mean, even though I wish
we could see him again
doesn't mean
that we should.
Ahh.
Are we being stood up?
Yeah, let's hope
that's all this is.
Nothing?
Straight to voicemail.
Something's not right.
What's she doing
on Bodega Bay?
She's working some kind of job.
She didn't really say.
I got to get a refill.
You know what, man?
Why don't you just pack it away
for a while?
All it does is remind us of him,
you know?
Yeah, I thought about that,
but, uh...not yet.
Let's go check out
Annie's hotel room.
These go back years --
disappearances never solved.
They stop
a few decades back,
then pick up again
just recently.
All teenagers.
Looks like
Annie found a spot
a lot of them liked
to poke around
just before
they went missing.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Old Van Ness house.
It's, uh, cheery.
Well, the police
combed the place.
They always come up dry.
Yeah, local law.
Always on the ball.
Guys...
So, built in 1862
by the Van Ness family...
I just made that curtain shimmy.
...Who lost it in the early 1900s.
Could you look in the
right place at the right time?
Put up for sale
a few years back. No takers.
Probably 'cause it creeps
their queso.
Balls,
this is exhausting.
It's just been sitting there,
boarded up, for ages.
Oh. Get this.
I guess
a couple months back,
someone put it
on one of those, uh,
"most haunted houses
in America" lists.
Let me guess -- that's when the
teenagers started going missing.
- Yep.
- Okay.
Now let's get rolling.
I say we get rolling.
Idjits.
Thank you.
Honey, I'm home.
Geez.
My people.
All right, let's go.
Hi.
I'm Bobby,
and I'm a ghost.
Hoping for a little
ghost orientation here.
Je m'appelle Bobby.
Chilly.
Annie?!
There's a whole lot
of something going on.
I know what you did
last night,
and you know
it was forbidden!
I don't brook that sort of thing
in my home.
Don't do it again, Dexter,
or there will be consequences.
The call to me
was the last one she made.
So where the hell is she?
Bobby?
Annie!
We've been looking
for you.
I can't believe
you're here.
Yeah. I'm a doornail.
Bad news here.
If you can see me,
you are, too.
Wow.
Dead. Ghost.
Me.
Three words you never want
to use in a sentence.
I feel like I was drugged.
I get it.
I figure it was a month
before I even knew
I was still here.
You're doing well.
Terrific.
So, uh...
So, you duck your reaper,
too?
What? No.
I never even saw one.
You --
Bobby.
You ran away
from your reaper?
On purpose?
That's why
you're still here?
You stupid, crazy old --
hey.
I remember a time when you liked
how crazy I was.
Oh, shut up!
I can't believe you.
You know what?
As a regular ghost
with no choice in the matter,
screw you.
Hey. I got unfinished business
here, same as you.
Uh-huh.
And there's my unfinished
business right now.
Kids!
Hello?
You're dead.
Well, they're not the brightest
bulbs on the string.
I came in,
they were roadkill.
Then this big guy
charges me.
And now I'm...
Crap.
Is there a fun aspect
to this?
Not really.
And so far, I can't crack
the code on any of it.
I mean, I've seen poltergeists
bench a piano as a warm-up.
I tried to help
the boys out once
by knocking a book
off the table
and blacked out
for two weeks.
So, Sam and Dean don't even know
you're here?
Wow.
That is messed up.
Hey, Annie, I'm e-mailing
you those news clippings
that you asked for.
We're redlining
all over the place.
Assume the worst?
Yeah, always do.
Okay.
Vengeful spirit.
Maybe lots of them.
Killing kids.
Look around.
No blood. No anything.
Certainly no bodies.
Well, if evil
is partying here,
it's got a hell
of a cleanup crew.
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
Here's something.
- From earlier this week.
- Okay.
Free me.
Where'd that come from?
You ever seen a phone number
look like that?
All right, that's cool.
Excuse me. Hey!
Boss!
Dick.
Yeah, well...
Ghosts ain't the most sociable
type to come down the pike.
But if he can do it...
Balls.
Graceful.
Novices.
You all make
the same mistakes.
Suppose you know
all about it.
Well, I've been
at it 80 years.
Yo, uh, fresh meat here.
Not even sure
what happened.
Really?
I got shot right in the melon,
never felt a thing.
You?
I was stabbed brutally,
right here at this bar,
April 17, 1932.
Who done ya?
I'm really very busy.
How come there's so many dead
folk in this place, anyway?
You know anything about that?
I guess we're not supposed
to talk about that.
I'm sorry.
Uh, my friend is
a little nosy, mister...?
Crane --
Haskel Crane.
Haskel...
you're right.
We are novices,
so, could you do me
a solid
and show me how to move
that chair?
It's one stupid chair.
Baby steps, gorgeous.
Try this first.
You're angsting at it.
You know what getting frustrated
will get you?
Nothing.
You've got two ways
to move things.
What I did --
which you obviously must --
is calm yourself.
You're saying
we should move crap
with the power of Zen.
I'm telling you
to let go of all that.
Calmly tell the thing
what to do.
You're getting tense.
You're not helpful.
What's option 2?
You said there were two ways.
Oh, you could use explosive
anger and pure, red-hot rage,
but that's impossible
to manufacture.
Sorry.
Makes sense.
Like poltergeists --
vengeful spirits.
I am vengeful.
You think I don't have
red-hot rage?
I think you're a sad excuse
for one of us,
and I'm unsurprised
that you're failing.
Take my help or don't,
but if you want
to move a flea,
surrender.
For the record,
I hated that Swayze flick --
romantic bullcrap.
What in cold hell
was that?
That's you one day.
That's all of us.
We deteriorate
at different rates --
some sooner, some later.
And eventually all...
like that.
Nothing left at all.
Ghost Alzheimer's.
I'm liking this less.
Well, that is every square inch
of this place.
No bodies, no pieces
of bodies -- no Annie.
A whole lot of sizzle
and no steak.
Well, maybe no news
is good news.
Meaning?
Meaning maybe
she's just not here.
Maybe she's still okay.
Yeah, and what does
your gut say?
Let's just see if there's
anything else in her research.
Sam! Dean!
Honey, don't you think
I've tried that?
I shouted myself hoarse.
But I'm right here!
Well, now you know
how all the ghosts
who have ever tried to talk
to us feel.
You just have to wait
until they find you.
But I don't even know
where I'm at.
And I've searched every room
five times.
No wonder
they're walking away.
Is it me,
or am I being checked out?
No, stud.
I'm being checked out.
Can I help you?
I'm Victoria.
Annie.
I saw you here
the other day.
I know the kind
of work you do.
Did.
Hey, I'm still doing it.
I mean, other-dimensionally
speaking.
Attagirl.
Wait. Your voice.
You're the one
on my phone.
When you were here, I was able
to call out to you that way.
Ah, spectral voice
transference.
Right. Ghost juju.
Sure.
So...
W-what exactly did you mean
when you said, "free me"?
Victoria,
free you from what?
Bobby!
Where'd Annie get her intel?
Do we know?
Stupid flask.
Bodega Bay
Heritage Society.
Boys, come on.
All the action's
back in the pool.
Let's go!
Damn it.
The house dates back
to the mid-19th century.
Miles Van Ness made his fortune
in the gold rush,
eventually settling his family
in Bodega Bay.
Anything...unusual ever happen
in the house?
Over the course
of a century,
things are going to happen
in a house.
"Tell it what to do."
Some locals swear
it's haunted.
Move.
Every village has its idiots.
We only want
the real scoop, of course.
Balls!
Whitman Van Ness.
Son and heir.
Handsome, charming,
dogged by tragedy
all his life.
He lost the family fortune,
then the house.
It became a bordello.
He lived in isolation
till his death at age 40.
He's still there.
Who's the, uh,
the bruiser there?
Dexter O'Connell.
A convict.
An extremely violent man.
He's there, too.
Mr. Van Ness
was socially progressive
and took pity on him.
He worked
as grounds keeper.
Dexter was convicted
for murdering Whitman's fianc?e
on the eve
of their wedding.
Another calamitous event
in the poor man's life.
Well, thank you.
The house is popular
this week.
What do you mean?
A lady came by
the other day
asking all sorts
of questions.
Uh, 30s, red hair, good-looking?
Mm.
I gave her the same advice
I'll give to you.
Stay away from the place.
It's extremely unsafe.
So, besides Whitman's fianc?e,
Dexter O'Connell
was also convicted
of killing a bunch of hookers
who worked at the brothel.
He escaped
before they could hang him.
But then he returned
to the house,
where he was found
shot to death.
Why would he escape
and then go right back to
the house where he got arrested?
I don't know.
Add that to a list of things
So what's the next move?
You know, if I could,
I'd be getting old waiting
on you two to figure this out.
All right, now.
I can kill werewolves,
fix a Pinto,
and bake cornbread.
I will be damned
if I can't get Zen.
We're posting this video
as a warning about...
Or possibly
a memorial to...
Our friends Debbie Tellen
and Dudley Scott,
last known whereabouts...
The Van Ness house...
Since the cops
haven't done crap...
In what may be the final moments
of their love story.
They've been together
since like eighth grade.
Yeah. They entered this house
and texted us.
We're going in.
Ooh-ooh-ooh.
Sam?
What?
Tell me you wrote that.
Uh...
No.
No, I didn't.
They came
into the house...
Well, then, who's there?
I said, who's there?!
Bobby?
They walked through...
these halls...
Seeking a grotto
of love.
Seriously?
Bobby?!
Yes.
This whole time, we've been
trying to talk ourselves out of it,
he's been --
what's he doing here?
Dude.
We don't have time for this!
Get your asses back
to that house!
We got to get back
to that house, stat.
What happened?
Hello?
You shouldn't have
come here!
Dexter.
I expressly forbid you!
Enough!
Thank you.
Dexter, you tried
to warn them away.
You have enough of us.
They're just children,
Whitman.
I can't watch this happen
all over again.
Shut up.
Ah, Victoria.
Grab the camera.
No. I can't.
We don't meddle
in Whitman's affairs.
Hold it.
Let's get real.
You sent me the S.O.S.,
and now I'm here.
So, give me a hand.
But now
he can get you, too.
Get me how?
I'm already dead.
Okay, you want to
help me understand?
Exactly what did he do
to Dexter?
Punished him.
He was trying
to warn them.
He tried
to warn you, too.
He drained him.
Drained?
What does that mean?
That's why he's so strong
and why you should
stay out of sight.
We're merely food to him --
food and perverse entertainment.
So, when he does that,
what happens?
Just...poof?
Forever.
See, I thought that Whitman
was some poor guy,
and Dexter
killed his fianc?e.
No. Whitman framed him.
Whitman killed
all of us.
When this house
was a brothel,
I worked here
as a fancy lady.
He slit my throat.
"Fancy lady"? A hooker?
Please.
And now, even in death,
every soul he traps here
makes him stronger.
Okay, so, where does
he keep the bodies?
I don't know.
Victoria,
you've been here forever.
You don't
follow him around.
Listen, we are going to pull
the plug on this bastard.
Now grab the damn camera.
Oh, dear.
It's him!
We combed the crap
out of this place.
If Annie's in there
and we didn't find her...
It's 'cause something
didn't want us to.
Awesome. Well, let's walk
right into that.
All right, I'll check upstairs.
Yeah.
Annie?!
Sorry, boys.
I'm leaving the pack.
It's Dean! And Sam!
That's not odd.
Sam, get back down here!
Annie?
Slimer?
What?
Check it out.
The final moments
of their love story.
They've been together
since like eighth grade.
Yeah. They entered this house
and texted us.
Oh, I hate these Indie films.
Nothing ever happens.
They came into the house.
They walked
through these halls.
Wait, wait.
Pause it.
Frame back a little bit.
Stop.
She's here,
and not in a good way.
Give them a moment.
They've got a little slower
since I left.
Annie?!
Got to let them know
that I'm here.
You have to do it.
We can't.
It's too dangerous.
These guys can help.
They just need to know
that we're here.
Whoa!
Please. I'm Victoria --
Victoria Dodd.
Where'd you come from?
Here.
I was a fancy lady.
A hooker?
Uh, is Annie here?
Yes.
You can't see her.
No, you're not
standing on her.
- You want to just tell them?
- I will.
In my day, we believed
in polite conversation.
Annie's in
terrible danger.
We all are.
- From?
- Whitman Van Ness.
But he's dead.
I thought you said
they were good.
Hey, I'm just processing,
okay, lady?
He's dead. You're dead.
Define "terrible danger."
Whitman has great power
over all of us in the house.
He killed Annie.
She says
you can free us.
Please, you must --
Victoria?
I'm gonna say she was
telling the truth,
considering that she just...
Got ghost-killed.
So, what?
Whitman Van Ness?
Now we know whose bones
to salt and burn.
Let's go.
Aw, hell no.
If I hadn't stashed
that flask here,
I'd still be glued
to Sam and Dean.
Real clever.
- Actually was.
- Son of a bitch.
I figured our one ace
was that bastard Whitman
couldn't leave
the house either.
Must have pulled a number
like you and the flask.
Probably planted something
on the boys.
Terrific.
Hey, listen, sweetie --
you could beat yourself up
all day about this,
or we could take advantage of
the fact that Whitman's gone,
do what
we're supposed to do.
Let's go figure this out.
Coming, Robert?
Well, we searched
everywhere else.
I'm telling you, Whitman guards
his room like Fort Knox.
Last time I checked,
ghosts didn't get cold.
Yeah.
That's Victoria.
That is how
he took her out.
But where did he get
her corpse?
Well, you said he dragged
those two dead kids away.
Where'd he take them?
Yeah, I don't know.
I couldn't risk following him.
What else did you say
this place was,
other than a whorehouse?
It was a lot of things.
It was a boarding house,
a school...
A speakeasy.
Yeah, well,
thing about speakeasies --
hell of a lot to hide.
Still got it.
Well, this pretty much
tells the story, don't it?
You know, you and me --
we burned our fair share
of bones,
sent a lot
of ghosts packing.
It's a little different
when you're on
the receiving end.
So, uh...
...what do you think
happens to 'em --
heaven, hell, or...
none of the above?
I don't know.
Just...gone,
most likely.
Yeah,
that's what I think, too.
That's what I want.
I want a Hunter's funeral.
Oh, come on.
It's better than this --
stuck to this house,
somewhere between existing
and not.
No, I'm...
ready for some peace.
Wasn't much of a life.
It was lonely,
what we do.
Yeah, well, the life I had
is the one I picked.
Yeah,
but you had the boys.
All I had was work.
It's gone now.
Yeah, well, I ain't done.
Okay, fine, but I am.
You're stronger
than I am now, Bobby,
so, uh, you got to do this
for me.
All right. Here we go --
cemetery, edge of town.
The Van Ness family
has its own mausoleum.
All right, we light up
the bastard and finish him off.
Take it easy.
We'll get there.
Uh, that's not me.
Why's he with us?!
I don't know.
There's got to be
something on us!
Hey, hey.
Ugh!
Sam!
Aah!
Did that do it?
Did that get rid of him?
I don't know.
I got a bad idea
we just snapped him back
to his favorite house.
Where Annie's
a sitting duck.
We got to find those bones.
Come on.
Let's build up the fire.
We can put some of these poor
bastards to rest, at least.
Well, let's get to cremating.
We ain't got all day.
Enjoy the view
from my room?
Planning to thin out
the population?
Is this how you repay
my hospitality?!
No!
I will not be taken!
How long was I out?
A while.
Are you okay?
Sure.
I mean...I'm dead,
I'm a ghost...
but, basically, swell.
Hi, boys.
Bobby?
Wait.
You can see me?
You're staring,
you know.
Annie's here, too,
by the way.
Hi, Annie.
H-hi, Annie.
Hi, guys.
She says you both look uglier
than she remembered.
Bobby,
h-how'd you stay here?
Yeah, well, uh...
suck on that, Swayze.
That's why
you never answered me.
I tried calling you --
the, uh, talking board,
the works --
but I was always alone.
Dean always had that thing
in his pocket.
That's why the EMF only went off
half the time.
We thought
we were going crazy.
S-so, what happened?
Did you get stuck
or -- or what?
I wanted to stay.
Bobby.
I need to help.
Not if it means
you have to...be this.
Well, life wasn't comfy.
Why should death be?
Now, come on.
Annie and I
found all the bodies.
Let's put 'em to rest.
And keep my damn flask away
from the fire...
Obviously.
Well, you coming?
I'll miss her.
Me too.
Yeah.
Well, you didn't know her
like I did.
Well, uh
Here's to Annie.
She got the Hunter's funeral
she wanted.
Kind of like the one
we thought we gave you.
Dean.
What were you thinking,
Bobby?
You could be in heaven
right now,
drinking beer at Harvelle's,
not -- not stuck --
stuck here with you?
We still have work to do.
I just thought that was
kind of important, Dean.
It's not right.
You know that.
Sorry.
You're right.
What was I thinking?
So, what do you think
we should do?
We did what we should do.
Now I don't know.
I mean, do you think
it's possible we could --
I don't know --
make it all work somehow?
I have no idea.
Maybe.
I've never heard of it.
But you know
what I do know?
It ain't the natural order
of things.
Everything
is supposed to end.
You know,
he was supposed --
And now...
What are the odds
this ends well?
What are the odds?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==