Hi, Amy.
You know me. You know
the kind of person I am.
She's dropping bodies, man,
which means we got to drop her.
She's done.
Trust me.
Okay.
You are what you are.
You will kill again.
What's going on with you?
You are what you are.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about whatever
you're not telling me about.
I know you didn't want
to let her go,
but it was the right thing
to do.
So, thanks.
No problem.
You know my motto --
"here to help."
Kind of like
you helped Amy?
I'm sorry.
You should just
go on without me.
All right.
Yes.
A spirit has gathered
around us.
Are you with us,
spirit?
I feel something.
I have goose bumps.
Uncle Danny?
We're going to
make contact now.
Rest your hands
on the planchette.
Let the spirit
guide our hands.
O spirit,
are you
the one we seek?
Are you...
Uncle Danny?
I'm not doing that.
Yeah.
She's pushing it.
It's okay
to be skeptical.
Danny,
if you're with us,
knock twice for yes.
Danny?
Can you ask him,
is he happy?
He is. He's happy.
Is sadie with him?
Now you're being
ridiculous, Cynthia.
Who cares about Sadie?
Ah, yes.
I see...
A family pet.
That's her.
Sadie was a Schnauzer.
She's with Danny, chasing
tennis balls in the afterlife.
Sadie loved
tennis balls.
There were
important papers.
No one can find them.
They weren't in the safe.
Can you
just ask him...
Of course.
I'll need you to place
your hands with me
on the planchette.
Maybe --
maybe Danny didn't like
the question.
Tell him
to quit fooling around.
He knows darn well
that's my money.
Can't you two
stop squabbling?
For Pete's sake,
he's dead.
Tell him we're sorry.
Maybe if we're nice,
he'll --
oh, my God.
Danny?
What's going on?
Run!
? Supernatural 7x07 ?
The Mentalists
Original Air Date on November 4, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Geez.
Have some pride.
Yeah.
Ooh! That make me hungry.
You're listening to
the morning chaos
with me, Bananas Foster.
The hell I am, ass-hat.
And now for the news of the weird --
Two very odd murders, to be exact.
Mediums are dying in Lily Dale,
the most psychic town
in America.
So if you want to know
your future,
stick to that 900 line,
'cause is it me,
or should those guys
have seen it coming?
O spirits of the further...
am I going to win
the Powerball?
I'm gonna be rich.
Hello!
First time
at Good Graces?
Yes.
Well, we're 100%
locally sourced, biodynamic,
and you get a free affirmation
with every order.
Think I'll source
a taco joint.
Just coffee,
black, extra shot.
You always wear a suit
to get your palm read?
Yeah. Not surprised
you caught this one.
It's on every morning zoo
in America.
You mind?
So, I, uh,
I went to the scene.
Wires, speakers, enough E.M.F.
to make your hair stand up.
Don't even think
about getting a reading.
Oh, and, uh, if this
hadn't have been two
psychics that bit it...
I would have just chalked this up
as being dumb and accidental.
And I know, I know.
This whole town's
supposedly calling ghosts.
But that takes some serious
spellwork and some serious mojo.
The only books this lady had
were Oprah crap.
When was the last time
you actually saw a real psychic?
Huh? Pamela?
Missouri?
Anyway, this is good.
And, uh, how you been?
And what can I get
for you?
Uh, pancakes, side of pig.
Coffee, black.
Fantastic.
You are a virile manifestation
of the divine.
What the hell
did he say to me?
Oh, it's funny?
Yeah, no. Go ahead.
Laugh it up, Sam. Hilarious.
Dean...
Oh, he speaks.
...Look...
Sam.
Look, we're both here.
All right, the chance
of either one of us leaving
while people are still dying
out there --
You might as well
bite the bullet
and work with me
on this one.
I don't know if I can.
I'm not asking you
to open up a can of worms.
Okay,
I'm not even asking you
where the hell you've been
for the past week and a half.
Good.
I'm just saying, let's
try and stop the killings.
That's it.
Okay.
Okay? Good.
Can I help you?
You're the brothers
from the --
Oh, no, no, no, no.
The Winchester guys on the news
a couple weeks back?
- No -- we get that a lot.
- Yeah, no.
Those depraved killers
got put down
like the dogs
that they were.
Us on the other hand,
we're completely harmless.
Oh, yeah!
I'm sorry. Silly me.
And I can see by your energies,
you're completely gentle.
Excuse my friend.
She's excitable.
Sweetheart, look at them, hmm?
They're FBI.
Oh!
I'm Russian.
We can spot the law.
You must be here
about the tragedies.
Oh, we're just beside ourselves
about what happened.
Yeah. And so close
to festival season, huh?
Yeah -- no --
Of course
we are worried.
We have no idea
what's going on, huh?
Nikolai.
Let me know if I can help you.
I'm highly intuitive.
Nikolai Lishin,
spoon bender?
Mm. World famous.
Come to my demonstration
at the festival, huh?
Ugh!
I teach you to harness
the power of your mind.
Come,
let's leave them be.
So glad we decided
to vacation here, huh? Right?
All right.
Here we go.
First death.
Second death.
What am I looking at?
Well, see this?
Now, this is Imelda Graven,
death number one.
She was brained
by her own crystal ball.
Bummer, and ironic.
Same necklace?
Yeah. See, Imelda gave it
to Goldy in her will.
Okay, so,
cursed object, maybe?
Worth looking into.
Goldy's next of kin
lives in town, also a psychic.
Oh, good.
I haven't had my fill.
He broke my spoon.
Melanie Golden?
Hi.
Uh...Got a minute?
You want me to stay?
No, that's okay.
Okay.
Thanks for
stopping by, hon.
Of course.
A friend.
She just heard
about my grandmother...
Which is, I guess, why you guys
are here, so come on in.
Sorry.
I just got back.
You were
out of town?
Yeah, I work the circuit --
hotels, conventions, you know.
Oh. Wait.
No offense, but...
You don't seem
all that psychic.
Why do you say that?
Well, I mean, just, you know,
where's all the...
crystals and pyramids?
I'm off the clock.
Also not psychic.
What?
It's an honest living.
Interesting definition
of "honest."
Well, I honestly
read people.
It's just less whoo-whoo,
more body language.
Like you two --
longtime partners,
but, um...
a lot of tension.
You're pissed.
And you're stressed.
It's not brain surgery.
It's kind of why my grandma
and me didn't get along.
I mean,
she'd go full smoke-machine,
but she still actually believed
in all that stuff, so...
You don't?
You do?
I've got an open mind.
You'd be surprised.
Hmm.
I'm sorry to have to ask,
b-but there's a necklace
of your grandmother's.
Don't have it. Everything
went straight to the emporium.
She had a deal
with the owner.
The emporium?
Mm.
You're looking...
for something.
You're good.
- You "Jimmy Tomorrow"?
- Mm-hmm.
We're looking for
a necklace.
Oh. Romantic.
It would have come in
with grandma Goldy's effects.
Oh. Yes, yes.
Now, you do know that this
is the Orb of Thessaly.
We did not know.
Very powerful,
very rare.
Let me guess.
Very expensive.
Worth every penny.
Well, in that case,
we'll be taking
the state's-evidence discount.
What's going on?
A murder investigation
that we'd like to personally
thank you for not obstructing.
You know, I give
private energetic readings.
No, thanks.
A loss weighs on you.
You're angry.
It's complicated.
Come see me, Agent.
Thanks, Jimmy.
We'll see you.
The bureau's gonna reimburse me
for the necklace, right?
Oh, we'll send you
a check.
Right.
Went a little "Mentalist"
on you there, didn't he?
All right. Next question.
What's an Orb of Thessaly?
I know one thing --
it's made in Taiwan.
Oh, a fake, around here.
Imagine that.
'Course, that means that
whatever's killing mediums
is still out there.
He probably
should have bent those
with the power
of his mind.
Chief.
- We met at the station.
- Right. Morning, Agent.
Morning.
Uh, this is Agent Borne.
So, what happened?
It's a weird one.
Chest full of cutlery.
All right.
We're gonna take a look around.
Let us know
if you get any leads.
Oh, I got leads
coming out of my ass.
As of 9:00,
our tip line had 46 calls,
all from clairvoyants that know
what really happened.
What's the popular theory?
It's a toss-up
between a ghost
and some sort of ogre
that only attacks Russians.
Policing Lily Dale
sounds fun.
It was either this
or Los Angeles.
So, these clairvoyants,
did they give any details
as to why they thought
it was a ghost?
Or a...
Russian ogre?
Their spirit monkey
said so.
Plus, apparently,
this guy claims
he had a vision
of his own death,
cutlery and all.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Agent Borne?
It's Melanie Golden.
Everything okay?
Did you mean it when you said
you had an open mind?
I hadn't checked it
until today.
I mean, the only person
who ever called my landline
was my grandma.
That's okay. Go on.
Look, I wouldn't
put any stock in it.
I mean,
she was always calling me
with some crazy dream
she was sure was a sign,
that kind of thing,
but...
Uh, is it true Nikolai
had a real vision of his death?
That's what
we were told, yeah.
Well, so did she --
the day she died.
What'd she say?
Well, you can listen to it
if you want.
She said
she was in a seance,
then the lights go,
it's freezing.
Wait, she said that?
That the room got cold?
Yeah. Why?
Is that important?
What? What is it?
A ghost.
The real deal.
Come on.
You're serious.
Yeah.
See, there's, uh,
fake whoo-whoo crap,
and there's
real whoo-whoo crap.
Well, yeah, but...
Ghosts?
Oh, trust me.
There's a lot weirder
out there than that.
So "The X-files" is real,
or you just stopped talking
like an FBI Agent.
Well, um...
We're not FBI agents.
I need a drink.
I support that.
You know,
if this is a spirit,
it ain't your average spook
tied to a house.
I mean, this thing
is boogieing all over town.
Not surprised.
I mean,
how many crystal balls
do you figure there are
in Lily Dale?
Somewhere between 50
and, uh, all of them.
Well, I mean,
quartz can act
as an antenna
for spirits, right?
I mean,
that's why mediums
started using crystal balls
in the first place.
Well, that means that
every storefront in town
has got a ghost
satellite dish.
Exactly.
And this place is packed
with people summoning spirits.
Yeah, but, dude,
most of these guys
can't even call a taxi.
All it takes is one.
That's gonna be like
looking for a needle
in a stack of fake needles.
It's worse.
I mean,
I'll bet you anything
some of these guys
got real juice.
I'm not talking
kill-people level.
I'm just saying,
enough to make it complicated.
I hate this town.
All right, so, what?
Start hitting up
the Miss Cleos?
I was thinking
split up and canvass.
It's faster.
Right.
'Course you were.
What is it?
My brother?
Is he
going back to prison?
Stay away.
His curse
will drag you down.
Folks do turn jail
into a habit, you know?
Oh, no, no.
Don't fret.
I's always say,
family...
Is a pain in the ass
anyhow!
Thank you,
Sister Thibideaux.
No, child.
Thank the spirits.
Now, will that be
cash or credit?
It's okay.
Like I said on the phone,
he can help.
Phony lawman, huh?
Yeah, 'cause nobody
can relate to phony around here.
Well, if you can
do something,
I don't care
if you call yourself the Pope.
All right.
What happened, exactly?
What happened is,
I had a friggin' vision.
Something is coming for me.
What's coming?
Did you get a look?
No.
But I sure felt it when it
started breaking my bones.
I don't want to die.
Okay.
We'll figure it out.
The vision happened
in here?
Yeah, by the cash box.
There any chance
good-lookin' was watching?
What was that?
What the hell?!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
W-was that, I mean,
an actual --
Bona fide. Yeah.
Well, no offense,
but nobody's having
psychic visions around here.
This, uh, spirit, whoever
she is, is giving them out.
And then killing people?
Until we stop her.
Well, the good news is
you said
you saw a clock
and it read 2:00 a.m.,
so that gives us
a little time.
Now, does anybody recognize
this chick?
You know,
I swear I've seen her,
like in a painting
or something.
A painting? Like, a --
No, not a painting.
In one of those old photos
in the museum.
Lily Dale has long been a haven
for the psychically gifted.
Tortured elsewhere,
they're embraced here.
My own family
has a modest natural gift.
We also celebrate
our long and colorful
history of...
Embellishers.
Ectoplasm illusion,
circa 1890.
Never ended well
for the siblings.
Why is that?
Mm, the strain
of working together,
or maybe just being around
each other all their lives.
Those two were the exception,
actually -- the Campbells.
Got along famously.
Of course,
that was just a stage name.
They weren't actually
brothers.
That was a cover
for their, um...
Alternative lifestyle.
Any other questions
I can answer?
Yes. Who are they?
Oh, the Fox sisters --
among the founders
of Lily Dale.
Kate Fox --
quite troubled,
apparently,
but mesmerizing onstage.
She's said
to be able to levitate objects
and foretell
one's death.
That's her.
Her older sister,
Margaret --
perhaps not
a natural psychic.
So, full of crap.
Yes, well...
She didn't have
her sister's charisma,
but she
looked after Kate.
Sometimes, one's true gift
is taking care of others.
So, what happened
to them?
Lived here
all their lives.
and died here?
Yes, well...
buried in the cemetery.
Great.
That was very educational.
Thank you.
Dean.
I don't normally do this
during business hours,
but do you know
an Eleanor...
or an Ellen?
She seems quite concerned
about you.
She wants to tell you --
pardon me --
if you don't tell someone
how bad it really is,
she'll kick your ass
from beyond.
You have to trust someone
again eventually.
Anyway, don't forget to visit
the gift shop.
All right.
Hit up the graveyard,
dig up Kate?
All right.
Wait a second.
All signs
point to her, Dean.
No. Just hold on
a damn minute.
Enough with
"just the facts."
We agreed --
No, we agreed
to work the case.
We didn't agree for you to be
a dick the whole time.
What?
You're pissed, okay?
- And you've got a right.
- Yeah, damn straight.
- But enough's enough.
- Says who?
Look, I'll work
this damn case,
but you lied to me,
and you killed my friend.
No, I put down a monster
who killed four people,
and if you didn't know her,
you'd have done the same thing.
I did know her, Dean.
Yeah, which is why
you couldn't do it.
Look, I get it.
There are certain people
in this world,
no matter how dangerous
they are, you just can't.
Don't pull that card.
That's bull.
Look, if I've learned
one thing,
it's that if something
feels wrong, it probably is!
Usually, yeah.
But killing Amy was not wrong.
You couldn't do it,
so I did.
That's what family does --
the dirty work.
And I would have told you
eventually,
once I knew that this whole
"waving a gun at Satan" thing
was a one-time show.
I think it's reasonable
to want to know
that you're off
the friggin' high dive, Sam.
You almost
got us both killed,
so you can be pissed
all you want,
but quit being a bitch.
I get
why she's killing people.
I don't get
why she's warning them.
Give them a taste
of the curse, maybe?
It couldn't have been
a joyride.
Here we go.
Sam!
Back off, crazy eyes.
Listen to me.
Why isn't anybody
listening?
No.
You don't get a vote.
No! Stop!
No!
Nice timing.
Got it.
And, Dean, thanks.
They took care of it.
Okay, so...
What -- just go home?
I guess.
Hey, why don't you come
stay with me a couple days?
Thanks.
Just one more minute.
It's fine, hon.
Oh, if you had
that vision,
you wouldn't want
to be here either.
Camille, it's okay.
Let's just go.
What is it?
Call them back! Now!
Melanie?
Dean,
you have to come back.
What's going on?
It's still happening!
Wait, what
do you mean it's --
She's still coming! Just tell me
what the hell to do!
All right. Listen to me.
Calm down.
Dean, just give me the phone
and drive.
Melanie? Hey.
Get to the kitchen.
Okay.
- Aah!
- She's here!
- All right, just go. Get salt.
- Aah!
It worked.
She's gone!
No, she's back!
Aah!
I'm out of salt!
Find iron.
Is there a fireplace?
Melanie!
Aah!
Oh, God! Mel!
Camille! Camille!
Camille! No!
Aah!
Should have known that whole
"good sis, bad sis" story
was just showmanship crap.
Oh, and it turns out
that Kate was just
trying to warn people
about her evil bitch
sister.
And we burned her bones,
so that's gone.
- Dean.
- What?
All we can do now
is go stop her.
That's not good enough,
by a mile.
I know. Believe me.
But --
can we talk
about this later?
Hey.
How you holding up?
Been better.
Listen, if you need
for us to leave --
I need you guys to leave.
Okay, we will.
It's just that...
Look -- Margaret
is still out there.
What do you guys
need to know?
Is there anything
that stood out?
Well, um...
She barely gave a crap
about me.
I mean,
I was just in the way.
She was all about
getting Camille.
- Okay. That's something.
- One other thing.
Um...She enjoyed it.
She was smiling.
I feel naked
doing this in daylight.
Yeah.
Let's just hurry up.
All right, mags.
My lighter's juiced
this time.
Geraldo'd.
Not good.
Never good.
Dean, if someone knew enough
to take Margaret's bones,
they're not
kidding around.
That's serious
binding magic.
Great.
Psychic ghost bitch
on a leash.
We got to find
those bones.
So we got to find
the bonehead.
So, what?
We call Bobby,
see what it takes
to harness
the power of a ghost?
Yeah.
Hey, Sam, you know why
I'm not going to spend my money
at the annual
Lily Dale E.S.P. Festival
and hot-dog-eating
contest this year?
Can't imagine.
Because all the headliners
are dead.
You know, after Nikolai...
They asked Camille
to take his spot.
I mean,
she's so popular.
Was so popular.
Okay, all these people --
would you say that they're
the, uh, you know,
top dogs in town?
Well, it's not really
like that.
But they were all doing well.
I mean, your grandma?
She wrote a few books.
Yeah, and Imelda was on
"the Nate Berkus Show" twice,
so, yeah, I guess
they were doing pretty well.
You think that's why
she went after them?
I mean,
if you had to guess,
who do you think
would be next in line?
I mean, I don't know.
Well, your grandma
was headlining at the big hall,
so who do you think they would
ask to fill in for her?
Probably...
...Me.
Hey.
Agent.
Are you here with my check?
I'm looking for someone
who bought some things from you.
How do you know from me?
I'm kind of doubting
they sell ash-wood altars
at the Gas 'n Sip.
Valid.
Let me see the list.
Ah. Here we go.
Credit-card receipt.
I assume you want
the address?
That would be great.
Thanks.
It's the least I can do.
I just heard about
Camille Thibideaux.
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
Are you sure
that'll work?
That should hold her off
long enough
for Sam to find the bones
and burn them.
Hopefully.
Hopefully?
Does it hurt 'em?
Burning their bones?
I never really
thought about it.
Probably, yeah.
Good.
Where's the altar?!
It's there!
You're...
not a necromancer.
This is a lamaze class,
I swear.
I-I believe you.
Sorry.
Om...
- Dean, it's the pawn-shop guy.
- How do you know?
He goose-chased me to
a friggin' pregnant yoga class.
All right, well, figure out
where he put her bones.
I will.
Fast, Sam.
Somehow, I just knew
you'd be back.
Hi, Agent.
Put the skull down.
Okay, okay.
Take it easy. Here.
All right.
That's enough.
- Is she gone?
- I doubt it.
But she can't get past
the line, right?
Right.
Nice binding spell.
It doesn't matter.
She helps me
because she wants to.
What?
Oh. Damn it.
I hate when they do that.
Get the salt. Go.
Dean!
Margaret and me
are the same.
We're the real thing.
But guess what --
sometimes the real thing
just isn't pretty
or entertaining enough.
When I show people what I'm
capable of, it scares them.
I can't pay my rent!
Get behind me.
That's as far
as you go, bitch.
Margaret's happy
to kill for me.
She likes the leash.
You're sick.
You know what else I am?
A real psychic,
you dick-bag.
Surprise.
Aw.
Sorry, handsome.
Where are
the rest of the bones?
These people
don't deserve to die.
Oh, come on!
Are you kidding me?
I live in squalor 'cause I can't
put on a show like them?
Don't do this.
- They're in the bedroom, aren't they?
- No.
You're not
getting in there.
Dean!
Too bad.
Dean.
In the bed?
They were in the bed?
Yeah.
Ugh. I can't believe
he was boning her.
Dean.
Can I get you
anything else?
Uh, just a refill.
And if you affirmate me,
I'm gonna punch you in the face.
All righty then.
Coffee, coming up.
I can't wait to get out
of this frickin' fortune cookie.
Dean.
I'm gonna go, um...
Do something outside.
Okay.
- Hi. Have a seat.
- Hi.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
You didn't stick around
so I could say thank you.
No reason to thank me.
You saved my life.
Yeah, but not
your friend's.
Well...
you didn't
send that ghost, so...
Thank you
for coming to kill it.
You and Sam
seem a little better.
You could tell that
from the walk up?
Take it or leave it.
Also guessing you're not so keen
to come visit here again,
so...this is goodbye.
Wish we'd met
on a better week.
I wish I had
better weeks.
Hm.
But, uh, hey.
You never know.
It's not like
you can tell the future, right?
Hmm.
Well, answer's hazy.
Try again later.
Right.
- Hey.
That's your stuff.
Yeah. Yeah.
I figured we'd take one car.
Works for me.
You still want to break my face?
No.
Uh, not at this moment.
Look, you know what?
Um...
You were right.
About Amy.
If she was...
just any monster,
I'm not sure I could have
let her walk away.
I don't know.
I mean, I'll never know.
So, what are you saying?
What I'm saying is...
I get why you did it.
You were just trying to
make sure no one else got hurt.
But here's the thing.
You can't just
look me in the face
and tell me you're fine.
I mean, you're not sleeping,
you drink for the record --
Oh, here we go.
Look, whatever.
Last one to preach. I know.
But...
Just be honest with me.
How are those
the actions of someone
who knows
they did the right thing?
- You want me to be honest?
- Yeah.
I went with my gut.
And that felt right.
I didn't trust her, Sam.
Of course,
ever since Cass,
I'm having a hard time
trusting anybody.
And as far
as how I been acting...
I don't know.
Maybe it's 'cause
I don't like lying to you.
You know,
it doesn't feel right.
So, yeah, you got me there.
I been climbing the walls.
I know how that is.
But, hey...
If I learned one thing
from that museum,
sibling acts are tough.
Oh, don't compare us
to that hall of crazy.
We're like poster kids
of functional family life
compared to them.
- It's a low bar.
- Well, hey... grading on a
curve has got me past everything
since kindergarten,
so don't knock it.
Whatever you say.
I still want to know
how that guy bent my spoon.
Forget it, Sam.
It's Lily Dale.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==