Frank Devereaux --
he's a jackass and a lunatic.
He's also a surveillance expert.
"Hey, Frank, go dig up some dirt
on Richard Roman."
That night, I was burned off
every I.P. I had.
Ears on my phone,
eyes on my house...
Dick's got people
watching you?
Frank! Don't shoot!
We're coming in.
Who's to say this ain't
the day they come for old Frank
who knew too much.
Bobby! Hey!
Your time is up.
Bobby. You ran away
from your reaper?
Hi, boys.
- Bobby.
- You can see me?
Rethink it, Bobby.
We still have work to do.
It's not right.
You know that.
What was I thinking?
So, what do you think
we should do?
I don't know.
Everything
is supposed to end.
You know,
he was supposed...
Now...What are the odds
this ends well?
What are the odds?
Yeah, I hear you. All right,
well, thanks for looking.
Yep. Bye.
So, Nora didn't see any pattern
to the dig sites either.
Yeah, 'cause they got
nothing in common.
And I got nothing
from local lore
50 miles in every direction
of all of them.
I mean, it's like
they're just...
old dirt.
What's Dick looking for?
Hey, hey, go easy,
you idjits.
Sorry for the jump scare.
So how does this work, huh?
I leave the cap off
and you just genie your way out?
I wish it were that easy.
The thing is --
Bobby?
Damn it.
It's hard to stay focused.
I'm still kind of worn out.
You've been pretty busy
for a dead guy.
All right. Listen.
I-I don't know how long
before my next ghost nap,
so let's just
skip to the skinny --
those numbers I gave you.
The empty lot
in Cheeseville?
Yeah, well, it ain't gonna be
empty for long.
I got a gander
at Dick's big plan,
right before
he Lincolned me.
They're breaking ground --
what month is this?
Uh, April.
Ground's broke.
They're surveying.
They're getting ready
to build something.
- Build what?
- Exactly.
What?
They're building
as we're yammering.
Check it out yourself.
It's all right.
I mean, you guys missed it
because you've been kind of busy
killing ghosts
the past few days.
But Dick is about to get into
the Soylent Green business.
That site'll show you they're
building a biotech lab, right?
Biotech my ass.
That sucker
is a state-of-the-art
slaughterhouse.
And we're the beef.
Don't you think that's
a little bold, even for Dick?
I bet you
no one will even notice,
'cause first,
he's gonna dumb us all down
with Turducken-style
munchies.
Make us docile.
It's in the meat.
We haven't been to Biggerson's
since that whole fiasco.
Biggerson's? He's bought a list
of joints 10 pages long.
Ah.
Next, he's gonna cure us.
Cure us of what?
All the biggies --
cancer, aids, heart disease.
Let's just say they got an
affinity for stem-cell research.
The, uh,
Leviathan real-estate mooks
building
that cancer center.
It's going to be
a research center.
Research for what?
They're not hunting anymore.
They're engineering
the perfect herd.
With the very first dose,
it starts to work on their DNA,
slowing their metabolism,
causing weight gain,
and dampening
their emotional range,
which makes them
perfectly complacent.
Now,
we've gone up against plenty --
liked to eat a few folk
in the woods.
This ain't that.
This is about knocking us off
the top of the food chain.
This is about them Levis
living here forever,
one-percenter style,
while we march
our dopey, fat asses
down to the shiny new
death camps at every corner.
It's an e-mail...
from Frank.
Frank's alive?
That jackass,
always stealing my thunder.
"Sam and Dean, if you're
reading this, I'm dead..."
"...or worse.
"This e-mail was sent
"because some prince is trying
to hack into my hard drive
"right this second.
So unless it's you,
you got trouble."
Um  okay
"my drive is full
of compromising info.
Your new aliases, hangouts,
where you stored your car..."
Baby?
Even though he encrypted
the crap out of his drive,
he says we should assume
that someone can hack into it
eventually.
He did put a tracking device
in it.
All right, let's see
where Frank's drive is.
Perfect.
It's in the middle
of the Death Star.
? Supernatural 7x20 ?
The Girl With the Dungeons and Dragons Tattoo
Original Air Date on April 27, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
? I used to think
maybe you loved me ?
? now, baby, I'm sure ?
? and I just can't wait
till the day ?
? when you knock on my door ?
? now every time
I go for the mailbox ?
? gotta hold myself down ?
? 'cause I just wait ?
? till you write me
you're coming around ?
? now, I'm walking on sunshine ?
? whoa ?
? I'm walking on sunshine ?
? and don't it feel good? ?
? hey ?
How'd it go last night?
Charlie,
it's a moral imperative you let
me live vicariously through you.
Pictures or it didn't happen,
right?
You hooked up
at a charity benefit?
If you can't score at a
reproductive rights function,
then you simply
cannot score.
Wait. Is that legal?
We were
two consenting adults.
No. That.
Why do you insist on breaking
the law on company property?
Mmm, faster Internet connection
here.
Oh, well, if Pete finds out,
he's gonna fire you...
or get you arrested.
Teddy Bear Pete?
Please.
You know I've been doing this
for like a month.
I can cover
my tracks, Harry.
Trust me.
Charlie!
My office. Now.
- I love you.
- I know.
Charlie Bradbury?
Dick.
Sit.
Charlie, I've been
running things for, well,
feels like since before
the dawn of man.
Always had a vision.
I'm close
to realizing that dream.
I don't want to brag, but
the world is my dinner plate.
And I don't want anything
to jeopardize that --
definitely not the actions
of one tiny, little person.
Sir, sir, I can fix this.
Please -- please don't fire me.
What's she talking about?
Is that about hacking
those Super Pacs?
'Cause that was adorable.
Tell me, how does
a high-school dropout
become one of the
brightest minds at Roman, Inc.?
Um...Honestly...
Historically,
I've had this problem
with -- with authority --
no offense --
so I realized the only way
to get away with being me
was to be as indispensable
as possible.
Sorry.
You're kind of completing me
right now, Charlie.
You have that spark,
that thing that makes humans
so special.
Not everyone has it,
you know.
Those people --
they can be replaced.
But people like you...
are impossible to copy.
C-copy?
Take the compliment.
This belonged
to one Frank Devereaux.
Thought he could bring down
the whole company.
He was wrong.
Let's keep him wrong.
It's encrypted, or whatever
you crazy kids say these days.
Break it open
and bring it to me.
Yeah, I'm on it.
And -- and thank you.
You're welcome.
You have three days
or you're fired.
Good talk.
Is this real life?
Dick Roman gave me
an assignment.
Is that...Good?
It means the Eye of Sauron
is on me.
Well, if you need anything,
I'll be back in the shire.
All right, H.
It's just you and me now.
Access denied.
Access denied. Access denied.
How about a nice game of chess?
Wait a second.
Seriously?
"Wargames"?
Access granted.
Shall we play a game, bitches?
That was hardly
the Chamber of Secrets, right?
Booyah.
And back to square one.
Let's see where
Frank's drive is.
Perfect.
It's in the middle
of the Death Star.
All right, well,
off to Chicago.
No, wait, boys,
you can't just break in.
They know your mugs.
What if we mailed in the flask?
Then I could ghost through
the joint.
I mean, it's not like
Dick can kill me twice.
What,
you got a better plan?
Come on.
Just because I'm dead
doesn't mean I don't know
how to do my damn job.
Bobby,
that's Dick's office.
I think
what Sam's trying to say is,
what happens
if you run into Dick
and, you know...
go vengeful.
You know it's not something
you can just shake off.
Come on.
Give me some credit.
What, I'm supposed to
just ride the pine?
Sorry, Bobby.
Did you go home
last night?
I'll get us some coffee.
I assume you want
some crack in yours.
Yes, please.
Finally.
Who is this d-bag?
Don't do it.
Roman said
to bring it right to him.
You're right, H.
You're always right.
What the frak's a Leviathan?
"The thing to know
about Leviathan
"is these monsters
are as old as time,
"strong as all get-out.
"Sodium borate --
commonly known as borax.
"Decapitation is the key.
"Then put that head in a box.
"These are the Superman
of monsters
"from the black hole
of purgatory.
"They can shapeshift, take your
face, your memory -- the works.
"The top boss
is Mr. Dick Roman.
He runs the show."
"Cut one, you see black goo.
"We're through
the looking glass.
"Blood is black,
and black is blood.
"Don't turn your back.
Get out of the building.
Get out of the county."
How goes it?
Pretty sure I spent the last 24
hours hacking into a loony bin.
Where's Pete?
Uh, probably snuck down
to the garage for a smoky treat.
How's it going
with that drive?
Uh, great.
Charlie was here
all night.
You know, that drive's
very important to me.
I'm gonna want
a watchful eye kept.
Well,
I will do just that.
No. You won't.
Bruce Springsteen, Eli Manning,
our own little Charlie --
you know what they are?
Irreplaceable.
You're more of a Tim Tebow,
Joe Biden type.
You got no spark in you.
In fact,
there's nothing in you...
except Daryl's dinner.
Hey, Pete, sorry I left
without telling you.
No, I just wasn't...
feeling well.
It's a...lady thing.
I will be in first thing.
Got to go -- cramps.
It's all right.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Get away from me, you...
Shapeshifter!
Look,
we're not shapeshifters.
Oh!
Geez!
Look, we're not Leviathans,
okay?
You want us to prove it?
You know what borax does
to them?
Sam?
Huh?
Your turn.
Good.
Who the hell are you guys?
America --
a nation of greatness...
...a nation
of hardworking individuals.
And, rest assured,
no one works harder for you
than Sucrocorp.
Here at Sucrocorp,
your well-being
is our number-one priority.
Sucrocorp --
eat well, live well.
So you're saying, you guys
are monster hunters.
So, there are other monsters?
Stop. Never mind.
Just shh.
Okay, I get
how you tracked the drive --
straight GPS --
but it's still at the office.
How did you find me?
Aw! Son of a gun
jacked my webcam?!
Welcome to Frank.
It's creepy,
but I'll give it to him.
So you're telling me everything
he had on his drive is true.
That and more.
Wait. How long did it take you
to crack into Frank's drive?
A day or so.
Is there anything
you can't hack into?
Not yet.
How about
Dick Roman's e-mail?
Why would I...
Oh. He's one of them.
No. Uh,
he's their leader.
So what's the end game --
steal our resources,
make us some slaves?
Planet-wide value meal.
We're the meat.
You can't be...serious.
Okay. All right.
Let's do this.
What am I looking for?
Well, for starters, uh, anything
about archaeological dig sites.
Like Indiana Jones stuff?
All we know is that Dick has
been digging all over the world,
and we need to know
what he's looking for.
You know, I was having
a really good week.
I met someone,
downloaded the new Robyn album.
Everything
was coming up me.
Oh, crap.
Look, we get it sucks.
No, not that. This.
Dick's e-mail isn't
on the company server.
It's on a private one,
in his office.
Meaning?
Can't get in it unless you have
his phone or you're at his desk.
So you're saying that if
we're inside Dick's office,
then we can hack into
his e-mail?
You can't.
Only someone like...
But I sure as hell
ain't doing it.
I am doing my job
and...
What are the chances
I see everything on that drive
and Dick lets me live
anyway?
I think you know.
So I erase the drive first,
protect me and you.
Then I go back
to my old life, right?
- What?
- It's not that easy.
You're on Dick's radar,
which means you don't have
an old life anymore.
I'm gonna die.
I should have taken that job
at Google.
Look, Charlie,
it's okay if you can't do it.
I mean,
you didn't volunteer for this.
Totally. Exactly.
But now I volunteer.
What?
I got to go back in anyways
to wipe Frank's drive.
Might as well
break into Dick's office, too.
Are you sure?
No. But these things
are gonna eat everyone I know.
What kind of douche bag
stands by for that?
However, I have never
broken into anything
in real life before,
so...plan?
Got a Bluetooth?
Yeah.
Security system --
can you get into that?
I can reroute any
surveillance cameras we need.
All right.
Let's start with that.
Do you have a key card
to get in the building?
Uh, yeah.
I can't duplicate it,
but I can make a fake backing.
How's it going?
Great,
since she set all this up.
Um, look.
See this?
I can put each camera
on a prerecorded loop.
Once I do that,
she'll have 15 minutes.
15 minutes
ain't a lot of time.
No.
She said if it took longer
to hack his desktop,
then she deserved
to be eaten.
I like her.
Wait. Is that...
Son of a bitch.
What?
Look at her bag.
Bobby.
Wait. Y-you think he --
hitched a ride after
we told him to cool his jets?
Yeah.
What the hell's he thinking?
He's not.
So what do we do --
call the whole thing off?
We only got
one shot at this.
? used to think
maybe you loved me ? --
Charlie, Dean.
Are you singing?
I sing when I'm nervous.
Don't judge me.
Judgment-free zone.
Listen, uh, check
the side pocket in your bag.
Oh.
Thank you.
Mmm. Good idea.
Yeah, no problem.
Look, that's, uh, kind of
a family heirloom.
It's a good-luck charm,
okay, so don't lose it.
Copy that.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Uh, Charlie?
I'm having a hard time moving.
You can do this.
Uh, I'm -- I'm not a spy.
No, I can't do it. I can't
do it. I can't do it. I can't.
Charlie, hey, it's Sam.
I'm sorry, Sam.
I'm sorry. I-I just --
it's okay.
Uh, listen, w-who's your favorite
"Harry Potter" character?
Uh, Hermione.
Hermione.
Well, uh, all right,
did Hermione run
when Sirius Black
was in trouble
or when Voldemort
attacked Hogwarts?
- Seriously?
- Shut it.
No, of course not.
What did she do?
She kicked ass.
She actually saves Harry
in practically every book.
And then she ends up
with the wrong --
Uh, stay on track.
Okay,
so she kicked ass, right?
So, then,
what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna kick it in the ass.
Good girl.
Oh, you go, dumble-dork.
I'm in.
I've always wanted to say that.
You're on the clock.
Move.
Hey, there's a big-ass guard
up here, blocking the door.
What do I do?
Just wait him out.
He's not going anywhere.
Okay, uh,
you work there every day.
- Do you know the guy?
- I guess.
I mean, I've seen him.
I've never talked to him.
Okay, when you've seen him,
does he look at you,
or does he just kind of
slide his eyes by?
Um...Eye contact?
I don't know.
He always kind of smiles a bit.
- I don't really --
- Good.
What you're gonna do is you're
gonna walk right up to him,
and you're gonna flirt
your way past.
I can't.
He's not my type.
You're gonna have to play
through that.
As in he's not a girl.
Oh, oh.
Pretend he has boobs.
Worse.
I don't know. Um...
Do you have any tattoos?
Give him a little sneak peek
there.
All tattoos are sexy.
Mine is Princess Leia
in a slave bikini
straddling a 20-sided die.
I was drunk.
It was Comic-Con.
We've all been there.
Okay, I'm gonna walk you
through this.
Start with a smile.
Relax, Charlie.
You just got home,
and Scarlett Johansson's
waiting for you.
Can I help you, miss?
Hey...Bill.
Charlie from I.T.
Oh. Burning the midnight oil,
huh?
Just like you -- I mean,
when you're not at the gym.
What, do you work out
with all your free time?
I try to get to the
gym at least three days a week.
You know, just trying to
get back to my fighting weight,
you know?
It shows. You look amazing.
It shows.
You look amazing.
This never happened.
Do you ever do anything else
with your free time,
like take a girl out
for a drink?
You do anything else
with your free time,
like take a girl out for a drink?
Stop laughing, Sammy.
Um...Y-you don't know
that bar --
Stop Laughing Sammy?
That place
is bringing sexy back.
Stop talking, Charlie!
Which is easy, 'cause they kept the receipt.
Stop talking, Charlie.
Right.
So, um, y-you were saying
about going out, drinks?
Um...Yeah, yeah.
That'd be great.
Cool.
Pencil that in.
Hey,
can I ask you a favor?
The ladies' room downstairs
is nasty.
Can I use the exec washroom
to powder my nose?
Yeah, yeah. Why not?
Um, it's right down the hall.
It's the first door
on the right.
I feel dirty.
You and me both, sister.
The eagle is landing.
Going radio-silent.
Let us know
when you're out.
So, guess we just wait?
Yeah.
Your password
is "w1nn1ng" with two 1's?
Ew!
Okay. Let's Yoda this.
Hey, you!
What are you doing
in here?
You said first door
on the left, right?
No, I said first door
on the right.
Oh! Silly me.
I am always forgetting things.
Do you know
what else I forgot to do?
Give you my phone number.
Uh, we really shouldn't
be in here.
Mr. Roman doesn't like
people in his office.
I'm sure.
Have you seen his bathroom?
Got to go.
Call me.
Well, this is awesome.
You know what? New plan.
From now on,
we just stay in the van
and send in
the 90-pound girl.
Dean, every chomper on earth
knows our face.
How many do you think
are in that building?
We wouldn't make it
past the lobby.
Yeah, I know.
Doesn't mean
I got to be happy
about sending in
freaking Veronica Mars.
She'll be fine...
Or we'll go in.
- We'll get as far as we can.
- Damn right.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Sending you all
the flagged dig files now.
Charlie,
you are a genius!
I know. It's a problem.
Damn it.
Hey, Pete!
Guess we're both on deadline,
huh?
How's it going?
Good, good.
I'll give you a full
progress report in a few hours.
Great.
Hit that deadline,
right?
Well, holler
if you need anything.
Hey, guys, you still there?
Yeah.
What the hell was that?
Oh, just my manager,
the monster.
Leave.
I can't. I got to act normal.
I told him I was working.
Let's just finish this.
Are you seeing this?
It looks like Dick stopped
digging days ago.
Why?
Guess he found
what he was looking for.
- Can you check?
- Way ahead of you.
Looking at travel reports,
expenses...
Here we go.
Something in his suitcase
left Iran last week.
Spent the last 72 hours in
armored cars and private planes.
Whatever it is, it's coming here
for Dick tonight.
So, w-what the hell is it?
I don't know. Whatever it is,
he wants it bad,
which means we got to grab it,
end of story.
Well, it's landing at
a private airport near here --
crap -- right about now.
A courier's set
to pick it up.
What's the exact
landing time?
42 minutes.
Can you make it?
We can try.
Uh, all right, Charlie,
one more favor,
and then
get the hell out of there.
Outstanding.
And you'll call as soon
as the package is in hand?
Absolutely.
I'm here waiting.
In fact, I've got time
for a light snack.
Hey, Charlie.
I was hoping
I'd find you here.
Hey. Watch it.
So now what?
I've been looking for this
for a very, very long time.
Now,
who could have done that?
A courier's set to pick it up.
- What's the exact landing time?
- 42 minutes.
Can you make it?
We can try.
Uh, all right, Charlie,
one more favor,
and then
get the hell out of there.
What do you need?
More time.
Then let's get you some.
Travel department's
e-mailing Dick.
Suitcase still en route,
but diverted by weather
and will be 30 minutes late.
I'll finish
mopping you guys off the drive
and get the hell out of Dodge.
Call us when you're clear.
Text you from the border,
bro.
Hey.
Watch it.
Hey, Charlie.
I was hoping
I'd find you here.
Um, hey, Mr. Roman.
Please. Dick.
Pete, we're good here.
Why don't you go grab a bite?
Show me what you found.
So now what?
See what we've won.
Did we just...steal
a-a hunk of red clay?
That's a good question.
Why don't we answer that a few
thousand miles away from here, though?
Where is Charlie?
So there's nothing
about my company?
Mnh-mnh.
Ah.
How about a Sam or a Dean?
I'm sorry, who?
Sam and Dean Winchester.
Give it a little peek,
would you?
Dick Roman.
Come on.
The girl's right there.
Worry about her.
Is it me, or did it
just drop 10 degrees in here?
It's a bit nippy, yeah.
I'll have maintenance
check the A.C.
I can't have you cold,
now, can I?
You miserable...
Damn it, Bobby, come on.
Nothing about
those Winchesters.
If items were deleted
from the drive,
would you be able
to tell?
Not if they were
deleted properly.
Well, they're crafty.
Have all the data
sent to me.
Of course.
So, really,
how did you do it?
Uh, do what?
You broke the unbreakable.
What's the thought process?
Walk me through it,
and ix-nay the jargon.
Um...nothing's unbreakable,
really.
Nothing's safe
if you poke at it long enough.
Nothing's safe.
I like that.
But that isn't
what I'm asking, Charlie.
Your spark --
it's one in a million.
Believe me,
but when you got it,
you invent guns and iPads
and viruses,
and, holy crap,
you can be crafty.
- What is that, Charlie?
- Um --
'cause I can feed every fact
in your brain to someone else,
they still wouldn't be able
to be you.
I guess
you can't clone me.
Don't think
that doesn't piss me off.
Yes.
Fantastic.
Bring it up to my office.
I'll be right there.
I think we're on
to something here.
Stay here, will you?
I'll be back in two shakes.
Nothing is safe, apparently.
Lock the building down now.
Hold on there, Charlie.
Dean, he's one of them!
That would explain it.
You're hanging
with the wrong crowd, kiddo.
Not so fast, Dick.
All right, enough!
Show yourself.
Let's do this
like real monsters.
Ha, ha, ha!
You got to do that again.
That tickled.
Dean, come on.
Come on!
Charlie, talk to us.
You okay?
No.
Why didn't you kill him?
'Cause we can't yet.
But we will.
The really evil ones
always need a special sword.
Oh, okay.
I'm gonna pass out now.
Because they have it!
Now get it back, before they
figure the damn thing out!
Please,
sir, d-don't bid me.
Bid you?!
Why would I waste
a perfectly good meal?
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I left your dumb flask
on the backseat, by the way.
Worst good-luck charm
ever.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Listen, um,
we can't thank you enough.
Actually, you can.
Never contact me again,
like, ever. Deal?
Deal.
Keep your head down
out there, okay?
This ain't the first time
I've disappeared.
You think my name
is really Charlie Bradbury?
Please.
So,
good luck saving the world.
Peace out, bitches.
She's kind of like the
little sister I never wanted.
We got to talk.
Well, you mean before we get
back to the car and the flask?
Exactly.
So, what the hell happened
back in the lobby, Dean?
Man, if I had a free shot,
I'd have bitch-slapped
the hell out of Dick.
Yeah, but, I mean, Charlie
got her freaking arm broken.
He didn't mean to do it.
Exactly.
He's not in control,
not about Dick.
That was
vengeful-spirit crap.
I know.
But it's still Bobby.
But if he really goes there,
he won't be anymore,
and then we won't be able
to pull him back.
And then what
are we supposed to do?
I know.
Look, let's just figure out
what that thing we stole is,
and then we'll figure out
what the hell to do with Bobby.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==