You know what Cass did?
The dam inside
your brother's head is gone,
and all hell's spilling loose.
Every time I close my eyes,
Lucifer is yelling into my head.
Good morning, Vietnam!
You know
he's not actually...
Yeah.
No, I know that.
Try telling that to the volume
control inside my brain.
Did you try
the hand thing?
Your brother's
probably dead.
Shut up.
He said "shut up" to me.
You let me in.
You wanted me, partner.
I do believe I've got you,
bunk buddy.
No net for you, Sammy.
Hey!
Dick!
Dude.
Get the hell away from me.
You speak friggin' English?
Go away!
It's okay.
No one's after me.
Why are you running up in here
like that?
Just...
Just leave me alone.
What the hell
did you take, anyway?
Nothing.
Shut up.
No, he's telling the truth.
Burned through that last beer
hours ago.
Right about the time
Dean passed out.
Come on, Sam.
Tell the nice tweaker.
You'd be sleeping by now
if the devil would just leave
you alone for five seconds.
Stupid Satan.
Chasing you all the way to...
Where the hell are we?
Ugh!
I just need some rest.
Hey. Sam.
Try the hand scar.
How many days
you been up, anyway?
Four.
Oh. Wait. Scratch that.
Five.
Hey, hold up! Wait!
Hold up!
You want to knock out?
I can knock you out.
? Good morning to you ?
? good morning to you ?
? our day is beginning ?
? so good morning to you ?
I thought you liked
my singing!
Pills?
You do get that you're just
bringing free drugs
to the party, right?
I am inside you, Sam.
Hey. Sam.
What's the longest
a normal human being
has ever gone
without sleep?
11 days.
Hey.
You always wanted
to be normal, Sam!
If you are,
you'll be dead in a week!
? Supernatural 7x17 ?
The Born-Again Identity
Original Air Date on March 23, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Okay, sir? You can't just barge
in here without an appointment!
They said, "Talk to Kadinsky."
You Kadinsky?
- You need to be scheduled!
- Well, then, schedule me!
He was in a car crash.
Why the hell
can't I see him?
You're Sam Smith's brother.
Yeah, what's going on?
I-it's fine.
Thank you.
Really.
Sam was admitted.
He was treated for a broken rib
and lacerations.
- Okay. That's not too bad. And?
- And...
He's on our locked
psychiatric floor.
I mean,
he's had some trouble...
So you're aware that Sam
is experiencing
a full-blown
psychotic episode?
Psychotic?
Come on.
I mean, the guy's...
It's not like the guy's
freakin' Norman Bates.
No, I'm sure he isn't.
We need to determine whether
his state was brought on
by the insomnia
or whether the insomnia is
a symptom of his condition.
Do you understand?
So that we can figure out
how to treat him.
Well, all I can say is that
the sleep thing is kind of new.
Right.
Well...we've pumped him
about as full of sedatives
as we safely can.
So far,
he won't go under.
I've never seen
anything like it.
I'm just sayin'.
Back when you had
no soul...
You never had to sleep.
Ah, Mr. Helpless.
Pull up a six-pack, buddy.
How are you feeling?
Maybe you
should cancel my UFC fight.
Yeah. Keep that
sense of humor, Sam.
It'll get you through this.
Sam, I'm gonna
find you help.
Now, that sounded
a little cynical.
I don't think
it's out there, Dean.
We don't know that.
We know better than most.
It's all snake oil.
Last faith healer
we hooked up with
had a reaper on a leash.
Remember?
Yeah...
Sam, I remember.
I'm just saying...
What?
That you don't want
my help?
No, I'm just saying
Don't do this to yourself.
Sam, if I don't find
something --
Then I'll die.
Oh, you're upsetting me.
Dean, we knew
this was coming.
- No. No.
- When you put my soul back.
Cass warned you about
all the crap it would --
Screw Cass!
Quit being dali frickin' Yoda
about this, okay?
Get pissed!
I'm too tired.
This is what happens
when you throw a soul
into Lucifer's dog bowl.
When you think there's just
gonna be some cure out there?
Oh, you guys
are having a moment.
I'm a friend
of Bobby Singer's.
I'm looking for some info.
If you could, uh,
call me back.
785-555-0128.
Thanks.
I am so sorry
to have bothered you.
Narcissistic
personality disorder.
Okay, now,
this one I could have.
Time for meds, Sam.
Sets unrealistic goals.
Check.
But trouble keeping
healthy relationships?
Not so sure about that one.
Thoughts?
Yeah. Thanks.
Yeah, hi. Uh...
my name's Dean.
I'm a friend of Bobby Singer's.
I'm, uh, looking for some info.
If you could call me back
at 785-555-0128.
Thanks.
Sam,
how are we feeling today?
Rib pain --
scale of 1 to 10?
- It's -- it's not bad.
- Um
3.
You don't have
to lie, Sam.
I'm -- I'm not.
You've suffered
terrible agony.
I mean, your 10
must be astronomical.
Yeah. I-I guess
I have a high threshold.
Yeah.
But the worst is knowing
that there's always a new 10.
What are you
talking about?
Well, I'm talking about
the truly elegant torture
I have prepared
for you today, Sam.
Just stay the hell
away from me.
But it's --
it's so nice chatting.
Sam, I hate these
one-sided conversations.
Come on, buddy.
Engage.
Sam?
You...
Me...
Locked ward.
Is it me, or is this
just like the cage?
This is Dean.
Mackey.
Calling you back.
Hey. Real sorry
about Bobby.
Yeah, me too.
Look,
what you called about --
I might have something
for you.
There's this guy.
He goes by "Emanuel."
He kind of roams.
First started hearing about him
a couple of months back.
Now, he was healing the sick,
curing the crazy.
Uh-huh.
Naturally, I think something
in the milk ain't clean.
Find this sucker,
punch his clock.
- Right?
- Right.
Heard the best way to get
to him is through his wife,
Daphne, out in Colorado?
So, I go.
Tell her I'm going blind.
It's true.
My right eye's burnt out.
She says, "Go home.
He'll come."
So, I go.
I set every trap,
every test in the book.
That's what I
would have done.
Emanuel shows.
He passes every one.
There ain't nothing weird
about this guy.
Except...
He's the real deal.
What do you mean?
He touched me,
and my eye was fixed.
Look -- I don't believe in much
that don't suck your blood.
But I wouldn't call you
on a maybe.
"Oh, my head hurts.
Make it stop!"
Hello?
You want this or not?
I saw you yesterday.
You didn't look too happy
with your in-flight meal.
Thanks. Uh...
Marin.
No problem.
Sam. Right?
"That's it.
I'm Sam."
"I'm Sam. Hi."
Hi. Uh, is this, uh,
Daphne Allen's house?
I'm looking for Emanuel.
Well, you found him.
Daphne's resting.
If you don't mind.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Um
So, I was hoping...
You were saying, Dean?
You know,
I'd think twice.
Or don't you know that your boss
issued a hands-off memo?
Please.
What have you done
for him lately?
Roman's head on a plate?
No?
Whatever Emanuel is,
Crowley's gonna want him --
a lot more than he wants you
these days.
So...
Aah!
What was that?
That creature hurt you.
I'm okay.
But, Emanuel...
They were looking
for you.
It's okay.
I'm Emanuel.
Dean. I'm...Dean.
Thank you for protecting
my wife.
Your wife. Right.
I saw his face.
His real face.
He was a demon.
A demon
walked the Earth.
Demons.
Whackloads of them.
You don't know about...
You saw the demon's
true face.
Emanuel has
very special gifts.
Yeah.
I-I've heard that about...
Emanuel.
That you can
heal people up.
I seem to be able to help
to a certain degree.
What's your issue?
My brother.
? Wake up, little susie ?
? wake up ?
? wake up, little susie ?
You know, you're actually
keeping it together
better than I thought.
Kind of...the way someone
pinned under a bus
keeps it together.
None of this is real.
And yet...
you know what really sucks?
It doesn't really matter.
Because I won.
Your madness won.
I mean, look at you.
It's hard to believe
you were the guy
that saved the world once.
Mmm! Sammy.
What'll be today?
Maggots again...
Or, uh, tapeworm?
Thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
How are you doing?
Uh...little better.
That girl, uh, Marin...
Look, I'm not really
supposed to talk about it.
Let's just say,
unlike you,
she didn't get here
'cause of no accident.
So, Daphne --
is that, uh, your wife?
She found me
and cared for me.
Meaning?
Oh, it's a...strange story.
You may not like it.
Believe me, I will.
A few months ago,
she was hiking by the river,
and I wandered
into her path,
drenched and confused,
and...unclothed.
I had no memory.
She said...
God wanted her
to find me.
So who named you Emanuel?
Bouncybabynames.com.
Well, it's working
for you.
Must be weird
not knowing who you are.
Well, it's my life.
And it's a good life.
Yeah, well, what if you were
some kind of...
I don't know...bad guy?
Oh, I...
don't feel like
a bad person.
Man,
you must be really determined
to wait out nap time.
Here.
Wait. Uh...
...share this with me.
Thanks.
I don't know why I'm thanking
you for a candy bar I stole.
So, how long you been here?
Five weeks and counting.
Going for the record.
How come?
It doesn't matter.
That's a lot of bandages
for "it doesn't matter."
You want the doctor answer?
I'm psychotically depressed
to a suicidal ideation.
And the not doctor answer?
I feel like crap.
I just...
want it to be over.
What?
Everything.
Come on.
Tell me I'm young
and have everything
to live for.
Why would you believe me?
True.
I heard you're here
because the voices
won't let you sleep.
Just one, really.
Who is it?
Like Charlie Manson
or the devil?
Kind of. Yeah.
Me too.
I...hear a voice.
Is that why
you set the fire?
Who told you that?
No one.
T-they're burns, right?
I didn't set the fire, o--
he did!
You know what? I don't even know
why I'm talking.
Marin, it's okay.
No, it's not!
You are crazier
than I am!
Charles Manson tells you
what to do.
At least
it's my own brother --
It's your brother?
Yes.
It sucks...
when it's your
dead brother saying...
kill yourself
to be with him...
...or he'll do it for you.
So, your brother...
Sam.
What's his diagnosis?
Well
it's not exactly medical.
That should be fine.
I can cure illness
of a spiritual origin.
Spiritual?
Okay.
Someone did this to him.
You're angry.
Well, yeah.
Dude broke
my brother's head.
He betrayed you,
this dude.
He was your friend?
Yeah, well, he's gone.
Did you kill him?
I sense that you kill
a lot of people.
Honestly, I-I don't know
if he's dead.
I just know that this...
whole thing
couldn't be messier.
You know, I used to be able
to just shake this stuff off.
You know,
whatever it was.
It might take me some time,
but...
I always could.
What Cass did...
I just can't --
I don't know why.
Well,
it doesn't matter why.
Of course it matters.
No. You're not
a machine, Dean.
You're human.
Your friend's name
was Cass?
That's an odd name.
Oh, hey, hey.
Just, uh, sit tight.
I'll be right out, okay?
Oh, come on.
Emanuel,
you son of a bitch.
Emanuel.
Yeah, not so much.
Meg.
Dean, Dean, Dean.
You got some 'splainin' to do.
Rumors are really starting to
fly about this Emanuel fellow.
My curiosity
sure got revved up.
Just tell me
what you want, Meg.
Imagine my surprise
when I track him down,
and he's snuggled up
with you.
And he's the spitting image
of poor, dead Castiel.
So, Dean,
what's poor, dead Castiel
doing in that junker
out there?
Christmas caroling.
Fun.
But how's he alive?
Last I heard, he played God,
went poof.
I don't know.
And neither does he,
so you got to keep it shut.
Oh, I do?
He doesn't know he's Cass.
I know.
Been watching you for hours.
So here's the deal.
You might remember
Crowley and me
were frosty
back in the day?
- Well, times haven't changed.
- Good.
That hurts my feelings.
I've been good to you, Dean.
No, you've been good to you,
sweetheart.
Look.
Right now, rumors
of this wandering healer
are strictly low-level.
But body count's getting
high enough to change that.
Folks start poking,
they sniff angel dust.
Yeah, they start falling
all over each other
trying to tell Crowley.
Now picture Crowley
with his hands
on harmless
little amnesia Cass.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm gonna burn
that smarmy dick.
My time's coming.
But right about now,
my army-of-one situation
is not cutting it.
It's cold out here,
there's a price on my ass,
and I need friends.
Yeah. I get that.
But I ain't it.
That's where
you're wrong, Dean.
'Cause I'm here
to help you,
and that makes us friends.
Help, huh?
You mean see if you can't turn
harmless little Cass out there
into an
angel-sized weapon?
Like you're taking
him caroling.
And by the way, you really want
to keep going with no backup?
Hey, I don't trust you,
either.
But I could really
use Emanuel.
And he trusts you.
So for now, it's in everyone's
best interests
to hold hands and cross
the street together, okay?
We go straight to Sam.
No detours.
I love it.
And one more thing.
My knife.
You sure
we wouldn't be safer
traveling with
a full-throttle Angel?
I could jog his memory.
Kidding!
We wouldn't want to upset
the poor guy.
Her face!
She's one of --
It's okay.
We come in different flavors.
She's, uh...a friend.
Meg.
Just here
for moral support.
I mean, after all,
we go way back.
Dean and me.
Just met you, of course.
I think we're gonna be
good friends, too.
All right.
Can we go?
Marin. Marin, hey.
Hold on.
Um...I'm sorry
I upset you.
It's okay.
Can I ask you something?
About?
The fire.
Look. You mean well,
but you have no idea --
You said
you didn't start it.
I believe you.
I can help you, Marin,
before he tries
to hurt you again.
You're worse.
Your organs need sleep,
you know.
Your hair and nails
are gonna fall out,
and your kidneys
are gonna shut down.
I saw it in a movie.
Sorry.
So, um, your brother --
when did he pass?
Uh, last year.
Do you see him?
So...
He just talks to you.
But at first
it wasn't so bad.
You must have missed him.
Did you just hear him
at the house?
Here too.
Whenever I'm alone.
I can always tell
he's coming
because I get
these chills.
You feel cold.
Yeah.
I mean, you're right.
At first it's like...
I knew I was crazy,
but...
I didn't really care.
I did miss him.
But then...
He started saying
he was lonely.
And he started
to get mad.
And one day
he started yelling,
and I tried to run
but the door was locked.
And when I turned around,
the whole room was on fire.
I barely got out.
How can you help me?
I can put your brother
to rest.
He's, um...
He's stuck here.
For real? Like --
Like he's a ghost.
Why should I trust you?
Because it's your
only shot.
Okay.
So, your brother --
was he cremated? Buried?
We cremated him.
And do you have
anything of his?
This.
He made it for me.
With a busted hand, too.
Sliced it open
doing stupid archery.
He bled on it?
Probably.
Good.
That's -- that's good.
Why is that good?
One more question.
Is there any chance in hell
you got a lighter?
This silence
is very uncomfortable.
Is there something
I should know?
I don't know.
Dean?
No.
Meg has that effect.
Awkward. You know?
That must be difficult
for you.
Dean's making a joke,
Emanuel.
Oh.
Nice.
Where'd you score that?
Grabbed it out of
Marcus' pocket.
Being locked up is really
turning me into a decent criminal.
We're laying down
a circle.
Help me open these, okay?
You're gonna have to do this
on your own.
It's okay. I'm okay.
I'm just having a little...
Brown acid moment.
...Dizzy thing.
It'll pass.
Definitely.
When your heart stops.
Great. Now, um...
Stay with me
in the circle.
No matter what.
No matter
what happens, okay?
What's gonna happen?
Give me the bracelet.
Marin, don't do this.
Please.
Marin, give me
the bracelet.
I'm so sorry. I have to.
Noooo!
Y-you got to go.
Go.
Thank you.
Sam?
How you feeling now?
His soul is broken, Doc.
Can you give him a pill?
I can't give you
any more medication.
The potential for overdose
is too great.
We need to talk
about surgical solutions.
Surgical?
Ooh. Lobotomy?
It's okay.
We're not talking lobotomy here.
Darn.
Sam.
Are you with me?
Oh, gracious.
Damn it. Demons.
All of them?
No grass growing
under your feet.
How many of those knives
do you have?
Just the one.
Well, then, forgive me,
but what do we do?
Yeah, Dean.
Got any other ideas
how we could blast through that?
Excuse us.
Meg?
Oh, for the love of...
Sam's in there.
I know you're enjoying
the double dip
with your old pal, but --
You think
it's that cut and dry?
Really?
You know what he did.
And you want to tell him
and just hope that he takes it
in stride?
He could snap.
He could...disappear.
Who knows?
I gather
we know each other.
Just a dollop.
You can tell me.
I'll be fine.
How do you know?
You just met yourself.
I've known you for years.
You're an Angel.
I'm sorry?
Is that a flirtation?
No, it's a species.
A very powerful one.
She's not lying.
Okay? That's why
you heal people.
You don't eat.
I'm sure there's more.
Why wouldn't you
tell me?
Being an angel --
it sounds pleasant.
It's not. Trust me.
It's bloody.
It's corrupt.
It's not pleasant.
He would know.
You used to
fight together.
Bestest friends,
actually.
We're...friends?
Am I Cass?
I-I had no idea.
I don't remember you.
I'm sorry.
Look.
You got the juice.
You can smite every demon
in that lot.
But I don't remember how.
It's in there.
I'm sure it's just like
riding a bike.
I don't know how
to do that, either.
All right, I'll try.
This ain't gonna go well.
I don't know.
I believe in
the little tree topper.
Hey, I know you.
You're dead.
Yes, I've heard.
I'm sorry, Dean.
That's my boy.
I don't think
running will save you.
That was beautiful,
Clarence.
Cass?
I remember you.
I remember everything.
What I did.
What I became.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because Sam is dying
in there.
Because of me.
Everything.
All these people.
I shouldn't be here.
Cass. Cass!
You stay here.
Cass!
Where...
Where -- where are we?
Electroshock therapy.
Let's just get you
settled.
Don't be freaked.
I've seen this help
a lot of people.
My brother.
Bite down.
Ordinarily, they keep
this thing set on low.
But I was thinking
we could experiment a little.
What do you say, Sam?
Let's get that head
strapped in.
If you remember,
then you know you did the best
you could at the time.
Don't defend me.
Do you have any idea
the death toll in heaven?
On Earth?
We didn't part friends,
Dean.
So what?
I deserved to die.
Now, I can't possibly
fix it...
So why did I even walk out
of that river?
Maybe to fix it.
Wait.
Amazing.
You just take those lickin's,
don't you, kid?
Well, if it's meat,
you can cook it.
You just got to turn up
the heat.
I should never have broken
your wall, Sam.
I'm here to make it right.
You're not real.
Sam...
...I'm so sorry.
I see that third
little pig was smart.
Went out and got
some bricks.
What the hell
do you mean you can't?
I mean there's nothing left
to rebuild.
Why not?
Because it crumbled.
The pieces got crushed
to dust
by whatever's happening
inside his head right now.
So you're saying
there's nothing?
That he's gonna be like this
until his candle blows out?
I'm sorry.
This isn't a problem
I can make disappear.
And you know that.
But I may be able
to shift it.
Shift?
Yeah, it would get Sam
back on his feet.
It's better this way.
- I'll be fine.
- Wait, Cass, what are you doing?
Now, Sam...
This may hurt.
And if I can't
tell you again...
I'm sorry I ever did this
to you.
Sam?
Sam!
Dean!
- Sam!
- Cass?
Cass, is that you?
Hello...Brother.
I don't know.
We can't just leave him.
Well, we can't bring him
with us.
Everything on the planet's
out for us, okay?
Word gets out,
we can't protect him.
Not really.
This is safer.
Every demon who knows
about Cass is dead.
Not everyone.
Look, Dean, this whole
"enemy of my enemy
is my friend" thing
feels kind of like
a demon deal.
It's not a deal.
It's --
It's what?
Mutually assured
destruction.
Look, man, I get it.
She's not our friend.
We don't even
have friends.
All our friends are dead.
Well, you certainly
have experience.
I'm impressed.
Tell me --
why do you want
to join our staff?
I really just want
to help the patients.
Watch over them.
Not to be immodest,
but I feel like
I'd make a great fit.
I can't argue with that.
Welcome to the team...
Nurse Masters.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==