I hate what...
oh, spewing the
bodily fluids everywhere.
It creepy, you know
it's downright unsanitary.
I-I can't hold them back!
- Hold who back?
- Leviathan!
They're like
shapeshifters only a lot
more into eating folk.
Nothing can kill 'em.
Yes, sir. Sam Winchester
was definitely here.
And I'll find out
where they went from here.
You know me. You know
the kind of person I am.
She's dropping bodies,
man,
Which means
we got to drop her.
She killed her own mom
to save me.
She's done.
You ever do something
behind someone's back
Because you had to?
You are what you are.
You will kill again.
I'm sorry.
Karen, don't second-guess
yourself.
Yes, your house is beautiful,
but didn't you tell me
a million times
that it's
Rick's dream house?
Selling it is how
you punish his ass, Karen,
and after what you've been
through, don't you deserve that?
You do, honey.
I'll have the papers ready
tomorrow.
Yay!
I'm proud of you.
Bye.
I'm not good.
I'm very good.
There you are.
All right.
10 minutes.
Holler if you need anything.
Chris!
Ow.
Chri--
Chris, get back here!
Chr-i-i-i-is!
Chris!
Oh, my God.
Somebody, help!
Aaaah!
? Supernatural 7x05 ?
Shut Up, Dr. Phil
Original Air Date on October 21, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Leave me alone!
I said shut up!
Just stop! Stop!
You are what you are.
You will kill again.
I won't. I swear.
Somebody
better be chasing you.
It's good for you.
No. No, it's not good for you.
Look at you.
Y-you're a mess,
and you stink.
Well, while you were out
being Lance Armstrong...
That would be biking.
...I was working.
You ever heard of a town
called Prosperity, Indiana?
Has anybody?
Two of their fine citizens died
over the past two weeks.
This one chick --
she, uh, roasted underneath
one of those beehive hair dryers
at the hair salon,
and this other guy
boiled in a hot tub.
- You don't see a lot of that.
- No, you don't.
- It's worth checking out.
- Yeah.
You know, one more thing.
What's going on with you?
We have had
this conversation, Sam.
No, we haven't.
See, to do that, you'd
have to, uh, sort of...speak.
Okay, let's see
if you can get this straight.
See [clears throat] you're --
you're new Sam, right,
Lance Armstrong.
Biking.
And, uh --
and I'm still me, okay?
All right, so -- so, you might
see things different now --
call it a runner's high
or some crap --
but that doesn't mean
that something's going on
with me, okay?
Yeah, okay.
No, don't say, "yeah, okay,"
like, "yeah, okay."
Yeah, okay.
Yes, sir, I understand.
Yeah, I definitely do realize
this Winchester thing
is taking far too long,
and I'm sorry about that.
No worries.
I can be there
in a day and a half.
Yeah, I'll hit the road now.
Just stopped
.
Thanks.
It'll be my pleasure.
I'm very sorry.
I-I know this is a tough time
to have to talk about all this.
I've already been through it
so many times with the lawyers,
the police,
the insurance guys.
Right.
I know. I know.
We just -- we have to conduct
our own separate investigation.
I'm sorry.
I know it's tough.
Can I ask you -- did your sister
have any enemies?
Why do you ask that?
You think her death
wasn't accidental?
No. No, no, no. We just have to
consider every possibility.
Is there anyone who might
have wanted to harm her?
You don't live here,
so you don't know.
Everyone...loved Wendy.
She volunteered
at the church.
She ran a group for kids.
I was the big sister,
and I looked up to her.
What about this man who died --
Carl Dunlap?
- Did she know him?
- I don't think so.
Well, Wendy was
in real estate, right?
Carl was an architect.
Maybe they had
some business dealings?
If they had worked together,
I would've heard the name.
Agent Sambora...
If someone did this
to my sister, find out who.
And nobody was back here
but Wendy.
No.
But I was only gone
for a minute.
You can't even crank
these things
past a certain temperature --
am I wrong?
If it started to blow a fuse
or something,
it would have shut down.
Oh.
Basically, you're saying that
this couldn't have happened.
Basically, I'm saying
it couldn't have happened.
The insurance adjusters
already did that.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Wait.
What kind of a coin?
It's not American.
I don't know where it's from.
It was wedged back
behind one of those machines.
Somebody
could have dropped it.
Of course,
they don't have pockets
in those robe thingies
that they make you wear.
I didn't realize
you were such a spa expert.
Shut up.
I observe with my eyes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
whatever you say.
So, you thinking it must be
some kind of hex talisman?
Maybe.
All right.
Pick me up.
Why don't you just
run home, Lance?
Dean --
Yeah, I'll be there
in a bit.
Oh, come on --
aaaah!
So, what do we know
about the vic?
Dewey Stevens -- owner,
Dewey Stevens Construction,
biggest outfit in town.
Rotarian, methodist,
tenor,
blue-ribbon pecan pie champ,
asthmatic.
We're a close-knit
community.
So, this, um,
pillar of the community --
he was taking a leak
before he, uh, sprung a few?
The crew had gone for the day.
Site was shut down.
Anything unusual
besides the nails in the eyes?
Well, we're...
still trying
to figure out
where they plugged in
the nail gun,
seeing as there's no generator
on the truck.
Well, when you figure that out,
let me know.
So, another victim
everybody likes.
Not everybody.
Another physically impossible
death.
- You got any ideas?
- Cirque du Soleil?
Oh, I, uh, found
another one of these,
just like at the, uh,
the hair-dryer/brain-roast.
And I found a connection
with all the vics.
These e-mail logs show
Wendy, the real-estate chick,
Carl, the architect,
and this Dewey guy
were all working on a
shopping-center project together.
Why didn't we know
about that?
Well, it all fell apart
for some reason.
I mean, there are
these e-mails back and forth,
pretty hot and heavy,
and suddenly they just stopped.
So, everybody working
on this project has died?
Well, not yet.
They were working
with a developer,
a guy named Don Stark.
Don Stark?
Why do I know that name?
Man, this Stark guy
is really plugged in, huh?
So, all the players in this --
this shopping-center project
have either
fried, boiled, or kebabbed.
He could be next.
Really?
From a freaking flask?
What are you, bad Santa?
- On the job?
- We're always on the job.
All right.
Bobby e-mailed back.
I sent him a few pics
of those coins you found.
He says the writing
is Romanian cyrillic,
used only in the mid-15th
to the 19th century.
Apparently, it's an antique
Wallachian ducat.
So, we're looking
for an old Romanian?
You know, is it just me,
or is this really weird?
Huh.
I've seen this once before,
where t-the plants
are all dead in one spot.
Where?
A bus bench with
Wendy Goodson's picture on it.
I mean, I'm no expert, but
I don't think plants are
supposed to act like this.
? No one knows he's crying ?
? no one knows
he's dying on the inside ?
? 'cause he's laughing
on the outside ?
? mm, no one knows ?
If the bureau's involved,
I assume you think
all three were murdered.
It's looking that way,
yes.
Now, Mr. Stark,
you had a relationship
with all three victims,
correct?
Oh, I knew them in business
circles, I guess, sure.
And you were all involved
in a, uh,
a-a shopping-center project.
Why'd that fall through?
Uh, t-these things happen.
Oh. Jenny.
These gentlemen
are from the FBI.
- Jenny Klein, my assistant.
- Hi, there.
Okay, Don,
I'm off to the cleaner's,
and then I'm gonna stop
at Beaman, Beaman, and Beaman
for the revised
contracts.
Hurry on back. You know how
things fall apart without you.
Oh.
Oh, I baked you some cupcakes --
coconut.
Coconut --
you're too good to me, Jenny.
Oh. I'll see you soon.
She bakes cupcakes.
Yummy.
You know what? Could you
point me to the restroom?
I had a little bit
too much java.
Yeah, around the corner,
down the hall.
Thanks.
So, uh, usually
in cases like these --
are there
cases like these?
Oh, you'd be surprised.
Uh, we start out
with the basics.
You have
any business rivals?
Sure, tons.
You know, real estate's brutal.
Well, that was easy.
On the other hand,
I've demonstrated my love
for this town,
and I think it's safe to say
I'm respected
for what I've done here.
Yeah, one
of my real treasures.
"To Don -- take no prisoners.
D. Trump."
The Trumpster!
Wow.
Like I said, success breeds
fierce competition,
but in the end, everyone here
respects and admires me.
Including your wife?
Sorry.
It's just,
we heard the two of you
were splitting up, right?
Yeah, that's, uh --
that's what we heard.
Yeah, Maggie and I
are going through a tough time.
It's a separation --
temporary.
Sometimes, you know,
you grow apart.
It's no one's fault.
Now, how would you
describe
the, uh -- the issues
between you and your wife?
Just one of those marital
misunderstandings, you know.
No, I'm sorry.
I don't.
It's one of those vague,
hard-to-define passages.
She caught you
cheating, huh?
I couldn't help
but notice, uh,
things were kind of cordial
between you and your assistant.
Pretty good with the ladies
there, Mr. Stark?
It's a blessing and a curse,
isn't it?
Guys,
I'm a people person,
and I admire
dynamic, confident women.
"Admire"?
Okay, look --
it's true I had a recent...
little thing
with a business associate,
but that's all it was.
- A "thing"?
- Yeah.
Like a -- like a shoe
or a golf club.
Right. Like a waffle iron.
Yeah.
Yeah. No, see, Don, uh, wives
generally think of an affair
as something
more than a thing.
Yes, and when Maggie
found out about it,
she needed some time off,
temporarily.
Now, if we were to guess
that the, uh, uh, business
associate was Wendy Goodson,
would we win
the weekend trip to Maui?
No, her death had nothing to do
with the affair.
It was over
long before her accident.
If it was an accident.
You're not implying
that Maggie was behind this.
No, we're not implying
anything.
We're just saying...
you should be careful.
And take her to dinner
and apologize.
Yeah, and, uh, grovel.
Wouldn't hurt.
Found a bunch of hex junk
in their stuff --
clearly her thing.
And the empty closet
didn't seem like she
was coming back anytime soon.
So, Don admires Wendy,
biblically,
Wendy dies weird,
and the scorned wife
is into the dark stuff.
While Don's
just in the dark.
Hmm. It's kind of
like "Bewitched."
You know, Don's Darrin,
doesn't even know it.
A lot laughs until,
uh, you cheat on your wife.
A "Bewitched" reference. Really?
Dude, Nicole Kidman
was in the remake.
Redhead. Hello!
Look at
all these dead plants.
Huh. It's kind of like
the real-estate lady's place
and Don's statue thing.
You know,
if she's strong enough,
just being pissed off
is enough to send some
pretty bad vibes their way.
Literally kill off
everything around her
just by pms-ing at it.
Eeh. That's not creepy
at all.
Bobby, hey, it's Dean.
Listen --
Winchester.
Yeah, very funny.
So, we need
our kind of terminix.
A witch.
Yeah, we're headed over
to her place to get you
some more specifics,
so if you could just,
uh --
y-- thank y--
He's on it.
Don, keep it
in your pants, man.
All circuits are busy.
Mrs. Stark.
Could I have a moment?
Of course.
Um, would you mind coming back
in, say, a half an hour?
It's just a really bad time
right now.
It's very important
that I talk to you.
Of course,
and I'm happy to.
I'm just in the middle of an
emergency, so please come back.
Thank you!
I'm sorry --
uh...
restless leg syndrome.
Spoiler alert --
Jenny Klein's next.
Swiped her photo
off a hex deck,
but Maggie's gonna notice
it's gone eventually.
We got to get over
to Jenny's.
Okay.
Hot.
Puterea magiei negre
te condamna
la suferinta si moarte.
Find the coin, now!
Come on, Sam!
Okay.
There were tiny beating
hearts in my cupcakes.
There were hearts
in my cupcakes,
hearts in my cupcakes!
That's never happened before!
Hearts in my cupcakes!
Should I slug her?
Give it a second.
Oh, my God.
What just happened?
You were hexed.
"Hexed"?
Who are you people?
What the hell do I do?
What you do is you go in there
and you pack a bag,
you get in your car,
and you go.
- Go where?
- It doesn't matter.
Look, 500 or 600 miles
ought to do it.
You got someone real powerful
real pissed,
and they're trying
to get rid of you now.
In line with that,
you might want to cool things
with Don Stark.
Don Stark?
What are you
talking about?
You and Don.
You know.
"You know"?
There's no "you know."
No?
Don Stark is my boss.
That's it.
He's married,
for God's sake.
Yeah, well...
Me and Don Stark.
Ew.
What are you doing?
Bunch these tables
more in the middle.
Give me a more air
between paintings.
Hey. Maggie, can you sign
for the flowers?
I've checked them.
They're fine.
Thank you, Sue.
What would I do without you?
Oh, please, I like helping.
What are best friends for?
It's just been so tough to focus
with Don, the whole mess.
It's like he put a knife
right in your heart, isn't it?
Yes.
Was I wrong to tell you
about him and Wendy?
No. No. You think
I'd want you to stand by
and watch him
make a fool of me?
- I love you for what you did.
- I love you, too.
No, no, no. The still life
doesn't go there.
It goes
on the left side.
So, uh, we're gonna need,
uh, one centerpiece
on each of the tables
and two at the back.
- Don.
- Where's my wife?
You mean the one
who's divorcing you?
Sue, I know you can hardly wait
until I'm out of the picture,
and I know
it's been a thrill
whispering lies
into Maggie's ear --
Oh, but they weren't lies,
were they, Don?
I made one mistake --
one.
I sincerely doubt that.
This is between Maggie and me.
- It has nothing to do with you.
- What do you want, Don?
I'd like to speak
with you.
Make it quick.
Okay.
You know what, Maggie?
I think I've been patient.
And you've had your fun.
It was very creative,
the thing with Wendy,
but, you know,
enough is enough.
No, Don, enough is not enough,
not even close.
What do you want,
my oysters on a tray?
Well, now
that you mention it --
The fact is,
none of this was my fault!
Maybe if you'd been
around a little more.
But between the art and the
charity and that evil bitch Sue,
I was edged
right out of your life.
Oh, boo-hoo,
Mr. Big Shot,
Mr. "I got to put my name
on every public works in town."
There was three of us
in this marriage --
me, you, and your ego.
That was the problem,
Don.
So, excuse me. I have
a charity event to arrange.
Two FBI agents came by,
asking questions.
Hunters, sweetheart --
that's what they are.
Oh, I can see you're terribly
concerned for my safety,
but don't worry --
I'll take care of it.
Maggie, this stops.
You hear me?
As of now.
You're so cute when
you try to tell me what to do.
Now she's
just getting nasty.
Killing the girlfriend
is one thing,
but his
commemorative bust?
That's got to hurt.
She'll take
the whole town out, Dean.
She don't care
who gets in the way.
Hey, Bobby. What do you got?
Yeah?
You think it'll take her out?
All right.
No, I don't need to write it
down. I'll remember. Go ahead.
Mm-hmm.
The -- wait.
Hang on. Hang on.
Yeah?
Wait. Wa--
ho-- ho-- hold on.
Hold on. Hold on.
Okay, what was the --
what was that last one?
Right.
Uh-huh.
I'll remember.
It's fine.
Hello, everyone,
and thanks for coming.
Most of you know
that philanthropy and art
are my two passions,
but what we've --
not there!
Where is the ice?
People will be here in seconds.
What we've assembled here
tonight
may be my crowning achievement,
not to be immodest.
See? I told you.
Everything's perfect.
Yeah, you --
you just reminded me --
I have to check
on the finger sandwiches.
Dude. Pie.
Ugh.
That is --
chicken feet,
just like the recipe calls for.
Butcher's fridge is down.
I can smell that.
Uh, says
the power's been wonky
and that he's lost
so much product,
he probably
won't make rent.
Ditto every shop
on the block --
nothing but burst pipes
and blackouts.
He says
it's like all of a sudden,
the town ran out of luck.
So, coincidence, right?
Uh...Yeah.
We're past the point
of dead flowers.
What can I say?
I guess the witch is pissed.
All right, let's, uh --
we better get a move on here.
Why don't you just --
c-can you take the feet?
Ugh.
To us.
I couldn't have done it
without you.
To us.
Aaaaah!
That is disgusting!
No.
Not my paintings.
Maggie?
What is going on?
He did this.
How could he?
He knew
what this meant to me.
Do you mean Don?
Don rigged all this?
- Yes!
- But how?
Just trust me.
He wants to hurt me.
Oh.
I told you --
he's a dick.
But we'll get through this
because
you have people who love you,
and he can't take that
away from you.
Fine, Donald.
It's war.
What the hell?
Whoa.
Clean-up on aisle 7.
Okay, I don't guess she'd
do this to her own auction.
No, obviously it was someone
who hated her guts
and wanted her party
trashed.
Don Stark.
So, the mister's a witch,
himself.
That means we got
not just one pissed-off witch.
We've got two.
It's full-on "War of the Roses."
"Bewitched"
just got a lot less funny.
It's like
when they switched Darrins.
Where is she?
She'll be here.
They've been
throwing thunderbolts
at each other's
favorite toys.
There's nothing left to destroy
but each other.
- This is basically ground zero.
- I hope so.
We're gonna need them
both in the same place
if we're gonna take them down.
Screens up, Captain.
Want one, sweetie?
Shove it.
We are so having it out
right now.
Furor divina virtute
in infernum eam detrude!
Let me guess --
chicken feet?
Not chilled?
For obvious reasons,
you won't be leaving this room.
Well, you will be leaving --
just not alive.
Maggie?
Puterea magiei negre...
- Okay, plan "B."
- What's plan "B"?
Talking.
...La suferinta...
Now? Really?
This is obviously
a domestic dispute.
So if you can't kill them,
counsel them.
Yeah. You know what?
Not my area!
...Supune-te
ordinelor mele --
okay, okay, okay.
Uh...
Look -- obviously, you two
are capable of wiping
each other out, right?
But you haven't, huh?
Which means
that you two --
you still value
whatever it is you got.
A-and you want keep
that dance going.
Maybe it's --
maybe it's punishment.
it's sick, messed-up,
erotic,
kinky, "clamps and feathers"
kind of love.
Okay, okay, t-that's --
that's going way too
deep, there, cowboy.
Look, what he's trying to say
is that -- is that you two --
whatever it is you have,
you're bonded.
Are you out of your mind?
He cheated on me,
humiliated me.
We're not trying to say
what Don did was right.
When a relationship cracks,
usually both parties
have a hand in it.
Indeed.
You're defending him?
- Ugh!
- Whoa! Okay, okay!
Okay, look --
n-nobody can defend Don.
Right? Uh, totally.
But, uh, we get that you feel
betrayed...because you were.
Don't suck up to her.
I was betrayed
by all of them.
Carl introduced you to Wendy.
Dewey covered for you.
- Wendy did you!
- Okay, okay, look --
I got to say I-I don't think
don was lying when he said
he regrets
the whole Wendy thing.
"Thing"?
- Sit down.
- Aah! Ohh!
Yeah, affair --
that's right, terrible.
I think the only thing
he regrets is getting caught.
Wendy was nothing to me.
It was over
as soon as it started.
She was
part of a pattern, okay?
I've had 800 years
of this.
Do not make me bring up
the Renaissance!
Oh! Oh!
You're one to talk.
1492 ring any bells?
The man
was about to set sail!
He could possibly fall off
of the edge of the earth.
I took pity.
So, what's your excuse?
I told you -- nothing happened
with the Medici chick!
You've always been
insanely jealous.
Oh, I wonder why!
Jenny. Wendy.
Jenny? Nothing happened with
Jenny. She's just my assistant.
That's true.
She, uh -- she told us --
just an assistant.
Whoa!
Is that true?
Yes, I swear it, babe.
I would never.
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry, Maggie.
See? See?
Guys, guys...
You're talking.
All these years,
you -- you buried your anger
and your disappointment
till it tore you apart.
All you needed to do
was talk.
And I would have missed the
nuking that my melon just took.
Well, who wants that?
- Nice touch.
- Thank you.
He's right.
I couldn't kill you.
All I ever wanted
is you, Mags.
I've been crushing on you
since forever.
You're the woman that
I want to never grow old with.
I could never murder you
either, Don.
It's crazy...
But true.
Somebody want to call
these things off?
Ex-- excuse me!
Oh, give me a break.
I didn't say anything.
It's been a long day.
And it's not over yet.
Hi, Sam.
Hi, Dean.
Do we know you?
Well, I definitely know you.
You're the dead guys.
Well, you will be
in a minute.
Sorry.
You're a bit outmatched.
Don.
Thank you.
We owe you.
Good God.
What is that thing?
I guess we should be figuring
that out.
It is
on our to-do list.
You know, find a bottomless pit
and drop it in.
Spell only lasts
for a few days.
Uh, what are you
even doing here?
Apparently,
saving your lives --
twice.
Got it.
Maggie? Seriously?
She was gonna kill us? We
just saved your damn marriage.
Yeah, but to be fair,
you also tried to kill her.
You know how she is
when she gets a bug up her ass.
Got to love her, right?
Right.
Bottomless pit.
Yeah, he's ready
for transport.
I just hope you got someplace
you can put him, Bobby.
All right.
We should hit the road.
You ready?
Hey, were you, um --
were you listening
to the Starks tonight?
Uh, a little,
when I wasn't getting slammed
into a wall or stung by bees.
You notice how they, uh --
you know,
how they --
how they opened up,
got everything
off their chest?
Yeah. Kudos on selling them
that crap.
It wasn't crap,
Dean. It worked.
Sam, I am so very, very,
very, very...Very, very tired --
Dean, like it or not,
the stuff you don't talk about
doesn't just go away.
It builds up, like whatever's
eating at you right now.
There's always
something eating at me.
That's who I am.
Something happens,
I feel responsible, all right?
The Lindbergh baby --
that's on me.
Unemployment -- my bad.
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Well, then what the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about whatever
you're not telling me about.
Look, Dean, it's fine.
You can unload.
That's kind of
what I'm here for.
I mean...
We're good, right?
We're good.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==