And so, due to one
architectural oversight,
the Toledo Bridge Disaster
of 1906
claimed the lives of 75 people.
Now, I hate to stop
while I'm on a roll,
but happy Halloween, ya crazies!
Hey, Professor Brosby,
you gonna come get beers
with us later?
Nah, I got a thing.
But you kids have fun
trick or treating.
This is a treat.
You're the coolest,
Professor Mosby.
Well, hot dog.
Did it hurt?
What?
Getting that kid's nose
surgically removed
from your ass.
It's not her nose that's in
my ass, Lily, it's her heart.
My class loves me;
I-I'm really making
an impression
on those guys.
I'd like to make impression
Man, I love the office
Halloween party.
It is so much sluttier
than the office Christmas party.
Though not as freaky
as the office President's
Day Rave.
Or the office Tu B'Shvat
Pajama Jammy-Jam.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Boss.
Hey, Randy.
Uh, you want a beer?
Oh, no, thank you.
I brew my own.
At the risk of bragging,
my Hazelnut Pilsner
won fourth prize
at the Weehawken Retirement Home
Clam Bake and Wheelchair
Maintenance Picnic.
I wouldn't consider any
part of that bragging.
Hey, it just occurred to me,
is your friend--
what's her name?--
Garbin, Flabin...
Robin?
Robin.
That's it, yeah.
Is she gonna be here?
Oh, not that I really care.
Robin has another
party to go to.
No! Damn it!
I'm leaving.
But she might stop by later.
I guess I can
hang out a little longer.
So, anyone going to see
the Halloween parade?
Oh, we were big fans of New
York's annual Halloween parade.
I don't mean the one
that takes place
Halloween night
in the Village.
I mean the one that takes place
the morning of November 1st--
the Annual Post Halloween
Walk of Shame Parade.
Look at them
heading home
after their
dirty, filthy hookups.
Looks like
that bee got busy.
Looks like that French maid
didn't turn down somebody's bed.
Oh, looks like Pocahontas
has a couple of wounded knees.
Come on, Marshall.
That's a line.
No, it's because of the...
We get it.
Does it get any better
than this?
Uh, yes.
Yes, it does.
Crap.
? How I Met Your Mother 6x07 ?
Canning Randy
Original Air Date on November 1, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
There she is-- Florence
Night-In-Bed-With-A-Stranger.
So, who's the lucky patient?
I don't want to
talk about it.
Please tell me
you're not hooking up
with one of your
co-anchors again.
My co-anchor's a woman.
Please tell me
you are hooking up
with one of your
co-anchors again.
Robin had
always believed
that the key to success
was intelligence,
hard work and professionalism.
Her new co-anchor Becky
had a different philosophy.
Boats! Boats! Boats!
It's the Farhampton Boat Show!
Remember 5th, 6th and 7th
at the Farhampton Civic Center.
Boats! Boats! Boats!
Come on down.
B-B-B-Boats!
You did a commercial?
Why not?
You're a journalist!
Don't you want
to be taken seriously?
No. I'm cute.
Okay, well, if you
really think
this is going to
help your image.
Hi, Becky. Boats, boats, boats!
Robin, a little help here?
Aw...
Oh...
Robin,
you gotta not worry so much
about being liked.
Oh, easy for you to say.
Everybody loves you
at your job.
Mm.
That was true
of my teaching job.
But I was also designing
the new headquarters
for Goliath National Bank,
and well...
Ted Mosby, we don't like you!
What do you have to say
for yourself,
tearing down a beautiful,
old building
just to put up a stupid
band headquarters?
Hmm...
Boo...
freakin'...
hoo.
Boo freakin' hoo? That's it?
The Arcadian
is an architecturally
significant...
Architecturally significant?!
Zoey, you're very pretty.
Your hair smells great.
Shampoo.
You should try it sometime.
You don't know the first thing
about architecture.
Key Ted Mosby's car.
Go on.
I'm a professor, okay?
I teach this stuff at one of the
best colleges in the country.
I don't go down
to your place of non-employment
and lecture you
about how your little protest
is a misguided waste of time,
except whoops, I just did.
Ha-burn.
Oh, good, the eggs are here.
Well, I should head up.
No, GNB was not popular.
That's why every year they
produced a feel-good video
to improve the bank's image.
GNB ANNOUNCER: What makes
Goliath National Bank
different from other big banks?
Here at GNB, we care.
I care about our precious Earth.
I care about old people.
I care about high-yield
offshore investments.
And so does Tugboat here.
Isn't that right, Tugboat?
Yeah.
Okay, get that camera
out of my face
before I flip you
like a cheese omelet.
All you have to do is say
"I care about
making dreams come true."
First of all, that line
makes me sound like a hooker
and saying it makes me
feel like a hooker, so.
Everyone is in this video.
Randy's in the video.
I don't want to brag,
but in 29 takes,
I only threw up thrice.
Wait. Randy, did you send the
Hermanson contracts downtown?
I did.
I sent them downtown.
Why are you saying it like that?
They never arrived
at the downtown office.
They...
Well, just to make sure
we're on the same page,
is "send them downtown"
not an expression
for shredding a document?
You shredded them?!
Yeah. I sent them downtown.
You know, down
into the shredder.
You-you feed the paper
in a downwards fashion,
so that's where the expression
comes from.
That's not an expression!
That has never
been an expression!
Okay, I can fix this.
I am all over this project.
I'll say this:
There is no quit in that guy.
You should fire him.
Okay, that, that right there.
That attitude is exactly why
I won't be in your video.
Because GNB doesn't care.
They hand out pink slips
like they're hors d'oevres.
Just last week,
I was talking to Arthur...
Oh, whoa, you're wearing
a green tie now.
I'm wearing a green tie.
GNB treats people like
they're disposable,
and I will not be
a part of that.
Marshall Eriksen
does not fire people, period.
Uh, just want you to know,
we are making good progress
on this new project.
Oh, you gentlemen
keep talking,
I will answer that.
Marshall Eriksen's office.
Yeah, I can get that for you.
Just a second.
Uh... bank.
The "B" stands for bank.
Okay, Mother, I'll see you
tonight.
Oh, yikes. I'd better
get Mr. Messy a napkin.
Period.
Just tell me who
you slept with!
Lily, I don't want
to get into it, okay?
Aha, it's someone we know.
If it was some ding dong
we didn't know,
you'd just give me his name.
Fine. It's Bill Pepper.
Bill Pepper?
Mm-hmm.
Kind of a coincidence
there happens
to be a bill and a pepper
shaker here on the table.
Any chance you and Bill had a
three-way with Fork Napkin?
Oh...
It's someone we know!
So, I'm assuming
you all read the chapters
on the Greek Revival
architecture.
Any questions?
Yes.
How do you sleep at night?
What are you doing here?
It was recently made clear to me
that I don't know the first
thing about architecture,
so here I am.
Very well, then,
let's get started.
Some examples of Greek Revival
architecture...
Ooh! Ooh!
Is The Arcadian Greek Revival?
No.
What's The Arcadian?
Oh, it's just this
beautiful, old building
that Professor Mosby
wants to tear down.
What?! No,
Professor Mosby
loves old buildings.
He wouldn't do that.
Right, Ted?
Getting back to Greek Revival...
I lost them.
Look, you're new at teaching.
In my kindergarten class,
I have had plenty
of troublesome students.
Like Johnny Marley...
Johnny?
Johnny!
He and that little stuffed
horsey raised all kinds of hell.
But I have a simple method for
shutting down troublemakers.
You know that '98 Taurus
that's always parked outside?
The one with the really
annoying alarm?
We're familiar with it.
Well, when a kid like Johnny
acts up in my class...
Shuts them right up.
Lily,
my students are adults,
and I treat them that way.
I'll just give them more candy
and make them a mix CD.
Problem solved.
Oh, baby, what's wrong?
Something bad happened.
Randy, hey, have you seen the...
Before you get to that,
regarding the earlier project
I was working on...
Voil?!
That's the Hermanson contract?
The Hermanson contract?
Oh, man, this is
the Filbert contract.
Damn it!
No...
Anyway, what's your thing?
I need the Filbert contract!
No!!
Well, I'll do what I can.
But in my experience, twice
shredded is fairly permanent.
Sorry, Randy, but...
this just isn't working out.
Marshall popped his cherry!
Oh!
Come on, Marshall, you have to
admit, the guy was a disaster.
I mean, it reflected badly
on the company.
He was an embarrassment.
A huge embarrassment.
You slept with Randy!
What?!
Why, it's elementary,
my dear Scherbatson.
Your co-host
is getting super-popular
because of her stupid
commercial,
"Boats! Boats! Boats!"
So, when you arrived at the GNB
party after we left,
you were feeling vulnerable
and drunk.
Then, from across the
not-so-crowded conference room,
your eyes met.
And as we all remember...
Randy has a unique condition.
Yeah, your nose is bleeding
like a faucet.
Oh, God, this happens
every time I get an erection.
I am so sorry.
That's...
...exactly what happened.
See, Marshall,
if getting fired
is an execution,
at least the guy
had a last meal.
I promise you,
tomorrow you'll feel
a lot better.
Randy, hey, what's going on?
I just wanted to say
no hard feelings.
Thank you.
So where you headed now?
Downtown.
No!!
It's okay, baby.
It wasn't okay.
So the next morning...
Arthur, I'm here
because I made a mistake.
I fired Randy yesterday.
That was a mistake.
You should have fired him
a year ago.
No, sir, that is what's
wrong with this company.
How can we say "GNB Cares,"
and then turn around
and treat someone like that?
I mean, sure,
he made a few mistakes,
but everybody makes mistakes.
Like, like Tugboat here.
Aw. I bet you
he's made some mistakes.
And you didn't fire Tugboat,
did you?
No, I got him fixed,
and he calmed down.
Exactly-- kind of.
Randy doesn't need to be fired.
He needs to be fixed.
Marshall, we do some pretty bad
things around here, but I...
No, sir, I'm saying instead
of getting rid of someone
when they screw up, we should...
we should help them.
We should nurture them.
Oh...
I changed the ice pack
on his crotch
every hour for three days.
Wow, Eriksen, if you want to
un-fire Randy, I support you,
because to come in here
and say what you just said,
well, you've got a couple
things that Tugboat doesn't.
Guys, Prof Rock is
a really good mix, okay?
A piece of New York history
is being torn down,
and all you could say
was "Boo freakin' hoo"?
Boo... freakin'...
I may have mentioned
our conversation
over a session of hacky sack.
The one day I miss
the sack circle,
you guys sub her in?
Why'd you miss?
Too busy tearing down
the Statue of Liberty?
No. I was returning a hot dog
costume that you all enjoyed.
They were all
turning against me,
so I figured, what the hell.
And did it work?
Like gangbusters.
We're buddies again.
After class, we
hacked a little sack
to the thumpin' strains
of my Prof Rock CD.
And no, none of them had
heard the Pixies B-side.
Actually, none of them
had heard of the Pixies.
Or a B-side.
Hey, guys.
Uh-oh. I know that smile.
Lily, there's no easy way
to say this.
Marshall's dead.
Randy murdered him.
No. I know why
Randy is smiling.
You're smiling
because of Robin.
Robin? Like how I think about
her when I'm in the shower?
I'm trying to eat
here, buddy.
No. Because you slept
with her on Halloween.
What? No.
I went home, had a shower
an-and went to bed.
You didn't sleep with her?
No.
Even in the shower,
the farthest we ever get
is hugging.
So why are
you smiling?
I'll tell you why.
This just isn't working out.
I'm fired. Great.
This is the candle kiosk
at the mall all over again.
Wait a minute.
I can get a severance check.
If I don't shred it,
I can use that money to start
my own brewery.
Imagine a beer
with my name on it.
Randy Wharmpiss, this is
the best day of your life.
Thanks to that severance check,
this time next year,
you'll all be enjoying
a frothy mug of Wharmpiss.
Randy, great news!
You're not fired!
No...!
Good morning, everybody...
Where's my class?
Hello, Professor.
Ha-boom.
I got you your
job back, Randy.
I thought that you'd be happy.
But I don't belong here.
I'm born to be a brewer!
A... a hopsmeister!
Well, then quit.
No one's stopping you.
I-I can't.
I need my severance check.
Well, I'm sorry Randy,
but that's called fraud.
It's not fraud.
I'm just asking you to get me
a lot of money to not work here
and not tell anyone about it.
Even if I wanted to fire you,
after my talk with Arthur...
Oh, come on,
Arthur can't remember that.
Marshall, what a memorable
talk we had yesterday.
Randy, on behalf of everyone at
GNB, both in and out of prison,
we're sorry.
And I want to assure you
you will never
be fired again.
You're going to work
here until you die, huh?
Huh?
Green tie?
Nice choice.
Thanks. It brings
out my eyes.
Yeah. I'll bring
out your eyes.
Listen, Randy, I'm sorry,
but I broke
my own moral code once
and I felt evil.
I will not let GNB change me.
I will never fire
anyone again ever.
Oh, we'll see about that.
Anyhoo, while I got you--
big smile.
"We care about
making dreams come true,"
in three, two...
No!
What are you doing?
Oh, are you unhappy
with my performance?
Well, I guess I'm fired, then.
I'd better turn in my I.D.
No, it's actually, um, nice
having some of this clutter
off my desk.
So thank you, Randy.
And there's more.
I don't know
what I'm going to use this for,
but it's great stuff.
Now am I fired?
I've been meaning to clean out
that file cabinet for ages.
I'm not even here.
Randy, the coffee.
Oh! Okay.
Okay.
Thank you, Randy.
I've been meaning to cut back
on my caffeine.
Here, try this,
but really go for it.
Remember, this guy
ruined your life.
That's just
the pick-me-up I needed.
Speaking of pickups, can we try
the first one again?
Hello.
It didn't work. They hate me.
How do I get them
to like me again?
You don't.
Ted, you're their teacher.
The only people that
like their teachers...
I like my teachers.
...are dorks.
Except for you, Miles.
Ted, you just have to learn
to embrace their hatred.
Because behind that hatred
lies fear.
And you can use
use that fear,
like I did with Johnny Marley.
Was there more to that story?
A little bit.
Lily, you're a psychopath.
Oh, a panda!
I thought about Lily's advice.
And I figured fear
was worth a try.
Well, Professor Mosby,
is there anything
you want to say to us?
Anyone not in class tomorrow
gets an "F."
You said that?
Well, technically,
they'd get an incomplete,
but I thought "F" had a nice,
scary ring to it.
Right?
Yeah.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Robin, who'd you sleep with?
I told you-- Randy.
He was a machine.
Where's the poop, Robin?
Fine. I didn't sleep
with anyone.
The thing is, ever since
Becky did that commercial,
everyone at work loves her.
So, the day after Halloween,
I was in a commercial.
What... Why didn't you tell us?
Bladder trouble--
it's embarrassing,
it's uncomfortable,
and it can affect anyone.
I'm going to the bathroom
right now.
Neat and discreet adult diapers
for anyone.
Say...
"Ah..."
Wow! I can't wait to see it.
Well, hopefully
you never will.
They said that they
might not even use it.
It ran for seven years.
Okay, you win.
Maybe trashing your office
was a mistake.
It's just,
uh, as long as I can remember,
making beer has been my dream.
Wharmpiss?
I know
it sounds dumb
to someone who's already
achieved his dream--
big-time lawyer
at a huge corporation.
You think working here
is my dream?
Of course.
Anyways, I'll clean
this stuff up.
Have someone get that dead
squirrel out of your desk.
Randy.
This is delicious.
You're fired.
Kids, the next morning--
my class had the highest
attendance it had ever had.
And not long after that,
Randy used his severance money
to start a little brewery.
Now you can have a Wharmpiss
at every bar in America.
And all because...
I care about
making dreams come true.
You got what you need?
Yep. That's a wrap.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
access.wgbh.org