Kids, in the fall of 2010...
it seemed like Aunt Lily could
only talk about one thing... babies.
Oh, God.
I have been craving this burger all day.
Do you know what plays a huge role
in helping a woman conceive?
- Mmm.
- Cervical mucus.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God. I can't wait to see this movie.
I hear it's really scary.
Oh, change of plans.
I thought violent images
wouldn't be good for my future fetus...
so instead,
I rented this video of a live water birth.
They don't know what it is.
It just showed up on my mom's X-ray.
Look at this crib.
But all and all, it wasn't a problem.
That is, until the night
of Barney's boutonniere.
- Oh, you're wearing a flower.
- Thank you.
- I didn't compliment. Just observed.
- I know, isn't it?
- Why are you wearing that?
- Why does Barney do anything ever?
Exactly! Science!
There is an 83% correlation...
between the times men wear boutonnieres
and the times they get laid.
Think about it...
proms, weddings, grandmas' funerals.
Thanks for the redhead, Nana.
The everyday boutonniere, by Stinson.
And nope. I'm sorry, Barney,
but no girl is going home...
with a guy with a flower on his chest...
unless he's a clown
and she's in the trunk of his car.
Along with 50 other clowns.
It's a clown car.
Robin, did you know that "boutonniere"
is French for "booty is near"?
- Hmm.
- True story.
- Une histoire vraie.
- Hmm.
Did you know that " Barney" is French for " sad
little guy who works way too hard to get laid"?
Woman, you best check yourself.
Yeah, on the bright side,
I guess suits are pretty boring without them.
Madam, that is an insult
that cannot be borne!
I demand satisfaction!
What, are we gonna duel?
No, I'm gonna show everyone
this embarrassing video of you.
It's Robin Sparkles 3, y'all.
Kids, by this point we knew Aunt Robin...
had been a teen pop sensation in Canada
known as Robin Sparkles.
And we also knew
that her Robin Sparkles character...
came from a Canadian TVshow
which we'd never seen...
until now.
I cannot wait to see what's on this DVD!
- You haven't watched it yet?
- No, of course not.
I wanted my first time to be
with someone I cared about.
- That's so sweet.
- I get that a lot. Well, once.
Hey, Robin, do you wanna go get
a Korean massage on Saturday?
I'd love to. I've got this knot in my neck
that's so annoying.
Yeah, I figured I should get one now...
because once I get pregnant,
no more massages.
- Just so annoying.
- Okay.
Space Teens?
Is this a porno?
No, dude! Dude! It's a kid show.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah!
I don't know.
This does have all the earmarks of porn.
Stripper pole. Bad lighting.
Delusional girl who thinks it's
a stepping stone to mainstream success.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a big ol' bowl of porn flakes.
Whoa! And who is this exquisite keytarist...
I assume you're about
to make sweet love to?
Oh, that's Jessica Glitter.
She was my B.F.F. on the show
and in real life.
Ah, B.F.F.'s.
Did you guys have sleepovers,
get mad at each other and wrestle...
but then end up kissing
in a tender embrace?
- Here, show us on Lily.
- You know what?
If you're gonna be disgusting,
we're not watching this, okay?
Yeah, come on, Barney.
It's just a cute little story about...
What exactly is this about?
Two average Canadian teenagers
who solve crimes in space using math.
- That sounds ridiculous.
- So sue me...
like the producers
of Milky Way Mathletes tried to.
Great job using long division
to catch that space burglar, eh?
What can I say? He'll be in galactic jail
for the remainder of his life.
Sparkles, Glitter.
We're about to enter an asteroid belt, eh?
Brace for turbulence!
- Ooh.
I have to say, as much as I hate
to agree with Barney...
this does seem to be a veritable pornucopia.
Okay, guys, come on! It's a kid show.
Like, uh, Electric Company
or Sesame Street or, um...
- You can't do that on television.
- Exactly.
No. You can't do that on television.
Robin, this show is so dirty...
I don't know whether to hug you
or run a shower for you...
so you can sit there alone,
crying and clenching your knees.
It's just bad camera work, okay?
Wayne, our camera guy...
he wasn't that great.
I don't know.
I think he did a pretty good job...
considering he was probably
only using one hand.
You know what?
I feel bad for you Americans...
that you can look at this wondrous and
educational adventure through space...
and see something obscene.
Can you just please try to look at this
with the innocence of a child?
- Innocence of a child. Got it.
- Here we go.
Girls, if you wanna get through
the asteroid belt...
you've got to use multiplication.
To the joystickl
Okay, Space Teens, let's multiply.
- Five times six?
- Ooh, 30.
Yesl Seven times four?
- Twenty-eightl
- Keep going.
- Eight times nine?
- Seventy-two!
Don't stop nowl Almost there.
Twenty-three times three?
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
I'm sorry. We gotta ration this.
It's like we're on a desert island
and this video is a really hot, naked chick...
and she's got, like, seaweed on her
and a seashell bra.
You all feel me.
Hey, if you and Jessica are B.F.F.'s,
how come we've never met her?
Okay, well, it was a long time ago, okay?
I get a Christmas card from her every year,
but we're not really friends anymore.
But B.F.F.'s are forever.
Oh, come on, Lily. Nobody stays friends
with their high school friends.
- I'm still friends with Punchy.
- Dude, he lives in Cleveland.
You see him once a year, at which point
he punches you really hard in the arm...
and tells everyone
how you dookied your pants.
I know on paper he sounds great,
but you guys aren't really friends.
Look, I may not see him a lot,
but it doesn't matter.
Observe.
Schmosby!
- Punchy!
- Schmosby!
- Hey, good talkin' to you, Ted.
- Yeah, you too. If you're ever in New York.
- Definitely.
We are just two peas.
I don't get it. How can you and Glitter
just stop being friends?
- Best friends don't do that.
- Well, we did, okay?
And I haven't talked to her
in, like, five years, so just drop it.
I gotta go.
Whoa.
What do you think came
between Robin and Jessica?
Much like our friends, the Space Teens...
I think I can solve this crime with math.
Okay. Okay, here is a Christmas card
that Jessica sent Robin.
- Lily, how old would you say that kid is?
- Four years, three months.
Which means Jessica
got pregnant five years ago...
right around the time
she and Robin stopped being friends.
Of course. Robin hates kids.
The last thing she would wanna do
is hang out with some little brat.
Thus, if I may...
When Glitter's womb a fruit did bear...
Robin said,
"To hell with this, I'm outta h-hare."
- Glitter got pregnant, so Robin dumped her.
- Oh!
Wow. That's gotta be it. Right, Lil?
- Lil?
- Robin's gonna dump me.
Oh, sweetheart.
Aha! When a second uterus
plumped becomes...
Dude.
Feel the room.
- No.
- We've been waiting all day.
Just watch it without me.
Two dudes on the couch together
watching porn? That's kinda weird.
Okay, it's not porn. It's a kid show.
Two dudes watchin'
a kid show might be worse.
- Okay, fine. I'll watch it with you.
- Yah!
But if either of you makes even one peep
about this show being dirty, I'm turning it off.
- I'm serious!
- We...
Hey, Jessica. How's your beaver?
Great. How's your beaver?
Busy as ever.
Our characters had pet beavers.
- Sure.
- The beaver is the official animal of Canada.
It's their national mascot.
It's a noble creature.
Okay, girls.
Everyone knows a beaver's
favorite food is wood.
I just hope we brought along enough of it
for a three-day galactic space journey.
So let's do the math.
If Robin's beaver devours six inches
of wood every half hour...
and Jessica's beaver devours
eight inches of wood every 45 minutes...
how much wood will I need to keep both of
these beavers well fed all weekend long?
While you figure it out at home...
how about we sing you a song
about our beavers?
Hey...
- Hey!
- You do not get to hear the beaver song!
It is a sweet song about friendship,
and you guys are being disgusting!
- And beavers are adorable!
- No arguments here.
'Sup, Schmosby! What's the man doin'?
Punchy, what are ya doin' here?
Well, yesterday you said
if I was ever in New York.
- 'Sup, turds?
- Ew.
Okay. Um, uh, where you stayin'?
In your mom's pants. Trick! She's old.
Hey, don't worry about me.
I'm cool on the couch.
- He's staying here? You're staying here?
- I know. It's so good, right?
Feels like you're dreaming?
But check your totem, brah.
Punchy's here in the flesh. So why don't
we get one of these, Ted? Yeah.
Remember these? High school.
Junior high.
Elementary school. Remember those?
- Look, Punchy's here.
- Yeah.
Hey, Schmosby, remember when you dookied
in your pants down by the lake?
Unbelievable!
Hey, Schmosby,
remember when you dookied on the couch...
in the form of your idiot
high school friend?
Unbelievable!
Come on. I worry about the guy.
He's had the same dead-end job
at a car rental place for 15 years.
- Don't care.
- He's been stuck in Cleveland his whole life.
- Get a hotel.
- Robin.
- LeBron.
- Okay. One night.
Gotta go.
Hey. Where are you goin'?
We just got here.
- Oh, uh, Korean massage.
- By yourself?
Well, I figured you'd be busy reading What
to Expect When You're Expecting to Expect.
Guys, did you see that?
She's going to a Korean massage without me.
That's our thing.
I'm telling you, she's gonna dump me
just like she dumped Glitter.
Lily, come on.
We don't even know that's what happened.
Um, hello. Somebody already solved
that crime using math, remember?
Look, Lily, Robin is clearly getting tired
of you constantly talking about babies.
I don't...
- Lily, how old am I?
- 384 months.
Busted!
Okay. So, before you
Lily all over the place...
maybe you should try hanging out with Robin
and not talking about babies.
So, Lily did just that.
- She tried not to talk about babies.
- Hey!
- Lily, what brings you to the crib?
- The crib.
- What's the matter? You look rattled.
- Rattled?
- I wanna talk about babies.
- What?
Look, I know you don't care about this stuff...
but I'm about to become a mother.
And as a future mother,
I'm gonna need the support...
Oh, my God! You're not even pregnant yet!
What's that supposed to mean?
It means that a fertilized egg
has not yet attached itself...
to the lining of your uterine wall.
You see? I read your Facebook updates.
It's like... It's all you ever talk about,
Lily, and I'm sick of it!
Well, guess what? I've got some good news.
When that baby comes,
you don't have to see it.
In fact, you don't have to see me.
This whole friendship thing... done.
- Great.
For crying out loud,
you broke up with Robin?
I had to. We were growing apart,
and we're better off without each other.
Okay, Lily, you sound
about as convincing as you did...
the time you accidentally shredded
my Joey Buttafuoco pants.
No!
Get on the phone, call Robin and fix this.
I can't. The damage is done.
- Can you just hold me?
- You know what? No.
I don't agree with what you did,
and so I refuse to comfort you...
despite how adorable you are when you cry.
Okay.
Okay, maybe just one cuddle,
but then that's it.
Time Square's da bomb!
I got so many great pictures
of all the billboards.
Yeah, you know, there's more
to New York than Times Square.
There's the Village,
Lower East Side, Central Park.
They got better billboards
than the ones in Times Square?
- No.
- Times Square's da bomb!
Here, you know what? Hold this, okay?
I'm gonna go pee in the jar
I got goin' in the alley.
Seriously, dude, he has got to go.
You need to be, like...
"You are the weakest link. Good-bye."
Punchy, the tribe has spoken.
Please pack up your knives and go.
Your work of art didn't work for us.
Your time's up.
I have to ask you to leave the mansion.
You must leave the ch?teau.
Your tour ends here.
- You've been chopped.
- Okay. Yeah, I know.
You've been evicted
from the Big Brother house.
Your dessert just didn't measure up.
Sashay away.
Give me a jacket and leave Hell's Kitchen!
I'm sorry. You did not get a rose.
You have been eliminated from the race.
You are no longer in the running
to be America's Next Top Model.
You're fired. Auf Wiedersehen.
Ted, come look at this.
I found a little wounded bird in the alley.
That's your scrotum.
You know it is, Ted. You know it is.
Come on, Ted. You always fall for that!
Yeah, he's gotta go.
What are we doing
in Madison Square Garden?
You refused to talk to Robin,
so I thought that you might like to talk to...
the organist for the New York Rangers.
Jessica Glitter?
How did you find Glitter?
Simple, really.
I used my powers of deduction.
You see, I knew that Glitter used to be
a keytarist, which is basically a piano...
so I just made a list of all the keyboard-based
occupations, and then I cross matched...
His friend Barney looked me up,
hoping to buy my Space Teens costume.
And, Glitter, be cool.
So, is this the one
who's best friends with Robin now?
No, more like ex-best friends.
Just like you.
Sorry to hear that.
I miss Robin.
Yeah, well, Marshall and I
are about to get pregnant...
and I know she stopped being friends with you
when you had a baby, so...
Oh, Robin didn't stop being friends with me.
- I stopped being friends with her.
- What? Why?
Because I had a baby.
Honey, when you have a baby,
all that best friend stuff...
hockey, bow hunting for caribou, math...
that all goes out the window.
I mean, I tried to stay friends with her,
but it just didn't happen.
She took it pretty hard.
I even thought
she might try to kill herself.
Charge!
Wow, you dumped her
just because you had a baby?
- That's cold.
- Didn't you do the same thing, minus the baby?
Oh, God. I gotta go.
I gotta go apologize to Robin.
l-I need to tell her I love her
and that she'll always be a priority.
Be careful, Lily.
I made those promises too.
And now I haven't even talked to her
in five years.
Sure, I thought about picking up the phone
and calling her a hundred times...
but I just never have the courage to act...
Hey!
Go ahead.
Hey, do you guys get
Big Chuck and Lil'John out here?
- Punchy, it's time to go back.
- Back to Times Square?
Uh, no. Back... Back to Cleveland.
I don't know if I can do that, bro.
I mean, yeah, I been jonesin'
for a piece of Cleveland-style pizza...
but I feel bad about leaving you out here.
- I worry about you, Ted.
- You worry about me?
Yeah. The other day when you called...
- Schmosby!
- Punchy!
- Good talkin' to you.
- You too. If you're ever in New York.
Definitely.
- Sweetie, who was that?
- It's my friend Ted.
- He sounded kind of depressed.
- Is this the Ted who got left at the altar?
Yeah. He's not doin' so good.
Poor guy lives in a tiny apartment
in New York nowhere near Times Square.
He's got no family around.
He's still single.
Doesn't have a backyard.
It's just a bummer.
Maybe you should go visit him,
cheer him up a little.
You know, buy him some shots,
do the whole wounded bird trick.
- You think that will work?
- Worked on me.
Wow. She sounds pretty great, Punchy.
She's my angel.
In fact, uh, we're getting married.
Wow! Wow! That's...
I'm... I'm really happy for you.
Thanks, Ted. Thanks.
Actually, that's the other reason
why I came out here.
I wanted to see if you'd be my best man.
- Of course I will.
- Yo!
That's great. Oh, no, you're...
- Cop out! Sucker! Oh, that's it! I'm not...
- Yeah.
That night, Lily went to
the one place she knew she could find Robin...
New York's premiere Canadian bar,
the Hoser Hut.
Oh, there you are.
Robin, I owe you a huge apology.
No, no. Me first.
I've been pulling away from you,
and I'm sorry.
It's just, the last time
my best friend had a baby...
I know. I know all about it.
It's not gonna happen with you and me.
And I'm sorry I've been going crazy
with this baby stuff.
It's... I know you hate babies.
Whoa. Look, I hate most babies.
But your baby...
I'm gonna love that kid so much.
- I'm gonna pick it up and everything.
- Oh!
- Ohh. I'm so happy you guys made up.
- Me too.
Where do I know this song from?
Oh, my God. It's the beaver song.
Okay, which one of you put this on?
# Hey, beaver, come on #
# When you feel alone #
# Just pick up that phone #
# And I'll be there to share my #
# Ice-cream cone #
# We'll lick it side by side #
- Wow, this is so dirty.
- Come on, Barney.
It's a sweet song about friendship.
Yeah. Dude, come on.
# Before the day is done #
# Two beavers are better than one #
# Da-da, da-da-da-da, da-da-da #
# They're twice the fun #
- # Ask anyone #
- Whoo-hoo!
# A second beaver can be #
# Second to none #
# Two beavers are better than one #
Whoo!
# Da-da, da-da-da #
# You're my favorite beaver #
# Two beavers are better than one #
# Da-da, da-da-da-da, da-da-da #
# They're twice the fun #
# Ask anyone #
# A second beaver can be #
# Second to none #
# Two beavers are better than one ##
Whoo!
English - US - SDH