previously on lost
right here, there's a line.
You cross that line,
we go from misunderstanding
to... something else.
What do i do?
the button must be pushed
i never entered the numbers
i never pushed the button
you're lying
No, i'm done lying.
it's a parachute
All right. Cereal goes
on the left, bernard.
So this isn't
bothering you at all?
What's "this"?
Well, this.
This.
Why is a bag of potato chips
gonna bother me?
Well, aren't you
remotely curious as to
where all this came from?
You're acting like we just
got back from the supermarket.
Well, i guess i was raised
never to question my blessings.
(chuckles) i was raised
to question piles of food
with weird labels that just
fall out of the sky, rose.
Well, honey, just because
you're having a bad day,
doesn't mean you have
to raise your voice.
Bad day? I've had
seven weeks of bad days
on the other side of the island,
just trying to stay alive
so i could get back to you.
But here...
my god, rose, they've built
a kitchen on the beach.
They've given up.
Given up? On what?
On getting rescued.
Hey.
You gonna get that?
When's the last time
you went in to see him?
A couple hours ago.
He was sleeping.
Did he eat?
Nope.
That's two days now.
No food, no water...
nothing to say.
I don't know about you,
but i'm tired
of waiting.
I hear you've lost
your appetite.
Okay, don't talk.
(chuckles) i was never that good
at bedside manner anyway.
I'm gonna change that dressing
on your shoulder.
If you try anything,
we've got a problem.
So, henry...
(chuckles) "henry."
I was thinking about
something you were saying
before we found out
who you are.
This is gonna sting.
Yeah. You were saying
that if you were
one of them,
that you'd lead us
into a trap...
capture our people...
force a trade.
Us, for you.
Pretty good idea, henry.
And since
you are one of them,
i thought now might be
a good time to use it.
I'm going out to the line that
we're not supposed to cross
and telling them
that we've got you.
And if they want you back,
it'll cost 'em.
(sighs)
And when we get walt back...
you might just have been worth
all the trouble.
Did you say something?
They'll never give you walt.
Cync by xxy
www.1000fr.com
-==http://www.1000fr.com==-
????????????
??????????????????
-=??FRM???=-
??:sallyxobu ???
??:sallyxobu
Don't gun it.
You're digging yourself in.
Just tap the gas lightly.
All due respect,
i have been driving in snow
my whole life.
You mind stepping back?
Well, you have
to rock it out.
You're not
gonna be able to...
(engine continues revving)
I'm calling triple "a."
Why, so they can send
a tow truck?
Trust me, i can do this.
Okay. Ease on the gas.
That's it.
You're doing great.
Almost.
Go, go, go... oh!
(rose) aah!
Are you... are you okay?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
I'm fine.
You know, i would have
gotten it out eventually.
Oh, sure.
July's right around the corner.
(both chuckling)
Well, um,
thanks for helping me.
Sure.
By the way, i'm rose.
Oh, uh, bernard.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh. Okay. Yeah.
(clears throat) okay.
Whew.
Drive, uh,
drive safe, now, okay?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
You, too.
Um... uh, bernard!
Yeah?
Can i buy you
a cup of coffee?
Uh, coffee would be ni.
Yeah. Okay.
I had to beat back
half the group to get these.
I saved 'em for you.
No way.
I'm on a new diet.
Nothing but fish
and water...
and... fish and water.
Hurley, what are you
doing right now?
Uh... talking to your wife?
Good. Can you get libby
and meet me
at the edge of the tree line
in five minutes?
Oh, and if you can get
jin and sun, jenkins
and that frogurt guy, the guy
who used to make frozen yogurt.
Neil?
Yeah. And craig
and anybody else
you can get.
Bernard,
what are you up to?
I got an idea.
Hey, richard. Craig, ralph, come
here. I've got a great idea.
I'm not so sure
trading people's their thing.
Well, talking to him
is getting us nowhere.
So, maybe we can get
something for him.
You want me to come
with you?
You need to stay here.
You need it more than i do.
Do yourself a favor, man.
(gun clicks)
Don't go out there alone.
All rit.
Ha ha.
That's how it's done.
Oh, well look at you.
What, that's, like,
four in the last half hour?
Let me call the guinness book.
You wanna help or not?
'Cause i got better things
to do with my time.
Oh, happy day.
Here comes dr. Giggles.
Hey.
Hey yourself.
I'm going back out
into the jungle
to talk to our friend
with the beard.
See if we can make a trade.
Ah, the old prisoner exchange.
And you're inviting me along
'cause you want a gun, huh?
I'm not inviting you.
I'm inviting kate.
And i've already got a gun,
but thanks for offering.
How in the hell
did you get a gun?
(chuckles)
Does it matter?
I'll get my things.
Okay. Two months we've been
on this island, right?
Two months.
And... and already
we have a water trough,
and we've got
a-a-a food pantry,
and people are taking showers
in your... hatch.
Have you forgotten that we all
crashed on this island?
It's like none of you
want to go home again.
How can you say that?
Of course we want to go home.
Then why aren't we doing
anything about it?
Dude, we, like,
built a raft...
that got blown up.
Okay.
So what
are we doing now?
That pallet of food
had a parachute,
which means
a plane dropped it here,
which means that there are other
planes that fly over the island.
So, we are gonna build a sign.
A massive sign
along the beach.
So that way,
if a plane flies over,
or a satellite takes pictures
from up there,
we want to make damn sure
that they know we're here,
that they know about us.
Maybe we should speak
to jack about this first.
Well, do we have to run
everything by jack?
I mean, he's not the president.
He's... he's a doctor.
You're a dentist.
Ahem. Uh, could l-i speak to you
for just a second?
Come on.
Honey, it is just a sign.
I don't see what the harm is.
The harm is, you are telling
these people about airplanes
and satellites coming out
of nowhere to save the day.
I'm just trying
to do something.
I want to get back
to our life.
Well, the only thing
you are doing
is giving these people
false hope.
Excuse me.
I have a sign to build.
Ahem. All right.
Um, uh, i wanna get
this going right away.
We've waited long enough.
It's just amazing,
isn't it?
Oh, sure, it's beautiful.
You're not impressed, hu
oh, yeah.
So, what does god have to do
to get your attention?
Bernard...
what are you doing?
(playing frank sinatra's
"the right girl for me")
Rose...
i've been a bachelor
for 56 years.
And then i met you,
and... we just fell
into this rhythm
like we had known ch other
forever.
I had always dreamed
of finding somebody like you,
but i'd given up hope
that i ever would.
Bernard...
oh, i know, i know.
It's crazy.
Uh, we just met
five months ago.
But five months
is long enough.
Because i knew
after five minutes.
Rose...
i love you.
Will you marry me?
Bernard, i'm dying.
I'm sick, and i'm dying.
Uh, would you excuse us
for a minute, please?
I've been in remission
for the last couple of years.
But now, it's back,
and this time,
it's not going away.
My doctor says
i have about a year,
maybe a little longer.
You haven't answered
my question.
Are... you sure?
Oh, i'm sure.
Yes...
yes.
Well, you bunk with a guy
for 48 days,
now he doesn't call
or write.
Hello, bernard.
What do you boys
got going up here?
Just working.
Well, listen.
I've got a whole team of folks
throwing together a big sign
down along the beach.
Hopefully, it'll get us spotted
by a plane or a satellite.
We could sure use
all the bodies we could get
to help put it together.
Sorry, i'm busy.
Charlie?
Ah, regrets, bernard. I've only
got two hands, you know.
Good luck, though.
Well, could i at least grab
some of these logs?
We could sure use...
we're using them.
For what, exactly?
A church.
A church?
Yes.
Everybody on this island
is building something.
I'm trying to get us saved.
People are saved
in different ways, bernard.
I think i liked you better
when you just hit people
with your stick.
I like you
just the way you are.
I need to talk to him.
The gun's with jack.
The door stays closed.
But if you wanna talk to him,
talk to him.
Henry, can you hear me?
It's john, henry.
Henry, did you enter
the numbers?
Did you push the button
or not?
Henry!
I need to know.
I want you to answer me.
Answer me!
Henry, can you hear me?!
What happened to everybody?
Where's, uh,
where's craig?
Where's frogurt?
Okay. All right.
Moving on.
We're gonna put the sign
across this entire beach,
which means the letters
have to be really big...
about 40 feet.
These black rocks will get
maximum contrast with the sand.
Dude, we're likely
to need a lot more rocks.
Yes, hurley.
We are gonna need
a lot more rocks.
There's a lava field
about a half a mile inland.
It's just loaded with them.
We're gonna haul them out
in 2-man teams.
So, uh, you guys double up,
and i am gonna start sketching
off the letters in the sand.
Let's do this.
Hey, um, i can sketch
the letters.
Everybody's got a job,
hurley.
I do my job,
you do yours.
(speaking korean)
What? What'd he say?
I think he's not so crazy
about the whole "carry the rocks
a half mile" thing.
Okay... well,
this is gonna take time.
But if this is the thing
that gets us off this plac
isn't that worth it?
Rome wasn't built in a day,
you know.
Ah, no, you don't... okay.
All right, let's get started.
Come on.
We're lost.
Oh, you saying we're lost
doesn't make us lost,
sweetheart.
I know exactly
where we are.
Me, too.
Driving around in circles
in the middle of the outback.
(laughs)
That's why i wand
to be on a beach
for our honeymoon.
Thank goodness.
Civilization.
Bernard,
let's get directions.
Oh, i don't need directions.
I told you, honey.
We're not lost.
Bernard, what's going on?
I brought you out here...
because i want you
to see this man.
His name is isaac of uluru
and he's helped
hundreds of people.
Now, i know how it looks,
but believe me,
he is completely legit.
Bernard...
you brought me
to a faith healer?
He's the real deal, rose.
Once i started telling people
about your situation,
i got three separate calls
recommending him.
My situation?
This is why you wanted
to come to australia?
To bring me
to some kind of a kook?
No, he's not.
Rose, i made a $10,000 donation
just to get you in to see him.
Normally...
i didn't ask for this!
It's just...
bernard...
i have made my peace
with what's happening
to me.
Well, i haven't.
I can't just do nothing,
rose.
That's not me.
That's not who i am.
I have to try.
Will you try, rose?
For me.
(bernard) okay,
it's just gonna be great.
It's gonna be a really big sign.
(sawyer) that's great.
If you have time
to fix your hut,
you'll have time
to move some rocks.
Come on. We could
really use your help.
What, you got union trouble
down at the sand factory,
norma rae?
Come on, sawyer.
I need your help.
Now what do you say?
(sighs) i say...
pas-adena.
Well, i hope you're happy.
About what?
This morning i had 15 people
willing to work on the sign,
and now i'm down to four.
And how is that my fault?
(sighs) at the very least,
i expected your support.
You had to go
and attack me.
Have you ever stopped
to think,
maybe the reason
people are quitting
is because you've got yourself
a management problem?
What is the matter with you,
rose?
I am just trying
to do something.
That's exactly right.
You're always trying to do.
Why can't you
just let things be?
If i didn't
always have to do something,
you wouldn't be here.
I'm flattered.
Yeah? Why is that?
'Cause you chose me to go
with you instead of sawyer.
I asked sayid first, but...
he turned me down.
And i only asked you
because they don't want you.
They grabbed you,
had you at gunpoint.
They could have kept you,
but they didn't.
Then again, they didn't
really want me, either.
Damaged goods.
Both of us.
What's that?
Kate.
It's a doll.
Wait, wait, no...
no, don't...
sorry.
You okay?
Yeah.
Oh, good.
So you can hear me.
This isn't one of theirs.
(grunts)
Must be one
of rousseau's traps.
Hopefully she's not
far from here.
Could be a week
before she shows up.
What are you doing?
I'm trying
to get the gun.
I can't get my arm around.
All right, here, let me.
All right. Hey!
(grunting)
Sorry.
I don't wanna shoot you.
Okay.
You got it?
Okay, ready?
Yeah.
Got it, got it, got it.
Oh, all right.
There, got it.
Now, give me the gun.
Why, what for?
Gonna try to shoot
the rope.
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey, hey!
I'm a better shot
than you are.
(laughs) oh, really?
Yeah, i told you.
I grew up hunting
with my dad.
Damn it!
Well, at least
they know where we are.
Okay, now give me
the gun.
And you're gonna waste
another bullet?
Don't worry.
We'll still have 13 more
to shoot each other with.
Come on.
Fine.
You have a better angle
than i do, anyway.
Oh, that's gonna be your excuse
when i make the shot.
When you make
the shot.
Okay.
Nice shot.
(laughs)
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
You're doing it all wrong!
I told you three rows.
Three... so they can see it
from the air.
(speaking korean)
Three rows!
How hard is that?
(groans) do i just
have to do everything myself?
No! No, no, no!
No, jin. No, wait.
Please...
i just want
to get my wife home.
Rose.
I wanna get rose home.
Sorry.
You're in my spot.
I can move.
Can you?
Oh, that's funny.
(laughs)
I guess your sense of humor
got trapped
under that door with your leg.
I saw your husband
walking through the jungle,
hauling rocks.
He's building a big sign
in the sand,
so the satellites
will see it.
That man doesn't know
the difference
between an errand
and a fool's errand.
Well, rose,
most of us don't.
So what are you doing
down here, john?
Can't remember
the last time
i saw you
out of that hatch.
I'm done with the hatch.
Oh, now,
you're just frustrated.
You'll be out of that splint
and running around the island
again in no time.
Hmm. And yet jack said
it'd be
at least four weeks.
But, honey,
you and i both know
it's not gonna
take that long.
(woman) right this way,
rose.
Please, make yourself
comfortable.
Isaac will be
right with you.
You must be rose.
Why don't you have a seat?
So, um...
how does this work?
I sit here and you chant?
Or, um...
pray or what?
There are certain places
with great energy...
spots on the earth,
like the one we're above now.
Perhaps this energy
is geological, magnetic.
Or perhaps
it's something else.
And, when possible,
i harness this energy
and give it to others.
May i?
What?
What... what is it?
I'm sorry.
Can't do anything
for you, rose.
I didn't expect you to.
It's not that
you can't be healed.
Like i said,
there's different energies.
This is not
the right place for you.
Where is the right place?
I wish i knew.
I'll return
your husband's donation.
Don't.
I'm gonna tell him
you fixed me.
I'm going to tell him
What did you mean
back there?
What?
In the net.
You said they were
sophisticated, the others.
Uh...
uh, last week,
when the baby got sick,
claire and i went
into the jungle
and, uh,
found another hatch.
What?
Like a medical station.
There was nothing you could use.
It was all cleared out, but...
i found some lockers.
They had clothes inside,
all worn and dirty.
They were on hangers, like...
like costumes, you know?
And there was a makeup kit...
and a fake beard.
When were you going
to tell me this?
When you decided to let me
back in the club.
What?
You can keep one of them
locked up
in the hatch for, like, a week,
and say nothing.
But then, when l...
we're here.
Are you sure? I...
that's where they took
the shot at sawyer.
Right over there
is where they pushed you
out of the jungle
with a bag on your head.
And right there is where i...
where i laid my gun down.
(shouting) hey!
Hey, i'm back!
You say you're watching us?
Do you hear me?!
We've got your man!
If you want him back,
you're gonna
have to come out here!
Come on out!
Jack!
I know you're out there!
I know you can hear me!
Jack, they're not here.
I'll be right here
until you talk to me!
I'll be right here!
i brought you some supper.
Thanks. You can just
set it down there.
Where is everybody?
I owe you an apology.
You don't have anything
to be sorry for.
It's my own damn fault
i'm out here by myself.
That's not why
i'm apologizing.
I lied to you.
Back in australia.
Isaac... he didn't heal me.
He didn't do anything.
Of course he did.
You're... you're...
bernard...
he didn't heal me.
But that doesn't mean
i'm not healed.
(rose) when you're sick,
and you've got
something inside you
that doesn't belong there,
you can feel it.
I couldn't feel it anymore.
At first, i thought
it was just shock.
But it wasn't.
It's this place.
But... but you said
isaac fixed you.
I told you that
so that you wouldn't spend
what time we had left
trying to do something.
Uh... rose, you could just
be in remission.
How do you know
it wasn't isaac who healed you?
Bernard...
how do you know
that he didn't heal you?
I know.
These yours?
Uh, thank you.
You're welcome.
Trust me.
I know.
You don't want
to be rescued, do you?
You think if you leave...
it'll come back.
And if you can't leave...
neither can i.
We won't ever leave, rose.
I would, uh,
i would offer to take down
the sign, but, um...
we didn't get very far.
hey.
Hi.
I pressed yourutton.
It's not my butt.
Where'd you go?
I just needed to...
stretch my legs.
how long are you
gonna wait, jack?
Till i get my voice back.
Then i'm gonna yellsome more.
Maybe they can't hear you.
They can hear me.
I'm sorry i kissed you.
I'm not.
(kate) michael.
edited by: abadaniell@gmail.com
Mantapp! Tunggu episod lepas nih!