Oh!
You were running
like the devil's chasing you.
Maybe he is.
- Good for you, keeping in shape.
- What do you want, Locke?
- What do I want?
- I've been here over a week.
You've never said two words to me,
and now you're sitting outside my tent?
We got a man locked up
down in the hatch.
There's a possibility
he's one of them, the Others.
- Who's "we"?
- Me and Jack.
He's keeping watch right now.
- How long's he been down there?
- Three days.
I'd like you to talk with him.
You have experience with the Others.
You were a cop.
You're the most qualified to figure out
if this man's telling the truth.
Does Jack know
you're coming to me with this?
We got a serious problem, Ana Lucia.
All of us.
I'm taking the necessary steps
to solve it.
I don't need Jack's permission.
Right now there's a man
sitting in a room in my hatch,
and I want him out.
I don't wanna give you anything.
It's the thought that counts,
and you didn't think.
I think all the time. Maybe you should
think about giving me a break.
Just hush, Bernard. Just hush.
Honey.
Are you all right?
I'm... I think
I'm just a little light-headed.
- Well, you look as pale as a sheet.
- Well, give her some water.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Don't pay him any mind, honey.
He's just mad at the world
because he forgot my birthday.
I didn't forget. I don't even know
what day of the week it is, Rose.
It's Saturday, Bernard.
- Honey, can you walk?
- Really, I'm all right.
- Maybe we should go get Jin.
- No.
I think I was just
out in the sun too long.
You spend a lot of time around the baby.
Maybe you caught something.
- At least talk to Jack.
- Really, I'm OK.
Thank you, both of you.
In English.
I'll...
I would like an iced tea, please.
- Very good.
- Thank you.
Morning, Jack.
You couldn't wait
until I was done in here?
The steam opens up my pores.
Man's got no shaving cream,
he's got to improvise.
I also thought this might be a good time
to talk about our problem.
- Our problem?
- Our Henry problem.
We've had him locked up
for three days.
I get the sense that he's just
not motivated to cooperate with us.
And how are we gonna
motivate him, John?
There's nothing we can do.
We need to bring in some new blood.
Obviously you have someone in mind.
What do you think about Ana Lucia?
Why her?
She's the one you went to
to start an army to fight these people.
Why not her?
Unless you're worried
about what she'll do to him.
- I'll talk to her.
- I already did.
In there with him now.
Were you on the plane, too?
I was in the tail section.
We crashed
on the other side of the island.
You walked across? All the way here?
That must have been fun.
It had its moments.
So, you gonna tell me your story, Henry?
Why bother? I've told it to everyone.
Jack, Locke, the big black guy
that cut off his beard in front of me.
Oh, yeah, and my buddy, Sayid.
- You see how much he liked my story.
- So, how about you try me?
I don't mean to be ungrateful, but why
are you gonna help me get out of here?
On the other side of the island,
there was this guy with us.
I was 100% convinced
that he wasn't on the plane.
So I dug a hole and I threw him in it.
And what happened?
I was wrong, and now he's dead.
But good news for you, Henry.
I don't make the same mistake twice.
So, how about you tell me your story?
Sawyer.
Well, hey there, sunshine.
What can I do for you?
How's your book?
Predictable. Not nearly enough sex.
I heard that you have
all the medical supplies.
- You heard correct.
- May I look through them?
No, you may not. But if you'll tell me
what you're looking for...
Forget it.
OK. Hold on.
Now I'm intrigued.
Tell you what, tell me what you're
looking for and it's yours, gratis.
Can't I just look myself?
It's not a drugstore, sweetheart.
I need...
a pregnancy test.
- I can't hear anything.
- She's only been in there 30 minutes.
He might have snapped her neck, John.
How do you know she hasn't snapped his?
So, you and your wife
travel around the world
and crash here in a smiley-face balloon.
Then she dies, you get captured
by a French chick who brings you here,
and then they lock you up.
Sounds silly when you say it like that.
- Why don't you have a beard?
- Because I shaved.
Because I needed something normal.
OK. So, why don't you draw me
a map to your balloon?
We'll go out there, find it,
and everybody'll believe you.
They all keep asking me to draw a map.
And if I mess up, they'll crucify me.
You flew around the world in a balloon,
and you don't think
you can draw a map?
Air travel, it's a different animal.
It's about wind currents...
Do you or do you not know where it is?
Yeah, I know where it is.
I went back there to bury my wife.
Why'd you do that?
Because that balloon
was the closest thing we had to home.
You people have been looking
for someone to punish
for everything that's happened,
someone to blame,
and now you've got him.
It doesn't matter what I do.
I'm dead already.
You draw up that map, Henry.
I'll find your balloon.
But if you don't,
things are gonna play out
just like you said.
Hey, Sun.
Look what I found
in the middle of the jungle.
It's not even melted or nothing.
Crazy, huh?
D'you wanna split it?
No. No, thank you.
I was just heading to the beach.
OK. Well, later, dude.
Coming out.
He told me the same story he told you.
- You believe him?
- I don't know yet.
I need more time with him.
- He's all yours.
- Tomorrow.
I wanna give him some time to think.
If that's OK with you.
I didn't tell anyone, Ana.
No worries, man.
Bit large for a dining-room table.
If we cut them in two,
it will suit the purpose.
Sayid, can I talk to you?
Of course.
Alone?
Whatever you need to say,
you can say it here.
- It's about the hatch.
- The guy locked in the closet there?
What about him?
It's to his balloon.
- How did you get him to do this?
- I asked nicely.
Do Jack and Locke know about this?
Jack and Locke are a little too busy
worrying about Locke and Jack.
All I wanna know
is if this guy's telling the truth.
Why come to me?
Judging from what you did to his face,
that's what you want, too.
This is at least a day's walk.
Then we should get going.
Oh!
- You OK?
- Fine. Thanks.
That cliff there appears to be this.
Score one for Henry.
Pointing out a touchstone does not mean
he's leading us to a balloon.
Maybe not, but at least
we're on the right island.
Humor's not his strong suit.
And I'm saying this to you.
- You looking at my bum?
- No, I'm looking at your gun.
My what?
Maybe you should give the gun
to somebody who knows how to use it.
Maybe I will. As I recall, the last time
you had a gun you murdered someone.
That's enough.
We'll go as far as the base of the cliff
and we'll camp there.
- How long is it supposed to take?
- Up to two minutes.
- I'm sorry. I'm just...
- I know.
Where did Sawyer
find one of these, anyway?
I mean, who flies
with a pregnancy test, right?
Have you ever taken one?
Yeah.
Thank you for waiting with me
and not asking
why you're here and not Jin.
You're welcome.
It's time.
You're pregnant.
Is it 100% sure?
There's only one way to find out.
These tests are pretty accurate.
A false negative in the first week,
maybe, but a positive is a positive.
- But it's impossible.
- Oh, no, it's possible.
Are you feeling queasy, light-headed?
Please, Jack, this is private.
Nobody can know.
- You're not gonna tell Jin?
- In time, I will. It's just...
It's complicated.
As complicated as Jin being the last one
here to find out you spoke English?
Sun, my advice, and it's just that,
because I'm the last person to ask
about this, but you should tell him.
And when you do, you should
tell him everything, the whole truth.
I've gotta get back to the hatch.
Congratulations, Sun.
You've been down there a lot, Jack.
Is everything OK?
Sure. Yeah. Everything's fine.
You OK?
Sun?
Sun, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
You were distracted
for our entire lesson. You're not fine.
We...
Jin and I went to see a doctor.
He said I cannot have children.
I'm very sorry, Sun.
I was glad.
I'm not saying you should stay for Jin.
You mind?
You should sleep while you can.
Yeah. I can't sleep.
People don't like me.
I've tried to get them to
most of my life, but...
I guess I just gave up a while back.
I mean...
I am what I am.
But you, you've got
a good reason to hate me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what I did.
You were trying to protect your people.
It wasn't you that killed Shannon,
it was them.
And once we find out he is one of them,
then something will have to be done.
What?
Nothing.
It's gonna rain.
- We should get moving.
- Who wants breakfast?
I have papayas and papayas.
Let's go.
Right. Why eat?
This is it.
This balloon,
it would be rather large, right?
Why am I not surprised?
- We need to look some more.
- This is where he said it would be.
If I'm gonna back your play on this,
Sayid, we need to be sure.
I'll divide the area into three grids.
We'll search as thoroughly
as you please.
Oh, for the love of God.
No, no, no, no. It's not for fish.
No, no, no.
Oysters.
Oyster.
- Pearl. For Rose. Pearl.
- Ah.
No oyster. No oyster here.
Of course not. Why would there be?
Yo, Daddy-o.
- Sawyer.
- Way to go, Papa-san.
You didn't waste much time.
I'd give you a cigar, Bernie,
but I'm fresh out.
- Sun's pregnant?
- Keep it down, there, Suzy.
I don't think Jin Senior here knows yet.
Daddy-o.
I... love... you.
How is it?
"Men reject their prophets
and slay them,
but they love their martyrs and honor
those whom they have slain. "
So what's the difference
between a martyr and a prophet?
Either way,
it sounds like you end up dead.
That's the spirit.
You in the mood for some breakfast?
- What's the computer for?
- Nothing.
Cereal.
Wow. Where'd you guys get cereal?
It was down here all along.
Pantry's full of food.
How old is it?
You guys don't know much, huh?
I'd be asking all kinds of questions
about all this stuff down here.
You guys don't even seem that curious.
Do you want the cereal or don't you?
This must be my reward
for good behavior, huh?
I guess I earned myself some goodwill
for finally drawing that map for Ana.
What map?
To my balloon.
- Did you?
- No.
Wow. You guys have
some real trust issues, don't you?
I guess it makes sense
she didn't tell you.
I mean, with the two of you
fighting all the time.
Of course, if I was one of them,
these people that you seem to think
are your enemies,
what would I do?
Well, there'd be no balloon.
So I'd draw a map
to a real secluded place,
like a cave or some underbrush.
A good place for a trap.
An ambush.
And when your friends got there, a bunch
of my people'd be waiting for them.
And then they'd use them
to trade for me.
I guess it's a good thing
I'm not one of them, huh?
You guys got any milk?