Previously on Lost:
l need you to go up through the grate
and into the vents.
That button has to be pushed.
OK.
l crawled through your vents
and l stood at your computer.
And you know what happened?
Nothing happened, John.
l never entered the numbers.
l never pressed the button.
lf you want to do
something nice for Libby,
there's a beautiful beach
three kilometres from here.
You could take her there.
Come on, give me the blankets.
- Blankets?
- l will handle the blankets, OK?
Take us to the guns. Now.
Oh, that bitch.
She stole my damn gun. Ana Lucia.
Why would she need a gun?
We caught one of them. The Others.
He's locked up in there.
Give me the gun. l'll kill him.
l'm sorry.
Michael?
What are you building?
- Hello, Ana.
- Well, hello, yourself.
So you gonna tell me? What is it?
l'm building a church.
Now, why the hell
would you wanna do that?
- Because l was told to.
- Told to by who?
l was just told.
l think it was in a dream.
A dream like this one?
You need to help John.
Yemi?
Hello, brother.
Yemi. Forgive me. l should have
listened to you. You were right.
l didn't mean to do what l did.
The work being done
in this place is important, Eko.
lt is more important than anything,
and it is in danger.
You must help John.
He has lost his way.
You must make him take you
to the question mark.
John will not want to show you,
so you must make him.
Eko. There are many distractions,
brother, but you must move past them.
What is done is done. Do you understand?
Yes, Yemi.
And, Eko? Bring the axe.
What's the matter?
You all right, mate?
l need to find John.
- What were you thinking?
- Leave him alone.
- No, don't.
- Shut it, Sawyer.
- lf Ana hadn't lifted your gun...
- Swell.
Gimpy McCrutch covers up that
the Artist Formerly Known As Henry Gale
tried to strangle your little amiga
and it's on me when she goes vigilante.
- How about you go back to the beach?
- Hey, enough. Both of you.
Michael. Hey.
- He shot me.
- Who?
- He's gone. He ran out.
- Go. l got him.
l was sleeping and l heard gunshots.
l got up.
l came out of the bedroom
and there was this guy.
He had a gun and...
All right, come on.
We gotta get you up, all right?
Let me help you.
She's dead.
Kate, we gotta get her up. We gotta
get her up to the back room, OK?
Grant us this mercy, O Lord,
we beseech thee.
Amen.
She's in shock. All right,
we gotta keep pressure on this one.
Can you do anything? Jack?
l heard you.
Just keep pressure on her, OK?
How is she?
l'm doing what l can.
- How long ago?
- What?
When did this happen?
How long ago did he leave?
l don't know.
Twenty minutes, maybe a half-hour ago.
We can pick up the trail,
catch up to him.
- Man's got a head start, a gun...
- He shot three people. One's dead.
Who's gonna take care of Libby while
you're off playing Daniel Boone?
l will go.
John, you have tracking experience, yes?
Yeah.
We will find his trail together.
You find anything,
you come right back here
and we figure out
what we're gonna do next together.
Let's go, John.
How long has it been
since your last confession?
Good question. Too many years
for me to even remember.
What do you wish
to ask God's forgiveness for?
- What sins have you committed?
- Well, let's see.
Well, l slept with another woman
besides my wife.
- Just once or many times?
- How many is ''many''?
To receive God's forgiveness
you must be penitent for your sins.
l also forged lD papers
for a guy pretending to be a priest.
Do you have it?
So what did you do, Padre?
Skim from the collection plate?
You know, l've got some friends in Los
Angeles. l could get you on with them.
- Doing what?
- You know, stuff.
- Morning, Father Tunde.
- Good morning, Monsignor.
Mr Caldwell has been helping me
arrange my trip to the United States.
l'm sorry, but l've got some bad news.
You're gonna have to postpone your trip.
lt appears we have a miracle.
My daughter, she... she drowned.
l'm very sorry for your loss.
Oh, no, you don't understand.
She came back to life.
We were out in the backblocks
and Charlotte must have slipped
and she went into the river
and she's not much of a swimmer.
She was dead,
and the next day she woke up.
Don't you understand? lt's a miracle.
A confirmation of faith.
Everyone needs to know about this.
- Where is your daughter now?
- At home with my husband.
And what does he think?
The world needs to know.
We need to tell the Vatican.
l'm sorry.
We can't just do that, Mrs Malkin.
The church needs to conduct an
investigation before anyone can be told.
Father Tunde will start this process,
if you'll permit him.
Mrs Malkin, would you
excuse us for a moment?
Of course.
Monsignor, with all due respect,
l cannot do what you have asked.
Why not?
Because l do not believe
what this woman says.
Why do you think l chose you?
Are you seeing something l'm not?
Hey.
l haven't seen a single track or
piece of sign since we left the hatch.
- What the hell are you following?
- Where is the question mark?
The what?
The question mark, John. Where is it?
You know what?
You keep chasing after your own shadow.
l'm going back.
l know you do not want to show me,
but you must.
- No, l don't have to show you anything.
- Then l'm sorry.
You hit me.
- Why did you...?
- Because you were being difficult.
Are you insane?
No.
Ana Lucia, your friend,
was just murdered and you...
Ana wants me to help you, John.
- Help me do what?
- Find the question mark.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
No.
But you know what l am talking about,
John, and that is all that matters.
Here. Here. You wanna find
your damn question mark?
Here, this is it right here.
Here, take it.
Because it's nothing. lt's a memory.
lt's ten seconds of nothing.
- This is your hatch, yes?
- lt's not my hatch.
lf the swan is where we came from,
then we go that way.
We shouldn't even be out here.
Ana Lucia would still be alive
if l'd just told Jack
that Henry attacked her.
Now she wants us to go here, John.
She wants us to go here, John. Together.
- She said this in my dream.
- Oh, of course, your dream.
Tell me, John,
haven't you ever followed a dream?
So, the Vatican's really interested
in this one, eh?
That depends
upon what l put in my report.
Why don't you just start
by telling me what happened that night?
Well, l got a call.
That was around 1 a.m.
Ambos brought this girl in dead.
She'd been in the water two hours.
Have you had experience
in this type of death?
Yeah, of course. l'm an undertaker.
Well, l mean, it's my day job.
l'm perfectly qualified to be a coroner.
l mean, l did go to medical school.
And when did you find out
that she was not dead?
During the autopsy.
During the autopsy?
lt's all right.
l didn't expect you to believe me.
l figured you'd want
to have a listen for yourself.
Decedent is a Caucasian female.
She's 16 1 centimetres, 5 1.3 kilos.
Body was prepped and washed
by the very lovely Valerie Mc Tavish.
Ian, stop it.
Commencing with the post.
This is a clear case of drowning.
- I'll begin with the thoracic...
- No!
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Val...
Take it.
No, please. l don't want to ever listen
to that tape again.
- You lost already?
- Your map is inexact.
- No kidding?
- These landmarks.
- ls this a river?
- No, it's a wavy line.
l didn't draw it. l just transcribed it.
l don't even know if it is a map.
- Let's assume it is.
- What's the axe for?
l don't know yet.
You were the one
that found this plane, yes?
Yeah.
lt was up there.
And what made it fall?
Boone.
Boone made it fall.
Then he died.
Sacrifice that the island demanded.
Excuse me?
Nothing. So, what's next?
We make camp, get some sleep,
and wait for further instruction.
Where in the hell are they?
Just calm down.
Finding his trail in the dark
is not gonna be easy.
They'll be back.
Jack.
She say anything? Libby?
She's still unconscious.
The bleeding's stopped.
- That's good, right?
- No.
lt's not good.
- And there's nothing you can...?
- l can make her comfortable.
But l don't have what l need.
l gave you all the damn meds
two days ago.
The heroin, Sawyer.
- Give me twenty minutes.
- Kate's gonna go with you.
- lt doesn't take two people to carry...
- Kate is going with you.
Why would he need me to go with him?
Jacko here knows his heroin's
in my stash with the guns.
So l can either show you where it's at
or let poor Libby suffer.
- That pretty much it, Doc?
- Yeah. Yeah. That's pretty much it.
Let's go, Freckles.
- l'm curious about something.
- Yeah, what's that?
How did Ana Lucia get your gun?
l don't know.
She must have lifted it off me.
She pickpocketed your gun?
How'd she do that?
Well, if l knew how she did it, she
wouldn't be able to do it, would she?
After you.
l thought you were taking me
to your stash.
Do you have to make everything
so damn difficult? Just go in.
You kept the guns here.
All this time, right under you.
Fooled you, didn't l?
Hey, guys.
You seen Libby around?
Eko.
Yemi.
You'll wake John.
Come. Follow me.
Yemi.
Wake up, John.
Are you all right, John?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, l'm fine.
You had a dream?
Was there a man? A priest?
The man that you saw was my brother.
Your brother?
This is why we needed to come together.
This is how we are going to be led,
how we will know where to go.
- l don't know where to go.
- Did he tell you anything?
- No. He...
- Nothing? Anything?
lt wasn't even me. lt was you.
lt didn't...
He wanted me to follow him.
Follow him where?
Wait here.
Eko, it was just a dream. lt's not safe.
Eko.
Father, it's not a very good time.
Come back later.
l must speak to your daughter.
- Yesterday you said...
- l know what l said.
Just right this minute
it's not a very good time.
All right. Get back in the house, Joyce.
Get her inside.
- Richard, please...
- lnside. Now.
l know why you're here, friend,
but save yourself the trouble.
What happened here was not a miracle.
The doctor that treated your daughter
feels differently.
Treated her?
You mean tried to cut her open.
He's trying to cover up
his own negligence.
He tell you the whole story,
how she supposedly drowned?
She fell into a mountain river.
Her body shut down.
She went into hypothermia,
which made her appear dead.
Then why is your wife
so convinced otherwise?
Cos she's a zealot.
All of this, everything she's doing,
it's to spite me.
- Why would she spite you?
- Because she knows l'm a fraud.
Because l make my living as a psychic.
You see, that's what l do. l gather
intelligence on people and l exploit it.
Every day l meet people
looking for a miracle,
desperate to find one.
But there are none to be had.
Not in this world, anyway.
l will report back to my monsignor
that there was no miracle here.
Your daughter is alive.
This is all that matters.
Eko. Be careful.
Eko.
l'm fine.
Hey, Eko. What's up there?
Do you see anything?
l don't see nothing.
- lt's salted.
- What?
The earth has been salted
so that nothing can grow.
Why would anyone wanna salt it?
There's nothing here.
l believe they made a circle, a target,
so that this place
can be seen from up above.
They? What place?
The place that this plane fell upon,
John. Come on.
John.
Will you help me with this?
Wait.
Eko.
- May l?
- Please. Be my guest.
We were gonna have our first date.
Date?
Yeah.
Picnic on the beach.
l'm glad you're OK, man.
John.
Hello. I'm Dr Mark Wickmund,
and this is the orientation film
for Station 5 of The Dharma Initiative.
Station 5, or The Pearl,
is a monitoring station
where the activities of participants
in Dharma Initiative projects
can be observed and recorded
not only for posterity,
but for the ongoing refinement
of the Initiative as a whole.
As Karen DeGroot herself has written,
''Careful observation is the only key
to true and complete awareness. ''
Your tour of duty in The Pearl
will last three weeks
and during this time you will observe
a psychological experiment in progress.
Your duty is to observe team members
in another station on the island.
These team members are not aware
they are under surveillance
or that they are subjects
of an experiment.
Working in eight-hour shifts,
you and your partner will record
everything you observe
in the notebooks we've provided.
What is the nature of the experiment,
you might ask?
What do these subjects
believe they are accomplishing
as they struggle to fulfil their tasks?
You, as the observer,
don't need to know.
All you need to know
is the subjects believe theirjob
is of the utmost importance.
Remember, everything that occurs,
no matter how minute or seemingly
unimportant, must be recorded.
Each time a notebook is filled
with the fruits
of your diligent observation,
roll it up, and place it
in one of the containers provided.
Then simply place the container
in the pneumatic tube
and presto,
it will be transported directly to us.
At the end of your eight-hour shift,
proceed to the Pala Ferry,
which will take you back to
the barracks to prepare for your next...
On behalf of the DeGroots, Alvar Hanso,
and all of us here
at The Dharma Initiative, thank you.
Namaste and good luck.
Would you like to watch that again?
No.
No, l've seen enough.
What are you doing?
l'm taking this back with us.
Why?
Because they may be important.
lmportant?
l'm sorry. Weren't you just watching
the same thing l was?
Yes, John, and l believe
the work you have been doing
is more important now than ever.
What work?
Pushing the button.
That's not work. That's a joke.
Rats in a maze with no cheese.
lt is work, John. We are being tested.
Tested?
The reason to do it, push the button,
is not because we are told to do so
in a film.
Oh, well.
Well, then, what is the reason, Mr Eko?
We do it
because we believe we are meant to.
lsn't that the reason
you pushed it, John?
l was never meant to do anything.
Every single second
of my pathetic little life
is as useless as that button.
You think it's important?
You think it's necessary?
lt's nothing. lt's nothing.
lt's meaningless.
And who are you
to tell me that it's not?
That's flight 81 5 leaving from gate 23.
- Thank you.
- 840 starting to board at gate 16.
- What are you doing here?
- l had to see you.
- Look, your father said...
- l know.
He doesn't want me talking to you,
and l know you probably think l'm crazy,
but l have a message for you
and l promised to deliver it.
A message?
- He says you were a good priest.
- Who says that?
Yemi.
Speaking about my brother is not a joke,
so you should be very careful
what you say next.
l saw him when l was between places.
He said that you would come and see me.
He said even though you were pretending,
you're a good man.
Who put you up to this?
Did your father tell you to do this?
He will see you soon.
He said that even though you don't have
faith in yourself, he has faith in you.
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you want?
- Why are you doing this to me?
- ls everything... all right?
He has faith in you.
One day you'll believe me.
Oceanic Airlines flight 8 1 5
is now boarding for Los Angeles.
This cross was worn by my brother Yemi.
Yemi was a great man,
a priest, a man of God,
and because l betrayed him,
he was shot and died.
He was placed on a plane
which took off from an airstrip
in Nigeria,
half a world from here.
Then the plane that l was on
crashed on this island.
And somehow, here,
l found my brother again.
l found him in the same plane
that took off from Nigeria,
in the same plane
that lies above us now
that has concealed this place.
And l took this cross from around
Yemi's neck and put it back on mine.
Just as it was on the day
l first took another man's life.
So let me ask you,
how can you say this is meaningless?
l believe the work being done in the
hatch is more important than anything.
lf you will not continue
to push the button, John,...
l will.
Can...
Can l talk to her?
Sure.
Hey.
lt's Hurley.
Hugo.
l'm sorry l forgot the blankets.
Libby?
- Michael.
He's OK. He made it, Libby.
lt's OK. lt's all right.