- They don't understand, Sergeant.
- They understand. Listen up.
I'll fire on three. One, two...
You.
- You in charge?
- No, I am not.
Who is?
There is no commanding officer here.
He left two hours ago for Hillah.
Your English is good, Abdul.
But you're lying.
And that ain't so good.
Delta 17,
this is Charlie 46...
That's him, Sergeant.
Let's go, hombre.
Son, we don't wanna be here
any more than you do,
but your pal Saddam
had to go marching into Kuwait.
Here we all are.
Buccelli here says you speak English.
You ever do any translating?
Formally, no.
Hell.
Fact that you know
what "formally" means... We're good.
Apache helicopter went down
in this sector two days ago.
Our sources tell us
the pilot was captured.
It's very important
that we get this pilot back.
He was taken to the Republican
Guard intelligence commander,
a man named Tariq.
- Do you know him?
- Yes. He was our commanding officer.
Do you know where he is?
When the bombing started,
he fled to Hillah.
Hillah, huh?
Yes, that is right.
Welcome to Hillah.
Where's Jack?
Why?
There. See?
Go back. I'll deal with this.
What?
Go back, Ana Lucia.
And don't tell anyone what you saw.
What are you doing here, Danielle?
Looking for you.
Where are we going?
You said you were looking for me.
What was your plan?
To hide in the woods,
hoping I would pass you by?
I was going to wait until dark,
and then find you at your tent.
Why?
- We need to keep moving.
- Tell me where we are moving to.
Trust me.
The last time we met, you warned us the
Others were coming, which they weren't.
In fact, it was a diversion
to kidnap Claire's baby.
So pardon me for not trusting you.
This place I am taking you to,
there is something that will help you,
something important.
As for trust,
take this.
If I'm lying, it's yours to use.
How much further?
Not far.
Ask him where he took the pilot.
He says he does not know.
We know for a fact he interrogated
the pilot day before yesterday.
Hell, probably in this room.
Tell him,
we get our man back safe and sound,
he goes free.
What's he saying?
He says he does not know.
I was born,
but I wasn't born yesterday, son.
You don't help me out here,
someone else will take over,
and that someone,
he won't play nice at all.
I am sorry. He does not know.
OK. You had your chance.
Guards.
Lock him back up.
This is unbelievable.
Hey. Hey, you hear that thing?
You hear that frog? Frog?
You wanna help me find it?
What? We ain't friends anymore?
- What you got there, Rerun?
- Nothing.
Yeah, well, you got a spot of nothing
on your chin there.
Dharma Initiative Ranch Dressing?
You're supposed to refrigerate that
after you open it.
Actually, on the back it says
it'll keep at room temperature
for up to seven years.
Well, well.
Looky who's got a secret stash.
Please, dude. You can't tell.
What? That you stole food
from the group?
Now, why would I wanna do that?
Come on, man. Please.
Son of a bitch.
- Dude, it's just a tree frog.
- Have you seen it?
Yeah.
Tell you what,
you help me find that thing,
you can keep right on Ranch dipping.
We got a deal?
How much further?
- Danielle?
- We're here.
And where exactly is "here"?
What is that for, Danielle?
Help me!
Hey! Over here!
Wait.
- Help!
- Sayid, listen to me.
Hey! Hey!
Over here!
Please! Help me!
- Help me!
- Don't believe a word he says.
- Hey!
- He's one of them.
I have no idea what she's talking about.
She's crazy.
- How long has he been up there?
- Since last night.
Please just cut me down.
My name is Henry Gale.
I'm from Minnesota.
- Please.
- He's lying.
- I'm going to cut him down.
- Don't.
- Thank you.
- You're making a serious mistake.
It's OK. It's OK.
You're all right. You're all right.
Hold on.
Take it easy.
- No.
- Wait.
Danielle, don't.
You could have killed him.
If I wanted to kill him,
I would have killed him.
- You shot this man with no provocation.
- He is one of them.
Tie him up.
You should take him to your doctor.
He's no good to you dead.
And then what?
You'll talk to him, Sayid.
As I recall, that is what you do.
But know this: He will lie.
For a long time, he will lie.
I wanna talk to you
about your buddy, Tariq.
Ah, look, I get it.
You're a man who values loyalty.
Even doing a little translating for us,
you feel like
you're doing the wrong thing.
I get that, and I respect it.
This is what Tariq was doing
before he took over command
of your intelligence unit.
He was the head of a chemical warfare
battalion in the north.
Personally supervised
the use of sarin gas on this village.
You recognize it, don't you?
You had relatives in that village
didn't you, Sayid?
So, you know what sarin gas does.
No discrimination.
The entire marketplace.
Innocent women, children.
Enough.
Please.
Loyalty is a virtue.
But unquestioning loyalty...
I don't think that's you.
Why should I believe you?
How do you think we knew
you had relatives in that village?
We liberated your personnel file
and Tariq's.
All we want is our pilot back,
so we can send him home to his family.
Tariq will never talk to you.
That's why you're gonna
have to make him talk to you.
John. John, wake up.
- What?
- Come out here.
Minnesota, huh?
That's the question, isn't it?
Wh... Where am I?
- Who are you?
- Henry. Henry Gale.
Ah, my back.
We're going to take it out,
but first I want you to relax.
How did you get to this island?
Four months ago.
We crashed, my wife and I.
Crashed in what?
A balloon.
We were trying to cross the Pacific.
Your wife, where is she?
She died. She got...
She got sick, three weeks ago.
We were staying in a cave off the beach.
My shoulder.
At least untie my arms.
What the hell's going on here?
Rousseau trapped him in the jungle.
- She believes he's an Other.
- Another what?
- You shot him with an arrow?
- Do I have a bow?
Hey, hey. You with me?
- You were gonna let him bleed to death?
- I was trying to get honest answers.
And his wound
is far from life-threatening.
We should let Jack treat him first.
Then we'll get our answers.
Jack. Do not untie him.
This is how people get killed
in scary movies.
If this were a scary movie, I'd be
with a hot chick, not you, Barbar.
- It's Babar.
- Why don't you shut up, Hammo?
Or your Ranch disorder's gonna be the
new lead item on the coconut internet.
Fine. Go ahead.
Tell everyone the fat guy's
been hiding Ranch dressing.
The fat guy likes to eat.
Yeah, I'm fat.
Fat, fat, fat, fat, fat.
You think I don't know that?
At least people like me.
Well, find the damn frog by yourself.
Hurley, wait. Wait. Hey, Hurley.
Look, man, I'm sorry. All right?
But this frog is killing me.
You gotta help me out.
Please.
- So, what do you think?
- What do you think, John?
I think he's pretty convincing.
Yes, he is.
The real problem is there's no way
we can be sure he's telling the truth.
That is not necessarily true.
Does Jack have the combination
to the armory?
For now he does.
How long would it take
for you to change it?
If you're angry,
looking for someone to punish...
Why would I need to punish anyone?
I want to find out who he is.
I want the truth.
We both know that Jack will have issues
with what must be done to get it.
So, how long, John,
to change the combination?
Couple of minutes, tops.
Then I suggest you get started.
- Did he say anything while...
- No, he didn't.
He was in shock.
We can't just leave him laying here,
Jack.
People will see him.
It'll create a panic.
- Where do you think we should put him?
- I say we put him in the armory.
It's secure.
Better to err on the side of safety,
Jack, at least until we can be sure.
OK.
For now.
We can pull that cot in here.
He shouldn't be on his back.
Good idea.
Sayid.
Hey. What the hell are you doing? Sayid.
- What needs to be done.
- Hey!
The pilot was executed two days ago.
He is buried in a field
four kilometers from here.
I can take you there.
Damn it. Sayid, open the door.
- Sayid, answer me.
- Jack.
Why isn't this combination working,
John?
Did you change it?
Yeah.
Why would you do that?
- You're raising an army.
- What?
Why you didn't ask me is your business.
But there's only one reason to raise an
army, and that's because we're at war.
And like it or not, whatever Sayid
has to do behind that door,
that's a part of it, too.
What if he's telling the truth, John?
What if he's not?
Get up.
What's happening?
Here. Let me help you.
You said you've been here
for four months.
What?
You said you came to this island
four months ago, yes?
Where am I?
Please. Answer my question.
Yeah, yes. We landed four months ago.
Maybe more. Who are you?
You were in a cave for all that time?
Off the beach.
- On the north shore of the island.
- How far from where you were captured?
- I don't know.
- How many days walk?
- Two. Two days.
- Why did you stay on the beach so long?
Why wouldn't we?
We wanted to be there for flyovers.
We had an emergency beacon,
a transmitter.
- What kind of transmitter?
- An ADF beacon.
We wanted to make sure we'd be spotted.
Look, whatever you think I am, I'm not.
Please, please, just tell me your name.
Your wife. What is her maiden name?
- Murphy.
- Where did you meet her?
- University of Minnesota.
- How did she die?
She got sick.
She got sick?
It started as a fever.
After two days, she was delirious.
Then she died.
I don't know why
you're asking these questions.
you're treating me this way,
why I have to explain to you who I am
when you don't tell me who you are.
I was 23 years old when the Americans
came to my country.
I was a good man. I was a soldier.
And when they left,
I was something different.
For the next six years
I did things I wish I could erase
from my memory,
things which I never thought myself
to be capable of.
But I did come to learn this.
There is a part of me
which was always capable.
You want to know who I am.
My name is Sayid Jarrah,
and I am a torturer.
Where is it?
There it is.
Gotcha.
Dude, nice catch.
Well, I'll be damned.
All that noise from this tiny critter.
Kind of reminds me of a turtle
I once had. His name was Stewart.
He ran off when I was ten.
Well, that's what Mom said.
I kind of think she threw him out.
Wow, you're a happy little fellow,
ain't you?
I have an idea.
Why don't I take him far from here?
Two beaches away.
Maybe he'll find a Mrs. Tree Frog.
That way he won't keep you up anymore
and everyone's happy.
Yeah, that's one idea.
Here's another.
Dude.
I hear with a little Ranch
they taste just like chicken.
Give you a hand?
- Jack, I know this isn't...
- Shut up.
Where are the pliers?
Tell me about this balloon.
- What?
- This balloon that brought you here.
- Tell me about it.
- What do you wanna know?
Everything.
She's 140 feet high, 60 feet wide.
And when she's up in the air,
550,000 cubic feet of helium
and 100,000 of hot air keep her up.
And if you could look down on her,
you'd see
a big yellow smiley face on top.
Why would you travel in that way?
Because I was rich.
Because it was my dream.
And Jennifer thought it would be neat.
You were rich.
I guess I'm thinking of things
in the past tense now.
How's that for optimism?
What did you do to become so rich?
- I sold my company.
- What kind of company?
- Mining.
- What did you mine?
We mined nonmetallic minerals.
I know. Everyone wanted to talk to me
at cocktail parties.
Give me your hands.
- Where is she buried?
- What?
Listen to me.
You said you buried your wife.
Tell me where.
- What are you...
- Where?
In the jungle.
By the balloon. In the jungle.
How deep?
How deep did you dig the grave?
- I don't...
- How many shovelfuls of earth?
Did you use your hands?
How long did it take you?
- I don't remember.
- You would remember.
You would remember how deep.
You would remember every shovelful,
every moment.
You would remember what it felt like
to place her body inside.
You would remember
if you buried the woman you loved.
You would remember if it were true.
Did you lose someone?
Did you lose someone here on the island?
Did you lose someone, too?
What happened to her?
It was an accident. It was an accident.
The woman responsible
thought she was someone else,
someone coming to hurt her,
someone like you.
Just, just... This is all a mistake.
Slow down here, OK?
- Hurting me isn't gonna bring her back.
- You know what I lost.
- Tell me the truth.
- No, stop.
- Tell me who you are.
- No, no, no. Help. Stop.
Tell me the truth.
- Tell me who you are.
- Stop, please.
- Sayid.
- I've told you everything.
- Jack.
- Tell me what I already know.
- Open it.
- Open it now, John.
- This has to happen.
You open that damn door,
you understand me? You open it now.
- No.
- Now.
- You're lying!
- What do you want me to say?
Whatever you want me to do, I'll do it.
Just, please...
I want you to tell me the truth.
Open the door.
- Let go of me, Jack.
- Or what? Wanna push the button?
Open the door.
It's under a minute now, John.
You better think fast.
- You wouldn't.
- What? I wouldn't what?
If we don't...
You would risk everyone's lives?
You talked me into pushing that button
once, John, but it's yours now.
You're the one who won't risk it. You.
I don't think anything's gonna happen
when we get to zero.
- Jack.
- You wanna see?
Let's just see what's gonna happen.
Who are you?
Who are you?!
OK, OK, OK. Right 15, left...
You think I'm stupid? You open it.
Hey, hey.
He's lying.
I'll tell you whatever you want.
He's lying! He's lying!
That's enough!
What the hell was that?
- He is one of them.
- Yeah? Did he tell you that?
- No.
- Then how do you know?
Because I know. He is one of them.
I think that's what Rousseau thought
about you once, Sayid.
She strapped you down, she shocked you,
all because she thought
you were one of them.
He is.
- What?
- He is one of them.
To Rousseau, we're all Others.
I guess it's all relative, huh?
You got a wife? Kids?
Come on down. Hurry up.
Get out. Get out. Stop there.
Get over here. Keep your eyes peeled.
I'll take him.
It's over. We're pulling out,
not going to Baghdad.
Your man Saddam gets to stay in power,
which means you, in all likelihood,
will remain in his employ.
I guess you're lucky
you have a new skill set you can use.
What you made me do, no human being
should ever have to do to another.
I will never do that again.
Yeah.
Good luck to you, Sayid.
Bus fare back to Ramadi.
Let's move out.
There is a man down in the hatch.
A stranger captured by Rousseau.
I beat him.
I beat him badly.
Why are you telling me this, Sayid?
Jack asked me how I knew,
knew for sure that this man was lying,
how I knew for sure that he was
one of them, one of the Others.
I know because I feel no guilt
for what I did to him.
But there is no way I can ever
explain that to Jack, or even Locke,
because both of them have forgotten.
Forgotten? What?
That you were strung up by your neck
and left for dead.
That Claire was kept for days during
which God knows what happened to her.
That these people, these Others,
are merciless
and can take any one of us
whenever they choose.
So, tell me, Charlie,
have you forgotten?