Oh!
How do you feel?
Oh...
I feel free.
They found something. Come on!
Hurry, guys.
Risotto. Nice.
No.
Where did this come from?
Locke said doors trapped him
in the hatch.
Maybe it was because of this,
so no one would see who dropped it.
Any of you guys see a plane last night?
Yeah, I saw it, Tattoo.
I just decided not to tell.
- Give that back.
- I saw it first.
- You saw me take those.
- No.
- Gimme my stuff!
- Hold on, take it easy!
You're like locusts.
How about a little order?
Shouldn't we
let someone trustworthy do this?
Like you, babynapper?
No. Like Hurley. Why not Hurley? He's
done it before, he could do it again.
No! No way!
- Not me! No! Not again! No.
- OK, hey, hey, guys, guys.
How about no one's in charge, OK?
I'm sure everyone can manage
to just take what they need.
Great plan, Moonbeam. After that,
we can sing Kumbaya and do trust falls.
- ... put them in there.
- ... pull this over here.
...savages about it.
We can do it any way you want.
Bacon?
Hey, get your hands off those cookies.
Out of my way.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Uh-oh.
Hey.
What you doing?
Nothing.
Who were you looking for up there?
No one.
When you ran off, it sort of seemed
like you were looking for someone.
- I tried to find you...
- I kinda...
don't wanna talk about it.
Sure. OK.
Pretty weird, huh?
You said the island
won't let you lose weight,
you destroy your stash, then bang...
More food falls from the sky.
How about that?
I'm proud of you.
- Proud of me for what?
- Not freaking out.
How's the diet coming, Hugo?
It's OK.
I had a salad and some chicken breast
for lunch.
That's great. It gets easier. I promise.
So,
I heard you had a visit with your mom.
How did that go?
- It was good.
- You're not still mad at her, then?
Nah.
I know she put me in here for a reason.
What reason was that?
The accident.
- You wanna talk about that today?
- Do we have to?
Hugo, you've been in here
almost two months now.
Don't you think it's time
to start getting our hands dirty? Hm?
OK, why don't we talk about the little
homework assignment that I gave you?
I was never really good at homework.
Remember what
you were supposed to do?
Just make a list of things
that you like about yourself?
- Nobody else did it.
- Nobody else? Meaning?
Well, Dave didn't do it.
He said it was a stupid idea.
Well, you know, I'm not Dave's doctor,
but we have talked about
how he can be a very negative influence.
Dave's the most normal person
in this place, man.
But he doesn't want you to change,
does he?
Come on, give me the ball.
Give me the ball! I can play defense.
Dude! Dude, I'm open! Dude! Dude!
It's called "dribbling," not "drooling!"
"Dribbling!"
Well, shoot it, then! Shoot it! What?
High percentage shot.
Excellent choice.
- Shoot!
- Want in the game?
Go for it.
Something tells me no one'll care.
What's the matter with you?
Nothing.
Dude! Dude, give up the rock!
Fantastic. Give it to the guy
who's not even in the game!
Hey, it's Taco Night, dude.
Let's blow this pop stand.
- What?
- Brooks said you're, like, negative.
Well, duh! So, what, you don't
wanna hang out with me any more?
- No, I don't know, it's...
- That quack getting inside your head?
Do not let him. You got much more
important things to think about.
- Like what?
- Like, hard or soft shell, baby?
Chicken or shrimp?
Sour cream or hot sauce?
- Yeah, I guess I could eat.
- Yeah, I thought so.
Noche de Tacos, amigo.
Good. Now, can you do the other one?
- Is it broken?
- Without an X-ray,
you'll have to do with my best guess.
Sorry.
- How you holding up?
- Depends on Jack's best guess.
There's a small fracture,
probably hairline.
This will reduce the swelling
until I get a splint.
- How long until I can walk on it?
- Keep off it a couple of weeks.
- There's a wheelchair back at camp...
- No. I don't need a wheelchair.
We took a pair of crutches from the
fuselage when we moved down the beach.
OK.
I'll be back in a while.
He could've escaped.
- Sorry?
- Henry.
During the lockdown. I was hurt.
He could have escaped...
But he came back to help me.
Why would he do that?
He didn't come back to help you, John.
He came back because he thought
his story was gonna check out.
He was dead already.
Four months ago,
I was part of the search party.
Henry Gale was hanging
out of the basket, neck broken.
So he was already dead?
Yes.
And then you buried him
and left the grave marker?
Yes.
You really should have checked
his wallet before you did that.
I assume Henry Gale did not have any
paper on which to compose his thoughts,
so he had to improvise.
There wasn't much space for that.
" Jennifer... "
"Well, you were right. Crossing the
Pacific isn't easy. I owe you a beer. "
"I'm hiking to one of the beaches
to start a signal fire,
but if you're reading this,
I guess I didn't make it. "
"I'm sorry. I love you, Jenny.
Always have, always will. "
"Yours, Henry. "
So tell me...
how did Henry Gale write a note
to his wife with a broken neck?
It wasn't me. I didn't kill him.
You don't understand...
How did you know his wife's name?
Did you interrogate him?
- Please... just listen... I'm just a...
- How many of you are there?
If I tell you about them,
you have no idea what he'll do.
He?
You mean their leader.
The guy with the beard.
- Him? He's no one. Nothing!
- Where are your people?
- I can't...
- How many of you are there?
- You don't understand!
- Understand this!
Hey.
You have three seconds to answer my
question. How many of you are there?
- One.
- He'll kill me!
I'll kill you.
- Two.
- Sayid!
You can't do this!
I am not a bad person!
Three.
What the hell's wrong with you?
- What's going on? I heard a shot!
- What happened?
- He's a liar.
- It's fine. Just get him out of here.
Jack!
Jack?
- Jack!
- I've got it covered, John.
- Thank you.
- Shut up.
Hey.
I noticed you were building something.
I thought maybe you could use this,
for whatever it is.
That's very thoughtful of you, Charlie.
Why don't you help me?
What are you making?
Hold that end.
Is it a Starbucks?
Help me carry one of those logs, please.
Are you gonna tell me?
Not right now.
You're not here!
Hey!
Wait!
Wait! Dave!
You OK, Hurley?
Did either of you see
a guy run through here?
In a bathrobe?
With a coconut?
No. I saw a polar bear
on rollerblades with a mango.
I did not see anything either.
Yeah, me neither.
- 4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42...
- Aw, dude.
Pretty sneaky, Leonard.
Using those magic numbers of yours
as a psych-out, aren't you, man?
Oh, yeah, that's right. You just
play dumb. I'm onto your juju, man.
- They're just numbers, dude.
- What the hell is that?
It's my mid-afternoon snack.
Dude, that's celery.
Celery is not a snack.
Leonard's got graham crackers.
You should snag one. He won't notice.
What's he gonna do? Call you a "23"?
- 4, 8, 15, 16...
- 4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42. Hike!
Hey, Hugo. Here's your meds.
Thank you, Nurse Lazenby.
Dude, you wanna get outta here with me?
- Don't take the horse tranquilizer.
- What do you mean, "get outta here?"
I mean, escape, man. Me and you. ASAP.
They're getting to you, dude.
We gotta split.
- Dr. Brooks says...
- Dr. Brooks does not care about you.
He's the one prescribing that crap.
What the hell is it anyway?
- Clonazepam.
- Hugo.
- Something wrong with your meds, there?
- No.
Me and Dave were just, you know...
talking about stuff.
Right. Well, sorry to interrupt.
Hello there, Dave.
Hello there, Dr. Brooks.
- And how are you today?
- Never been saner.
I'm taking pictures for the bulletin
board. I've got everyone except you two.
- Would you guys mind?
- OK.
OK. Why don't you
get a little closer together?
Are you gonna make us
look at the ducky, too?
Say cheese!
- Cheese!
- Queso!
Great. OK, you...
you need a little water with that?
Nope. I'm good.
OK. Well, fine. See you later, guys.
Thanks for the photo op.
8, 15, 16, 23, 42...
- Dude...
- Dude.
The revolution has begun, man.
Lay low. When the time is right, we fly.
You gotta twist it.
To get the frosting.
Pulling it'll only break your cookie.
Well, that's what I get for not going
to the expert in the first place.
What can I do you for, Deep Dish?
I was kind of looking for something.
Forget it. I'm done trading.
I got enough food now
to open a chain of mini-marts.
Hey, you think Sayid needs a job?
Well, actually, I was sort of
hoping you'd do me a favor.
Remember when I helped you out
with that tree frog...
which you killed?
Yeah, I remember.
Well, I sorta... need some medicine.
What do you need?
- It's called Clonazepam.
- Clonaze-what?
What the hell's that?
It's so you can calm down
or for when you're seeing things...
that aren't supposed to be there.
What stuff are you seeing?
I don't know, maybe, like,
a bald guy in a bathrobe.
You mean like that guy there?
Gotcha.
- Think you're funny?
- What are you doing?
- Who do you think you are?
- Get off!
- Let go of me!
- Lambchop!
Pork Pie! Babar! Jabba! Stay-Puft!
- Kong! Deep Dish!
- Let go of me! Get him off me!
Get off me! You out of your mind?
What the hell's the matter with you?
Get off me!
- You're crazy!
- I'm not crazy.
I'm not crazy.
So he just attacked you, huh?
Try to contain yourself, Freckles.
What? I'm worried.
- You look like you got your ass kicked.
- Don't you got an adventure to get to?
I think Timmy fell down a well
over that way.
- Why would Hurley of all people...
- I got no idea! I didn't do nothing.
- He just Hulked out on me.
- For no reason at all?
OK.
You walk off
and have yourself a nice long giggle.
But steer clear. The man is crazy.
Hurley?
Hey.
- You OK? What happened with Sawyer?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- So, you beat him up?
- Guess you know what happened, then.
- I'm on your side. Whatever you...
- Look, I don't wanna talk, OK?
- What?
- That's a lot of peanut butter.
I'll need a lot of protein
where I'm going.
- Where are you going?
- Back to the caves.
No one lives there,
so I won't bother anybody.
I'm gonna live alone
and be one of those guys.
You know, the crazy guys, with a big
beard, no clothes, who's naked
- and throws doody at people.
- Hurley, you don't have to do this.
Just leave me alone.
You can't help me. No one can.
You're not here.
You were in the hospital.
- You can't be here.
- Sorry, dude. I am here.
I like that I have a good relationship
with my mom.
I like making my Grandpa Tito laugh.
I like chicken.
No, that last one wasn't about you,
Hugo.
I like that I like chicken?
So tell me,
how did it feel writing that?
Was that difficult?
Kinda.
I think I messed up some spelling.
You didn't say anything
about the way you look.
Are you comfortable
with your appearance?
Well, it's not like...
I mean, I can't really
do anything about it, right?
If I...
If I... wasn't so fat...
they never would have died.
There were 23 people on that deck.
It was built to hold eight.
And it would have collapsed
whether you went out there or not.
Yeah, but I did walk out there.
And it did collapse.
- And I killed them.
- It was an accident.
It was my fault.
Look, after those people died, you were
in a practically catatonic state.
You stopped talking, you stopped
going out, you stopped sleeping.
But you never stopped eating,
because that's how you punish yourself.
Dave's right about you.
You're nothing but a quack.
- Dave doesn't want you to lose weight.
- You know, Dave cares about me.
He's my friend.
I'm gonna show you something,
and it may upset you.
This is the photo
that I took for the bulletin board.
Dave isn't your friend, Hugo...
because Dave doesn't exist.
Psst! Hey! Wake up, dude.
Finally. You could sleep
through a damn NASCAR race, man.
But, you're not... You're...
You're a hallucination.
- Ow!
- Was that a hallucination?
Maybe I just imagined you slapped me.
- Ow! Damn it!
- We can do this all night.
Dr. Brooks showed me
a picture from the rec room,
and my arm was around nothingness.
Uh... Kinko's? Photoshop?
Think they really
blew up the Death Star?
- No.
- Then stop talking crazy, man.
Come on, we're on a clock here.
Hey, you in or you out, dude?
OK, come on, come on.
Yo, check it out,
Marcus didn't finish his lasagna.
That is a waste, man. One for the road?
Wait for it. Wait.
Tippytoes, big guy. V?monos!
OK, man, you got the keys, hombre.
You took 'em off Brooks' desk earlier.
Come on, man, open it, open it.
Oh-oh-oh!
Can you taste that?
That is freedom, baby.
Know what tastes
even better than freedom?
Cheeseburgers.
Come on, man! Chili fries on me.
I don't think I can do this.
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry? What, are you kidding me?
You're not real.
You're trying to get me to run away
and get cheeseburgers because...
I want cheeseburgers.
- Did you take those pills, man?
- No, man, I'm just not coming.
- Look, you don't want me to change.
- You don't need to change, man.
- You are fine. You are great.
- No, I'm not.
You just want me to stay fat.
You don't want me to get better.
You wouldn't care
if I ate myself to death.
Do not do this, man.
If you don't come with me right now,
you will never get outta here.
Bye, Dave.
You wouldn't happen to have my slipper,
would you?
Thank you.
Oh, man! You got peanut butter on it.
OK, look, I know you're freaking out
right now, and I'm sorry, but...
it's gonna get a little worse
before it gets better.
- Worse?
- Yeah. Kinda.
You ready, dude?
You remember that night
you closed that window on me?
Remember what you did
after that night?
Yeah.
- I realized you were imaginary.
- Mm-hm.
And... that was a breakthrough.
And a little while later,
Brooks let me out,
and I went home to live with my mom,
and I got my job at Mr. Cluck's back,
- and I got better.
- OK. Good. Great. Yeah.
Except, see, here's the thing. Uh...
None of that ever happened.
- What?
- You're still at Santa Rosa, man.
You never left the hospital.
- That's not possible.
- It's hard, I know.
But, I mean, all this?
You? Me? This island?
That peanut butter?
None of it's real, man.
None of it's happening.
It's all in your head, my friend.
The second you closed that window,
your brain popped a gasket.
You went back into your coma thing,
and that's where you are
right this very second.
In your own private Idaho
inside Santa Rosa.
No.
I had...
My mom...
My friend Johnny...
- I won the lottery.
- Whoa! Wow!
Awesome, dude.
What numbers did you play?
Leonard's numbers, right?
From the hospital? What a coincidence.
You seen them around anywhere else?
- The hatch.
- Bingo! The hatch.
With the button that you gotta push
every 108 minutes or the world ends.
Oh, oh, oh,
and what's the code for the button?
Oh, yeah. The numbers.
But I got better.
- I changed.
- Changed? Are you kidding?
You've been on a deserted island
for over two months
and you haven't dropped ten pounds.
How is that even possible, man?
I just destroyed my stash.
And I've been exercising.
- Libby says it won't...
- Right, Libby.
The mega-cute blonde chick
who magically appeared
from the other side of the island.
Oh, yeah, and who just happens
to have the hots for you?
Come on, man. Let's take a walk.
- So this is all in my brain?
- Every rock. Every tree.
Every tree frog. Even me. The real me,
the one they told you was imaginary?
He went out that window, man.
Right now, he's probably bouncing
from hot chick to hot chick.
Unlike me, who's really you,
who's got more important things to do.
- So I'm making you up?
- Well, sorta.
I'm part of your subconscious, man.
All the people on this island are.
What part of me are you?
I'm the part of you
that wants to wake up, man.
Follow me.
This is it, dude.
- It?
- The big finale.
The answer to all your problems.
A way for you to wake up,
snap out of it.
I don't wanna kill myself.
Who said anything
about killing yourself, man?
This is gonna bring you back to life.
The only way for you to bust out
is to tell your mind
that you don't believe any of this.
So...
if I...
All this will be gone?
I'll just wake up?
That's right.
And when you do wake up, come find me.
I'm sure I miss you.
See you in another life, Hurley.
Dave!
Jack not back yet?
Nope. He's telling everyone at the beach
that we've got one of 'em.
Something tells me people have
a lot of questions about our houseguest.
I want to talk to him.
I don't think that's on today's program.
Well, all due respect, Ana Lucia,
but I don't care what you think.
Five minutes.
I earned five minutes with him.
What's your name?
Your real name.
Why don't you
just keep calling me Henry?
I've gotten used to it.
Did you get caught on purpose?
You and your people have been here
for God knows how long,
- and you got caught in a net...
- God doesn't know.
Excuse me?
God doesn't know
how long we've been here, John.
He can't see this island any better
than the rest of the world can.
May I ask you a question?
What possible reason could I have
for putting myself through all this?
Maybe your people
were looking for this place.
This place?
This place is a joke, John.
What are you talking about?
I crawled through your vents
and I stood at your computer
as the alarm beeped.
And you know what happened?
The timer went all the way down to zero.
And then some funny red pictures
flipped up in its place.
They looked like hieroglyphics,
but I'm no expert.
Then things got real interesting.
There was a loud... clunking
and a hum like a... magnet,
a big magnet.
It was really very frightening.
And do you know what happened next?
Nothing happened, John.
Nothing happened at all.
Your timer just flipped back to 108.
I never entered the numbers.
I never pressed the button.
You're lying.
No, I'm done lying.
Dave!
Who's Dave?
- What are you doing here?
How did you know where I was?
- Jin saw you while he was fishing.
- Ha! Jin doesn't speak English.
Sun was with him. She translated.
Hurley, what is going on?
No! You're just the part of me
that's scared.
You don't want me to wake up.
Well, guess what? I'm not scared.
OK, Hurley,
you're having some sort of panic attack.
I get that.
- But this isn't like you.
- Like me? You don't know me.
I was starting to.
Yeah, well, did you know I'm so fat
that I killed two people?
And that I have an imaginary friend?
Hurley, please.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
No, I'm not!
Because this isn't happening.
None of it. I'm just imagining it.
This isn't real life.
Why would you say that?
Because in real life...
no girl like you would ever like me.
You remember when I said
I knew you from somewhere?
Well, maybe it's 'cause I made you up.
What was the man's name
who broke his leg?
The day of the crash.
On the other side of the island,
Eko brought a man
with a broken leg to me for help.
What was his name?
I don't know.
You don't know. You know why?
Because it happened to me.
His name was Donald, and I buried him.
I buried a lot of people, Hurley.
So don't tell me that
that wasn't real.
And don't tell me you made me up.
It's insulting.
When you saw me on the beach
this morning, was I holding a slipper?
No, not that I can remember, no.
Hurley...
look at me.
I am real.
You're real.
The way I feel about you, that's real.
And that was real.
Maybe you should do it one more time.
Just to be sure.
Ready to go back?
Do you really think I can,
you know, change?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Why don't you
get a little closer together?
- Say cheese!
- Cheese!
Great.
You need some water to go with that?
- Nope, I'm good.
- OK. Well, fine.
See you later, guys.
Thanks for the photo op.
Here's your pill, Libby.