Previously on Lost...
I met my real father.
Great news, right?
He pretended to love me just
long enough to steal my kidney.
I followed you last night.
Is it your father's house?
But you have to promise me that you're
not gonna go to that place anymore.
All right.
You think you're the first
person that ever got conned?
You needed a father figure,
and I needed a kidney.
- Hey, Helen--
- You're gonna have to choose.
Him or me.
My name is Henry Gale.
I'm from Minnesota.
You draw up a map to your balloon,
we go out there, we find it.
And if I mess up,
they'll crucify me.
Do you or do you not
know where it is?
I went back there
to bury my wife.
- It's to his balloon.
- This is at least a day's walk.
Then we should get going.
This is where he
said it would be.
We need to be sure.
If I was one of them, these people that
you seem to think are your enemies,
there'd be no balloon,
so I'd draw a map to
a real secluded place.
And when your friends got there, a bunch
of my people would be waiting for 'em.
I guess it's a good thing
I'm not one of them, huh?
So, what did I do
to deserve this?
What?
Can't a fella take his girl out
for a picnic lunch just 'cause?
- "Fella"?
- That's right. Fella.
So, where you taking me?
I'm not tellin',
so just quit askin'.
Can I be of any help?
You just read your obituaries
and drink your coffee, and
I'll take care of
the everything.
Don't knock the obits.
It's the nicest part of the paper.
No one ever says anything mean
about people once they're dead.
Mm. Now here I am, thinking the funnies
are the nicest part of the paper.
John?
John, what's your
father's name?
Why?
Is it Anthony? Anthony Cooper.
Yes, that's right.
He's dead.
Draw it again.
The map to your balloon.
I was joking.
I was making a joke.
There's nothing out
there besides my balloon.
I was just frustrated.
It was a stupid thing to say.
I'm sorry.
It's too late, anyway.
She's already long gone, Jack.
So, what's done is done.
That's right.
Put him back in the armory.
Why do you let him
talk to you like that?
- Hey, wait. I--
- Shut up.
John?
I'm sorry.
John!
Maybe he's wrong.
We should search the
other side of the cliff.
We've been searching for three hours.
This balloon does not exist.
Charlie!
Then why'd he draw the map?
You told him you would protect him
whether we found this balloon or not.
You've given him two more days to stall,
to figure out how to escape.
We're done.
Charlie!
Over here!This way!
Sayid!
He said he buried her, right?
His wife?
Why isn't it raining here?
Hurley. You seen Ana Lucia?
She took off into the jungle with
Charlie and Sayid yesterday.
Yesterday.
They say anything about
where they were going?
Well, that would, like, assume that
anyone actually tells me anything.
Maybe, if I were in the loop,
I could be more helpful.
There is no loop, Hurley.
Excuse me, Jack,
he's been really hot and fussy.
- Do you mind having a look?
- Yeah, sure. Sure.
Loop, dude. Loop.
So, the fever's
completely gone?
Completely.
You're not just
saying that, right?
- You seem a bit distracted.
- No, I'm fine.
- And so's Aaron.
- Thanks.
Doctor still in?
I was grabbing for
mussels in the tide pool,
and pissed off a sea urchin.
Well, it doesn't look infected.
- A little neosporin wouldn't hurt.
- Yeah, right. Neosporin.
I think the current
rate of exchange is
ten loads of
laundry for a tube.
Right.
What was that?
J ohn?
What's the matter?
You sure you want to do this?
We could just go on that picnic,
you know.
Hmm.
Soon, I promise.
Hey...
maybe he left you his kidney.
For we who are alive,
who are left,
will be caught up together with them in
the clouds to meet the Lord in the air,
and so we will live
with the Lord forever.
We commit the soul of
Anthony Cooper to you,
but we shall never
be separated.
And now, we are united with Christ
as we go towards him. Amen.
Do you wish to say
anything, John?
I forgive you.
John?
Hey, you out there?
What's that noise? John?
What's going on? Talk to me.
Will you be quiet?
Tell me what's happening.
What the hell is--
Will  you shut up?!
11... 10... 9... 8...
7...
6... 5...
Maybe you should get Jack.
3... 2...
- I said shut up!
- 1.
What happened?
I bet four papayas.
You can't bet. I just bet.
You can either call or raise,
or lay 'em down, mutton chops.
Don't look at me.
Lay 'em down, Hurley.
He's got you beat.
- Dude, I got a killer hand here.
- No, you don't.
- But you don't even know what I--
- You got a baby straight.
He's got the flush.
What about me? What do I got?
Hard to say, but you're just
playing for the fun of it.
Well, fun's not bad.
You should try it sometime.
Don't call him, Hurley.
Hey, Amarillo Slim,
think 'cause you watch poker on tv,
you can tussle with the big boys?
I gotta head back to the hatch.
Hatch ain't goin' nowhere, doc.
How 'bout you put your
mangoes where your mouth is?
Guess I could play
a hand or two.
Hey!
What's going on?
Are you still out there?
John. John?
I'm here.
What were those noises?
What's wrong? Did something--
Nothing is wrong.
So, what's the verdict,
Mr. Locke?
Uh, the seismic bolting
is all first rate.
There's no visible mold.
No dry rot.
It'll all be in my report,
but, uh,
I think you and your husband
got a pretty nice house here.
If I had a husband,
I'm sure he would be happy to hear that.
If you'll just sign
this invoice...
Hello, son.
What do you want?
Look, John,
I know what I did
to you was wrong.
You stole my kidney.
I was dying.
You could've asked me.
You could've just asked me.
What do you want from me?
I killed myself off because
there are two men out there
who were gonna beat me to it.
Oh. What did you do,
steal their livers?
No. I took them for $700,000.
Retirement con.
I put the money in
a safe deposit box,
but these two guys may be sitting on
the bank to see if I show my face,
which is why I need you to go
in there and get it for me.
You think I'm stupid?
I want you to take
200 grand of it.
It won't make up for
what I did to you,
but it's the best I can do.
I'll be at the
Flight Line motel--
it's out near the airport--
until tomorrow afternoon,
and then I'm gone,
money or no money.
And, John,
if I don't see you again...
I'll understand.
We're locked in.
What?
These glass doors came down.
The whole living area's sealed off.
I can't get out.
- Did you try to pry--
- Yeah, but I couldn't...
Maybe...
maybe if the two of us...
- You want me to help you?
- Yeah.
And if I do help you
get these doors up,
then you're just gonna lock
me back in here, aren't you?
That's right.
Then I'm gonna need
your word, John.
I'm gonna need your word
that you won't let your
people  do anything to me.
Well, if you're who you say you are,
then what are you worried about?
Things have happened to them,
things that I have
nothing to do with.
But they've got no one to blame,
except for me.
So I'm gonna need your word
that you'll protect me,
no matter what.
Who are you?
My name is Henry Gale.
I'm from Minnesota...
and I crashed on this
island just like you.
All right.
You have my word.
- Dude, you got me.
- I'm out.
Think  you're in my head, doc?
Still got three papayas.
Call or fold.
Well, you're in trouble now,
cool hand.
Pocket queens makes me a set.
Kings wired.
Whoa, dude.
But at least I'm
not in your head.
- Well, I guess that's it.
- What do you mean, it?
Sawyer, you're busted.
I got it all.
Wouldn't really be fair for you
to go out and pick more mangoes.
Oh, I got a hell of
a lot more mangoes.
You wanna play real stakes?
Name 'em.
- It's a pile of fruit, man.
- And I want it back.
Should I go and get a ruler?
Fun time's over, Mongo.
Why don't you hit the buffet?
- But I wanna--
- Come on, Hurley.
Let's go leave these
boys to their sandbox.
One more hand, doc.
What's it gonna take?
The medicine you stole from the armory.
All of it.
Okay.
Ready? One. Two. Three.
Let's go.
Harder.
I'm losing it.
The toolbox. Get the toolbox.
I'll hold it.
- You sure?
- Get it!
Come on! Come on! Put it under.
John, wait. Don't you think--
You have to stop the door.
Put something else
under the door.
Come on! Come on!
Stack them, stack them.
You have to stop the pressure.
Come on, come on, come on.
All right, all right.
Let's get you out.
Let's get you out. Come on.
No, no, no, stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
All right. We'll wait till
somebody comes. All right?
It's only a matter
of time. Yeah?
No, we don't have time.
Honey...
put on your sunday best.
I am taking you out to paint--
John, we have visitors.
Um, these men say they
knew your father.
Hi, John. I'm Jimmy Bane.
I'm sure Helen told you that
I didn't know him very well.
She told me--
But I'd like to ask you a couple
questions, if that's okay.
Sure, of course.
Have you seen your father since he died,
Mr. Locke?
How-- have I--
Well, we were thinking,
possibly, he's not dead, and
maybe you know that.
I mean, for his son,
you didn't look too
shook up at his funeral.
How dare you?
If you had any idea what
that man did to him,
what that son of a bitch--
Hey, Helen...
We were there to get past him,
to get on with our lives,
to let him go.
- Get out of here.
- Helen--
Okay. Okay.
Just one thing before we go.
What's in the bag, John?
Work papers and stuff.
I'm a home inspector.
Mind if we take a look?
Well... there you go.
Thanks for the coffee, miss.
Helen, I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Were you lying to
those men, John?
No, I was scared. I was...
I was scared.
So, where'd you learn
to play cards, doc?
Phuket.
What the hell were
you doin' in Thailand?
What, you don't think
I know where Phuket is?
Just 'cause I dropped out of ninth
grade don't make me an idiot.
Far East, huh?
Wouldn't have taken you
for a world traveler.
That where you got the
art on your shoulder?
How about you deal again?
What?
And this time,
from the top of the deck.
Well, I had to try.
- What does it do?
- We're not exactly sure.
-  And you push it...
- Every 108 minutes, yeah.
How soon does this
alarm go off?
Very. Which is why
I need you to go up through
the grate and into the vents.
Grate's bolted shut. I tried.
Yeah. There's another grate in the
pantry. You can get up through there.
Take the vent into the dome.
Maybe we should wait--
Oh, we can't wait.
It's gonna go off any minute.
I trusted you, Henry.
Now you've got to trust me.
That button has to be pushed.
Okay. What do I do?
Once you're inside,
you'll hear the alarm beeping.
Then you just have to
enter the numbers.
4,  8, 15, 16, 23, 42.
And then, you press "execute."
It has to be exactly those
numbers in exactly that order.
- Do you--
- 4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42.
- I got it.
- Go.
Can you reach it?
I think so.
Be careful.
Henry!
What's going on?
Jack and Sawyer are finally
gonna beat each other up.
Ten mangoes.
Okay. I'll call you
with the aspirin,
and raise you a bottle
of amoxicillin.
Do you even know
what amoxicillin is?
You may have been
to Phuket, doc,
but I been to Tallahassee.
Let's just say somethin' was burnin',
and it wasn't from the sunshine.
I'm all in.
Well, that's the move of a man
who wants me to lay it down.
You're not gonna lay it down.
I'm not, huh? Why is that?
Because there's a bunch of
people watching us right now,
and you don't want
them to see you lose.
Again.
Hmm. Well, all right. I call.
What you got?
A pair of nines?
You pushed in with a pair of nines?
You caught me.
Let's see 'em.
Guess it was enough, huh?
Son of a bitch.
I'll come get the meds later.
Hey.
When I asked you what
you wanted for stakes,
why didn't you
ask for the guns?
When I need the guns,
I'll get the guns.
Henry?
Get up, damn it.
Henry!
Henry, are you all right?
What happened?
Listen to me. You have to get
up into the vents and enter
the numbers into the computer.
How long was I--
Please, you have to go right now.
We're running out of time.
Yeah.
Be careful!
Henry?
Henry, can you hear me?!
Henry!
Henry.
Yeah, who is it?
It's John.
- Can I come in?
- Yeah, of course.
- Any problems?
- No.
Your date at my funeral--
she got a name?
Helen.
Well, that's a nice name.
Pretty girl, too.
I'm, uh,
I'm going to ask her to marry me...
tonight, actually.
Well, good for you.
Congratulations.
Yeah, thanks.
Your share.
Should buy you a nice honeymoon.
I didn't do this for the money.
Then why did you do it?
Well... all right. Uh...
My plane. I got a--
I got a cab waiting.
If you don't want the cash,
the maid's gonna
get a hell of a tip.
Bye, John.
Are you him?
Listen, sweetheart--
How could you?
How could you do this to him?
We were moving past this.
Helen, wait.
Helen, wait. You don't understand.
I was gonna tell you everything.
- You lied to me.
- No, please, I can explain.
You looked me right in the eye,
and you lied to me.
You've made your choice, John.
- No, no, no.
- You need his love more than mine.
No, my choice is you.
I was gonna...
I love you.
No, please. Please.
Please, Helen.
Please, I love you, and--
and I want to spend my
life with you, and--
and I can't live
without you, Helen.
So...
so...
will you marry me?
Helen.
Henry!
Henry.
Henry...
Please say something.
Aah!
Henry!
Henry?
Anybody here?
Henry!
You came back.
What, did you think I was
going to leave you here?
Come on. Can you stand?
I don't...
I think so.
Thank you, Henry.
Thank you for not leaving me.
You're welcome, John.
Hey. Hey, Jack. Wait up.
- You heading back to the hatch?
- Yeah.
Mind if I join?
Been a while since I had a shower,
and I was just hoping that--
Actually, the--
the plumbing's busted.
Busted?
Yeah, the water's
been running muddy.
I guess we got a cracked pipe, but
it's gonna take some time to find it.
Oh. Well,
I guess I wasted a trip, then.
Well, I'll let you know as soon as
we get things worked out down there.
Okay.
I'm glad you beat Sawyer.
You know what?
The hatch can wait until morning if
you'd like me to walk you back to
the beach.
- Do you see that?
- Yeah.
A parachute.
Wait.
It's food.
What the bloody hell is that?
What'd you find?
I got you. Easy, easy.
Sorry.
How did you do--
What did you do to end it,
to make the doors go up?
I did what you told me to.
I punched in the code and
pressed the execute button, but
nothing happened,
other than that clock flipping back.
I was just climbing back into the
vent when the lights went out.
Ten seconds later,
the doors went up.
I didn't do anything.
So you think it was
all just random?
Don't look at me.
It's your hatch.
- Get away from him.
- Wait. You don't--
Step back right now.
- Sayid, it's okay.
- I said get away!
It's all right. I let him out.
There was some kind of lockdown or
something. He-- he was helping me.
Couldn't you find my balloon?
Yeah, we found it.
We did find your balloon,
Henry Gale,
exactly how you described it.
We also found the grave you described--
your wife's grave.
The grave you said you dug
with your own bare hands.
It was all there. Your whole story,
your alibi-- it was true.
But still I did not
believe it to be true.
So I dug up that grave,
and found that there was not a
woman inside. There was a man.
A man named Henry Gale.
Synchro: Travis
Transcript: Raceman
www.forom.com