Clegane, look into the flames.
What do you see?
A wall of ice.
The Wall.
The only thing standing
between us
and the army of the dead
is the Wall,
and the Wall hasn't been
properly manned in centuries.
Last time we saw
The Night King,
it was at Hardhome.
Closest castle to Hardhome
is Eastwatch by the sea.
And that's where I'll go.
Looks like we're
the Nightswatch now.
This suits you, Lady Stark.
- Jon left you in charge?
- He did.
- Lord Tarly.
- I believe you know my son.
Do you fight with us...
or with the fallen savages
and eunuchs?
What do you think I should do?
If you use them to melt castles
and burn cities,
you're not different.
You're just more of the same.
Listen.
You could've killed me.
The fuck were you doing
back there?
Ending the war.
Killing her.
You saw the dragon
between you and her?
And?
Listen to me, cunt.
Till I get
what I'm owed,
a dragon doesn't
get to kill you,
you don't
only I get
to kill you.
That was only
one of them.
She has two more.
If she decides to use them,
to really use them...
- You're fucked.
- Don't you mean we're fucked?
No, I do not.
Dragons are where
our partnership ends.
I'm not gonna be around
when those things
start spitting fire
on King's Landing.
I have to tell
Cersei.
May as well jump
back in that river.
I know what Cersei
has told you.
That I've come
to destroy your cities,
burn down your homes,
murder you,
and orphan your children.
That's Cersei Lannister,
not me.
I'm not here
to murder,
and all I want
to destroy
is the wheel that has
rolled over rich and poor
to the benefit of no one but the
Cersei Lannisters of the world.
I offer you a choice...
bend the knee
and join me.
Together, we will leave the world
a better place than we found it.
Or refuse...
and die.
Step forward,
my lord.
You will not kneel?
I already have
a queen.
My sister.
She wasn't your queen
until recently,
though, was she?
When she murdered
your rightful queen
and destroyed House Tyrell
for all time.
So it appears your allegiances
are somewhat flexible.
There are
no easy choices in war.
Say what you will
about your sister,
she was born
in Westeros.
She's lived here
all her life.
You, on the other hand,
murdered your own father
and chose to support
a foreign invader.
One with no ties
to this land...
with an army of savages
at her back.
You will not trade
your honor for your life.
I respect that.
Perhaps he could take
the Black, Your Grace.
Whatever else he is,
he is a true soldier.
He'd be invaluable
at the Wall.
You cannot send me
to the Wall.
You are not my queen.
You will have
to kill me, too.
Step back
and shut your mouth.
Who are you?
A stupid boy.
I am Dickon Tarly,
son of Randyll Tarly.
You are the future
of your house.
This war has already wiped one
great house from the world.
Don't let it happen again.
Bend the knee.
I will not.
Your Grace, nothing scrubs
bold notions from a man's head
like a few weeks
in a dark cell.
I meant what I said.
I'm not here
to put men in chains.
If that becomes an option,
many will take it.
I gave them a choice.
They made it.
Your Grace, if you start
beheading entire families...
I'm not beheading
anyone.
Your Grace.
Lord Randyll Tarly,
Dickon Tarly,
I, Daenerys of House
Targaryen, First of My Name,
Breaker of Chains,
and Mother of Dragons,
sentence you to die.
Dracarys.
My... my lord...
How many men
did we lose?
We haven't done
a full accounting.
It's not only armies
that win wars.
We have the Tyrell gold,
we have the Iron Bank behind us.
We can buy
mercenaries.
Not the same as our men,
but they'll fight
if they're well paid,
which they will be.
I just saw
the Dothraki fight.
They'll beat
any mercenary army.
They'll beat any army
I've ever seen.
Killing our men wasn't war
for them, it was sport.
Her dragon burnt
a thousand wagons.
Qyburn's scorpion fired
bolts bigger than you.
They couldn't stop it.
And she has three of them.
This isn't a war
we can win.
So, what do we do?
Sue for peace?
I sit on
her father's throne,
the father you betrayed
and murdered.
And in her mind,
she's winning.
What sort of offer
do you think she'd make?
Maybe we can count on Tyrion
to intercede on our behalf
by way of apology for
murdering our father and son.
He didn't.
You saw the crossbow,
you saw his body.
I'm not talking
about Father.
Tyrion didn't kill Joffrey.
He had nothing to do with it.
- After all this time, it still amazes me that you...
- It was Olenna.
She confessed
before she died.
And this was
before or after
she drank the poison
you so kindly provided her?
After.
And you believed her?
If you were Olenna,
would you rather have seen
your granddaughter married
to Joffrey or Tommen?
Which one would Margaery have
been better able to control?
Which one would have
made Olenna
the true ruler
of the Seven Kingdoms?
She was telling
the truth.
I shouldn't have
listened to you.
She should have
died screaming.
She's dead,
like her son,
her grandchildren,
her whole house.
And if we don't find a way out
of this war, we'll follow them.
So we fight and die
or we submit and die.
I know my choice.
A soldier
should know his.
They're beautiful,
aren't they?
It wasn't the word
I was thinking of, but...
but, yes, they are.
Gorgeous beasts.
They're not
beasts to me.
No matter
how big they get
or how terrifying
to everyone else,
they're my children.
You weren't gone long.
No.
And?
And I have fewer enemies
today than I did yesterday.
You're not sure
how you feel about that.
No, I'm not.
How many men
did your army kill
taking Winterfell back
from the Boltons?
Thousands.
We both want
to help people.
We can only help them
from a position of strength.
Sometimes
strength is terrible.
When you first
came here,
Ser Davos said you took a knife
in the heart for your people.
Ser Davos
gets carried away.
So, it was
a figure of speech?
Your Grace.
Jon Snow, this is
Ser Jorah Mormont,
an old friend.
I served
with your father.
He was a great man.
You look strong.
You found a cure?
I wouldn't be here
if I hadn't.
I return to your
service, my queen,
if you'll have me.
It would be my honor.
Ravens.
We need to send ravens.
I put very little stock
in it myself.
Prophecies of doom
are never in short supply,
especially
when winter comes.
I remember Wolkan.
A little timid,
but a sharp mind.
Eh, the North has dulled
many good maesters' wits.
Hard to say whether
it's the cold, the drink,
or the company.
A crippled boy
claims to have seen
dead men on the march
beyond the Wall,
thanks to the magical help
of a raven with three eyes?
Yes, it is a bit much.
- Still, we ought to write back...
- Brandon Stark.
- The crippled boy.
- Do you know him?
I led him through
the Wall years ago.
I saw him go
beyond the Wall.
And?
Somehow,
a crippled boy
survived for years beyond the
Wall when no one else could.
Not the Night's Watch,
not the wildlings, no one.
Perhaps we ought to listen
to what he has to say.
Perhaps you need more scribing
work to discipline your mind.
I sense a more detailed
proposal is forthcoming?
Everyone in Westeros
trusts and respects you.
If you tell people the threat
is real, they'll believe it.
If you advise all the lords
to send their men north
to hold the Wall,
they'll do it.
And if you tell every
maester in the Citadel
to search every word
of every faded scroll
about the Long Night,
they may find something
that lets us defeat
the Army of the Dead
for good.
It could be done.
And this news
could be authentic.
It's possible.
It's also possible
that this message
is part of a ploy
by the Dragon Queen
to lure southern armies away from the
lands they are currently defending
to open those lands
to easy conquest.
That does
seem far more likely
than magic birds
talking to cripples.
Archmaester, please.
It's real.
I've seen it.
We will write
to Maester Wolkan
at Winterfell
for clarification.
I promise you we will get to the
truth of it one way or another.
- Archmaester, please...
- That will be all, Tarly.
It brings to mind the
work of Jenny of Oldstones,
the charlatan who claimed descent
from the children of the forest.
Don't forget the prophet Lodos,
who promised that the Drowned God would
rise up and destroy Aegon the Conqueror.
Ah, Lodos.
Is he the one whose father and
brother were just burnt alive?
I'm afraid so.
Horrible business.
I haven't had the heart
to tell him yet.
He's a good lad.
Right.
The ravenry was falling apart
the last time I checked.
All rulers demand
that people bend the knee.
That's why
they're rulers.
She gave Tarly
a choice,
a man who had taken up
arms against her.
What else
could she do?
Not burn him alive
alongside his son?
I am her Hand, not her head.
I can't make
her decisions for her.
That's what I used to tell
myself about her father.
I found the traitors, but I wasn't
the one burning them alive.
I was only a purveyor
of information.
It's what I told myself when I
watched them beg for mercy...
I'm not the one
doing it.
When the pitch of their
screams rose higher...
I'm not the one
doing it.
When their hair
caught fire
and the smell of their burning
flesh filled the throne room...
I'm not the one
doing it.
Daenerys is not
her father.
And she never will be
with the right counsel.
You need to find a way
to make her listen.
- Who's that for?
- Jon Snow.
Did you read it?
It's a sealed scroll
for the King in the North.
What's it say?
Nothing good.
I thought
Arya was dead.
I thought Bran
was dead.
I'm happy for you.
You don't look happy.
Bran saw the Night King
and his army
marching towards
Eastwatch.
If they make it
past the Wall...
The Wall has kept them out for
thousands of years, presumably.
I need to go home.
You said you don't
have enough men.
We'll fight
with the men we have.
Unless you'll join us.
And give the country
to Cersei?
As soon as I march away,
she marches in.
Perhaps not.
Cersei thinks the Army of the
Dead is nothing but a story
made up by wet nurses
to frighten children.
What if we
prove her wrong?
I don't think she'll come see
the dead at my invitation.
So bring
the dead to her.
I thought that was what
we were trying to avoid.
We don't have to
bring the whole army.
Only one soldier.
Is that possible?
The first wight
I ever saw
was brought into Castle
Black from beyond the Wall.
Bring one of these things
down to King's Landing
and show her the truth.
Anything you bring back
will be useless
unless Cersei
grants us an audience
and is somehow convinced
not to murder us
the moment we set foot
in the capital.
The only person
she listens to is Jaime.
He might listen to me.
And how would you get
into King's Landing?
I can smuggle you in,
but if the gold cloaks
were to recognize you,
I'm warning you,
I'm not a fighter.
Well, it will all
be for nothing
if we don't have
one of these dead men.
Fair point.
How do you propose
to find one?
With the queen's permission,
I'll go north and take one.
You asked me to find a
cure so I could serve you.
Allow me
to serve you.
The Free Folk
will help us.
They know the real north
better than anyone.
They won't follow
Ser Jorah.
They won't have to.
You can't lead a raid
beyond the Wall.
You're not in the Night's Watch
anymore, you're King in the North.
I'm the only one here
who's fought them.
who knows them.
I haven't given you
permission to leave.
With respect, Your Grace,
I don't need your permission.
I am a king.
And I came here
knowing that you could
have your men behead me
or your dragons
burn me alive.
I put my trust
in you, a stranger,
because I knew it was the
best chance for my people,
for all our people.
Now I'm asking you
to trust in a stranger...
because it's
our best chance.
The King in the North
should stay in the North.
We did not choose you
to rule us, my lady.
But perhaps we should have.
The Knights of the Vale came
here for you, Lady Stark.
Aye.
You are very kind,
my lords.
But Jon is our king.
He is doing what
he thinks is best.
I warned Jon
this would happen.
That he couldn't
leave the North
and expect it to just sit
and wait for him like Ghost.
He didn't. He trusted
you to hold it for him.
Well, he's not making it easy.
The Northern lords are proud.
These are Mother
and Father's chambers.
And?
Nothing.
Don't do that.
- What?
- Say what you mean.
You always liked
nice things.
They made you feel
better than everyone.
Are you angry with me?
They were insulting Jon,
and you sat there
and listened.
I listened
to their complaints,
which is my responsibility
as Lady of Winterfell.
Their opinions
are important to you.
Glover has 500 men,
Royce has 2,000.
Offend them
and Jon loses his army.
Not if they lose
their heads first.
Winterfell didn't just
fall into our hands.
We took it back,
and the Mormonts
and the Hornwoods
and the wildlings
and the Vale.
All of us,
working together.
Now, I'm sure cutting off
heads is very satisfying,
but that's not the way you
get people to work together.
And if Jon
doesn't come back,
you'll need
their support...
so you can
work together
to give you
what you really want.
How can you even think
such a horrible thing?
You're thinking it
right now.
You don't want to be,
but the thought
just won't go away.
I have work to do.
My lady.
Last time I was here, I killed
my father with a crossbow.
Last time I was here, you
killed my son with wildfire.
There's a path to the left
that hugs the cliff.
The guards
hardly ever patrol it.
Too many steps.
You're not
staying here?
I've got my own business
in Flea Bottom.
What if someone
takes the boat?
Then we're fucked.
Best hurry.
We don't have time
for this.
We should be preparing
the city for a siege.
The Dothraki
are coming.
All the more reason
for you to train.
Unless you plan on fighting
Dothraki 12-year-olds.
Well, I seem to recall them giving
you a bit of trouble as well.
And here I am,
ready to train.
Why down here?
I don't think
you want people to see
how you look swinging
that thing yet.
Today might be the day
I kill you by accident.
Oh, you won't be
swinging it at me.
I'll leave you
to it.
I needed to see you.
And I knew you'd
never agree to meet.
You made me look
like a complete fool.
I thought I'd surprise you
by hitting Casterly Rock,
but you were
three steps ahead of me.
Abandoned the family home,
completely unsentimental.
Father would have
been proud.
- Don't talk about Father.
- Listen to me...
I once told Bronn
that if I ever saw you
again, I'd cut you in half.
It'll take you a while
with a sparring sword.
He was going to execute me.
He knew
I was innocent.
He didn't hate me
because of anything I did,
he hated me
because of what I am.
A little monster
sent to punish him.
Did he...
did he think...
did he think I wanted
to be born this way?
- Did he think I chose it...
- What do you want?!
Daenerys will
win this war.
You're
a military man.
You must know there's
no way around that.
Daenerys
is not her father.
She's even willing
to suspend the hostilities
if Cersei agrees
to certain terms.
If you want Cersei
to bend the knee,
you can ask her
yourself.
I... I don't.
And Daenerys doesn't.
Not right now,
anyway.
She has a more
important request.
I wasn't sure
I'd find you.
Thought you might
still be rowing.
I looked in shops,
taverns, brothels.
Should have known to come
straight to the Street of Steel.
Aren't you worried
about the gold cloaks?
Haven't been here
in years.
Why should
they recognize me?
Sometimes I hardly do.
Nothing fucks you
harder than time.
Anybody give you
any trouble?
Here I am,
arming Lannisters,
and I never get
a second look.
But you were right.
Safest place for me was
right under the queen's nose.
Don't be so sure.
Safety is never a permanent
state of affairs.
Bad things are coming.
You came to get me.
You want me to come with you.
- Well, the thing you need to understand is...
- I'm ready.
- You...
- Let's go.
You should know
what you're heading into.
What do you think
I've been thinking about
with every swing
of the hammer?
How happy I am
making weapons
for the family
that killed my father?
The family that
tried to kill me?
I've been getting ready.
I never knew what for,
but I've always known
I'd know it when it comes.
You might want to bring
one of those swords.
I don't know much
about swinging swords.
But this...
this I know.
Keep your father's name
to yourself.
Situation's complicated
enough already.
Well, who should
I say I am?
I told you, Clovis, if we
don't get out of here soon,
- someone's going to...
- You there!
No weapons, friends.
I promise.
What can I do
for you?
- Is that your boat?
- It is.
- The docks are that way.
- That they are.
I try to stay
away from them
to avoid good men
such as yourselves.
- Still five gold dragons?
- Are you joking?
You must be even older
than you look.
- 15.
- 15?!
Apiece.
I can't say it was a pleasure
doing business with you.
What's in the boat?
Not more gold.
- Wine?
- Mm.
- I like wine.
- Or hams.
Come have a look.
- Fermented crab.
- What?
Fermented crab.
One bucket of this triples a
brothel's earnings for the week.
A man thinks he's done.
He's ready to go back
to his loving family.
But before he gets
his breeches up,
his lady of the hour pops a tiny
spoon of that into his mouth.
Five minutes later,
he's back in the race.
Here, have a taste.
I'd hurry to your
favorite establishment,
or you'll put a hole
in that chainmail.
Oi, dwarf!
I really wouldn't
try any more
until you see how
the first bite hits you.
That dwarf...
Where'd you get
that scar?
Fish hook. Some men
you just can't teach.
We was looking for a dwarf with
a scar like that a while back.
Perhaps there's
some arrangement?
Arrangement?
You gonna arrange to pay us
more than Queen Cersei...
This is Gendry.
He'll do.
Go, go, go.
I could give you something.
That won't
be necessary.
Ser Jaime.
Why was Qyburn here?
He's the Hand of the Queen.
Why are you here?
I met with Tyrion.
What did our brother
have to say?
Daenerys
wants to meet.
To discuss
her surrender?
an armistice.
She's just won a great victory.
Why would she want a truce now?
Because an army
of dead men
is marching
on the Seven Kingdoms.
Tyrion claims
he'll have proof.
- Are you going to punish him?
- Tyrion?
Bronn.
He betrayed you.
He set up a meeting without
your knowledge or consent.
Do you think
anything of importance
happens in this city
without me knowing?
You let it happen.
Why?
I've come
to believe that
an accommodation
with the Dragon Queen
could be in our
immediate interest.
She has the numbers. If we want to
beat her, we have to be clever.
We have to fight her
like Father would have.
Dead men, dragons,
and Dragon Queens...
Whatever stands
in our way,
we will defeat it.
For ourselves,
for our house,
for this.
Who will you say
is the father?
You.
People won't like that.
Do you remember what Father
used to say about people?
The lion does not concern himself
with the opinions of the sheep.
Never betray me again.
We're leaving today.
- The king's got a lot on his mind.
- I understand.
He doesn't need to be thinking about
harboring the bastard of a dead king.
- You don't have to worry.
- You're just Clovis,
a smith who's come
to pay his respects
before he heads off to work
at the Winterfell forges.
Understood.
Begging your pardon,
Your Grace.
You survived King's Landing.
Yet again.
Your Grace, this is Clo...
Name's Gendry,
Your Grace.
I'm Robert Baratheon's son.
Bastard son.
He was meant
to keep that to himself.
Our fathers
trusted each other.
Why shouldn't we?
I saw your father once
at Winterfell.
I met yours
in my shop.
- You're a lot leaner.
- And you're a lot shorter.
I grew up on
stories about them.
All I ever knew is that
they fought together and won.
Ser Davos told me where you're
going, Your Grace, and why.
Let me come
with you.
Don't be a fool.
You're not a soldier.
No,
but I'm a fighter.
And he won't be needing a
smith with a sword like that.
You know
how to use one?
Well,
that's a problem.
I prefer a hammer.
He can handle himself.
We could use the help.
As my father
used to say,
"It's better to be
a coward for a minute,
than dead for
the rest of your life."
I owe you my life.
Twice over.
But if what you said is true
about what's up there,
I can't wait out
this war.
Yeah, nobody mind me.
All I've ever done
is live to a ripe old age.
All right, come on.
You may not believe it,
but I've missed you,
Mormont.
Nobody glowers
quite like you.
Not even Grey Worm.
This is the coin
the slaver gave me
when I suggested he free us
and pay us, remember?
It was supposed to last us
the rest of our lives.
Take it with you.
But bring it back.
Our queen needs you.
We should be better
at saying farewell by now.
Your Grace, I...
If I don't return, at least
you won't have to deal
with the King
in the North anymore.
I've grown used to him.
I wish you good fortune in the
wars to come, Your Grace.
Heave!
Do you know how many
steps there are in the Citadel?
No.
15,782.
Guess how many windows are
in the Great Sept of Baelor.
None anymore.
That's true.
This High Septon Maynard,
he recorded everything.
He even recorded
his own bowel movements.
What does
"annulment" mean?
It's when a man
sets aside his lawful wife.
Maynard says here that he issued
an annulment for a Prince "Ragger"
and remarried him to someone
else at the same time
in a secret ceremony
in Dorne.
Is that a common thing
in the south or...?
These maesters...
they set me to the task of preserving
that man's window counting
and annulments and bowel
movements for all eternity,
while the secret to
defeating the Night King's
probably sitting on some dusty shelf
somewhere, completely ignored.
But that's all right,
isn't it?
We can all become slavering, murderous
imbeciles in thrall to evil incarnate
as long as we can have access
to the full records
of High Septon Maynard's
15,782 shits!
Steps.
That number
was the steps.
Are you sure
you want to do this?
You always wanted
to be a maester.
I'm tired of reading about
the achievements of better men.
I found it, my lord.
It, uh, took
some searching.
Maester Luwin's archives
are very thorough.
You're sure this is the
only copy in Winterfell?
Uh, yes, my lord.
Lady Stark thanks you
for your service.
Isn't it your
job to talk him out
of stupid fucking
ideas like this?
I've been failing
at that job of late.
How many queens
are there now?
Two.
And you need to convince
the one with the dragons
or the one who
fucks her brother?
Both.
How many men
did you bring?
Not enough.
The big woman?
We were hoping some of
your men could help.
- Hmm.
- I'll be staying behind.
I'm a liability out there,
as you well know.
You are.
You really want to go out there?
Again?
You're not
the only ones.
My scouts found them
a mile south of the Wall.
Said they were
on their way here.
You're the Hound.
I saw you once
at Winterfell.
They want to go
beyond the Wall, too.
We don't want to go beyond
the Wall, we have to.
Our Lord told us that
the Great War is coming...
Don't trust him.
Don't trust
any of them.
They're the Brotherhood.
And the last thing
their lord told them to do
was sell me to a red witch
to be murdered.
Thoros?
I hardly
recognized you.
Ser Jorah Mormont.
They won't give me anything
to drink down here.
I haven't been feeling
like myself.
You're a fucking Mormont?
Like the last
Lord Commander?
He was my father.
He hunted us
like animals.
You returned the favor,
as I recall.
Here we all are
at the edge
of the world
at the same moment,
heading in the same direction
for the same reason.
Our reasons
aren't your reasons.
It doesn't matter
what we think our reasons are.
There's a greater
purpose at work.
And we serve it
together,
whether we
know it or not.
We may take the steps,
but the Lord of Light...
For fuck's sake,
will you shut your hole?
Are we coming
with you or not?
Don't you want to know
what we're doing?
Is it worse than sitting in a
freezing cell, waiting to die?
He's right.
We're all
on the same side.
How can we be?
We're all breathing.
Death is the enemy.
The first enemy and the last.
The enemy always wins.
And we still need to fight him.
You're scared, aren't you?
What are you scared of?