With Christmas just around the corner,
your Uncle Barney, gave me the
horrible gift of an unwanted secret.
Tomorrow night on the roof
of the World Wide News
building--
that's Patrice's favorite spot--
I'm gonna ask her to marry me.
Ah, poot-tu-tat!
You're jinxed.
I'll unjinx you if you'll follow
these two rules:
one: you can't try to talk me
out of it,
and two: you can't tell anybody.
Agreed?
Yeah that nod was a lie.
You see Robin had been hurting
over Barney all fall.
And as her friend,
I knew I had to tell her.
I just had to find
the right moment.
Uh, there he is!
The youngest architect ever
to build a skyscraper
in New York City!
The shockingly still
single Ted Mosby.
You hear that,
ladies?
I can't believe
the GNB Tower opens tonight.
Ted, your building finally
gets unveiled to the whole world.
You hear that, ladies?!
Nervous?
Everything comes out of my
body in liquid form now.
Ignore that, ladies.
Plus, I, I keep
having this nightmare
where King Kong
shows up to the opening
but refuses to climb
my building
because, in his words,
"It's a bit derivative."
Oh, stop it, tonight
is gonna be amazing.
And we are definitely gonna be
there to toast you,
but we might have to leave
a little early if that's okay.
My dad just gave us the most
amazing Christmas gift ever.
Our first night away
since Marvin was born.
24 hours straight without
that little bastard.
We're maximizing
our time away
by planning everything
down to the minute.
See?
2:12 p.m.-- guilt Ted
into saying it's okay
if we leave early tonight.
It's okay if you leave
early tonight.
Look, I just
appreciate you
showing up at all
on your big night away.
I mean, Barney's not
even gonna be there.
What?
This is the biggest
night of your career.
Why isn't Barney coming?
I don't know--
he said,
"Legendary" and "Challenge
accepted," and then he winked.
"Wait for it," you know,
all that stuff.
That does sound like him.
Well, we're your
real friends
and we wouldn't miss
it for the world.
That is why we will
see you tonight
from 7:03 to 7:14.
Bye, guys. Good night.
Bye.
Okay, what's the real reason
Barney's not coming?
Here was my chance
to tell Robin about Barney.
Yeah, actually, Barney didn't
say what he was doing tonight.
Anyway, uh, you know, I'm not
taking anyone to the opening,
so you want to be my date?
Sure.
? How I Met Your Mother 8x12 ?
The Final Page, Part Two
Original Air Date on December 17, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Okay, Dad, I-I
made you a list
of Marvin's nightly schedule
down to the minute.
Okay.
Uh, "9:06 p.m.--
put on edible underwear."
Wrong list, wrong list.
Come on, relax.
I know this little guy
like the back of my hand.
Dear Lord, what is that?
Oh, jam, okay.
Just jam.
Oh, I-I forgot
the lullaby.
Do you know
Marvin's lullaby?
We sing it
to him every night.
? Night, night,
little Marvin ?
? Stars twinkle for you
? The Dreamland train's
a-chuggin' ?
? All your dreams
will come true ?
? And the horsie
says, "Good night" ?
? And the birdie says,
"Good night" ?
? And the elephant
says, "Good night" ?
? And the skeleton playing
his own rib cage ?
? Says, "Good Night"
? And the robot says,
"Good night" ?
Good night.
Enough with the damn music!
? And Mr. Nesbit says,
"Good night" ?
? And the whole world says,
Take it, Mommy.
Got it-- load him up
with cough syrup,
watch Breaking Bad
until he conks out.
Just kidding.
We did it.
Yeah, we did.
Now that we're out the door,
I actually don't feel anxious.
Whoa, oh, my God, it's your dad!
Oh, something horrible
happened-- aah!
Oh, it's Ted, relax.
Bar, now.
What is it?
He needs me.
But, baby, what about
our magical romantic night?
In four minutes we're supposed
to be doing hand stuff
in the cab.
I'll be quick--
I'm sure it's nothing huge.
That's huge.
And I knew that
I had to tell Robin.
But?
I may have, uh...
asked her to be my date instead.
What is wrong with me?
Deep down,
is there still
some crazy part of me
that thinks I'm gonna
wind up with Robin?
Am I that deluded?
If so, I need to grow up.
Oh, um, by the way,
I'm breaking a jinx swear here,
so don't tell Barney
or he gets to whack me
in the nuts three times
with a Wiffle ball bat.
Sure, pretty standard.
Robin deserves the chance to go
after Barney one last time
if that's what she wants.
I'm gonna go tell her.
One quick thing.
Yeah.
Don't.
Hey, um, I'm gonna be
a little while, baby.
It's a long story,
but Ted needs my help.
Okay, but hurry
or I'm gonna start doing
number 11 on my own.
You can do that by yourself?
Pilates, bitch.
Okay, why shouldn't
I tell Robin?
Because deep down
some crazy part of you
still thinks you're gonna
wind up with her, and I agree.
Marshall...
I'm sorry, I'm Team Tedward.
Always have been,
always will be.
Now, listen.
I want my best friend
to be happy.
And if Robin could mean
happiness for you,
then, dear God, why help her
go after another man?
Because she might still be
in love with him.
To not tell her,
to not give her that chance,
it's... it's selfish.
So be selfish.
I can't do that.
Tell that to the onion rings
we just "split."
Robin is my friend.
She's always been more
than that and you know it.
Now, as we speak,
my wife is in a hotel room
cheating on me...
with herself.
But I'm not
leaving here
until you promise not to say
a word about this to Robin.
Now repeat after me. "I..."
Well, I can do more
at a time than "I."
"I, Ted Mosby, promise to stop
"putting everyone else's
interests ahead of my own,
and for once in my life,
do what's best for me."
I...
Sorry, what was
the rest of that?
Hey, Dad, just taking a break
from our amazing night
to check in.
I bet Marvin's pretty devastated
that I'm not there, huh?
Not at all-- I don't think
he even noticed you're gone.
It's kind of like Mommy who?
Oh... oh, good.
But I should probably sing him
his nighttime lullaby
over the phone, just in case.
Sang it already-- nailed it.
Did you do the horsie?
Yep.
The birdie?
Elephant?
Yep.
Moose.
No moose, trick question.
Robot.
Affirmative.
Look, I should go.
Marvin's asleep in my arms.
Mmm, his head smells like love.
Bye.
Whoa.
Hello... and
hubba-hubba.
Aw, thanks.
But tonight is
about my main man Mosby.
Really?
Why?
Oh, Ted, tell Ranjit
the huge thing
that's happening tonight.
Barney's getting engaged.
Ranjit out.
Bar-Barney's getting engaged?
He asked me to keep it a secret,
but I thought
you deserved to know...
in case you wanted
to do something about it.
Do you?
Do you, Robin?
Ranjit, a little
privacy, please?
Sorry, not listening.
Nice, uneven floor
there, Ted.
Lily, are you drunk?
What? I...
I'm on vacation.
I may have cracked open
the minibar to celebrate.
Who invited the narc?
Hey, listen,
I know that
you miss Marvin, but it's not
like we could've brought him
to a black tie event anyway.
Yeah, these parents are
so lame and-and clingy.
Yeah, it's like, cut the cord
already, right, guys?
Yeah, yeah,
that baby's not even cute.
Super ugly baby.
It's almost
physically repulsive.
Aw....
Aw...
Great, I just
started lactating.
Me, too.
So, what do you want to do?
Robin, I do not
want to meddle,
but this is like the classic
love song says...
Ranjit.
Ranjit, let's just communicate
via text from now on, okay?
I appreciate
what you're doing.
But I'm not chasing
after Barney anymore.
I-I just got done being
crazy about all that.
I mean, why would I want to
throw myself back in that pit?
Because you're in love with him.
No, I'm not.
I'm happy for him.
So, it doesn't bother you that
Barney Stinson's gonna propose
to another woman on top of
the World Wide News building?
Wait, why the top
of the World Wide News building?
I guess it's Patrice's
favorite spot in the city.
Damn it, Patrice, that's my
favorite spot in the city!
Whoa.
Ranjit says, "Whoa."
Okay...
maybe that one detail stings
a little bit,
but that doesn't mean
I'm in love with Barney.
"Sounds like she's
in love with Barney."
Okay, is this divider
even slightly soundproof?
"Yes."
With a little
winky face.
Look, I... I hope it goes
well for Barney.
I really do.
But tonight there is
no place I would rather be
than at your building.
Celebrating with you.
This kid does not mean
that you're special.
It just means that you're
horny and you're easy.
Now, come on,
let me smell his head.
Li-Lily, Lily,
no, no, no, no, come on.
Seriously, Ted,
what is up with the floor?
Lily.
What?
Is it harder
than we thought
to be away from
Marvin? Yes.
But are we gonna have fun
or are we gonna wallow
in the corner like idiots?
? Night, night, little Marvin
? Stars twinkle for you
? The Dreamland train's
a-chuggin' ?
? All your dreams
? Will come true.
Hey.
Do you realize that something
you thought up in your head
now exists as a part
of the Manhattan skyline?
That's huge.
It's just a building.
I mean, I'm incredibly young
for such an achievement,
but it's just a building.
I mean, Architecture
Vision Weekly
may have dubbed it
"more than just a building,"
but it's just a building.
So let's not get carried...
Okay, you're right, it's huge.
It is huge.
You're the star of the party,
and who knows?
Maybe the future Mrs. Ted Mosby
is gonna be there.
Yeah, maybe she will.
Oh.
Wait, this isn't your...
This is
the World Wide News building.
Go get him.
I told you,
I am done chasing Barney.
Now can we please go
to your party?
Robin, do you want to spend
tonight making small talk
with a bunch of bankers
in a daring yet refined
contemporary masterpiece
King Kong should feel lucky
to climb...
...or do you
want to follow your heart?
Why do you keep insisting that
I have feelings for Barney?
Because you do.
See, even Ranjit agrees.
Oh, he's got to pee.
The point is,
you're not over Barney.
That's why you freaked out
about him proposing
on the roof
of the World Wide News building.
I did not freak out.
It's just...
a teeny, tiny bit annoying
that I am the one
who showed her that roof
in the first place!
Damn it, Patrice!
Whoa.
"Never mind; I found
a soda bottle."
Okay, that's disturbing.
What do you want me
to do, Ted?
Run up to that roof,
knock the ring
out of Barney's hand,
and say, "Sorry to interrupt,
but you should be with me"?
Is that what you want?
No.
I don't.
I can't keep making
an ass of myself.
Well,
a word in defense of making
an ass of yourself,
it's underrated.
Eight years ago
I made an ass
of myself chasing after you,
and I've made an ass
of myself chasing after you
a bunch of times since then.
But I have no regrets.
Because it led me to something
that I wouldn't trade
for the world.
It led to you being my friend.
So, as your friend
and a leading expert
in the field
of making an ass of yourself,
I say to you
from the heart,
get the hell out of this car.
But, Ted,
your big night.
It's just a building.
The Robin.
Step one: admit to yourself
that you still have feelings
for this girl.
I am hopelessly,
irretrievably in love with her.
More than she knows.
Step two:
choose the completely wrong
moment to make a drunken move
after hanging out
at a strip club
and get shot down on purpose.
Step three:
agree that you two don't work,
locking the door
on any future
you could have together.
I'm done trying to get you.
I can't do it anymore.
Which will drive Robin nuts.
Huh.
Step four:
Robin goes nuts.
Step five:
find the person
who annoys Robin most
in the world...
Nobody asked
for your help, Patrice!
...and ask for her help.
Oh, hi, Barney.
What are you doing here?
Actually, I'm looking for you.
This may sound kind of weird,
but I have a proposition...
Explain everything to Patrice
and hope she agrees to help.
Yay. I love Robin.
Of course I'll help.
Good, good.
Step six:
check with your doctor
about possible broken ribs.
Step seven:
pretend to be dating Patrice.
Nobody asked you here,
Patrice!
Actually, I did.
Step eight:
wait until Robin inevitably
breaks into your place
to find the Playbook
and show it to Patrice,
which you'll monitor
via the hidden cameras
you have in your apartment.
Patrice, the robin's
in the nest.
That means Robin broke
into my apartment
Were you even listening
when I explained the codes?
Step nine: after Patrice
finds the Playbook,
have your first big fight.
This is going so well.
Thank you so much.
I know, but what the heck
are Lily and Ted doing here?
I don't know.
My friends have no boundaries.
How can I ever thank you?
Will you watch my
cat next weekend?
No.
Come on, we should probably
go back inside.
Step ten:
prove your loyalty to Patrice
by burning the Playbook,
and actually burn it.
You don't need it anymore.
Step 11:
because your friends
have no boundaries,
they'll inevitably have
an intervention for Robin,
which you'll monitor
via the hidden cameras
you have in Marshall
and Lily's apartment.
Step 12:
tell only Ted about your plan
to propose to Patrice.
You can't tell anybody.
Agreed?
Step 13:
wait and see
if Ted tells Robin,
and if he does...
Barney's getting engaged.
...it means your best bro
in the world
has let go of Robin
and has given you his blessing.
Step 14:
Robin arrives
at her favorite spot
in the city
and finds the secret final page
of the Playbook.
The last play
you'll ever run.
Step 15: Robin realizes
she's standing
underneath mistletoe.
Seriously, Barney?
Even you,
even someone
as certifiably insane as you
must realize
that this is too far.
You lied to me,
manipulated me for weeks.
Do you really think I could
ever kiss you after that?
Do you really think
I could ever trust you
after that?
This...
this is proof
of why we don't work,
why we'll never work.
So thank you.
You've set me free because...
how could I be with a man
who thinks that this...
trick, this enormous lie
could ever make me want
to date him again?
Turn it over.
Robin Scherbatsky...
...will you marry me?
Yes.
? In the oceans deep
? In the canyons steep
? Walls of granite
? Here I stand
? All my desperate calls
? Echo off the walls
? Back and forth...
And so, let's all raise a glass
to Ted Mosby.
None of this
would have been possible
without him.
To Ted.
? Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
? Oh-oh-oh-
oh-oh ?
? Oh-oh
? To believe
? I walk
? Alone
? Is a lie
? That I've ?
? Been told
? So let your heart hold fast
? For this soon shall pass
? There's another hill ahead. ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==