NARRATOR: Kids, this is
the story of the night
Barney's life
completely fell apart.
My life is finally perfect,
and that is never
going to change.
Fired up for dinner
with my mom tonight?
Yeah. To help streamline
the rest of our lives,
you can always assume my answer
to that question is no.
W...
I'm pretty nervous.
Nervous? Why?
It's just gonna be two hours
of "I love Barney the most."
"No, I love Barney the most."
You're right. I may not even
get a chance to talk.
But I'm still--
I-I don't know. I'm worried
she won't think
I'm good enough to be engaged
to her precious
little Love-Love.
Okay, first of all,
it's "Wuv-Wuv."
And second,
don't worry.
I'm just gonna drop off
our catering deposit,
and then I will be there for you.
Mm.
Okay, well,
please don't be late.
I am counting on you tonight.
And be careful--
that's 5,000 bucks in there.
Uh, I think I'll be okay
walking four blocks here
on the Upper East Side.
(chuckles)
(grunting)
Please, I swear I never talked
to the North Koreans!
Unless you are
the North Koreans, in which case
I never talked
to the South Koreans!
MAN (menacingly):
Barney Stinson,
you are being
kidnapped.
For your surprise
bachelor party!
(both laughing)
? How I Met Your Mother 8x22 ?
The Bro Mitzvah
Original Air Date on April 29, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
A kidnapping.
Respect.
I was secretly worried
you might not be able
to pull off my bachelor party.
Yeah, it wasn't that secret.
You two?
Planning my bachelor party?
(chuckles)
Look, you seem like nice kids.
But this is a sacred event,
a man's rite of passage
with his bros.
His... bro mitzvah!
You didn't just
think of that.
You've been saying it
for months every...
But here's my dilemma:
my average night is like
an average guy's bachelor party.
So, no offense,
but if you two plan it,
it's gonna be ordi--
why wait for it?-- nary.
Ordinary.
I can help.
You?
(chuckles)
Look, you seem like a nice kid,
but bros' fianc?es
cannot plan bachelor parties.
Sorry. You two are on your own.
And you will disappoint me.
But make it great, okay?
But this is a strong start.
The students
have become...
the intermediate
students.
I just have
to make one call.
(phone rings)
Hello.
Robin, great news!
I've been kidnapped
for a surprise bachelor party
so I won't be there
at all!
What? Barney, I-I can't
do dinner with your mom alone.
Okay, I'll call her,
make up an excuse and cancel.
And don't worry,
I'll take all the blame.
Hold on.
Hi, Wuv-Wuv.
Hi, Momsies.
I forgot, I'm mentoring an
underprivileged child tonight,
and Robin can't stand the idea
of dinner with you by herself,
so we're not gonna be able to...
Don't bother.
She's already here.
Hold on.
Robin? Too late.
She's already there.
Barney, don't...
Robin can't stand the idea
of dinner with me?
Great! We're all set then.
Don't you leave me alone
with her. I told you...
That problem is solved.
So what's the plan?
Well, you know the Taj
Mahal in Atlantic City?
Yeah.
You know the
secret penthouse
in the top of the Taj
Mahal in Atlantic City?
Yeah!
Boom! There it is.
Visible from our window.
In the distance.
Behind the refinery.
Okay, you can't
quite see it.
Why are we outside
Atlantic City?
Well, we thought it was best,
what with your weakness
for games of chance.
NARRATOR:
Kids, Barney was addicted
to one Chinese gambling game
that was, well,
sort of complicated.
But don't worry.
Back when you were
engaged to Quinn,
you told us everything
you wanted for tonight.
A bachelor party is a man's...
bro mitzvah!
Did you just think of that?
Totally! We can wear...
bro-mulkes...
spin the bro-del...
and consult the wisdom
of the Bro-rah.
Written in... He-bro.
Not at all
bro-ffensive.
Ooh, ooh! Couple other ideas--
and I'm just spitballing here--
so take 'em or leave 'em.
Booze, duh; cigars, duh;
strippers, duh...
Ooh! Things should get so
crazy that at some point
we should fear
for our lives.
Oh, we'll fear for our lives,
all right.
When we watch Al Gore's
An Inconvenient Truth!
(chuckles) Yeah. We're
gonna pound a beer
every time we
hear the word
(imitates Al Gore):
"catastrophic""
(knocking)
Oh!
Could that be...
the next item on your list?
BARNEY: Mind-blowing
entertainment,
like a naked fire show
or a naked magic show.
There's a good chance
our engagement
doesn't work out, isn't there?
Not now, honey.
Or a naked
contortionist!
Or... a balloon contortionist!
(honking)
Balloons.
Not the inflatable, round,
squishy pouches
I was hoping to see tonight.
(cell phone ringing)
Hold on.
TED (quietly):
I told you no clown.
Well, you didn't like
the bubble guy either.
Hey, Robin.
Did you tell your mother
I'm a virgin?
What? Why would you think that?
Save yourself room for dessert.
Mmm.
And I hear you excel
at saving yourself.
(chuckles):
You are so funny.
What's gotten into you?
Oh, that's right-- nothing ever.
You may be nervous
as to what goes where
on your wedding night.
It's really simple.
Let me show you.
Let's start with
the fundamentals.
Why would you
tell her I'm a virgin?
I panicked.
Look, I really want her
to like you,
so just go with it, okay? Okay!
Listen, Wuv-Wuv,
you better get your ass back...
(knocking)
Another guest?
Who could this be?
Why, it's Lily!
And she's here
to deliver
one of your requests!
Oh, thank you,
Marshall.
Oh, not that one.
An appearance by
my all-time idol,
the Karate Kid!
NARRATOR: The Karate Kid
was an uplifting '80s classic
about a teen,
played by Ralph Macchio,
who defeats the local jerk,
played by William Zabka.
At least, that's how
most people saw it.
Here he is, just as hot
as when his Tiger Beat
photo spread gave a young girl
the courage to explore
the suddenly unfamiliar
topography
of her changing body...
the Karate Kid!
Hey, Barney. It's Ralph.
Listen,
it's always flattering...
No!
I hate Ralph Macchio!
I hate him, hate him, hate him!
He is not the Karate Kid!
The Karate Kid
was William Zabka,
star pupil
of the Cobra Kai Dojo,
who this monster
defeated
with a cheap,
illegal head-kick
in the most tragically haunting
film ending of all time.
Oh, see, I thought
you meant fun-crazy.
Shut it, Ralph Macchio.
Why don't you go have
a party with Luke Skywalker
and Harry Potter and War Horse
and all the other movie bad guys
and stop ruining mine!
This night has been
catastrophic.
"Catastrophic"!
Everybody pound.
Sorry, bro.
I'm staying.
If this is anything
like my bachelor party--
strippers, booze,
definitely no hand stuff--
wink-wink--
it is gonna be in--
wait for it-- credible.
Incredible!
TED:
Wow.
You guys are
actually a lot alike.
You take that back, sir!
I am nothing like
Ralph Macchio!
I mean, did you guys
even get a stripper?
Bro.
(chuckling)
Of course we
got a stripper.
Do we look like
the kind of dweebs
who wouldn't get a stripper?
(scoffs)
(knocking)
And as the saying goes,
what happens in
the sensibly-priced
business hotel outside
Atlantic City stays
in the sensibly-priced business
hotel outside Atlantic City.
Who is it?
WOMAN: Police. We got
a noise complaint from...
Oh, who am I kidding?
I can tell it's dead in there.
I'm the stripper!
Barney?
Quinn?
This is your bachelor party?
You're engaged again,
less than a year
after we broke up?
Is it Robin?
Now, hold on.
You're not the only one
with questions here.
You didn't vet the stripper?!
Well, I'm glad
you're so happy.
After we broke up,
I had to move out of the city,
my car got totaled,
and I had to go back
to stripping just to pay rent.
It's like everywhere I look,
my life is a dead-end.
Wow.
I am... I'm so
sorry, Quinn.
So, how does this work?
Do you give me a private
show, or does everyone...?
I am not stripping for you.
Whoa, whoa! I was
promised boobs.
Oh, Ralph,
if you want, I can...
Lily.
Is that the Karate Kid?
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
No!
He's a lot like
Barney, huh?
(gasps) You take
that back, madam.
I am nothing
like Ralph Macchio!
QUINN:
Okay, okay.
I'll tell you what.
I am going to strip
for everyone here
except Barney.
And I'm gonna make it dirty.
Yeah, um, I'm the bachelor.
Kind of no stripping
without the lap of honor.
Back me up, bros.
(people whooping,
dance music playing)
(phone ringing)
MARSHALL:
How'd you even do that?
TED: What the...?!
LILY: Oh, my God, yeah!
Hey, Robin.
Hey, sweetie, having fun
at your bachelor party?
No.
Good, 'cause my night's been hell!
And that's the inverted
chimney sweep,
the last of the 17 basic
sexual positions.
Now, bondage...
Stop! I'm not a virgin!
My napkin ring has seen
plenty of breadsticks.
And one baguette.
I dated a center for the Knicks.
Oh, thank God
you're not a prude.
Now we can really talk.
Four cosmos, pronto!
Now she's drunk,
holding up a napkin ring
and three breadsticks,
and talking about her night
with Crosby, Stills and Nash.
Waiter, can I have
another breadstick?
And Young.
Please come back.
(people cheering)
Okay.
I'll be there soon.
Real nice.
So beautiful.
I think we really did it.
I think we did it, you know?
You didn't miss a thing.
MARSHALL: Oh, Quinn?
Yeah?
You got a little...
something.
Oh! Oh.
(sighs)
Let's head back, guys.
This night has been
completely half-assed.
You obviously missed
the strip show.
Hey-oh!
(horn honks)
Ted, this was my bachelor party.
A man only gets two or three
of these in his lifetime.
And this is all you do for me?
That's it, I'm calling it.
Who needs a ride back
to the city?
Oh.
Oh, guys, wait,
hold on, hold on.
Drinking.
A shot.
Shooting.
A gun.
Shot, gun.
Shotgun?
(sighs)
Man, it's crowded
in here.
I know,
it's like a clown car.
Well, I can make some room
by grinding on Ralph's lap.
ing!
I-I meant, I meant sitting.
This is the worst
bachelor party ever.
Man, my bachelor party
was incr-- wait for it--
and I hope you're hungry,
'cause the second half
of this word is-- edible!
Incredible!
(chuckles)
Self-shake.
(gasps)
You take that
back, clown.
I am nothing like Ralph Macchio!
RALPH:
Yeah.
You've got more in
common with the clown,
except his suit's
more expensive.
Hey, yo!
(horn honks)
I mean, what kind of loser
has his bachelor party
ten yards from A.C.
and doesn't even gamble?
(tires screeching)
(screams)
Oh. Oh, sorry.
Sorry. Sorry.
(chuckles)
Sorry.
Oh... oh, wait.
Just a little more.
Okay, sorry.
(sighs):
Okay.
(speaking Chinese)
...bro mitzvah!
(laughs)
NARRATOR: Kids, I'll skip over
the gambling.
Like I said, it was
a complicated game.
Although your old man
did pick it up pretty quickly.
(crowd cheers)
Hey!
You just won 300 bucks!
I just lost $5,000.
Oh, right.
'Cause the chicken.
Yep, that-that's
$5,000, yeah.
(laughs)
See, I'm laughing
because you couldn't see me
take my top off,
but I just saw you lose your shirt.
Hey-yo!
(horn honks)
We have to go back.
(sneezes): Loser!
Sorry, that was a real sneeze.
Might have made you miss
what I was saying.
Loser!
(laughs):
Loser.
We're not going anywhere.
I can still make
this night legendary.
Uh, uh... (speaks Chinese)
(replies in Chinese)
Oh, oh.
Okay, I got some credit.
I just... mm...
Marshall, stand over there
for good luck?
Oh, sure.
Okay, okay.
(crowd chants in Chinese)
(speaks Chinese)
(crowd cheers)
(laughs):
Oh! Oh!
You crazy son of a bitch,
you did it!
I just lost $80,000.
Oh, right, right, yeah.
'Cause the black jelly bean.
That-That's $80,000.
He's right.
(clears throat)
You know, Ralph,
earlier at the salon, I
waxed on, then waxed off.
(whispers):
Everywhere.
Uh, listen, lady,
your husband is, like...
Hey, where is
your husband?
Marshall?
Where's Marshall?!
Okay, Lily,
don't overreact, but...
Oh, oh.
Okay, I got some credit.
Marshall, stand over there
for good luck?
Oh, sure.
You sold my husband?!
Lily, can you be more like
the Chinese mobster
and give me some credit?
I'm going back for Marshall;
I just need to get some money.
You have nothing to worry about;
these are the "good" mobsters.
Wow, what kind of bozo
does that to a friend?
Shut it, Ralph Macchio!
No, you shut it!
Ralph Macchio's right,
you are a bozo.
Um, I think they prefer
"people of bright color."
You know what
a bachelor party's about?
Hanging out with your friends
and having a good time.
But you only care about
the good time, not the friends.
So you know what?
I'm-I'm done
caring about you then.
I'm out of here.
Ted...
Ted, Ted, I have...
I just tore your mom away
from a living version
of a Nick Nolte mug shot
and put her in a cab home.
Thank you for abandoning me
on what has been one of
the worst nights of my life.
So, it's my usual fee,
plus I always charge
an extra hundred for
girl-on-clown action.
What the hell
is she doing here?
Robin, I swear,
nothing happened.
That means just hand stuff.
(horn honks)
You...!
Oh!
No, no, stop, stop, stop!
Sorry, Barney,
this... this-this is
unforgivable.
It's over.
You know...
I never got to do that.
(sighs)
Ted?
Robin.
We're right on schedule.
Barney is suicidal.
I know, it's awesome!
(both laughing)
NARRATOR:
Yep, kids, we had planned out
every step of the night.
It started three weeks earlier.
...and you will disappoint me.
But make it great, okay?
Oh, it'll be great,
all right!
Okay, after two weeks
of brainstorming,
all I have on my list
so far is Purell.
Marshall, what
do you got?
Well, nothing now.
This is impossible!
How do you make something
memorable for a guy
who makes every night
the best night of his life?
Give him the worst night
of his life.
We'll give him
the worst hotel room
with the worst entertainment,
(horn honks)
the wrong Karate Kid,
and the absolute last stripper
he would want to see.
Hold on.
You want me to pretend
my life's gone to crap
and I'm back to stripping
just screw with my ex-fianc??
I love it!
That party will be so terrible,
he'll have to leave it.
Then I'll instruct
his arch-nemesis to say...
I mean, what kind of loser
has his bachelor party
ten yards from A.C.
and doesn't even gamble?
ROBIN: Barney will take
the envelope of cash I gave him
and head straight
into our trap.
Hold on.
You want us to rig a casino game
to trick one of
our former high rollers?
Um...
I love it.
Well, then
you get Barney
to use one of these
guys as collateral.
He'll probably choose me.
What?
Well, I'd be worth more.
Yeah. Perfect teeth.
(clears throat)
Yeah, it's just, uh,
just I'm way more athletic
than you.
Yeah, this coming
from the guy
who's never beaten me
at skee-ball.
The only reason a mobster
might choose you is because
they'd be afraid I'd go all
"Marshall Unchained" on them,
which obviously isn't
a risk with you.
Oh, you want to see
some "Ted Unchained," huh?
I'll show you Ted Unchained!
Marshall, would you mind
standing over there
for good luck?
Oh, yeah, sure.
ROBIN:
Meanwhile, I'll make sure
he's abandoned me
in my nightmare scenario.
Hold on. You want me to
help you trick my own son?
I love it.
(sighs)
Barney deserves it.
You know, he told me
you were a virgin.
(scoffs)
Ridiculous!
I know.
(laughs)
You are a dirty ho-bag
just like me.
But he loves you so much.
And so do I.
(mouthing)
Wait, hold on.
Is there any chance
this is all too
mean to Barney?
(laughter)
Just kidding.
Okay, we just need
the finale.
Oh! The Chinese mobsters
chop off my hand
right in front of Barney!
Yes, we're all
equally enthused!
Okay, here's the plan.
After I storm off...
MARSHALL:
Barney!
Barney, hurry!
Give them the money!
Please, hurry!
Oh, no!
The Chinese mobster
is giving Marshall back
and taking me hostage instead,
because he says
I'm obviously more valuable!
Can you, can you
unlock the door?
Barney, please!
They're gonna
chop off my hand!
No, they're not!
They said you're free,
and I think
we agreed that's not
something mobsters would do.
Ted, come on!
This is my thing!
Don't hurt him.
I've got the money.
Too late!
(screaming)
Not my skee-ball hand!
No...!
No!
Please, just don't shoot me
in the face... or the crotch!
ALL:
Surprise!
What's going on?
Well, we decided to give you
everything you wanted
for your bachelor party
without you even realizing it.
Wait, so that's why you made me
think Marshall might die?
And I'd lost all that money
and my friends hated me
and my wedding was off?
You just decided
to-to check off
everything on this list
in the most
twisted way imaginable?
That is awesome!
And it was all planned
by a girl.
(laughs):
Wow!
So, Lily...
later on tonight,
you want to, um...?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
That was all just
part of the act.
Y-You knew that, right?
Yeah! Totally.
We pulled it off, right?
Platonic shake!
Everyone, everyone, thank you
for an incredible bro mitzvah.
Mazel brov!
ALL:
(chuckles)
Mm, oh, you didn't really get
everything on the list.
N-No offense
to Ralph Macchio,
but he ain't the Karate Kid.
I couldn't agree
with you more.
You know,
they almost didn't get me.
But after
18 voice mails...
I returned Robin's call.
And she told me
how you're one of the
few people in the world
who truly gets
The Karate Kid movie.
So when she asked if I'd help,
well, my answer
just had to be...
Hai!
William Zabka!
(all cheering)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==