Mom.
Mom is a babe.
-Are you a hunter?
-Hey, Winchester. Son of a bitch.
-How you doing, corporal?
-Hey, Mr. D.
Dad?
This is gonna sound a little crazy.
-Mary is my mother.
-Excuse me?
And I am your grandson.
My parents are Mary...
-...and John Winchester.
-I don't know--
Mary gets killed
by a yellow-eyed demon.
-You don't want these people's souls.
-I want their children.
-Why any of them?
-I'm gonna stand over their crib...
...and I'm gonna bleed
into their mouth.
DEAN: So you've been using
your freaky ESP stuff?
SAM: No.
DEAN: Sure about that?
SAM: You didn't want me
to go down that road.
-I didn't go down that road.
-Let's keep it that way.
We know what Azazel did
to your brother. We don't know why.
Your brother is heading down
a dangerous road, Dean. So stop it...
...or we will.
Where's Lilith?
Kiss my ass.
-I'd watch myself if I were you.
-Why? Huh?
Because you're Sam Winchester,
Mr. Big-Hero?
And yet here you are
slutting around with some demon.
-Real hero.
-Shut your mouth.
Tell me about those months
without your brother.
About all the things
you and this demon bitch do in the dark.
Huh? Tell me, hero.
[GAGGING]
-How'd that feel?
-Good.
-No more headaches.
-None? That's good.
Hey, hey. I gotcha. It's all right.
So...
...anything you wanna tell me, Sam?
Dean. Hold on, okay?
-Just let me ex--
-You gonna say, "Let me explain"?
You gonna explain this?
How about this,
why don't you start with who she is...
...and what the hell is she doing here?
Good to see you again, Dean.
Ruby?
Is that Ruby?
SAM:
Don't!
Ruby, Ruby, Ruby. Stop it.
Well, aren't you
an obedient little bitch.
Ruby.
Ruby. He's hurt.
Go.
-Where the hell you think you're going?
RUBY: The ER.
Unless you wanna go
another round first.
Dean.
Dean, what are you doing?
-Are you leaving?
-You don't need me.
-You and Ruby go fight demons.
-Hold on. Dean. Come on, man.
You satisfied?
I guess not.
Do you know how far off the reservation
you've gone?
How far from normal? From human?
-I'm just exorcising demons.
-With your mind!
-What else can you do?
-I can send them back to hell.
It only works with demons.
And that's it.
-What else can you do?
-I told you.
And I have every reason in the world
to believe that.
Look, I should've said something.
I'm sorry, Dean. I am.
-But try to see the other side here.
-The other side?
I'm pulling demons out of people.
-Use the knife!
-The knife kills the victim.
What I do, most of them survive.
Look, I've saved more people in the last
five months than we save in a year.
That what Ruby wants you to think?
Kind of like the way she tricked you
into using your powers?
Slippery slope, brother.
Just wait and see.
Because it's gonna get darker
and darker.
-And God knows where it ends.
-I'm not gonna let it go too far.
It's already gone too far, Sam.
If I didn't know you...
...I would wanna hunt you.
And so would other hunters.
You were gone.
I was here.
I had to keep on fighting without you.
And what I'm doing...
...it works.
Well, tell me, if it's so terrific...
...then why'd you lie about it to me?
Why did an angel tell me to stop you?
-What?
-Cas said that if I don't stop you...
...he will.
See what that means, Sam?
That means that God
doesn't want you doing this.
So are you just gonna stand there
and tell me that everything is all good?
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hey, Travis. Yeah, hey.
It's good to hear your voice too, yeah.
Look, it's not
a really good time right now.
Yeah, okay.
Well, just give me the details, and....
"Carthage, Missouri.
Looking for Jack Montgomery."
-Jack, are you stoned?
-What?
It's good. I'm starving.
-Is there dessert?
-It just so happens.
Hey, babe?
Are you gonna finish your steak?
You're kidding, right?
You've had two already.
I don't know. I'm just hungry.
-Or you have a tapeworm.
-Please.
I've never felt better.
[GROANING]
Ah!
[CRUNCHING]
[GRUNTING]
I can't believe it.
Mom? A hunter?
I wouldn't have believed it either
if I hadn't seen it myself.
Boy, that woman could kick some ass.
I mean, she almost took me down.
How'd she look?
I mean...
...was she happy?
Yeah, she was awesome.
You know, funny and smart.
So hopeful.
You know, Dad too.
Until, of course....
What?
Nothing.
It's just, our parents, and now
we find out our grandparents too?
Our whole family, murdered.
And for what?
So Yellow Eyes could get in my nursery
and bleed in my mouth?
Sam, I never said anything
about demon blood.
-You knew about that?
-Yeah, for about a year.
-A whole year.
-Look, I should've told you. I'm sorry.
You've been saying that
a lot lately, Sam.
But whatever. You don't wanna tell me,
you don't have to.
-It's fine.
-Dean.
Whatever.
-Hey, babe, when's dinner?
MICHELLE: Forty-five minutes.
-I'm starving.
-Jack.
A delicious, un-microwaved,
non-takeout, homemade meal is coming.
DEAN:
Well, you sure that's him?
-Only Jack Montgomery in town.
-And we're looking for...?
Travis said to keep an eye out
for anything weird.
-Weird?
-Yeah.
All right, well, yeah,
I've seen big weird, little weird...
...weird with crazy on top.
But this guy....
Come on, this guy's boring.
I don't know, Dean.
Travis seemed pretty sure.
MICHELLE:
Honey?
I'd say that qualifies as weird.
Travis.
See, Sam?
Told you we should've hid the beer.
Smart-ass. Get over here.
[TRAVIS LAUGHS]
TRAVIS:
Oh, good to see you.
-You too.
-Good to see you.
SAM:
You too, Travis.
Man, you got tall, kid.
-How long has it been?
-Gotta be 10 years.
You still a...? Oh, what was it?
A mathlete?
-No.
-Yep, sure is.
Been too long, boys.
I mean, look at you. Grown men.
John would've been damn proud of you,
sticking together like this.
Yeah. No, we're as thick as thieves.
Nothing more important than family.
TRAVIS:
Sorry I'm late for the dance.
Thanks for helping out an old man.
I'm a little short-handed.
-So you track down Montgomery?
SAM: Yeah, we found him at his home.
-And?
-He had a hell of a case of the munchies.
Topped off with a burger
that he forgot to cook.
TRAVIS: That's him, all right.
-What's him?
-Boys, we got a Rougarou on our hands.
-A Rougarou?
-Is that made-up? That sounds made-up.
-They're mean, nasty little suckers.
Rotted teeth, wormy skin, the works.
Well, that ain't this guy.
He was wearing a cell phone on his belt.
He'll turn ugly soon enough.
They start out human
for all intents and purposes.
They go through
some kind of metamorphosis?
TRAVIS:
Yep, like a maggot turning into a blowfly.
[SNIFFING]
Ow!
But most of all, they're hungry.
-Hungry for what?
-At first, for everything.
But then for long pig.
-Long pig?
-He means human flesh.
And that is my word of the day.
Hunger grows in
until they can't fight it.
Until they gotta take themselves
a big, juicy chomp, and then it happens.
-What happens?
-They transform completely, and fast.
-I think I need stitches.
-I gotta go.
What?
-I gotta get out of here.
-Where are you going?
Jack?
One bite's all it takes.
Eyes, teeth, skin all turns.
No going back either.
They feed once,
they're a monster forever.
-Jack's headed there on a bullet train.
-Well, how'd you find this guy...
-...if he's a walking, talking human?
-It runs in his family.
-You mean--?
-Killed his daddy back in '78.
Son of a bitch mangled eight bodies
before I put him down.
Guy used to be a dentist.
Cadillac. Trophy wife.
Little did I know,
pregnant trophy wife.
She put the boy up for adoption.
By the time I found out,
he was long gone, lost in the system.
You mean to tell me
you couldn't find someone?
I'm not sure I wanted to.
The idea of hunting down some poor kid.
I don't think I'd had the heart.
No. I wanted to wait.
Make damn sure I had the right man.
Apparently I do.
One more, please.
Can I get some more peanuts?
MAN:
Come on. What are you drinking?
-It's my treat.
WOMAN: No, thank you.
Well, don't be like that.
Have a drink with me.
-I'm waiting for someone.
-Okay, well, where is he?
Hey, douche bag.
She doesn't wanna talk to you.
I'm sorry, I didn't hear you.
I said...
...she doesn't wanna talk to you...
...you fat, sweaty dick.
Now, leave her alone.
You seriously wanna do this, guy?
You know, I really think I do.
[CRUNCH]
[MAN SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
So fire, huh?
The only way I found
to kill these bastards, deep-fry them.
Well, that's gonna be horrible.
-That what you did to Jack's dad?
-Uh-huh.
-Not wasting any time, are you?
TRAVIS: None to waste.
The guy hulks out, we won't be
finding bodies, just remains.
Well, what if he doesn't hulk out?
I did a little homework. I've been
checking out the lore on Rougarous.
What, my 30 years of experience
not good enough for you?
What? No.
No, I just wanted to be prepared.
-I mean, not that you didn't....
DEAN: Sam loves research.
He does. He keeps it
under his mattress right next to his K-Y.
It's a sickness. It is.
Look, everything you said checked out,
of course.
But I found
a couple of interesting stories...
...about people who have
this Rougarou gene or whatever.
See, they start to turn,
but they never take the final step.
-Really?
-See, if they never eat human flesh...
-...they don't fully transform.
-Go vegan, stay human?
Basically. Or, in this case,
eat a lot of raw meat, just not--
-Long pig.
-Right.
Good on you
for the due diligence, Sam.
But those are fairy tales.
The fact is,
every Rougarou I ever saw or heard of...
...took that bite.
Okay, well,
that doesn't mean that Jack will.
So, what do we do? Sit and hope,
and wait for a body count?
No, we talk to him.
Explain what's happening.
-That way, he can fight it.
-Fight it?
Are you kidding me?
You ever been really hungry?
I mean, haven't-eaten-in-days hungry?
Yeah.
Right, then.
So somebody slaps a big, juicy sirloin
in front of you, you walking away?
That's what we are to him now.
Meat on legs.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure he's a stand-up guy.
But it's pure, base instinct.
Everything in nature's gotta eat.
You think he can stop himself
because he's nice?
I don't know.
We're not gonna kill him...
...unless he does something
to get killed for.
What's up with your brother?
Don't get me started.
Oh, God.
You scared me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to sneak up on you.
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling pissed, Jack.
I had to drive myself to the hospital
last night. I was there until 2.
I'm so sorry.
-What happened?
-I don't know.
I saw your blood, and I got dizzy,
and I just had to get out.
You could've called.
I left you a dozen messages.
I know. My phone died.
I couldn't find a pay phone. I....
It was a mess.
But I am sorry.
And I promise
it won't ever happen again.
And certainly...
...not to a wife as stunning as you.
Better not.
I swear, you know, one little cut....
You know,
blood's never bothered you before.
Well...
...I've changed.
This doesn't get you off the hook,
you know.
No, no. Think diamonds.
Think Kobe-size.
-What has gotten into you?
-I don't know.
Hey, Jack, just slow down.
Jack. Jack, I mean it, stop.
Jack. Ow!
Jack, stop! Stop it! Stop it!
-You son of a bitch.
-I'm sorry.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I don't know.
We're gonna go have a little chat
with this guy, which, you know...
...I'm down.
I just wanna make sure, if push comes,
you're gonna shove.
-Meaning?
-Odds are...
...we're gonna have to burn
this guy alive.
This guy has a name and a wife.
Yeah, who we're probably gonna make
a widow, okay? You heard Travis.
-He's gonna turn. They always turn.
-Maybe he won't.
-Maybe he can fight it off.
-Maybe he can't. That's all I'm saying.
-We'll just have to see, then, okay?
-See, this is what I mean, Sam.
You sure your emotions
aren't getting in the way here?
What are you talking about?
You know, nice dude,
but he's got something evil inside him.
Something in his blood.
Maybe you can relate.
Stop the car.
-What?
-Stop the car, or I will.
Wanna know why I've been lying to you?
Because of crap like this.
-Like what?
-The way you talk to me.
The way you look at me
like I'm a freak.
-I do not.
-Even worse, like I'm an idiot.
Like I don't know the difference
between right and wrong.
What?
Do you know the difference?
You've been strolling a dark road.
You have no idea
what I'm going through. None.
-Then enlighten me!
-I've got demon blood in me, Dean.
This disease
pumping through my veins...
...and I can't ever rip it out
or scrub it clean.
I'm a whole new level of freak.
And I'm just trying to take this curse...
...and make something good out of it.
Because I have to.
Let's just go talk to the guy.
I mean, Jack.
Okay?
Jack Montgomery?
I'm Sam Winchester.
This is my brother, Dean.
We need to talk.
About?
About you.
About how you're changing.
Excuse me?
You're probably feeling your bones
move under your skin.
Your appetite's reaching, you know,
Hungry, Hungry Hippo levels.
How am I doing so far?
Who the hell are you guys?
We're people who know something
about something.
We're people who can help.
Please just hear us out.
-A what?
DEAN: A Rougarou.
Sounds made-up, I know,
but believe me, it's not.
All right, I've noticed certain things.
I mean, some strange things.
But I just-- I don't know.
I'm sick or something.
Your father was one of these things.
Your real father.
He passed it on to you.
No. Are you guys listening to yourselves?
You sound like--
Let's skip the whole "you guys sound
crazy," shall we? You're hungry, Jack.
You're only gonna get hungrier.
-Hungrier for...?
-Long pig.
A little "Manburger Helper"
may have crossed your mind already.
-No.
-It doesn't have to be like this, Jack.
-You can fight it off. Others have.
-No.
We're not gonna lie.
It's not gonna be easy.
You're gonna feel like an alcoholic
swimming in whiskey.
But I'm telling you, you gotta say no.
-Or--
-Or what?
SAM:
You feed once, and it's all over.
And then we'll have to stop you.
Stop me?
My dad, did somebody stop him?
Yes.
Get off my property right now. I see
you guys again, I'm calling the cops.
Jack, your wife, everybody you know,
they're in danger.
Now!
Good talk.
MICHELLE: Jack, I don't know where you
are, but you're scaring me. Come home.
We need to talk. Please?
[BEEP]
Damn it, Jack, no.
Come on.
No.
WOMAN:
Ah!
-Wait! We're here to save you, I guess.
-I'm calling the police.
-We should go.
-Yeah.
Michelle, I'm home.
Hey, babe?
Are you here?
[MUMBLING]
Michelle.
Okay, we're gonna stay calm.
We're gonna give this man
whatever he wants.
Okay? Anything.
Just take it and go, please.
I'm sorry about this, Jack.
I truly am.
It's not the way that I wanted it to go.
JACK:
Who are you?
You already met some friends of mine.
Two brothers.
They said that if I--
Look, I haven't hurt anybody.
Not yet, but you would've.
They always do.
-I'm doing you a favor, son.
-Jack, what's he talking about?
Tell her, Jack.
Tell her the truth.
She deserves to know.
Just let her go.
She's not a part of this.
A part of what?
Jack?
I really do apologize,
but she is part of it.
What?
TRAVIS:
Michelle.
Tell him what you told me
when I got here.
Michelle?
I said, "Don't hurt me...
...because I'm pregnant."
-Just hold on a minute.
-Now you see the mess we're in?
I can't make this mistake
all over again.
I won't be around in 30 years.
This has got to end now.
I know you don't believe me, but I'd
give anything not to have to do this.
No. You don't-- No. No.
-Oh, God. Please, no!
-You don't have to do this.
If you wanna kill me, kill me,
but not my wife. Okay?
-I'm begging you.
-Ain't got no choice.
My condolences.
No.
Jack.
[GRUNTING]
Jack!
Ah!
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
-Stay away from me!
-Michelle.
-I guess now we know where Travis is.
-That stupid son of a bitch.
Oh, God.
Think that's Travis?
What's left of him.
Guess you were right about Jack.
Dean!
Dean?
Dean can't come to the phone
right now.
-Jack! If you hurt him, I swear to God--
-Calm down!
Your brother's alive.
But not if you don't calm down.
All right. Jack, listen.
Open the door.
We can figure this out, okay?
Oh, we'll have ourselves
a little brainstorming session.
-Jack, please.
-I don't think so.
-After what you did?
-What? What are you talking about?
You send your friend here.
He tried to burn my wife alive.
What? Why?
He didn't say.
I guess psychopaths
don't know how to explain themselves.
Listen to me. You gotta believe me.
My brother and I,
we never would've hurt her, okay?
-Oh, God, I'm so hungry.
-Jack, don't do this.
I can't ever see my family again.
You two.
-Your friend. You made me into this!
-No one's making you kill us.
Listen to me. You got this dark pit
inside you, I know.
Believe me, I know.
But that doesn't mean
you have to fall into it.
You don't have to be a monster.
-Have you seen me lately?
-It doesn't matter what you are.
It only matters what you do.
It's your choice.
[GRUNTING]
Jack!
[JACK SCREAMING]
You did the right thing, you know.
That guy was a monster.
There was no going back.
I wanna tell you I'm sorry.
I've been kind of hard on you lately.
Don't worry about it, Dean.
It's just that your psychic thing,
it scares the crap out of me.
Look, if it's all the same,
I'd really rather not talk about it.
What? You don't wanna talk? You?
There's nothing more to say.
I can't keep explaining myself to you.
I can't make you understand.
Well, why don't you try?
I can't, because this thing,
this blood...
...it's not in you the way it's in me.
It's just something I gotta deal with.
Not alone.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
These powers...
...it's playing with fire.
I'm done with them.
I'm done with everything.
Really?
Well, that's a relief. Thank you.
Don't thank me.
I'm not doing it for you.
Or for the angels, or for anybody.
This is my choice.
[ENGLISH SDH]