SAM: So this is Ruby, huh?
DEAN: She's a demon, Sam.
RUBY: Her name is Lilith.
She doesn't like you very much.
-How long did they give you?
-One year.
[GUNSHOT]
Did you know about Dean's deal?
-That Lilith holds the contract?
-Yes.
You got two months.
You're not gonna go to hell.
It's not Ruby. It's Lilith.
-Where's Ruby?
-I sent her far, far away.
Sic him, boy.
[BARKING]
DEAN:
No!
[SCREAMS]
Somebody help me.
Sam!
[GASPING]
[VOICES HOWLING]
[COUGHING]
[LIGHTER CLICKING]
[PANTING]
[IN RASPY VOICE]
Help.
[COUGHS, GASPS]
[CREAKING]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS, PANTS]
Aah!
[PANTING]
[KNOCKING]
Hello?
[BOTTLE CAP CLATTERS]
[EXHALES]
[PANTING]
September.
[SCREAMS]
[GASPS]
[STATIC HISSING]
[COWBOY TUNE PLAYS OVER RADIO]
[HIGH-PITCHED HUM]
[GRUNTS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[WIND HOWLING]
[PHONE BEEPS]
WOMAN [ON RECORDING]:
We're sorry...
...you have reached a number
that has been disconnected.
[LINE RINGING]
BOBBY:
Yeah?
-Bobby?
-Yeah?
-It's me.
-Who's me?
Dean.
[LINE DISCONNECTS,
DIAL TONE HUMS]
[LINE RINGING]
BOBBY: Who is this?
-Bobby, listen to me.
This ain't funny.
Call again and I'll kill you.
[LINE DISCONNECTS,
DIAL TONE HUMS]
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Come on, come on, come on.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
[CHUCKLES]
Surprise.
I-- I don't....
Yeah, me neither.
But here I am.
[GRUNTING]
Bobby.
-Bobby, it's me.
-My ass.
Wait. Your name
is Robert Stephen Singer.
You became a hunter
after your wife got possessed.
You're about the closest thing
I have to a father.
Bobby, it's me.
[CHAIR SLIDES]
Heh.
[GRUNTING]
-I am not a Shapeshifter.
-Then you're a revenant.
All right, if I was either,
could I do this with a silver knife?
[DEAN GRUNTS]
Dean?
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
[CRIES]
-It's good to see you, boy.
-Yeah, you too.
But how did you bust out?
I don't know.
I just....
I just woke up in a pine b--
-I'm not a demon either, you know.
-Sorry.
Can't be too careful.
That don't make a lick of sense.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're preaching to the choir.
Dean, your chest was ribbons.
Your insides were slop.
And you've been buried four months.
If you could slip out of hell
and back in your meat--
I know, I should look
like a "Thriller" video reject.
-What do you remember?
-Not much.
I remember
I was a Hellhound's chew toy.
And then lights out.
Then I come to 6 feet under.
That was it.
Sam's number's not working.
He's not...?
Oh, he's alive, as far as I know.
Good.
-What do you mean, as far as you know?
-I haven't talked to him for months.
-You just let him go off by himself?
-He was dead set on it.
-You should have been looking after him.
-I tried.
These last months haven't been easy,
you know.
For him or me. We had to bury you.
Why did you bury me, anyway?
I wanted you salted and burned.
Usual drill, but Sam wouldn't have it.
-I'm glad he won that one.
-He said you'd need a body...
...when he got you back home
somehow.
-That's about all he said.
-What do you mean?
He was quiet. Real quiet.
Then he just took off.
Wouldn't return my calls.
I tried to find him,
but he don't wanna be found.
Damn it, Sammy.
-What?
-Oh, he got me home okay.
But whatever he did, it is bad mojo.
-What makes you sure?
-You should've seen the grave.
It was like a nuke went off.
Then there was this....
This force, this presence,
I don't know.
But it blew past me at a fill-up joint.
And then this.
-What in the hell?
-It was like a demon just yanked me out.
Or rode me out.
-But why?
-To hold up their end of the bargain.
You think Sam made a deal?
That's what I would have done.
[WOMAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY
OVER PHONE]
Yeah, hi, I have a cell phone account
with you guys and I lost my phone.
I was wondering if you could
turn the GPS on for me.
-Yeah, the name's Wedge Antilles.
-The last four digits of your social?
-Social is 2474.
-Thank you, sir, it's active.
Thank you.
How'd you know he'd use that name?
You kidding me?
What don't I know about that kid?
[TYPING]
Hey, Bobby.
What's the deal with the liquor store?
Your parents are out of town?
Like I said...
...last few months
ain't been all that easy.
Right.
[BEEPING]
-Sam's in Pontiac, Illinois.
-Right near where you were planted.
Right where I popped up.
A coincidence, don't you think?
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING INSIDE]
So where is it?
Where's what?
The pizza that takes two guys
to deliver?
I think we got the wrong room.
Hey, Sammy.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
-Who are you?
-Like you didn't do this?
-Do what?
BOBBY: It's him. It's him, Sam.
I've been through this already.
It's really him.
What...?
I know.
I look fantastic, huh?
[SNIFFLING]
So are you two, like, together?
What? No. No.
He's my brother.
O-oh--
Got it, I guess.
Look, I should probably go.
Yeah, yeah.
That's probably a good idea. Sorry.
-So call me.
-Yeah, yeah. Sure thing, Kathy.
Chrissy.
Right.
So tell me, what'd it cost?
The girl? Heh. I don't pay, Dean.
That's not funny, Sam.
To bring me back.
What'd it cost?
Was it just your soul,
or something worse?
-You think I made a deal?
-That's what we think.
Well, I didn't.
Don't lie to me.
I'm not lying.
So, what, now I'm off the hook
and you're on, is that it?
You're some demon's bitch boy?
I didn't wanna be saved like this.
Look, Dean,
I wish I had done it, all right?
There's no other way
this could have gone. Tell the truth.
I tried everything. That's the truth.
Opening the Devil's Gate...
...hell, I tried to bargain, Dean,
but no demon would deal, all right?
You were rotting in hell for months.
For months, and I couldn't stop it.
So I'm sorry. It wasn't me, all right?
Dean, I'm sorry.
It's okay, Sammy.
You don't have to apologize.
I believe you.
Don't get me wrong, I am gladdened
that Sam's soul remains intact...
...but it does raise a sticky question.
If he didn't pull me out then what did?
So, what were you doing here if you
weren't digging me out of my grave?
Well, once I figured out
I couldn't save you...
...I started hunting down Lilith,
trying to get some payback.
BOBBY:
All by yourself?
Who do you think you are,
your old man?
Uh....
Yeah, I'm sorry, Bobby. I should
have called. I was pretty messed up.
Oh, yeah. I really feel your pain.
[SAM CHUCKLES]
Anyways, I was tracking these demons
out in Tennessee...
...and out of nowhere,
they took a left, booked up here.
-When?
-Yesterday morning.
When I busted out.
You think these demons are here
because of you?
But why?
I don't know. But some badass demon
drags me out, now this?
-It's gotta be connected somehow.
-How you feeling, anyway?
I'm a little hungry.
No, I mean, do you feel like yourself?
-Anything strange or different?
-Or demonic?
Bobby, how many times
I have to prove I'm me?
Listen, no demon's letting you loose
out of the goodness of their hearts.
They gotta have
something nasty planned.
-I feel fine.
SAM: We don't know
...what they're planning.
We got a pile of questions...
...and no shovel. We need help.
I know a psychic
a few hours from here.
Something this big,
maybe she's heard the other side talking.
-Hell, yeah, it's worth a shot.
-I'll be right back.
Hey, wait.
You probably want this back.
Thanks.
Yeah, don't mention it.
Hey, Dean, what was it like?
What, hell?
I don't know.
I must have blacked it out.
I don't remember a damn thing.
-Thank God for that.
-Yeah.
[SNIFFS]
[VOICES HOWLING]
She's about four hours
down the interstate.
Try to keep up.
I assume you'll wanna drive.
[LAUGHS]
I almost forgot.
Hey, sweetheart, you miss me?
Oh.
-What the hell is that?
-That's an iPod jack.
You were supposed to take care of her...
-...not douche her up.
-Heh.
Dean, I thought it was my car.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[JASON MANNS' "VISION" PLAYS]
Really?
[MUSIC STOPS]
DEAN: There's still one thing
that's bothering me.
Yeah?
Yeah, the night that I bit it. Or got bit.
How'd you make it out?
Lilith was gonna kill you.
-She tried. She couldn't.
-What do you mean, she couldn't?
She fired this, like,
burning light at me.
And...
...it didn't leave a scratch.
Like I was immune or something.
-Immune?
-Yeah. Heh.
I don't know who was more surprised,
her or me.
[SIGHS]
She left pretty fast after that.
Huh.
-What about Ruby? Where's she?
-Dead, or in hell.
You've been using
your freaky ESP stuff?
-No.
-You sure about that?
I mean, now that you've got immunity,
whatever the hell that is...
...just wondering
what other weirdo crap you got.
Nothing, Dean.
You didn't want me to go
down that road, so I didn't go.
It was practically your dying wish.
Yeah, well, let's keep it that way.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[BOTH LAUGH]
-Bobby.
-Pam.
[BOTH GRUNT, LAUGH]
BOBBY:
You're a sight for sore eyes.
So are these the boys?
Sam, Dean, Pamela Barnes.
Best damn psychic in the state.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Mm-mm-mm.
[CHUCKLES]
Dean Winchester.
Out of the fire
and back in the frying pan, huh?
Makes you a rare individual.
If you say so.
Come on in.
[CHUCKLES]
So you hear anything?
Well, I Ouija'd my way
through a dozen spirits.
No one seems to know
who broke your boy out or why.
-So, what's next?
-A s?ance, I think.
See if we can see who did the deed.
You're not gonna summon
the damn thing here?
No. I just wanna
get a sneak peek at it.
Like a crystal ball without the crystal.
I'm game.
[SIGHS]
PAMELA:
Let's see.
Who's Jesse?
[PAMELA LAUGHS]
-Well, it wasn't forever.
-His loss.
Heh.
Might be your gain.
-Dude, I'm so in.
-Yeah, she's gonna eat you alive.
Hey, I just got out of jail. Bring it.
-Ha.
-You're invited too, grumpy.
You are not invited.
Right.
Take each other's hands.
And I need to touch something
our mystery monster touched.
Whoa!
-Well, he didn't touch me there.
-Ha-ha-ha. My mistake.
[DEAN CLEARS THROAT]
PAMELA:
Okay.
[CHANTING]
I invoke, conjure and command you...
...appear unto me before this circle.
I invoke, conjure and command you,
appear unto me before this circle.
I invoke, conjure and command you--
Castiel?
No. Sorry, Castiel, I don't scare easy.
Its name. It's whispering to me,
warning me to turn back.
I conjure and command you,
show me your face.
-I conjure and command you--
-Maybe we should stop.
I almost got it.
I command you, show me your face.
Show me your face now.
[SCREAMING]
BOBBY:
Call 911.
[GASPING]
[SOBBING]
I can't see. I can't see.
-Oh, God.
SAM: We have an injured woman.
PAMELA:
Oh, God.
-Be up in a jiff.
-Yeah, you bet.
-What'd Bobby say?
-Uh, Pam's stable and out of ICU.
And blind because of us.
Still no clue what we're dealing with.
-That's not entirely true.
-No?
We got a name. Castiel or whatever.
With the right mumbo jumbo,
we can summon him.
You're crazy. Absolutely not.
We'll work him over.
After what he did?
Pam took a peek at him
and her eyes burned out of her skull.
-You wanna have a face-to-face?
-Got a better idea?
Yeah, as a matter of fact I do.
I followed some demons to town, right?
-Okay.
-So we go find them.
Someone's gotta know something
about something.
Thanks.
[SIGHS]
You angling for a tip?
I'm sorry,
I thought you were looking for us.
Dean.
To hell and back.
Aren't you a lucky duck?
-That's me.
-So you get to just stroll out of the pit?
Tell me, what makes you so special?
I like to think
it's because of my perky nipples.
I don't know.
Wasn't my doing.
I don't know who pulled me out.
Right. You don't.
-No, I don't.
-Lying's a sin, you know.
I'm not lying.
I'd like to find out, so if you
wouldn't mind enlightening me, Flo....
Mind your tone with me, boy.
I'll drag you back to hell myself.
No, you won't.
-No?
-No.
If you were,
you'd have done it already.
Fact is, you don't know
who cut me loose.
You're just as spooked as we are.
And you're looking for answers.
Well, maybe it was
some turbo-charged spirit.
Hmm? Or Godzilla.
Or some big, bad, boss demon.
But I'm guessing at your pay grade,
that they don't tell you squat.
Because whoever it was,
they want me out.
And they're a lot stronger than you.
So go ahead, send me back.
Don't crawl to me
when they show up on your doorstep...
...with Vaseline and a fire hose.
I'm gonna reach down your throat
and rip out your lungs.
That's what I thought.
Let's go, Sam.
For the pie.
[LOW GROWL]
[DOOR OPENS]
-Holy crap, that was close.
-We're not gonna leave them, are we?
There's three of them, probably more.
We only got one knife.
I've been killing more demons
than that lately.
Not anymore.
The smarter brother's back in town.
Dean, we gotta take them.
-They are dangerous.
-They're scared.
Scared of whatever had the juice
to yank me out.
We're dealing with a bad mofo here.
One job at a time.
[LOCK CLICKS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[STATIC HISSING,
VOICES OVER RADIO COME AND GO]
[HIGH-PITCHED HUM]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
BOBBY:
Dean. Dean!
How you doing, kid?
Aside from the church bells
ringing in my head...
...peachy.
[DIALING]
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
-Hey.
-What are you doing?
-Couldn't sleep. Went to get a burger.
-In my car?
Force of habit. What you doing up?
Well, Bobby's back.
We're going to grab a beer.
All right, well, spill some for me, huh?
Done. I'll catch you later.
-Why the hell didn't you tell him?
-He'd just try to stop us.
-From what?
-Summoning this thing.
-It's time we face it head on.
-You can't be serious.
As a heart attack.
-It's high noon, baby.
-We don't know what it is.
It could be a demon,
it could be anything.
So then we gotta be ready
for anything.
We got the bigtime magic knife,
you got an arsenal in the trunk.
This is a bad idea.
Couldn't agree more,
but what other choice do we have?
We could choose life.
Whatever this is, whatever it wants,
it's after me.
That much we know, right?
Well, I got no place to hide.
I can either get caught with my pants
down again, or we can make our stand.
Dean, we could use Sam for this.
No, he's better off where he is.
[MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
[SIGHS]
[SAM GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
Your eyes.
I could still smell your soul
a mile away.
It was here. You saw it.
-I saw it.
-What was it?
[SOBS]
It's the end.
We're dead. We're all dead.
What did you see?
Go to hell.
Funny, I was gonna say
the same thing to you.
[GASPING]
[GAGGING]
[EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
Damn it.
[DOOR OPENS]
Getting pretty slick there, Sam.
Better all the time.
What the hell's going on
around here, Ruby?
I wish I knew.
We were thinking
some high-level demon pulled Dean out.
No way.
Sam, human souls
don't just walk out of hell...
...and back into their bodies easy.
The sky bleeds, the ground quakes.
It's cosmic.
No demon can swing that.
Not Lilith.
-Not anybody.
-Then what can?
Nothing I've ever seen before.
It's a hell of an art project
you got going there.
Traps and talismans
from every faith on the globe.
How you doing?
Stakes, iron, silver, salt, the knife.
We're set to catch
anything I've ever heard of.
This is still a bad idea.
Yeah, Bobby,
I heard you the first ten times.
What do you say
we ring the dinner bell?
[SPEAKS IN LATIN]
So, million-dollar question:
You gonna tell Dean
about what we're doing?
Yeah, I just gotta figure out
the right way to say it.
-Look, I just need time, okay? That's all.
-He's gonna find out.
-If not from you, he's gonna be pissed.
-He's gonna be pissed anyway.
He's so hard-headed about this psychic
stuff, he'll just try and stop me.
Maybe I'll just take a step back
for a while.
I'm not exactly
in your brother's fan club.
But he is your brother.
And I'm not gonna
come between you.
I don't know if what I'm doing is right.
Hell, I don't even know if I trust you.
-Thanks.
-What I do know is...
...I'm saving people...
...and stopping demons.
And that feels good.
I wanna keep going.
[BOBBY WHISTLING]
You sure you did the ritual right?
Sorry. Touchy, touchy.
[WIND WHISTLING, LOUD THUDDING]
Wishful thinking,
but maybe it's just the wind.
Who are you?
I'm the one who gripped you tight
and raised you from perdition.
Yeah, thanks for that.
[KNIFE CLATTERS]
[YELLS]
We need to talk, Dean.
Alone.
-Your friend's alive.
-Who are you?
Castiel.
Yeah, I figured that much.
I mean, what are you?
I'm an angel of the Lord.
Get the hell out of here.
There's no such thing.
This is your problem, Dean.
You have no faith.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
Some angel you are.
You burned out
that poor woman's eyes.
I warned her
not to spy on my true form.
It can be overwhelming to humans.
And so can my real voice,
but you already knew that.
You mean the gas station
and the motel?
That was you talking?
Buddy, next time, lower the volume.
That was my mistake.
Certain people, special people,
can perceive my true visage.
I thought you would be one of them.
I was wrong.
And what visage are you in now, huh?
What, holy tax accountant?
This? This is a vessel.
You're possessing some poor bastard?
He's a devout man.
He actually prayed for this.
Look, pal, I'm not buying what
you're selling. So who are you, really?
I told you.
Right.
And why would an angel
rescue me from hell?
Good things do happen, Dean.
Not in my experience.
What's the matter?
You don't think
you deserve to be saved?
Why'd you do it?
Because God commanded it.
Because we have work for you.
[ENGLISH SDH]