Lilith is trying to break the 66 seals
to free Lucifer from hell.
-Who are you?
-Castiel. I'm an angel of the Lord.
PAMELA: Anna, you all right?
-I remember now who I am.
I'm an angel.
[SCREAMS]
Aah!
ALASTAIR: You can't run, Dean.
DEAN: Alastair.
CASTIEL:
This is Uriel. A specialist.
Pamela Barnes,
best damn psychic in the state.
[GRUNTING]
-Pamela.
DEAN: Uhn!
They took me off the rack
and I tortured souls and I liked it.
No matter how many people I save,
I can't fill this hole.
It's not the psychic
I got a problem with.
Yeah, I know what you got
a problem with, but tough.
-It's the only way.
-No.
PAMELA: I know what you did
to that demon, Sam.
[COUGHING THEN GASPING]
Pamela.
[CAR ALARMS BLARING
AND HORNS HONKING]
[NOISE STOPS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Goodbye, sister.
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
[INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
What the hell?
Ruby will meet us outside Cheyenne.
-She's been tracking some leads.
-Mm.
She's not on your Christmas list
but if she can help us get to Lilith--
Hey, man, work with Ruby, don't.
I don't really give a rat's ass.
-What's your problem?
-Pamela didn't want anything with this.
We dragged her back into it, Sam.
-She knew what was at stake.
-Oh, yeah. Saving the world.
And we're doing
such a damn good job of it.
-Dean--
-I'm tired of burying friends, Sam.
Look, we catch a fresh trail--
And we follow it. I know.
Like I said, I'm just getting tired.
Well, get angry.
Home, crappy home.
Winchester and Winchester.
-Oh, come on.
-You are needed.
Needed? We just got back from needed.
Now, you mind your tone with me.
No, you mind your damn tone with us.
We just got back from Pamela's funeral.
Pamela. You know, psychic Pamela?
You remember her.
Cass, you remember her.
You burned her eyes out.
Remember that? Good times.
Yeah, then she died saving
one of your precious seals.
So maybe you can stop pushing us around
like chess pieces for five freaking minutes.
We raised you out of hell
for our purposes.
Yeah, what were those, again?
What exactly do you want from me?
-Start with gratitude.
-Oh.
Dean, we know this is difficult
to understand.
And we...
...don't care.
Now, seven angels have been murdered.
All of them from our garrison.
The last one was killed tonight.
Demons?
-How they doing it?
-We don't know.
I'm sorry, but what do you want us
to do about it?
A demon with the juice to ice angels
has to be out of our league.
We can handle the demons,
thank you very much.
Once we find whoever it is.
So you need our help hunting a demon?
Not quite.
We have Alastair.
Great. He should name your trigger man.
But he won't talk.
Alastair's will is very strong.
We've arrived at an impasse.
He's, like, a black belt in torture.
I mean, you are out of your league.
That's why we've come to his student.
You happen to be the most qualified
interrogator we've got.
Dean, you are our best hope.
No. No way.
You can't ask me to do this, Cass.
Not this.
Who said anything about asking?
[WHOOSH]
Damn it!
This devil's trap is old Enochian.
He's bound completely.
Fascinating.
-Where's the door?
-Where are you going?
Hitch back to Cheyenne,
thank you very much.
-Angels are dying, boy.
-Everybody's dying these days.
I get it. You're all-powerful,
you can make me do whatever you want.
But you can't make me do this.
This is too much to ask, I know.
But we have to ask it.
I wanna talk to Cass alone.
I think I'll go seek revelation.
We might have some further orders.
Well, get some donuts while you're out.
[CHUCKLES]
This one just won't quit, will he?
I think I'm starting to like you, boy.
[WHOOSH]
You guys don't walk enough.
You're gonna get flabby.
I'm starting to think junkless
has a better sense of humor than you.
Uriel's the funniest angel in the garrison.
Ask anyone.
What's going on, Cass?
Since when does Uriel
put a leash on you?
My superiors have begun to question
my sympathies.
-Your sympathies?
-I was getting too close...
...to the humans in my charge. You.
They feel I've begun to express emotions.
The doorways to doubt.
This can impair my judgment.
Well, tell Uriel, or whoever...
...you do not want me doing this,
trust me.
Want it? No.
But I have been told we need it.
You ask me to open that door
and walk through it...
...you will not like what walks back out.
For what it's worth...
...I would give anything
not to have you do this.
[THUD]
[PANTING]
[SINGING "CHEEK TO CHEEK"]
[LAUGHING]
I'm sorry.
This is a very serious...
...very emotional situation for you.
I shouldn't laugh, it's just that--
I mean, are they serious?
They sent you to torture me?
You got one chance. One.
Tell me who's killing the angels.
I want a name.
You think I'll see all your scary toys
and spill my guts?
Oh, you'll spill your guts,
one way or another.
I just didn't wanna ruin my shoes.
Oh, yeah.
Now answer the question.
Or what? You'll work me over?
But then, maybe you don't want to.
[IN SINGSONG VOICE]
Maybe you're a-scared to.
-I'm here, aren't I?
-Not entirely.
You left part of yourself back in the pit.
Let's see if we can get the two of you
back together again, shall we?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
-You're gonna be disappointed.
-You have not disappointed me so far.
Come on.
You gotta want a little payback
for everything I did to you.
For all the pokes and prods.
Hmm?
No?
Um....
How about for all the things
I did to your daddy?
I can still smell them.
Seriously, Sam. I'm not exactly dying
to tangle with angels again.
I need you to find out
where they took Dean.
Not sure I see the problem.
You know they have Alastair strung up
six ways from Sunday.
Dean cuts himself a slice...
...Al's a quivering heap,
the good guys get the goods.
-What's wrong with that?
-He can't do it.
I get it. You don't want him going all
torture master again.
No. I mean, he can't do it.
He can't get the job done.
Something happened to him downstairs,
Ruby.
He's not what he used to be.
Not strong enough.
And you are?
I will be.
I had your pop on my rack
for close to a century.
You can't stall forever.
John Winchester.
Made a good name for himself.
A hundred years.
After each session, I'd--
I'd make him the same offer
I made you.
I'd put down my blade
if he picked one up.
Just give me the demon's name, Alastair.
But he said nein each and every time.
Oh, damned if I couldn't break him.
Pulled out all the stops, but John...
...he was, well,
made of something unique.
The stuff of heroes.
And then came Dean.
Dean Winchester.
I thought I was up against it again.
But daddy's little girl, he broke.
He broke in 30.
Oh, just not the man your daddy
wanted you to be, huh, Dean?
Now...
...now we're getting somewhere.
Holy water? Come on.
Grasshopper, you're gonna have to get
creative to impress me.
You know something, Alastair?
I could still dream, even in hell.
And over and over and over,
you know what I dreamt?
I dreamt of this moment.
And believe me...
...I got a few ideas.
Let's get started.
[ALASTAIR GROANING]
ALASTAIR:
Oh, man.
[ALASTAIR GROANING]
Let me know if you want some more.
There's plenty left.
Go directly to hell.
Do not pass go, do not collect $200.
[RUBY CHANTING]
Relax. The fire is our friend.
Besides, the only part of the map
we need...
...is the "Where's Dean?" part.
Out.
There. Your brother's there.
It's a good thing angels aren't concerned
with hiding their dirty business.
Not used to being spied on.
I mean, who'd be stupid enough to try?
Ruby, it's been weeks.
I need it.
You don't seem too happy about it.
You think I wanna do this?
This is the last thing I--
[SIGHS]
But I need to be strong enough.
It's okay.
It's okay, Sammy.
You can have it.
It's okay, Sam.
It's okay.
There's that little pig-poker.
I wondered where it went.
Do you really think this is gonna fix you?
Give you closure? Oh.
That is sad.
That's really sad.
Sad, sad.
[SIZZLING]
[GROANING]
I carved you...
...into a new animal, Dean.
There is no going back.
Maybe you're right.
But now it's my turn to carve.
No!
[GROANING]
[CREAKING]
-Anna.
-Hello, Castiel.
Your human body....
[ALASTAIR CONTINUES GROANING]
It was destroyed. I know.
But...
...I guess I'm sentimental.
Called in some old favors and....
You shouldn't be here.
We still have orders to kill you.
Somehow, I don't think you'll try.
Where's Uriel?
He went to receive revelation.
Right.
[GROANING]
[GASPING]
[LAUGHS]
Now, it's your professionalism
that I respect.
Why are you letting Dean do this?
He's doing God's work.
Torturing? That's God's work?
Stop him, Cass, please.
Before you ruin
the one real weapon you have.
Who are we to question the will of God?
Unless this isn't his will.
-Then where do the orders come from?
-I don't know.
One of our superiors, maybe, but not him.
[SCREAMING AND GURGLING]
Who's murdering the angels?
[GASPS]
The Father you love,
you think he wants this?
You think he'd ask this of you?
You think this is righteous?
What you're feeling...
...it's called doubt.
[ALASTAIR GROANING]
These orders are wrong and you know it.
But you can do the right thing.
You're afraid, Cass. I was too.
But, together, we can st--
Together?
I am nothing like you.
You fell.
Go.
Cass....
[WHOOSH]
You just not getting deep enough.
Well, you lack the resources.
Reality is just, I don't know,
too concrete up here.
Honestly, Dean...
...you have no idea
how bad it really was...
...and what you really did for us.
[BANGS CONTAINER ON TABLE]
-Shut up.
-The whole bloody thing, Dean.
The reason Lilith wanted you there
in the first place.
Well, then I'll just make you shut up.
Lilith really--
[SCREAMS]
[GURGLING]
[WHEEZING AND COUGHING]
Something caught in my throat.
[COUGHS]
I think it's my throat.
Well, strap in
because I'm just starting to have fun.
You know, it was supposed to be
your father.
He was supposed to bring it on.
But, in the end, it was you.
Bring what on?
Oh, every night, the same offer,
remember?
Same as your father.
And finally you said, "Sign me up."
Oh, the first time
you picked up my razor...
...the first time you sliced into...
...that weeping bitch...
...that was the first seal.
You're lying.
And it is written
that the first seal shall be broken...
...when a righteous man
sheds blood in hell.
As he breaks, so shall it break.
We had to break the first seal
before any others.
Only way to get the dominoes
to fall, right?
Topple the one at the front of the line.
Hmm.
When we win...
...when we bring on the apocalypse
and burn this Earth down...
...we'll owe it all to you...
...Dean Winchester.
Believe me, son...
...I wouldn't lie about this.
It's kind of a...
...religious sort of thing with me.
No...
...I don't think you are lying.
But even if the demons do win...
...you won't be there to see it.
You should talk to your plumber
about the pipes.
[GROANING]
You got a lot to learn, boy.
So I'll see you back in class...
...bright and early, Monday morning.
[CHOKING]
[GRUNTING]
Well, almost.
Looks like God is on my side today.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[ALASTAIR YELLS]
Well...
...like roaches, you celestials.
Now, I really wish
I knew how to kill you.
But all I can do
is send you back to heaven.
[CHANTING IN LATIN]
[GRUNTS]
Oh....
Stupid pet tricks.
Who's murdering the angels?
How are they doing it?
You think I'm gonna tell you?
Yeah, I do.
[GASPS]
How are the demons killing angels?
I don't know.
Right.
It's not us.
We're not doing it.
I don't believe you.
[ALASTAIR GRUNTING]
Lilith is not behind this.
She wouldn't kill seven angels.
Oh, she'd kill a hundred...
...a thousand.
[ALASTAIR GROANING]
[SIGHS]
Oh, go ahead.
Send me back...
...if you can.
I'm stronger than that now.
Now I can kill.
[ALASTAIR GROANING LOUDLY]
[SCREAMS]
[EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PA]
-Sam--
-Get in there and heal him.
-Miracle, now.
-I can't.
-You and Uriel put him in there--
-No.
--because you can't keep
a simple devil's trap.
I don't know what happened. That trap...
-...it shouldn't have broken. I am sorry.
-This whole thing was pointless.
You understand that?
The demons aren't doing the hits.
Something else is killing your soldiers.
-Perhaps Alastair was lying.
-No, he wasn't.
Castiel...
...I received revelation from our superiors.
Our brothers and sisters are dying
and they...
...they want us to stop hunting
the demon responsible.
[SIGHS]
Something is wrong up there.
I mean, can you feel it?
The murders, maybe they aren't demonic.
Sam Winchester said
the demons had nothing to do with it.
If not the demons, what could it be?
The will of heaven.
We are failing, Uriel. We are losing the war.
Perhaps the garrison is being punished.
-You think our Father would--?
-Maybe our Father...
...isn't giving the orders anymore.
Maybe there is something wrong.
Well, I won't wait to be gutted.
[WHOOSH]
CASTIEL:
Anna.
Anna, please.
[CRACKLING]
Decided to kill me after all?
I'm alone.
What do you want from me, Castiel?
I'm considering disobedience.
-Good.
-No, it isn't.
For the first time, I feel....
It gets worse.
Choosing your own course of action...
...is confusing...
...terrifying.
That's right.
You're too good for my help.
I'm just trash. A walking blasphemy.
Anna.
I don't know what to do.
Please tell me what to do.
Like the old days?
No.
I'm sorry.
It's time to think for yourself.
[WHOOSH]
[WATER DRIPPING]
[CREAKING]
URIEL:
You called?
What do you say, Castiel?
Will you join me?
Will you fight with me?
Strange.
Strange how a leaky pipe...
...can undo the work of angels...
...when we ourselves are supposed to be
the agents of fate.
Alastair was much more powerful
than we had imagined.
No.
No demon can overpower that trap.
I made it myself.
We've been friends for a long time, Uriel.
Fought by each other's sides,
served together, away from home...
...for what seems like forever.
We're brothers, Uriel.
Pay me that respect. Tell me the truth.
The truth is, the only thing
that can kill an angel...
...is another angel.
-You.
-I'm afraid so.
And you broke the devil's trap...
...set Alastair on Dean.
Alastair should never
have been taken alive.
Really inconvenient, Cass.
Yes, I did turn the screw a little.
Alastair should have killed Dean
and escaped...
...and you should have gone on
happily scapegoating the demons.
For the murders of our kin?
Not murders, Castiel.
No. My work is conversion.
How long have we waited here?
How long have we played this game
by rules that make no sense?
-It is our Father's world, Uriel.
-Our Father?
He stopped being that, if he ever was,
the moment he created them.
Humanity, his favorites.
This whining, puking larva.
Are you trying to convert me?
I wanted you to join me. And I still do.
-With you, we can be powerful enough to--
-To...?
To raise our brother.
-Lucifer.
-You do remember him?
How strong he was?
How beautiful?
And he didn't bow to humanity.
He was punished for defending us.
Now, if you wanna believe in something,
Cass, believe in him.
-Lucifer is not God.
-God isn't God anymore.
He doesn't care what we do.
I am proof of that.
But this?
What were you gonna do, Uriel?
Were you gonna kill the whole garrison?
I only killed the ones who said no.
Others have joined me, Cass.
Now, please, brother, don't fight me.
Help me.
Help me spread the word.
Help me bring on the apocalypse.
All you have to do...
...is be unafraid.
For the first time in a long time...
...I am.
[GRUNTING]
You can't win, Uriel.
I still serve God.
You haven't even met the man.
There is no will.
No wrath.
No God.
[GRUNTS]
Maybe or maybe not...
...but there's still me.
Aah.
[SCREAMS]
CASTIEL:
Are you all right?
No thanks to you.
You need to be more careful.
You need to learn how to manage
a damn devil's trap.
That's not what I mean.
Uriel is dead.
-Was it the demons?
-It was disobedience.
He was working against us.
Is it true?
Did I break the first seal?
Did I start all this?
Yes.
When we discovered
Lilith's plan for you...
...we laid siege to hell...
...and we fought our way to get to you
before you--
Jump-started the apocalypse.
And we were too late.
Why didn't you just leave me there, then?
It's not blame that falls on you, Dean...
...it's fate.
The righteous man who begins it...
...is the only one who can finish it.
You have to stop it.
Lucifer?
The apocalypse?
What does that mean?
Hey.
Don't you go disappearing on me,
you son of a bitch.
What does that mean?
-I don't know.
-Bull.
I don't.
Dean, they don't tell me much.
I know...
...our fate rests with you.
[VOICE BREAKING]
Well, then you guys are screwed.
I can't do it, Cass. It's too big.
Alastair was right. I'm not all here.
I'm not strong enough.
Well, I guess I'm not the man
either of our dads wanted me to be.
Find someone else.
It's not me.
[ENGLISH SDH]