Sam, Dean, Pamela Barnes,
best damn psychic in the state.
Don't you recognize me?
But we were so close.
Alastair.
Lilith is trying to break the 66 seals.
Lucifer will bring the Apocalypse.
I don't know when it happened.
The Sam I knew is gone.
The lies, the secrets.
What else aren't you telling me?
You're holding me back.
I'm a better hunter.
Stronger, smarter.
I can take out demons
you're too scared to.
I didn't mean the things I said.
- It was just the siren's spell talking.
- Of course. Me too.
- So we're good?
- Yeah, we're good.
Okay, okay. Now, come on. You tell me.
Now, why kick that field goal?
- Because it's called football.
- No, it's called fantasy football.
Those three points screwed me.
Seriously, you need to get a life.
- Yeah.
- I'm telling you.
Hey, guys. You got any change?
Sorry, pal.
- How about your wallets?
Hey, no- No problem.
- Take it easy.
- The wallets!
- No problem.
- Hold on, man.
Jim!
Jim! Jim.
Call 911 now!
Come on.
Hey.
Jim, Don't move, man.
I feel okay.
You- You're not even bleeding.
Give me a hand.
How are you even alive right now?
I don't know.
No, no, no, you're right,
it's definitely weird.
Okay, Bobby. Thanks. Ahem.
- What's up?
- Uh-
Bobby found something in Wyoming.
- A job?
- Maybe.
Small town, no one's died in the past
week and a half.
That so unusual?
Well, it's how they're not dying. Um-
One guy with terminal cancer
strolls out of hospice.
Another guy gets capped by a mugger,
walks away without a scratch.
Capped in the ass?
"Police say Mr. Jenkins
was shot in the heart...
...at point-blank range
by a 9 millimeter. "
And he's not a donut?
Locals are saying it's a miracle.
Okay.
It's gotta be something nasty, right?
Maybe people making deals
or something?
You think?
What else would it be?
I don't know.
All right. Get that to go.
Come on.
What?
- You want me with you?
- Why wouldn't I?
Ah, I don't know, I don't wanna be
holding you back or nothing.
Dude, I've told you a hundred times,
that was the siren talking, not me.
Can we get past this?
Yeah, we're past it.
Now, you two said you were bloggers?
Yes, sir. FlooredByTheLord. com.
All God's glory fit to blog.
People around town are saying
what happened to you was a miracle.
- It was, plain as day.
- How can you be so sure?
How else do you explain it?
The doctors can't.
There's a bullet in my heart.
It's pumping like a piston.
Well, how do you explain it?
What's that?
Look, honestly...
...I was nobody's saint.
Not exactly father of the year either.
Okay.
But when that guy shot me
and I didn't bleed a drop...
...I just knew the Lord
was giving me a second chance.
That so?
I had this feeling
like angels were watching over me.
I wouldn't expect you guys
to understand.
Well, we'll just have to try.
You wouldn't have happened to have swung
by a crossroads in the past week or so?
- No.
- Maybe you met someone?
With black eyes?
Or red?
Who'd you guys say you were again?
Never mind. Thank you for your time.
Hey.
Anything?
That cancer survivor?
He was clinically dead.
His wife pulled the plug and now he's
taking her out for their 20th anniversary.
- Any sign of a deal?
- No.
What about you? Find anyone dying?
Not since Cole Griffith.
He dropped 10 days ago.
It was the last death I could find.
So, what are you thinking?
- Maybe it is what the people say it is.
- Miracles?
Dean, our experience,
when do miracles just happen?
There's no deals.
There's, uh, no skeevy faith healers.
I mean, these souls
just ain't getting dragged into the light.
Maybe because there's no one around
to carry them.
What do you mean?
Well, Grim Reapers,
that's what they do, right, schlep souls?
- If death ain't in town-
- Then nobody's dying.
So, what, the local Reaper's on strike?
Playing the back nine?
I don't know, Sam.
Well, then let's talk to somebody
who might.
- Last I checked, Huggy Bear ain't available.
- No, dude, the kid.
The kid? The kid's a doornail.
Exactly.
If he was the last person to die,
then maybe he's seen something.
We should talk to him.
I love how matter-of-fact
you are about that.
Strange lives.
You sure this is gonna work?
No.
But if his spirit's around,
this should smoke him out.
What?
This job is jacked, that's what.
How so?
You want me to gank a monster
or torch a corpse?
Hey, pbbt, let's light it up, right?
But this?
If we fix whatever this is,
people will start dropping dead.
Good people.
Look, I don't want them to die either,
Dean.
But there's a natural order.
- You're kidding, right?
- What?
You don't see the irony in that?
You and me, we're like the poster
boys of the unnatural order.
All we do is ditch death.
Yeah, but the normal rules
don't really apply to us, do they?
We're no different than anybody else.
I'm infected with demon blood.
You've been to hell.
I know you wanna think of yourself
as Joe the Plumber, but you're not.
Neither am I.
Sooner you accept that,
the better off you're gonna be.
Ah, Joe the Plumber was a douche.
You gonna help me finish this?
Hey!
- What are you doing here?
- Uh-
Look, just take it easy.
What the hell is this?
Oh, this- This is not what it looks like.
Really?
Because it looks like devil worship.
What? No, no. This is not devil worship.
This- This is- This-
This is the-
I don't have a good answer.
Look, we're leaving.
You're not going anywhere...
...ever again...
...Sam.
Alastair.
I thought you got deep-fried,
extra crispy.
No.
Just the pediatrician I was riding.
His wife's still looking for him.
It's hilarious.
Anyway...
...no time to chat.
Got a hot date with death.
Dean!
You're stronger, Sam.
You been Soloflexing
with your little slut?
You have no idea.
How you doing?
I'm in pain, that's how I'm doing.
- I think I have a concussion.
- You want aspirin?
No, thanks, House.
So demons, huh?
Yeah. So much for miracles.
- What happened with Alastair again?
- I told you.
He tried to fling me or whatever
and it didn't work, so he bailed.
How come he couldn't fling you?
He chucked you pretty good last time.
Got no idea.
Sam, do me a favor.
If you're gonna keep your little secrets,
then I can't really stop you.
But just don't treat me like an idiot,
okay?
What? Dean, I'm not keeping secrets.
Mm-hm.
Whatever.
So did you go back
and Q&A the dead kid?
Didn't have to.
Bobby called.
He did some digging.
And?
He thinks I'm right.
Local Reaper's gone.
Not just gone, kidnapped.
By demons? Why?
Listen to this:
"And he bloodied Death
under the newborn sky.
Sweet to taste,
but bitter when once devoured. "
Swanky. What the hell does that mean?
Well, it's from a very obscure,
very arcane version of Revelations.
Which means what I think it means?
Basically, you kill a Reaper
under the solstice moon-
Tomorrow night, by the way.
- you got yourself a broken seal.
How do you ice a Reaper?
Can't kill Death.
I don't know. Maybe demons can.
Where are the angels is what I wanna know.
We could use their help for once.
It looks like we'll have
to take care of this.
We gonna just swing in and
save the friendly neighborhood Reaper?
- You got a better idea, I'm all ears.
- Dean, Reapers are invisible.
The only people that can see them
are the dead and the dying.
If ghosts are the only ones
who can see...
Yeah?
...then we become ghosts.
You do have a concussion.
Sounds crazy, I know.
It is crazy.
How?
I can't even begin to tell you
how crazy you two are.
Well, Pamela,
you're a sight for sore eyes.
Aw, that's sweet, Grumpy.
What do you say to deaf people?
Which one of you brainiacs
came up with astral projection?
Yo.
Of course. Chachi.
Chachi?
So let's be clear.
You wanna rip your souls
out of your bodies...
...and take a little stroll
through the spirit world?
Mm-hm.
Do you have any idea
how heavy-duty insane that is?
Maybe, but that's where the Reaper is,
so-
- So it's nuts.
- Not if you know what you're doing.
- You don't know what you're doing.
No.
- But you do.
- Yeah, I do.
And guess what?
I'm sick of being hauled...
...back into your angel-demon,
Soc-greaser crap.
I'd love to be kicking back with a cold one,
watching Judge Judy too.
- Nice. More blind jokes?
- You know what I mean.
We're talking the end of the world here,
okay?
No more tasseled leather pants,
no more Ramones CDs, no more nothing.
We need your help.
Tell me something, geniuses.
Even if you do break into the veil and you
find the Reaper, how you gonna save it?
With style and class.
You're gonna be
two walking pieces of fog.
You can't touch or move anything.
You'll be defenseless, hotshot.
I seem to recall a bunch of ghosts
beating the crap out of us.
Yeah, they had plenty of time
to practice.
Well, then I guess
we gotta start cramming.
Wow! Couple of heroes.
All right.
Lie down.
Close your eyes.
Okay, guys.
That's it.
Show time.
Ah!
Well, nothing like shooting blanks.
What's plan B?
Oh, I'm so feeling up Demi Moore.
All right, so I'm assuming
you're somewhere over the rainbow.
Remember, I have to bring you back.
I'll whisper the incantation in your ear.
You have got a great ass.
What'd she say? What'd she say?
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
That was wild.
Am I making you uncomfortable?
Get out of me.
You're such a prude. Come on.
We've been spooking this town
for hours.
And no demons, no black smoke.
I say we hit Victoria's Secret,
get our peep on, huh?
Hey, hey. Three o'clock.
Kid in the window.
Am I crazy or is he looking at us?
That's because we've seen him before.
- We have?
- Newspaper. Cole Griffith.
Last person to die in this town.
Cole?
It's Mom.
Your dad thinks I'm crazy.
Are you here?
A picture frame fell over.
I could've sworn it was you, baby.
Are you still here with me?
Oh, my God.
Sam! How are you doing that?
- Who are you?
Relax, Cole.
It's okay.
- How do you know my name?
- Look...
...this isn't gonna be easy to hear...
...but you're dead.
You're a spirit. Us too.
Yeah, thanks, Haley Joel.
I know I'm dead.
What do you want?
We just wanna talk.
About what?
I was outside all morning.
They tell you to be careful
when it's cold.
Cold air can cause an asthma attack?
Then I was in my room.
It happened so fast.
I called out for my mom,
but nothing came out.
Everything started spinning
and then I was just standing there...
...looking down at my body.
And that's when you saw the man?
Creepy old guy in a black suit.
Wanted me to go with him...
...but I didn't wanna go.
Reaper.
How'd you get rid of him?
I didn't.
The black smoke did.
Black smoke?
It was everywhere.
I hid in the closet.
And when I came out,
it was gone and so was he.
Do you know
where the black smoke went?
No.
But I know where it is.
- They're back.
- Who?
- Another Reaper.
- Hey!
Hey! Wait, we need to talk to you.
Dean.
Do I know you?
We go way back.
You don't remember me?
Honestly, if I had a nickel for every time
I heard a girl say that...
You're gonna have
to freshen my memory.
Tessa.
That's one of my names, yeah.
So you do know her.
From the hospital, after the accident.
The accident with Dad?
So this is the Reaper
that came after you.
Yeah.
Well, this was fun.
- Now, if you'll excuse me-
- Wait, wait, wait. You can't-
- You can't take the kid.
- Why?
Demons are in town, that's why.
They've already snatched your Reaper pal.
- Kid knows where.
- So?
So you should shag ass.
For all we know, they could try
and snatch you too.
Except that this town is off the rails.
And someone has to set it straight.
Yeah, we understand that.
- But these are special circumstances.
- What, your whole angel-demon dance-off?
I could care less.
I just wanna do my job.
Right. We wanna help you do your job.
- So if you would just bail town-
- No.
Well, then could you hold off
until we fix this?
Please.
All right, but just so we're clear,
when I start reaping again...
...I'm starting with the kid.
Understood.
I'll find him.
Wait, wait, wait. What-?
What are you gonna say to him?
Whatever I have to.
This all must be pretty overwhelming,
huh?
Pretty scary too.
The worst is my mom.
Must be hard seeing her like this.
She's always coming in here...
...talking to me...
...telling me how sad she is.
I knock some stuff over to let her know
I'm here, but she only gets sadder.
Yeah.
You might wanna ease up
on the flying soccer balls.
I'm not telling you where the smoke is.
Hey.
What if I told you
that if you helped me...
...you wouldn't have to leave here ever?
What about the one downstairs?
Tessa? Oh, she wouldn't bother you.
No Reaper would.
You could just stay here with your family
for as long as you wanted.
You can do that?
Yeah, you bet I can do that.
You swear?
I swear.
I'll tell you, life is funny.
What do you mean?
You and me, together again.
Are you-?
Are you making a move on me?
You're the one that got away, Dean.
You'd be surprised
how little that happens to me.
Can I tell you something
between you and me?
Who am I gonna tell?
After our little, uh, experience...
...for that whole year...
...I felt like I had this hole in my gut.
Like I was missing something.
I didn't know what.
But you know what it was?
It was you.
The pain of losing my father...
...and Sammy.
I just-
I wish I'd gone with you for good.
But I guess things are different now.
What?
The angels on your shoulder?
So you know about that, huh?
Well, hey, don't get me wrong. Most
of the ones I've met are dicks with wings.
But still...
You know, I've done things.
Horrible things.
And someone upstairs still decided
to give me a second chance.
It just makes me feel...
I don't know.
Uh-huh.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Cole.
I'm Tessa. I'm not going to hurt you.
It's okay, Cole.
Just tell them what you told me.
I saw the black smoke at my funeral.
At the cemetery?
At the funeral home.
It was everywhere.
- Are you doing that?
- No.
Tessa?
Cole, are you okay?
- How are we supposed to fight that?
- Learn some ghost moves?
By tonight?
Yeah, sure, I'll meet you back
at Mr. Miyagi's.
Who's Mr. Miyagi?
It won't move
if you don't concentrate.
I am concentrating.
Here we go, baby.
You pull a muscle?
All right, Yoda, let's see what you got.
Dude! You are so Amityville.
This isn't even the good stuff.
If you wanna hit something,
you gotta get mad.
Yeah, got it.
Now you try. Hit me.
Ah, I think I'll stick to just
picking on somebody my own size.
Hit me as hard as you can.
I won't do Fight Club with a 12-year-old.
All right, cut it out.
Make me.
Whoa, whoa, you gotta teach us that.
Place looks like New Jack City.
Can nobody see this?
Maybe it's demon invisible ink.
Only see it in the veil.
Any idea what it's for?
We'll find out.
Dude, check me out.
Well, you know, this ghost thing,
it's kind of rad.
It's iron.
Boys.
Find the place okay?
Rock salt's not so much fun anymore,
is it?
Alastair.
You bastard.
Well, go on.
Why don't you try some of your mojo
on me now, hotshot?
It's hard to get it up
when you're not wearing your meat, huh?
- Go to hell.
- Oh, if only I could.
But they just keep sending me back up
to this Arctic crap hole.
- To kill Death?
- No, to kill Death twice.
It takes two to break a seal.
I figured another one would show up,
you know.
They're like lemmings.
By the way...
...it's good to see you again, Dean.
You can shoot us all you want,
but you can't kill us.
Ah.
That so?
Anywho...
...moon's in the right spot.
The board is set.
Let's get started, shall we?
You gonna kill a Reaper with that?
It's a little on the nose, don't you think?
Is it?
An old friend lent it to me.
You know, he doesn't really ride
a pale horse.
But he does have three amigos.
And they're just jonesing
for the Apocalypse.
It pays to have friends in low places.
Don't you think?
No.
Stop!
I know you're here.
What's the matter,
you reeking son a bitch?
You afraid of a skirt?
Son of a bitch.
Bye-bye.
- Where's your brother?
- I'll find him. You get out of here.
Oh.
Pamela.
- What's so funny?
- I can't die.
Not in this town.
Look.
Pamela.
Quit your worrying, Grumpy.
- How about you make me a drink, huh?
- You need a doctor.
Make me a drink, Sam.
You can't run, Dean.
Not from me.
I'm inside that angsty little noggin
of yours.
What the hell?
Guess again.
What just happened?
You and Sam just saved a seal.
We captured Alastair.
- Dean, this was a victory.
- Well, no thanks to you.
What makes you say that?
You were here the whole time?
Enough of it.
Well, thanks for your help
with the rock salt.
That script on the funeral home,
we couldn't penetrate it.
That was angel-proofing.
Why do you think I recruited you and
Sam in the first place?
You recruited us?
That wasn't your friend Bobby
who called, Dean.
It wasn't Bobby
who told Sam about the seal.
That was you.
If you want our help,
why the hell didn't you just ask?
Because whatever I ask...
...you seem to do the exact opposite.
What now? People in this town,
they just gonna start dying again?
Yes.
These are good people.
Don't you think
you can make a few exceptions?
To everything, there is a season.
You made an exception for me.
You're different.
Dean?
I could use your help.
Hey, Cole.
Tell your brother thanks for nothing.
Look at her, Cole.
Do you see how unhappy she is?
That's why I wanna stay with her.
As long as she can feel you,
she'll be in pain.
Because she can't let go.
Because you won't let go of her.
Why won't anybody tell me
what's on the other side?
Maybe nobody wants to ruin the surprise.
That's not an answer.
She won't answer you, Cole.
Reapers never do.
But trust me.
Staying here is a whole lot worse
than anything over there.
Why?
Because one day,
your family will be gone.
And there'll be nothing left here for you.
- It's okay to be scared.
- I'm not scared.
We're all scared.
That's the big secret.
Are you coming?
Oh, I'm sure I'll be there
sooner than you think.
Look out for that boy.
Look out for yourself, Dean.
What do you mean?
I've been around death...
...from the get-go.
You know what I see most?
Lies.
"He's in a better place. "
"At least they're together now. "
You all lie to yourselves, Dean.
Because like you said...
...deep down, you're all scared.
Stop lying to yourself, Dean.
What?
The angels have something good
in store for you.
A second chance.
Really?
Because I'm pretty sure...
...deep down...
...you know something nasty
is coming down the road.
Trust your instincts, Dean.
There's no such thing as miracles.
What are you saying?
Hey.
We just gotta talk to Tessa, get her to
hold off reaping until we get you better.
I'm pretty sure she started up again.
What happened?
Dean, where's Tessa?
She's-
Pamela...
- ... I'm so sorry.
- Stop.
- You don't deserve this.
Yeah, I don't.
I told you I didn't want
anything to do with this.
Do me a favor?
Tell that bastard Bobby Singer...
...to go to hell for ever introducing me
to you two in the first place.
Take it easy, Pamela.
If it's any consolation,
you're going to a better place.
You're lying.
But what the hell, right?
Everybody's gotta go sometime.
Come here.
I know what you did to that demon, Sam.
I can feel what's inside of you.
If you think you have good intentions...
...think again.
Pamela?
Pamela!
What did she say to you?