Then
You left.
Your brother and me --
We needed you.
You walked away, sam.
You walked away!
You're the one who said
"don't come back," dad.
You're the one
who closed that door, not me!
Sammy, i just couldn't accept
the fact That you and me --
We're just different.
We're not different.
Not anymore.
Ruby, it's been weeks.
I need it.
do you even kn eff
the reservation you've gone?
How far fyour ??
brit's alreadyded
down a dangone
??? too far, sam.
If i didn't know you,
I would want to hunt you.
Now
Aah!
No! Go away!
No!
Aah!
Oh, my god.
???
Oh, god. Oh, lord.
Ohh.
Ah??? Oh, god.
Oh, g.
Okay. God.
????
www.1000fr.com presents
SuPerNaTuRal s04e19
Capture:??±¦
Sync:???? ???? mzinfo
Jump the shark
Hey.
How'd you sleep?
How do you think?
I'm starving.
Let's get breakfast.
Where? We're like
two hours from anything.
But i'm hungry now.
There's probably a sandwich
in the backseat still.
Ahh.
???
Ist that dad' done?
Hello?
Is this john?
He can't come to the phone.
Can i help you?
No. I really need
to talk to john.
???
Well, sorry to be the one
to break this to you, pal,
But john died
more than two years ago.
Who is this?
I'm his son.
windom, minnesota
Dean, look, best i can tell,
adam milligan is real. Um,
born september 29, 1990,
to kate milligan.
No father listed
on the birth certificate.
He's an eagle scout, graduated
from high school with honors,
And currently goes to
the university of wisconsin --
Biology major, pre-Med.
Dean?
You listening?
This is a trap.
Dean, i'm telling you --
The kid checks out.
Great, so he's an actual person
on the planet earth.
Sucks he's got a demon in him.
- hi. Welcome
to cousin oliver's.
- thanks
- Can i --
- We're actually
waiting on somebody.
Thank you.
What are you --
- Holy water?
- Yep --
One sip of jesus juice, this evil bitch
is gonna be in a world of hurt.
And what if
he's not possessed?
Then he is
a shapeshifter.
Hence the silver.
Look, either way,
this thing is gonna bleed.
I mean, using dad as bait?
That's the last mistake
of its short, pitiful life.
What?
- What?
- Dean...
listen -- There's an entry
in dad's journal From january of 1990
Saying he's headed to minnesota
to check out a case.
That's, roughly, oh, about nine months
before the kid was born.
- Coincidenc
- coincidenc
Next two pages
of the journal --
Torn out.
you're not ?? buying this, ???
?? to believe ???
I'm just saying it's possible.
I mean, dad would be gone
for weeks at a time,
And he wasn't
exactly a monk.
I mean,
a hunter rolls into town,
Uh, kills a monster,
saves the girl...
sometimes
the girl's grateful.
Well, now i'm thinking
about dad sex. Stop talking.
Maybe he slipped one
past the goalie.
Dude!
Adam?
You sam?
Yeah.
Uh, this is dean.
Hi.
so um...
...how ?? my dad?
Uh,
we worked together.
- How did he die?
- On the job.
- He was a mechanic, right?
- A car fell on him.
Hey, adam.
How you doing?
Oh, i'll take that.
I am very thirsty.
The usual, adam?
Uh, yeah.
Thanks, denise.
So, uh...
when's the last time
you -- You saw john?
I don't even know.
It's...a couple years.
W-Why did you decide
to call him now?
I didn't know
who else to call.
He's the only family
i got.
My mom's missing.
Really? I'm sorry.
Uh, for how long?
It's tragic -- Really.
But if you're john's kid,
Hocome we've never heard of you?
'Cause john and me
didn't really know each other.
Not until
a few years ago, anyway.
- What do you mean?
- My mom never talked about him.
- I knew some stuff.
- What kind of stuff?
?? nurse, And ???
hunting accident or something.
And i knew his name --
John winchester.
That's about it.
We're not exactly a nuclear family.
Yeah, well,
who is these days?
So, when did you, uh,
when did you finally meet him?
When i was 12.
My mom had
one of his old numbers, and...
and after i begged her --
God, 24/7--
She finally called him.
God, when john heard
he had a son, he raced to town.
I mean, he dropped everything.
He drove all night.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
Well,
that's heartwarming.
- You mind?
- No, please -- Dig in.
He would swing by once a year or so,
You know, called when he could.
But still...
he taught me poker and pool And
even bought me my first beer
when i was 15.
And, uh...
he showed me
how to drive. Dad --
He had this beautiful '67 impala.
Oh, this is crap.
You know what -- You're lying.
- No, i'm not.
- Uh, yeah, you are.
I'm sorry, but who the hell
are you to call me a liar?
We're john winchester's sons,
that's who.
We are his sons.
- I've got brothers?
- No, you don't have brothers.
Look, man, i don't know if you're a hunter
Or what kind of game you're playing here.
I have never been hunting
in my life.
Whatever. I'm out of here.
Come on, sam.
I can prove it.
He took you
to a baseball game?
Yeah,
when i turned 14.
Dad was around
for a few of my birthdays.
September 29, 2004.
One word --
"Minnesota."
He took you
to a freakin' baseball game?
Yeah,
Why? What'd dad do with you
on your birthday?
Oh...
adam, you said you called dad
because your mom was missing.
- Yeah.
- How long has she been gone?
Three days.
Who was the last person
to see her?
Mr. Abbinanti,
our neighbor.
He saw her come home
tuesday night,
But she never showed up
to work on wednesday.
- Did you call the police?
- Mom's supervisor at the hospital did.
And then i drove down here
as fast as i could.
I should have been here.
What'd the, uh,
what'd the cops say?
That they, uh,
they searched the house.
They didn't find anything.
She wouldn't leave
without telling anybody.
It's like she just dropped off
the face of the earth, you know?
The, uh, nightstand was knocked
over. Was there anything else?
Oh, not really. The sheriff said
there's no sign of a break-In.
What -- You think
the cops missed something?
Maybe.
They don't have my eyes.
You're a mechanic.
Yeah. That's right.
Dean, what else
can you tell me about dad?
You knew him.
Not as well as you.
Trust me, kid --
You don't want to know.
Give us a minute.
You talk to the cops?
Yeah. Like adam said,
no leads on his mom.
- Ocker there.
- But i did find this. Um...
here.
In 1990, there were
17 grave robberies in windom.
You think that's why
dad came through here?
I'd say so.
Check it out.
All right, so he was
hunting something. What?
??? se-Snatchinghoa were the pages
started up again --Journal.
But last month, ???
??? Bodies from the local cemetery.
So whatever heer??? ,
he didn't kill it. It's back.
And...what -- It's stepped up
its game to fresh meat? I mean,
kate's missing, and, uh...
so is a local bartender --
A guy named joe barton.
Hey, does your mom
know joe barton?
Uh, i don't think so.
Why?
- What is it?
- Watch out.
Give me a hand
with the mattress.
Every time.
Why didn ??? paper?
Who the hell are you?
Adam, hey.
Take it easy.
No, don't tell me
to take it easy, okay?
My house is a crime scene,
my mom's probably dead, And you two --
Well, you tell me to call the cops,
But you got to bail before they show?
So, who are you really?
Cops didn't know where to look
for my mom, dean, but you did.
and i heard you talking earlier --
Something about grave robberies.
You're not mechanics.
I just want to know
what's going on.
Please.
We're hunters.
- Sammy!
- He deserves to know, dean.
What do you mean, "hunters"?
Okay, so...
basically, You're saying
that every movie monster,
Every nightmare that
i've ever had -- That's all real?
"Godzilla's" just a movie.
We hunt them.
So did dad.
Okay.
"Okay"? That's it?
What am i supposed to say?
That we're liars,
that we're crazy.
Nobody just says "okay."
You're my brothers.
You're telling me
the truth, right?
- Yeah.
- Then i believe you.
Now, what took my mom?
We're not sure.
Something's in town stealing
bodies -- Living and dead --
But we don't know what.
There's a long list of freaks
that fit the bill.
You think maybe
she might still be alive?
Oh.
How can i help?
You can't.
This thing killed my mom.
If you're hunting it, i want in.
- No.
- Dean, look, maybe --
Maybe what?
He lost his mother. Maybe we can
understand what that feels like.
Why do you think dad never
told us about this kid, sam?
Huh? Why do you think
he ripped out the pages?
- Because --
- Because he was protecting him!
Dad's dead, dean.
That doesn't matter!
He didn't want adam
to have our lives, okay?
And we'anre gonna
respect s wishcb.
- do i get a say in this? no!
- no
- Basid.???
- Whe g?
I'm going out!
Is he always like that?
Welcome to the family.
Here.
I'm gonna teach you
a few things.
Uh, dean said --
I know what dean said.
And i know what it's like
to want revenge.
This tomb was built in 1926.
Four generations of the millsap
family were interred here.
They don't build 'em
like this anymore.
Tell me, agent nugent,
have you thought about Where you
might like to spend eternity?
All the damn time.
So, three bodies went missing.
Any idea who did it?
Hooligans --
Sick, deranged hooligans.
This isn't blood.
What is this?
No, it's embalming fluid.
Whoever committed this crime
didn't just take the corpses.
They opened them up.
firsbeer's on the house fops.  ???
???????Cbhat ss?E l esanyoveot
at "w
???
So, what's the fbi
doing in windom?
I'ing to
the dippearance of jn.
I assume you knew him?
A little.
I'm his wife. Lisa.
Well, ???
same thing can you tell me
i told the sheriff.Sappearance?
He stayed late friday before
last to do inventory --
Never came home.
D the police?
Nothing.
Uth is, i was scared
they stopped looking.
But now you're he
joe was a cop?
For a little wle.
At was a long time ago.
He didn'het happen to work
the, uh, te,e --
The grave-Y case '90?
He did. Yeah.
Joe was the one
who found those bodies.
He got an award
for that.
That was
an interesting case.
He ever tell you
how he did it?
Most of the time,
he said good, solid police work.
But after a few beers,
he'd admit he had a little help.
From who?
A "specialist" --
T"'s all he'd say.
Cops ever find the guy
that stole the bodies?
No.
But when i asked joe about it,
he'd say not to worry --
That "we took care
of what done it."
Sam...
how did dad really die?
Demon.
You hunted it down?
Got revenge?
Dean killed it.
So it's over for you.
It's never over.
- What the --
- Shh.
Stay here.
It'itin t vents t
Go!
where's your car?
Over here.
???
here.
Sam!
Dean, help!
i winged it.
Did you see anything?
I didn't get
a good look.
What the hell
is this thing?
Why -- Who --
Should we go after it?
No, no.
In that maze?
That thing's long gone.
All right, so, we don't know what it is,
But we do know who it's going after --
- Joe barton, adamo's mom.
- and adam.
It was under his truck,
just waiting for him.
It set a trap,
and i walked right into it.
Doesn't matter. You're right --
There's a pattern.
Joe barton was a cop.
I'm pretty sure he helped out dad.
So we've got him,
dad's girl...
and his son.
All the people
dad knew in town.
At least we know
why it's back.
It wants revenge.
grab your stuff.
We'll hit the road.
We shouldn't leave.
Yeah, let's stay here,
the kid's mom got gankgot
- Good one.
- I'm serious.
No, sam, we're gonna take the kid,
We're gonna drop him off at bobby's,
Are gonna come back here
And finish what dad started.
How?
We got no leads,
no witnesses.
We do have
what this thing wants.
You want to use the kid
as bait?
That's why
you want to stay here?
Maybe this thing will come back.
We could train adam --
Get him ready.
He could die, sam.
We could all die, dean.
Even if we do kill this thing, There are
tons of other freaks that want revenge --
On dad, on us.
What if they find the kid
instead and he's not ready?
I'll do it.
Whatever it takes,
i'll do it.
I want to do it.
- Whoa.
- It's easy.
Just feel the recoil
and time the trigger pulls.
Three taps.
- Yeah?
- Go ahead.
Beginner's luck,
right?
Nah, man.
You're a natural.
- Good shooting.
- Thanks.
So, then we lit it on fire.
With a homemade
flamethrower?
Yeah.
They're easy to build.
I'll show you.
That is some job
you got, man.
Being a hunter
isn't a job, adam.
It's life.
You're pre-Med.
you got a girlfriend, friends?
Not anymore you don't.
If you're
really gonna do this,
You can't have those kinds
of connections -- Ever.
They're weaknesses.
You'll just put those people
in danger -- Get them killed.
That's the price we pay.
You cut 'em out,
and you don't look back.
There's only one thing
you can count on --
Family.
Sam.
Can i talk to you?
What the hell
was that?
What?
"Hunting is life.
You can't have connections."
Dad gave you that
exact same speech, remember?
It was just before
you ditched us for stanford.
You hated dad for saying that stuff,
And now you're quoting him?
Yeah, well...
turns out dad was right.
- Since when?
- Since always.
Dean, when i look at adam,
you know what i see?
- A normal kid.
- No. Meat.
Because the demons and monsters
out there, That's all he is.
I hated dad for a long time.
??
But now i think i understand.
So we didn't have a dog
and a white picket fence.
So what?
Dad did right by us.
He taught us
how to protect ourselves.
Adam deserves the same.
- Listen to yourself, man.
- You think i'm wrong?
I think
it's too late for us.
This is our life.
This is who we are, okay?
And it's fine.
I accept that. But with adam,
he's still got a chance, man.
He can go to school.
- He could be a doctor.
- What makes adam so special?
- What, are you jealous of the kid?
- Are you?
Dean...
all this...
it's not real.
The dad adam knew --
He wasn't real.
The things out there
in the shadows -- They are real.
The world is coming to an end.
That's real.
Everything else is just part of the crap
People tell themselves to get through the day.
Dad didn't have a choice with us, okay?
But with adam, he did.
- Adam doesn't have to be cursed.
- He's a winchester.
He's already cursed.
No.
No, whatever's hunting adam,
i'm gonna find it.
- You already looked everywhere, dean.
- Well, then i'll look again.
??S cb home sweet h scb
Sloppy joe.
Oh, son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch.
All right.
We've closed off every
other way into the house.
If this thing's coming,
it's coming through there.
You were saying?
Adam!
- ??
- Mom?
- No.
- Mom!
Adam!
Mom.
Adam, no! Wait!
It took me, but i got away.
- ??
- I got away.
Adam, step away from her.
Sam, what the hell?!
She's not your mother!
Adam, who -- What is going on?
- get away from him!
- What is going on?
- You listen to me.
- It's really her, okay?
There was too much blood.
Your mother's dead.
There was too much blood in the vents!
Adam!
- Shoot it!
- He's crazy! It's me!
- Look -- Adam!
- It's me!
That's not your mother!
- ??
- Shoot it! It's not human!
I know.
Silver.
??
You're not shapeshifters.
??You'
You know, i find that term racist.
Fresh meat. So much better
than what we're used to.
i should have known.
It was the fresh kills that threw me.
Ghouls don't usually go after the living.
See, you're just filthy scavengers,
Feeding off the dead --
Taking the form of
the last corpse you choke down.
And their thoughts. And their memories.
Like adam, for instance.
- Well, we are what we eat.
- You're monsters.
You know, you use that word a lot, sam.
But i don't think you know what it means.
His blood -- It tastes different.
Our father was a monster?
Why?
Because of what he ate?
He never hurt anyone, sam.
Living, anyway.
No.
He was no monster.
But the thing that killed him was.
A monster named john winchester.
Holy crap.
??Thanks ur daddy,
??, brother and i grew up on our own.
At least we had each other.
Like you and your brother --
Inseparable.
Actually, it was very hard
to get you on your own.
Like you said, sam, the only
thing you can count on is family.
And for 20 years, we lived like rats.
Graveyard after graveyard,
all that stinking flesh.
Then we thought, "hey,
why not move up to fresher game?"
And we knew just where to start.
Revenge -- It's never over, is it, sam?
First, it was john's cop friend,
And then his slut, and then his son.
Then i called john, but...
The son of a bitch was already dead.
So i guess you and dean
will have to do instead.
Dean won't interrupt us this time.
We're gonna feed on you
nice and slow --
Like we did with adam.
Oh, and, by the way,
He really was your brother.
You should know that.
He was still alive
when we took our first bites.
And he was a screamer.
Sam, the more you struggle,
The faster you're gonna bleed out.
So you might
as well lie back and relax.
Hey!
Dean, they're ghouls!
Which means head-Shot.
Dean!
??Come on. Come on. Come on.
Hang on.
All right, here we go.
Here we go.
Hang ouddy.
??Ght. All right.
Thank you.
That's what family's for, right?
Keep pressure on that.
You sure we should do this?
Ghouls didn't fake those pictures.
They didn't fake dad's journal.
Adam was our brother.
He died like a hunter.
He deserves to go out like one.
Maybe we can bring him back...
Get ahold of cass, call in a favor.
No, adam's in a better place.
You know, i finally get why
you and dad butted heads so much.
You two were practically
the same person.
I mean, i worshipped
the guy, you know?
I-I dressed like him,
i acted like him,
I listen to the same music.
But you were more like him
than i will ever be.
And i see that now.
I'll take that as a compliment.
You take it any way you want.
welcome to www.1000fr.com