the movie shut down
supernatural season 4  episode 5
YYeTs www.yyets.net
No,I -- I agree.
it's a hell of a case.
A little more gusto,please.
It's just...the world
is coming to an end.
Things are a little
complicated,you know?
Yeah,well,we can't save
the world,not today anyway.
But what we can do is
chop off some vamps' heads.
Come on,man,it's like
the good old days.
An honest-to-goodness
monster hunt.
It's about time the
winchesters got back to tackling
A straightforward,black-and-white
case.
We still got to see
the new "raiders" movie.
­ Saw it.
Without me?
You were in hell.
That's no excuse.
Big pretzel!
Thank you.
Guten tag.
"guten tag" yourself.
Looks like that's our man.
Sheriff dietrich.
Are you the boys from the fed?
Agents angus and young.
We called ahead
about your,uh,problem.
Right. um...
I'll tell you what,
Why don't we talk this out
away from the crowd,huh?
26 Marissa wright,26,
Just up from lockhard for the 'fest.
Terrible. just terrible.
It's the last thing
This town needs at
peak tourist season.
Definitely the last thing
marissa wright needed.
What the hell?
Yeah,you got
me -- I mean,
This killer's some kind of grade
-"a" wacko,right?
I mean,some satan-worshipping,anne
rice-reading,
Gothic,psycho vampire wannabe.
Sheriff,in your report,you
mentioned a witness.
Yeah,I wished I didn't.
but our witness insisted.
That's ed brewer.
Not exactly what you'd call reliable.
I remember you.
And I remember you...
"jamie."
I never forget a
pretty... everything.
We're looking for ed brewer.
What do you want with ed?
Well,we are,uh...
...federal agents.
Mr. brewer was witness to
a serious crime. we just
Wait a minute. you're a fed?
Wow,you don't come on like a fed.
Seriously?
I'm a maverick,ma'am.
A rebel with a badge.
One thing I don't
play by -- the rules.
Okay,maverick.
Um,so,where can we find mr. brewer?
I told the cops everything I saw.
No one believes me.
Why should you be any different?
Believe me,mr.
brewer,we're different.
I spoke the god's honest
truth,and now I'm the town joke.
Marissa wright's
murder is no joke to us.
And we want to hear everything,
No matter how strange it may seem.
­ We have a lot of
experience with strange.
It was just after midnight.
I just left here,and
like I do every night,
I cut through the
park on the way home.
At first,I thought it
was a couple kissing.
But she was... struggling too much.
And this man,
He was -- well,he
was biting her neck.
Can you describe her assailant?
Oh,he was a vampire.
Okay,right. and
by that,you mean --
You know,a vampire.
So,he looked like
He looked like a vampire,
You know,with the fangs
And the slicked-back
hair and the fancy cape
And the little medallion
thingy on the ribbon.
You mean like a dracula?
­ Exactly. like a dracula.
Right down to the accent.
The accent. yep.
What did he say?
You know,something like...
"stay away,mortal!
The night is mine!"
You do believe me,don't you?
They must be here following
up on that murdered woman.
Crazy ed and his vampire story.
He might be weird,but he's not crazy.
Look,you're just saying that
'cause the guy has a crush on
you and he tips you in $20s.
Lucy.
So,you got a beer back there for me?
I don't know,agent
young. you off duty?
And then some.
So,what do you think?
Goth,psycho vampire wannabe,right?
Definitely not our kind of case.
­ Agreed. but who cares?
Room's paid for,and it's oktoberfest.
Come on,brother.
Beer and bar wenches.
Pretty sure women
today don't react well
To the whole "wench" thing,Dean.
Hey,bar wench,where's that beer?
Coming up,good sir!
Dude,oktoberfest.
There you go.
­ What can I get you?
Oh,he doesn't drink.
He's a christian scientist.
doesn't even take aspirin.
He's a real drag on stakeouts.
You're funny.
I'm a lot more than that.
I'd love to get a chance
to show you the rest.
What time you get off?
Ha ha. like I said,"funny."
Man,it is time to right some wrongs.
Come again?
Look at me.
I came back from the furnace
Without any of my old scars,right?
You know,bullet wounds,knife cuts,
None of the off-angled
fingers from all the breaks.
I mean,my hide is as
smooth as a baby's bottom,
Which leads me to conclude,
Sadly... that my virginity is intact.
What?
-I have been
re-hymenated.  -re...
Please.
Dean,maybe angels can
pull you out of hell,
But no one could do that.
Brother,I have been re-hymenated.
And the dude will not abide.
All right,dude.
Well,you go do
whatever you got to do,
And I'm gonna go back to
the room and get some sleep.
So? how 'bout tonight?
Oh,sorry. I promised
lucy a girls' night out.
Besides,no self-respecting bar wench
Lets herself get picked up by
a customer on the first try.
Well,I'm not a customer.
I'm a federal agent.
Try again tomorrow,g-man.
I wish I could.
-I don't think we're staying on the case.
-what?
Is it too weird for you?
Not weird enough.
-Rick. did you hear that?
-what?
It sounded like a wolf.
Come on,marie,don't
change the subject.
I told you what could happen
to a man if he doesn't --
-  - -Those stories
aren't true. -they are.
Baby,if a man doesn't get the stuff
Out of his system
regularly,it can back up
And cause all kinds of...
medical-type problems.
Shh,do you hear that?
Anne marie,there aren't
any wolves in pennsylvania.
And then it just -- it just
tore rick into little pieces.
Ma'am,we understand how hard this is,
But can you describe the creature?
Oh.
It was a werewolf.
A werewolf?
-You're sure?
-oh,yeah.
With the furry face
and the black nose
T- And the claws and the
torn-up pants and shirt,
Like from the old movies.
Um,well...
Okay,so...
Thank you for your time.
­  First a dracula and now a
full-on movie-time wolf man?
What the hell is
going on in this town?
Ohh. whew.
Damn!
All right.
Whatever did this
wasn't a psycho wannabe.
Look at those bite marks.
Right down to the bone...
And deeper.
Strong enough to tear a healthy
man apart limb from limb.
Could be a werewolf.
Yeah,except,look.
The heart's still there in one piece.
They never leave the heart behind.
Thus I reiterate -- what
the hell is going on?
Well,I was hoping you
boys could tell me.
I just got a rush
job back from the lab
On those fibers we found on the body.
Canine. wolf hairs.
I'm getting a headache.
I don't know,man.
Looks like we've stumbled
on to a midnight showing
Of "dracula meets wolf man."
Is that it?
I don't know.
I mean,wolf man seems real enough.
­ It makes dracula seem a
little less impossible,I guess.
Yeah,but werewolves
don't grow wolf hair.
-  - -That's just
a myth. -yeah.
So,what? we've got a vampire
And a werewolf monster
mashing this town?
Looked like you guys
are staying a while.
I heard about rick deacon.
Yeah,this case just got weird enough
For,uh,our department.
Well,beers are on me.
And,just so you know,I get
off at midnight tonight.
Oh,it's not
another,uh,girls' night out?
Doesn't have to be.
-    -  -Okay,then. I'll
see you tonight. -okay,then.
­ Hey,you think this dracula
could turn into a bat?
bat would be cool.
That's right.
Yeah,an egyptian kind of deal.
No,it was just sitting
there on the loading dock.
No,doctor,there's
no shipping invoice.
There's no nothing.
You think helen has any
record of it in her files?
Holy mother of crap!
No!
This sarcophagus isn't ancient.
It's from a prop house in philly.
Well...
It goes well with
the bucket of dry ice
He was keeping in it.
Is he making his own special effects?
Yeah,a mummy with a good
sense of showmanship.
This is stupid.
Oh,damn it. jamie. I'm late.
You're good here with
the mummy and the...
Crazy
--
-  - -Yeah.
-yeah.
Your loss,g-man.
Good evening.
­ I have watched you
many nights from afar.
My passion knows no bounds!mina
You are the reincarnation
of my beloved,
And I must have you.
Ohh!
... Mary,son of a...
Jamie!
Jamie.
Son of a bitch.
You should not use such language
In the presence of my bride.
Okay.
Jamie,run!
­  You have no choice
in the matter,mr. harker.
Mina is mine!
Hey. you guys all right?
Yeah,I think so.
And I think I know what's going on.
Yeah?
Part of it at least.
Uh,the ear part?
­  Ripped it off of
dracula's head. touch it.
Feel familiar to you?
Oh,man.
The skin of a shapeshifter,
Just like st. louis
and just like milwaukee.
Of course this one's all
holding buckets of crazy.
Oh,and,uh...
This must have fallen
off during the fight.
Look at the label on the ribbon.
It's a costume rental.
All three
monsters --
The dracula,wolf
man,and the mummy --
All the same critter,
Which means we need
to catch this freak
Before he "Creature from
the black lagoon's" somebody.
So,you guys are like Mulder
and Scully or something,
And the x files are real?
No,"the x files" is a
tv show. this is real.
Okay,so,the stagecraft,the costuming
It's like he's trying to reenact
His favorite monster-movie moments,
Right down to the bloody murders.
­mina Wait a second.
who the hell is mina?
Mina? yeah.
That's what he called jamie.
And he called me mr. harker.
­ Jonathan harker?
They're characters from
the movies and the novels --
­ Mina,dracula's intended bride,
Harker,the fianc that
stands in the way.
Seems like he's fixating on you,
Like he sees you as his bride.
Wow. lucky me.
But to fixate on you,
My guess is that the shifter
has to have seen you before
Or been around you.
Jamie,has anybody
strange come to town,
Somebody that has taken
a specific notice of you?
I don't know,Dean. it's oktoberfest.
I'm a bartender.
there's lots of people.
I...
Wait a second. there is ed.
"ed brewer" ed?
Yeah.
He moved here about a month ago.
Lucy swears he has a crush on me.
He comes in almost every night.
But,you know,I don't think
he's the type of guy --
Where does ed live?
I don't know.
But he works at the
old movie theater.
I think he's a projectionist there.
Take care of mina? yep.
So,monsters are real.
Some of them,yeah.
And the shapeshifter,
He can turn into different people.
Yeah.
­ Yeah,except this one's turning
Into the great
monsters of screenland,
Which is a new one for me.
You're not really fbi,are you?
Not so much.
So,this is what you do?
You and your partner just
tramp across the country
On your own dime
Until you find some
horrible nightmare to fight?
Some people paying for.
What?
That must suck.
I mean,you're giving up your
life for this terrible...
I don't know,responsibility.
Last few years,I started
thinking that way,
And,uh,you know,it started
sort of weighing on me.
Of course,that was before...
A little while ago,I had this
­ It's called a
near-death experience.
Very near.
...when I came to...
­ There were different.
My life's been different.
I realize that I help people.
Not just help
them,though. I save them.
I guess it's
-- it's awesome.
It's kind of like a gift...
Like a mission.
Kind of like a... a mission from god.
So,does that make you...
Some kind of monk or something?
You know,celibate?
Man,I hope not.
Holy crap. oh,my god. jamie.
Guys,I'm --
I'm sorry.
I thought you guys were going out.
Lucy,it's -- it's
okay. - uh,listen...
You know what? I just..
- I came to borrow a bottle.
I kind of got something
going back at my...
Anyway,uh,you guys look really busy,
So I'm just gonna
get out of your hair.
Seriously,lucy,it's
been a crazy night.
Stay for a drink.
Yeah. stay for a drink.
You,fbi man --
what did I --
Shut up,okay,you know
what you did. what?
I know what you are.
I'm not anything. I just
like to play the casio.
Had time to grow the ear back,huh?
What?! ow!
Ow! ow! ow!
It's supposed to come off.
No,it's not!
Oh,that sounds awful.
jamie,honey,are you okay?
Oh,I am fine.
He didn't even touch me.
Dean,he just  blew right
in and fought him off.
Well,I didn't actually fly,
But I'm sure it seemed
that way at the time.
It was really,really something.
Jamie?
So,Dean,are you like
a black belt or what?
Well,I guess they train you
To fight at the academy or whatever.
Dean,what are you doing?
It's you,isn't it?
Oh,damn it!
What did you put in the drinks?!
­ That's all right.
I'll skin you myself.
And...scene.
Oh,come on.
She is beautiful,no?
3 Bride number three
from the first film.
She never got the
acclaim that she deserved.
Which is why I chose her shape,
Her form to move among
the mortals unnoticed,
To listen to the cricket
songs of the living.
That is when I discovered
my bride had been reborn
In this century.
­ I can't get over
what a pumpkin-pie-eyed,
Crazy son of a bitch you really are.
­  You're not dracula.
you get that,right?
Or even if you think you are dracula,
What the hell's up with the mummy?!
I am all monsters!
Life ain't a movie,you sorry sack of
Aah.
Life is small,
Meager,messy.
The movies are grand,simple,elegant.
I have chosen elegance.
You think "elegance"
is really the word
For what you did to
marissa or rick deacon
Or any of the others?!
But of course.
It is a monster movie,after all.
You do realize what happens
At the end of every monster movie?
Ah. but this movie is mine.
And in it,the monster wins.
The monster gets the girl.
And the hero,he's...electrocuted.
­ And tonight,jonathan harker,
You will be my hero.
Wait,wait,wait,wait.
Please,excuse me.
Good evening.
Uh...pizza delivery.
Ah,you've brought a repast.
Excellent.
Continue to be of such service
And your life will be spared.
Uh-huh.
That'll be $15.50.
Tell me... yeah?
...is there garlic on this pizza?
I don't know. did you order garlic?
No!
Then no.
Look,mister,I got four
other deliveries to make.
You want to just pay me
the money so I can go?
Of course. yes.
But I have a coupon.
Dean,hey,listen,uh,ed is not our guy.
Um,I'm guessing you're
at home with jamie,
So just give me a cat1,okay?
Lucy.
You wake.
The gown,it suits your beauty.
Please,put it on.
Where am i?
What have you done with Dean?
Harker is resting elsewhere.
Please,put on the
gown and you may dine.
We are having pizza.
What?
What is wrong with you?
You made up lucy,right?
pretended to be my friend.
I needed to know if you were the one.
You could try talking to people!
But instead you become this?
The gown.
I don't want to play
your stupid game,okay?
I just,I just want to go home.
Put on the gown!
I-i scared you.
You were the only one
I don't want to scare.
­ I used to love the movies.
They aren't real.
You can't make them real.
"real" is being born this way.
Different.
"real" is having your
dad call you "monster" --
It's the first time you hear the word
And he tries to beat you
to death with a shovel.
Everywhere I ran,everywhere
I tried to hide,
People found me,dragged
me out and attacked me,
Called me "freak,"
called me "monster."
Then I found them.
The great monsters.
In their movies,they were strong.
They were feared.
They were beautiful.
And now I am like them.
Commanding.
Terrifying.
Lonely.
­ Was lonely.
Now I
I have you.
Ever think that maybe you're lonely
Because you kill people?
Or I kill people because I'm lonely.
Did you hear that?
What?
Dean?
Dean!
Oh,thank god. just
in the nick of time.
That guy was about
to frankenstein me.
Hey there,handsome.
Shut up!
Let's go.
You will never be van helsing!
And you,harker,now you die.
How 'bout now you shut the hell up?
Silver?
It was beauty that killed the beast.
No,mina,do not weep.
Perhaps this is how
Well,thank you,g-man.
You have been a great
service to your country.
Oh,yes,I'm very,very patriotic.
Bye.
You guys saved my life,you know?
So,thanks.
I like her.
Feels good to be back
on the job,doesn't it?
Yeah,it does.
The hero gets the girl,
Monster gets the gank --
all in all,happy ending --
With a happy ending,no less.
Real classy,Dean.
Hey,all I'm saying is
The shifter man had a point,you know?
It would be nice if
life was movie simple.
Although,if I was
turning life into a movie,
I wouldn't do this "Abbott and
Costello meet the monster" crap.
Yeah. no,I know what you'd pick.
No,you don't.
Yeah,I do.
You don't. "porky's II."
What? you heard me.
Lucky guess.