SAM: When I told Dad I was scared
of the thing, he gave me a .45.
DEAN: What was he supposed to do?
-I was 9 years old.
SAM: The weapon training?
And melting the silver into bullets?
Man, Dean, we were raised like warriors.
Lock the doors, the windows,
close the shades.
-Most important--
-Watch out for Sammy.
[GROWLS]
I don't understand the blind faith
you have in the man.
-It's called being a good son.
-Dad's gonna be here, right?
He'll be here, promise.
-Where is he, anyway?
-On business.
-That's why you ran away.
-I was going to college.
It was Dad who said if I was gonna go,
I should stay gone.
Your brother and me, we needed you.
You walked away, Sam.
-You walked away.
DEAN: Stop it.
You're the one who said
don't come back.
You closed that door, not me!
This isn't the life I wanted for you.
[SCREAMING]
I'm sure Dad would have been here
if he could.
[SNIFFS]
She's such a slut.
So?
Personally, I'm very pro-slut.
-What happened, anyway?
-She banged Jamie Jaffe, that's what.
She gave him the reverse cowgirl
and everything.
Hi, Taylor. How was your weekend?
Fine, I guess.
You didn't go to the rodeo?
[STUDENTS CHUCKLE]
That's my spot.
Sorry. This is a skeev-free zone.
STUDENTS [GIGGLING]:
Ooh....
[COUGHING]
Slut. Slut.
CHEERLEADER: Bye.
BOY: Bye.
ALL [COUGHING]:
Slut, slut...
...slut, slut...
...slut, slut, slut...
...slut, slut, slut....
[BANGS TRAY ON TABLE]
-You shouldn't listen to those jerks.
-Leave me alone.
I just mean-- I'm sorry, that's all.
You?
You're sorry?
Don't you feel sorry for me,
you fat, ugly pig.
[FOOTSTEPS LEAVING]
[STUDENTS MURMURING]
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
You think I'm ugly?
Look, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I didn't mean it, okay?
[TAYLOR SCREAMS]
[TAYLOR SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS]
I'm not ugly.
[TAYLOR GASPING AND SCREAMING]
[FLUSHING]
You're ugly.
I'm not talking about it anymore.
I already told the cops and the doctors.
No one believes me.
They think I'm crazy.
SAM: Well, I'm a little bit more
open-minded than most.
April, why did you tell the police
you were possessed?
It doesn't matter.
It matters to me.
When I--
When I hurt Taylor, I was there,
in my head.
But I couldn't control my body.
I could see what I was doing.
But I couldn't stop.
I just wanted to stop.
[SIGHING] I'm sorry.
-You don't need to apologize.
Some of the kids at school
told the police...
-...that you and Taylor didn't get along.
-Yeah.
But I never wanted to kill her.
Never.
Do you believe me?
Yeah, I do.
[SIGHS]
A couple more questions.
On the day this happened,
did you happen to smell anything?
Anything, like what?
Like rotten eggs or sulfur?
No.
Okay, um....
Did you notice any black smoke?
What, are you crazy?
[SIGHS]
So?
I think she's telling the truth.
The way she talked about
being there mentally but not physically.
Kind of sounds like demonic possession
to me.
-Kind of?
-She didn't see any black smoke.
Or smell sulfur.
Maybe she's not a demon.
Kids can be vicious.
Well, I mean, we're already here,
might as well check out the school.
Right. The school.
-What?
-Truman High, home of the Bombers.
-What's your point?
-I don't know.
We went there for a month,
a million years ago.
-Why you so jazzed to go back?
-I just think it's worth looking into.
All right, what's our cover?
FBI, Homeland Security?
-Swedish exchange students?
SAM: Don't worry.
I got an idea.
Okay.
[CAR ENGINE REVS]
DEAN:
Thanks, Dad.
Got your lunch?
-Books? Butterfly knife?
-Yeah, Dean.
-You okay?
-Sure.
Sammy?
I mean, look, this is the third school
we've been to and it's only November.
-I'm just sick of being the new kid.
DEAN: You'll be fine.
If anyone gives you any trouble,
you let me know.
[SCOFFS]
Relax, Dad said this hunt
will take him two weeks, tops.
As soon as he gets back,
we're out of here.
To another school.
Awesome.
[DEAN SIGHS]
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
Ladies and gentlemen,
please say hello to Sam Winchester.
ALL:
Hi, Sam.
Class, say hello to our new student,
Dean Winchester.
Dean, is there anything you'd like
to tell us about yourself?
Not really, sweetheart.
STUDENTS: Ha-ha-ha.
-Take your seat.
Is there anything you'd like
to tell us about yourself?
Not really.
Okay. Uh, grab a seat.
BARRY:
Whoa.
That's yours?
Awesome.
Dean?
Where are your books?
Don't need them, sugar.
Not gonna be here long enough anyway.
[STUDENTS MURMURING
AND CHUCKLING]
All right, gang...
...essay assignments.
[CLASS GROANS]
Yeah, yeah, my heart breaks for you.
[WHISPERS]
Hey.
-I'm Barry.
WYATT: Now, I want three pages...
-Sam.
-...on your memorable family experience.
WYATT: Just a reminder, though, this
is going to be worth half your final grade.
Leave him alone.
WYATT: Don't screw it up.
-Shh, I'm going for a record.
WYATT:
Um, what you write about....
I said leave him alone.
WYATT:
--than how you write about it.
I wanna know how--
You wanna take his place, midget?
WYATT:
I'm looking for the brutal, funny...
-Yeah. Sure.
-...maybe even the painful truth.
WYATT: Okay, everybody,
if you have any questions?
All right, let's get started. Good luck.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Today, you will have the honor of playing
one of the greatest games ever invented.
A game of skill, agility, cunning.
A game with one simple rule.
Dodge.
[BOY MOANS AND GASPS]
Sorry.
-Uh, substitute coach Roth.
DEAN: Yes.
Miss Boudreaux
never let us play dodge ball.
Well, Miss B's in Massachusetts
getting married, so we're playing.
She says it's dangerous--
[BLOWING WHISTLE]
-Take a lap.
-But--
[DOOR CLOSES]
Go nuts.
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
Having fun?
The whistle makes me their god.
Right. Nice shorts.
Find anything?
Been over the entire school twice,
no sulfur.
No sulfur, no demon. No demon, no case.
-I don't know, maybe I was wrong.
-It happens to the best of us.
We hit the road, huh?
But after lunch, it's, uh, sloppy-joe day.
[BOY SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
Good hustle, Colby.
Walk it off.
[WHIRRING]
TEACHER: Always make sure that
your cover is securely fastened, Jamie.
Hey, I need to copy
your Algebra homework again.
TEACHER:
Good. Step two.
Hey.
TEACHER:
Okay, now, my darlings...
-Why?
-...that's enough.
Because you're a stupid, brain-dead dick?
[WHIRRING]
I'm gonna shove my fist down
your throat, little freak.
-That fist?
-Yeah.
[SCREAMING]
JOCK [YELLING]:
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
[STUDENTS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
BOY:
Oh, man.
What happened?
[EMF METER HUMMING]
[TURNS METER OFF]
How's the non-violence assembly going?
Shoving a kid's arm into a Cuisinart
is not a "healthy display of anger."
The kid had ectoplasm
leaking out his ear?
Which only comes
from a pissed-off spirit.
It's gotta be ghost possession.
-That's pretty rare.
-Yeah, but it happens.
They get angry enough, they could
take control of a person's body.
So, what, we got a ghost in the building?
Yeah, but where? I mean, there's no EMF.
Maybe we could find out who it is.
Check and see if somebody died
around here.
Way ahead of you. I had to break
into the principal's office to get this.
Oh, and FYI,
three of the cheerleaders are legal.
-Guess which ones.
-No.
Ahem, there was one death on campus.
It was a suicide back in '98.
Some kid named Barry Cook.
What?
[SIGHING]
I knew him. How'd he die?
He slit his wrists
in the first-floor girls' bathroom.
-That's where--
-Where the chick got swirlied to death.
So, what, this ghost is possessing nerds?
And using them to go after bullies, yeah.
Well, does that sound like Barry's M.O.?
Barry had a hard time.
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
JOCK:
Oops.
[GIGGLING]
Thanks, Sam.
Great school.
I don't care.
Three years and I'm out of here.
Going to Michigan State. They got
the best vet program in the country.
You like animals?
They're a lot nicer than people.
So tonight, I'm thinking you, me,
a bucket of popcorn, extra butter.
Hmm, kinky.
[GIGGLES]
And the midnight screening
of I Spit on Your Grave at the Cinedome.
AMANDA:
Unh.
I can't.
I have a curfew at 11.
So?
So if I break it,
my folks will ground me for a month.
Yeah, parents. Terrifying.
Mm-hm, when's your curfew?
I don't have one.
[CHUCKLES]
Your parents just let you
stay out all night, don't they?
My dad's out of town on a job.
It's just me and my brother.
Hmm, for how long?
Couple of weeks.
[CHUCKLES]
Seriously?
Yeah, we've got a pretty sweet setup
at the Pines.
Unh.
-The motel?
-Mm-hm.
HBO, Magic Fingers, free ice, it's great.
Yeah.
I guess.
I do whatever I want, whenever I want.
It's perfect.
Yeah...
...but don't you miss your dad?
Yo, Sammy.
That's your brother
with Amanda Heckerling?
-He's cool.
-Yeah.
He thinks so.
DIRK:
Hey, tough guy.
I've been looking for you.
Still wanna take Barry's place?
-Get out of here, Barry.
-I'll go get a teacher.
-Wanna go?
-I'm not gonna fight you, Dirk.
Why not? Chicken?
-Come on.
-No.
[STUDENTS GASP]
Get up.
Get up. Come on, get up.
Get back. Get back.
That is enough.
WYATT: Dirk? Dirk, stop.
BOY: You suck, Winchester.
WYATT:
Dirk, stop right there.
[FIRE ROARS]
So long, Barry Cook.
You all right?
Barry was my friend.
And I just burned his bones.
Well, he's at peace now, Sam.
If Dad had let us stay just a little longer...
...maybe I could have helped the kid,
you know?
You read the coroner's report
same as me.
Barry was on every anxiety drug
and antidepressant known to man.
School was hell for that kid.
His parents had split up.
He just wanted out.
It's tragic, but it's not your fault.
To tell you the truth, I'm glad we got out
of that town. I hated that school.
It wasn't all bad.
Heh, how can you say that
after what happened to you?
[STUDENTS YELLING]
DEAN: That kid's dead.
-Dean--
I'm gonna rip his lungs out!
-It's not a big deal.
-Not a big deal? Look at yourself.
-If Dad was here--
-He's not.
I am. And as soon as I'm finished
with that dick--
Just shut up, okay?
-I don't need your help.
-That's right, you don't.
You could have torn him apart.
So why didn't you?
Because I don't wanna be the freak
for once, Dean.
I wanna be normal.
So taking a beating, that's normal?
Any word from Dad?
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
He called this morning. He said
he's going to be another week, at least.
We weren't supposed to be here
this long.
At least you've got Amanda.
She's cool.
Dude, she wants me to meet her parents.
I don't do parents.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
Mr. Winchester, can I talk to you?
Um, I'll wait for you outside.
Look, if this is about the fight,
I didn't start it.
Oh, no, it's not about the fight, Sam.
You know this assignment
was nonfiction, right?
Yes, Mr. Wyatt.
So you and your family killed a werewolf
last summer, huh?
Why would you write
something like this, Sam?
It doesn't matter.
As soon as my dad gets back,
we're leaving.
-So you can flunk me if you want to.
-I'm not flunking you.
I'm giving you an A.
Aside from the werewolf...
...is that really
how you describe your family?
Yeah.
Well, your brother's quite a character.
And your father, he seems, uh, driven.
Anyway, it's good, Sam. It's really good.
Have you ever thought about
pursuing writing?
I can't.
I have to go into the family business.
Family business?
Yeah, my dad's a--
My dad's a mechanic.
So I have to be a mechanic too.
Do you wanna go
into the family business, Sam?
No one's ever asked me that before.
Well?
More than anything, no.
You know...
...I don't wanna, uh, overstep
my bounds here...
...but you don't have to do anything
you don't wanna do.
Look, I mean, I know what it's like.
I come from a family of surgeons,
and that wasn't me.
So, you know, I traded in the money
and prestige of being a doctor...
...for all the glamour you see around you.
The point is...
...there are maybe three or four big
choices that shape someone's whole life.
And you need to be the one
that makes them, not anyone else.
You seem like a great kid, Sam.
Just live the life you wanna live.
We came back here
so you could talk to the teacher?
He's a good guy.
Well, whatever.
Go have your Robin Williams,
"Oh, captain, my captain" moment.
Just make it quick.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
GIRL:
Excuse me, sir?
Can you tell me how to find room 305?
Sure, um--
Down the hall, take your first right
and it's the third door on the left.
Thanks, Sam.
[GRUNTS]
You got tall, Winchester.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
[SPIRIT THUDS]
[PANTING]
[OBJECTS CLANKING]
Trust me, this will help.
[SIGHS]
That ghost is dead.
I'm gonna rip its lungs out!
You know what I mean.
It knew my name, Dean.
My real name.
We burned Barry's bones.
-What the hell?
-Well, maybe it wasn't Barry.
Maybe we missed something.
We just gotta go back.
No way. How did we not see this before?
-What?
-Check it out.
Martha Dumptruck,
Revenge of the Nerds, Hello Kitty.
-They all rode the same bus.
-Okay, so maybe the bus is haunted.
That would explain why there's no EMF
at the school, but not the attacks.
Ghosts are tied to the places
that they haunt. They can't just bail.
Unless this one can.
There's lore about spirits
possessing people, riding them.
Whenever they leave the body, they're
bungeed back to their usual haunt.
But until then,
the ghosts can go wherever they want.
So a spook just grabs a kid on the bus
and walks right into Truman?
It's possible.
Ghosts getting creative,
well, that's super.
[EMF METER WHINING]
SAM:
Definitely ain't clean.
Here ghosty, ghosty, ghosty.
-Come out, come out, wherever you are.
-I don't get it.
No one ever died on this bus.
It's not like there's a body here.
But a flap of skin, a hair--
Hell, a hangnail--
Something's gotta be tying the ghost
to this place. We gotta find it.
SAM:
Yeah.
Got a new driving permit,
issued two weeks ago.
[CLICKS OFF EMF METER]
-Just before the first attack.
-Yeah.
Name of the bus driver
is Dirk MacGregor Sr.
39 North Central Avenue.
-MacGregor?
-Yeah.
What?
I knew his son.
You knew everybody at this school?
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
DIRK:
Gotta watch where you're going.
Leave him alone, Dirk.
You never learn, do you, midget?
Get to the bus, Barry.
[STUDENTS MURMURING]
What's the matter? Scared?
Don't worry, I'll go easy on you this time.
Come on, Losechester,
let's see what you got.
Come on, freak.
Freak.
[GRUNTING]
[STUDENTS GASPING
AND CHATTERING]
[STUDENTS GASP]
You're not tough. You're just a jerk.
Dirk the Jerk.
BOY 1: Hey, Dirk the Jerk.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
STUDENTS:
Yeah, totally. Dirk the Jerk.
BOY 2: Dirk the Jerk.
BOY 3: Dirk the Jerk.
STUDENTS [CHANTING]
Dirk the Jerk, Dirk the Jerk
Dirk the Jerk
SENIOR: So you were friends with Dirk?
SAM: Uh, yes, sir, in high school.
SENIOR: I don't recall
Dirk having many friends at Truman.
Sit down.
When did, uh-- When did Dirk pass?
He was 18.
What happened to him?
Well, there was, uh--
First, drinking, then drugs.
And then too many drugs and--
He just slipped through my fingers.
It was my fault.
I should have seen it coming, you know.
Dirk, he, uh-- He had his troubles.
What kind of troubles?
School was never easy for Dirk.
We didn't have much money...
...and, well, you know, kids,
they can be cruel. They picked on him.
They picked on him?
Mm-hm.
They called him poor and dirty and stupid.
They even had a nickname for him.
Dirk the Jerk.
-After what happened to his mother, he--
-His mother?
Yeah, Jane, my wife.
She died when Dirk was 13.
Cancer.
I was working three jobs,
so it fell to Dirk to take care of her.
And he was a great kid.
He made sure Jane got her medicine.
He helped her, cleaned up after her.
But, you know,
you watch somebody die, slow.
Waste away to nothing.
It does things to a person.
Horrible things.
I didn't know about his mother.
He-- He wouldn't talk about her...
...not even to me.
Lot of anger in that boy.
I'm sorry.
We'd really like to pay our respects,
Mr. MacGregor.
Um, do you mind telling us
where Dirk is buried?
Oh, he wasn't. I had him cremated.
All of him?
Well, I kept a lock of his hair.
Oh, that's-- That's nice.
Where do you keep that?
On my bus, in my Bible.
Thanks for subbing tonight, Eddie.
My pleasure, coach.
Eddie, you wanna ease up
on the pedal there?
I got it all under control.
[TIRES BURST]
What the hell was that?
[TIRES SQUEAL]
Everyone okay?
SAM:
Dirk.
[GUN CLICKS]
Winchester.
What are you gonna do, shoot me?
Don't need to.
That rope is soaked in salt water, Dirk.
You're not going anywhere.
Everybody stay where you are.
You'll be okay.
Aren't you the P.E. teacher?
Not really. I'm like 21 Jump Street.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
The bus driver sells pot.
Yeah.
It's not here!
-Where is it?
-No way you'll ever find it.
SAM:
Where is it?
Sam Winchester, still a bully.
You, you jocks.
You popular kids, you always thought
you were better than everybody else.
And to you,
I was just Dirk the Jerk, right?
Now you evil sons of bitches
are gonna get what's coming to you.
I'm not evil, Dirk.
I'm not.
And neither were you.
Trust me.
I've seen real evil.
We were scared and miserable
and we took it out on each other.
Us and everybody else.
That's high school.
But you suffer through that...
...and it gets better.
I'm just sorry you didn't get a chance
to see that.
You or Barry.
Nothing is gonna get better for me.
Not ever.
[EDDIE GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
[GRUNTING]
SAM:
Dirk, no.
Dean, find the hair.
[SAM GRUNTING]
Hey, buddy, this isn't what it looks like.
[BLOWS LANDING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[SAM STRUGGLING AND GASPING]
Little help.
Unh.
[CHOKES]
He's giving you the full cowgirl.
Yeah.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Five more minutes, Jerry.
[DOOR OPENS]
Amanda, hey.
Uh, Gettysburg Address, 1863, right?
[SIGHS]
History test next period, we're studying.
Come on, baby,
she means nothing to me. Don't be mad.
I'm not mad, Dean.
I thought maybe, underneath your whole
I-could-give-a-crap-bad-boy thing...
...that there was something
more going on.
I mean, like, the way you are
with your brother.
But I was wrong.
You spend so much time trying
to convince people that you're cool...
...but it's just an act.
We both know that you're just a sad,
lonely little kid.
And I feel sorry for you, Dean.
You feel sorry for me, huh?
Don't feel sorry for me.
You don't know anything about me.
I save lives.
I'm a hero.
A hero.
What?
GIRL 1: Good job.
BOY 1: Hey, way to go, Sam.
BOY 2:
Good job, buddy.
BOY 3:
Yeah, nice job, Winchester. Winchester.
BOY 4: Sam, great job
with Dirk the Jerk, ha, ha.
BOY 5:
Nice, Sam. Yeah, you know it.
BOY 6:
Sam the man.
GIRL 2: Hey, Sam, good job, man.
GIRL 3: Good job, Sam.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Dad?
Finally.
I can't wait to get the hell out of here.
This place sucks.
[CAR HONKING]
Come on, Sam.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Mr. Wyatt?
Yes.
You probably don't remember me, um--
But my name is Sam Winchester,
and, uh...
...I just wanted to thank you.
-For?
-I was a student here.
And, uh, you gave me some advice once.
Winchester. Right, right. Yeah, you, uh--
-You wrote that horror story.
-Yeah, yeah, I did.
Yeah, it's kind of all been
one long horror story, unh.
-What do you mean?
-Nothing, sorry.
So, what was this advice?
I might need to plagiarize myself
down the line.
You told me I didn't have to go
into the family business.
You said I should make my own choices.
Ah, so you managed
to do your own thing, huh?
Yeah, uh, for a while, yeah.
And I think I went to college
because of you.
But, you know, people grow up.
Yeah.
Responsibilities and--
But still, um...
...you took an interest in me
when no one else did.
That matters. So thank you.
Well, you know, the only thing
that really matters is, uh...
...that you're happy.
Are you happy, Sam?
[ENGLISH SDH]