-Why would an angel rescue me?
-Because we have work for you.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
ALASTAIR:
You got a lot to learn, boy.
Is it true? Did I break the first seal?
-Did I start all this?
-Yes.
Why didn't you just leave me there?
The righteous man who begins it
is the only one who can finish it.
You have to stop it.
Our fate rests with you.
Find someone else.
It's not me.
[BEEPS]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO]
WOMAN: NPR Morning Edition.
It's time for this waste and--
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
All I wanna know is when are they gonna
have another show like Project Runway?
Man.
Net profitability aside, it's the
client-retention rate that concerns me...
...vis-?-vis maximizing return on sales.
Buzz once you've seen the spreadsheets.
-Mr. Adler.
-Dean.
-Good stuff.
-Good stuff?
-Big things. Good stuff.
-Good stuff.
I hear you.
No, I haven't been to the gym in ages.
Carrying a little bloat around myself.
Heh-heh.
It's a sedentary lifestyle, my man,
no two ways.
All right, tell me one more time.
You said lemon and-- What was it?
Cayenne and maple syrup.
Are you serious? How much did you lose?
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[DOORS CLOSE]
[ELEVATOR WHIRRING]
-Do I know you?
-I don't think so.
I'm sorry, man,
you just look really familiar.
Save it for the health club, pal.
[PHONE RINGING]
Tech Support, this is Sam Wesson.
Okay. Well, did you try turning it off
and then on?
Okay, go ahead and turn it off.
No, no, no. Just off.
All right, give it a second.
Turn it back on.
Okay, is it printing now?
Great. Anytime.
-Hey.
-Yo.
What do you think of Mimi?
-She's okay.
-Might have to hit that.
Oh, dude, that's totally age-inappropriate.
-Experience.
-Trifocals.
There's a MILF there, Sam, I just know it.
-Maybe a GMILF.
-Come on.
-Coffee break?
-Yeah, for sure.
-Paul. Time for a refuel, buddy.
-Sorry, no time.
Since when?
-Dude, we get paid by the hour.
-Working.
-Okay.
-He seems stressed.
Freaked because he got busted
surfing porn on the Internet.
-No, no, no way. When?
-Got sent up to H.R. yesterday.
Guess they put the fear of God in him.
[MICROWAVE DINGS]
-Ian, dude.
-Just doing a little shopping.
Running low at home.
So, Sam, had any of those dreams lately?
What? Don't be like that.
Come on. It's the highlight of my day.
I never should have told you.
They're genius.
Don't hold out on me, dude.
Share with the class.
-You're just gonna be a dick about it.
-What? No way.
I won't say a word, total respect.
Go.
I dreamt that I saved a grim reaper
named Tessa from demons.
[LAUGHS]
Classic.
How much "DnD" did you play
when you were a kid?
Oh, my-- Okay, so you--
Rescuing the grim reaper.
That's-- You're a hero.
I mean, thank God we got Harry Potter
here to save us all from the apocalypse.
-Dick.
-Wizard.
[YAWNS]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[GASPS]
Can I ask you a question?
-I told you, I'm not into--
-Come on, I'm not either.
I just wanna ask you one question.
Sure.
What do you think about ghosts?
Ghosts?
Do you believe in them?
Uh, tell you the truth,
I've never given it much thought.
-Vampires?
-What? Why?
Because I've been having
some weird dreams lately.
You know what I mean?
No. Not really.
So you've never had any...
...weird dreams?
All right, look, man.
I don't know you, okay?
But I'm gonna do a public service...
...and let you know that you overshare.
Did you turn it off then on?
All right, well, let's try that.
No, no. It's fine, I'll wait.
Is it printing now? Oh, that's great.
Anytime.
IAN:
What you doing?
Nothing.
You get an e-mail from Human Resources?
No. Why?
Damn it. Guess it's just me then.
I'm supposed to, quote,
"Report to H.R.," unquote.
They're finally busting you
for snaking all those office supplies.
I hope they spank me.
PAUL: No, no, no. Come on.
Don't do this to me. Please.
SAM:
Hey, man, you okay?
It froze.
-They're crap. They freeze all the time.
-You don't understand.
When I rebooted, everything was gone,
a day's work.
-Well, did you back up?
-No, I didn't back up.
I wish to God I backed up, but I didn't.
I'll get it back. I'll find it.
It's somewhere. I'll find it.
Paul, it's okay, man.
These things happen.
PAUL:
Come on.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Please. Please.
All that work. Gone.
Failed.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[HEAD SQUELCHES]
[MICROWAVE DINGS]
[SIGHS]
Something about this
seem not right to you?
Yeah, try the whole thing.
I'm telling you, man,
I'll never eat popcorn again.
Yeah, right.
Two weeks?
Hey. Why would someone
kill themselves...
...two weeks
before they were supposed to retire?
I mean, Paul was two weeks
from freedom.
He should have been happy, right?
I don't have time for this, Sam.
That's very funny.
What's with you?
I'm working. It's important.
H.R. bust your balls or something?
You're wearing the shirt.
Did you shave?
[PHONE RINGS]
Tech Support, this is Ian.
Be right up.
Gotta go up to 22, speak to a manager.
Hi. Ian, is it? Yeah, come on in.
Yesterday you filled out a 445-T...
...and no problem, just a few errors
when we did your switch to Vista.
So I'm sure you're used to filling out
the dash-R's, right?
-Oh, no.
-No, no. It's fine, it's fine.
I just need you to redo one so I can get
the show on the road with the invoicing.
-Oh, my God.
-No, it's fine. Re-file it and we're square.
I can't believe I did this.
I can't believe I-- I can't believe I did this.
-Hey, guy, come on.
-No, no.
It affected profits, it--
I screwed up, I-- I can't-- I can't--
I am so sorry, I-- How could I do that?
I failed Sandover.
-I failed the company.
-Why don't you sit down, Ian?
-No.
-Ian? Ian. Hey.
Ian, hey. Just chill out, man. Okay?
It's--
Ian, hey, maybe we should
get out of here, huh? Come on.
Ian.
Look at me.
[IAN GASPING]
[IAN GURGLES]
Somebody help me!
No, I followed him into the bathroom.
He was-- He was standing there
in front of the mirror, and then....
COP:
Continue. Sir.
And he stabbed himself in the neck.
I'm sorry, that's....
[RINGS]
Tech Support, this is Sam.
DEAN:
I need to see you in my office. Now.
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Come on in. Shut the door.
Who the hell are you?
[SCOFFS]
-I'm not sure I know.
-What the hell does that mean?
Sam Wesson.
I started here three weeks ago.
All right, you cornered me
in the elevator...
...talking about ghosts.
And now....
Now what?
Now nothing. I, uh....
So you started working here
three weeks ago, huh?
Yeah, me too.
It's the Master Cleanse. You tried it?
Phenomenal.
Detoxes you like nobody's business.
When you were in that bathroom
with Ian...
...did you see something?
I don't know. I don't know what I saw.
Wait. Are you saying that--?
Did you see a ghost?
I was freaking out.
The guy penciled his damn neck.
You did, didn't you? Okay, listen.
What if these suicides aren't suicides?
I mean, what if they're
something not natural?
So, what, ghosts are real?
And they're responsible
for all the dead bodies around here?
Is that what you're telling me?
I know it sounds crazy.
But yes. That's what I'm telling you.
Uh-huh. Based on what?
Instinct.
-I've got the same instinct.
-Seriously?
You know those dreams
I was telling you about?
-I was dreaming about ghosts.
-Yeah.
And then it turns out
that there's a real ghost.
So you're telling me that your dreams
are special visions...
...and you're some kind of psychic?
No, I mean, that would be nuts.
I'm just saying something weird
is definitely going on around here, right?
So I've been digging around a little.
I think I found a connection
between the two guys.
You broke into their e-mail accounts?
I used some skills that I happen to have
to satisfy my curiosity.
Nice.
Yeah. Okay. So it turns out Ian and Paul
both got this same e-mail...
...telling them to report to H.R.,
Room 1444.
-H.R.'s on seven.
-Exactly.
-Should we go check this out?
-Like right now?
No. No, it's getting late. You're right.
-I am dying to check this out right now.
-Right?
Hello?
[RUMBLING]
[MAN YELLS]
Whoa.
-How'd you know how to do that?
-I have no idea.
Holy crap, dude.
Yeah. I could use a beer.
Oh, sorry, man. I'm on the cleanse.
I got rid of all the carbs in the house.
Hey. How the hell did you know
that ghosts are scared of wrenches?
Crazy, right?
And nice job kicking that door too.
That was very Jet Li.
What are you,
like a black belt or something?
No. I have no clue how I did that.
It's like we've done this before.
What do you mean, "before"?
Like Shirley MacLaine before?
No.
I can't shake this feeling
like I don't belong here.
You know? Like I should do
something more than sit in a cubicle.
I think most people who work
in a cubicle feel that way.
No. Well, look, it's more than that.
Like, I don't like my job.
I don't like this town.
I don't like my clothes.
I don't like my own last name.
I don't know how else
to explain it, except that...
...it feels like I should be doing
something else.
There's just something in my blood.
Like I was destined
for something different.
What about you?
You ever feel that way?
I don't believe in destiny.
I do believe in dealing
with what's right in front of us, though.
All right, so, what do we do now?
We do what I do best, Sammy. Research.
Okay.
Did you just call me Sammy?
Did I?
I think you did. Yeah.
Don't.
Sorry.
-Oh, jackpot.
-What you got?
I just found the best site ever.
Real, actual ghost hunters.
These guys are genius. Check it out.
Instructional videos?
-We know why you're watching.
-You've got a problem.
-A ghost problem.
-A ghost-related problem.
A ghost-- It's like a ghost-adjacent pr--
It's like a problem that's--
Whatever.
You've come to the right place.
The only decent place, really, because
the Ghostfacers know how to solve it.
-Period.
-Watch and learn.
The first step in any supernatural fight:
[BOTH READ ON-SCREEN TEXT]
That's him. That's the ghost.
P.T. Sandover. Died 1916.
Devoted his life to his work.
No wife, no kids.
Used to say he was the company.
His very blood
pumped through the building.
Wow, okay. So slight workaholic.
Maybe he's still here, you know,
watching over the company...
...even killing for it.
Plus, this isn't the first time people
started killing themselves in the building.
1929.
But lots of guys jumped off
high rises that year.
How many companies had 17 suicides?
Phew.
Okay, so P.T. Sandover,
protector of the company.
His ghost wakes up and becomes active
during times of grave economic distress.
The worst time
since the Great Depression--
Is now. Yeah, now sucks.
My portfolio's in the sewer.
I don't even wanna talk about it.
-So Sandover's helping the bottom line--
-By zapping some model employees.
Yeah. I mean, Ian and Paul.
It was like he turned them
into different people.
Perfect worker bees, exactly.
So devoted to the company...
...that they would commit hara-kiri
if they failed it.
One more interesting fact,
the building wasn't always that high.
Used to be 14 floors.
And the room
where the ghost attacked, 1444?
Once upon a time,
that was the old man's office.
HARRY: Once you've got that thing
in your sights--
-You kill it.
-Using special ghost-hunting weapons.
-First, salt.
It's like acid to ghosts.
Burny acid.
-Not LSD.
-No. It's a bad trip for ghosts.
Next up, iron.
-That's why the wrench worked.
ED: Pure power in your hand.
HARRY:
Dissipates ghosts instantly.
Next little trick. We learnt this
from those useless douche bags--
-That we hate.
-The Winchesters.
-Gun.
-Shotgun shell.
Pack it up with fresh rock salt.
-Very effective.
-Winchesters still suck ass, though.
-Affirmative.
Suckage, major.
Where do we even get a gun?
Gun store?
-Isn't there some kind of waiting period?
-I think so.
-How in the hell--?
-I don't know. Seems pretty impossible.
Right.
The aforementioned super annoying
Winchester douche-nozzles...
-...also taught us this one other thing.
-You have to burn the remains.
Okay, this next part gets a little gross.
Sometimes you might have to dig up
the body.
-Sorry.
-It's illegal in some states.
-All states.
-Possibly all states.
-Sandover was cremated.
-What?
So, what do we do now?
Now, if the deceased has been cremated--
-Don't panic.
-Gotta look for some other remains.
HARRY: A hair in a locket.
-Fingernails, baby teeth--
-Milk teeth.
Genetic material.
You know what we're talking about.
Go find it.
-Fight well, young lions.
-Godspeed.
Set your cell phone to walkie-talkie
in case we get separated.
How are we gonna find some ancient
speck of DNA in a skyscraper?
Well, that creepy storeroom
used to be Sandover's office, right?
[CREAKS]
What the hell are you doing here?
-Nothing. I just--
-Come with me.
Man, listen. Look. It's okay, I work here.
Whatever. Tell it to the cops.
[ELEVATOR SCREECHES]
Well, come on.
[METAL GROANING]
What?
Last time this happened,
it took them two hours to get here.
Let's just wait.
Seriously, I'll wait.
Look, I don't have the rest
of my life here.
DEAN [OVER PHONE]:
Hey. You okay?
Call you back.
-Dean, you there?
DEAN: Yeah, listen, I think I got it.
-Meet me on 22.
-Okay, yeah. Just take the stairs.
Whoa.
That's a lot of blood.
Yeah, I know.
Right. So in there.
P.T. Sandover's gloves.
How much you wanna bet
there's a smidge of DNA in there?
Like a fingernail clipping or a hair?
Something.
So you ready?
I have no idea.
Me neither.
-Go for it.
-All right.
[DEAN GRUNTS]
[SAM GRUNTS]
Oh. Nice.
Dean.
[SAM CHUCKLES]
-Nice catch.
-Right?
-That was amazing.
Right?
Man, I gotta tell you.
I've never had so much fun in my life.
Me neither.
Was a hell of a workout too, wasn't it?
-We should keep doing this.
-I know.
I mean it.
There gotta be other ghosts out there.
-We could help a lot of people.
-Right, we'd be like the Ghostfacers.
No, really. I mean, for real.
What? Like, quit our jobs
and hit the road?
Exactly.
How would we live?
You gotta be kidding me. How would we
get by, with stolen credit cards?
Huh? Eating diner food
drenched in saturated fats?
Sharing a crap motel every night?
-All just details.
-Details are everything.
You don't wanna go fighting ghosts
without health insurance.
[SAM CLEARS THROAT]
All right. Uh....
-Confession.
-What?
Remember those dreams I told you about
with the ghosts?
Yeah?
I was fighting them.
-Okay.
-With you.
We were these, like, hunters...
...and we were friends.
More like brothers, really.
I mean, what if that's who we really are?
You saw us back there working together.
The ghost was scrambling brains.
What if it scrambled ours?
-That's insane.
-Is it?
Think about it for just one second.
What if we think this is our life,
but it's not?
The ghost is dead, we're still standing.
I mean, I'm sorry, but--
Look, all I know is,
this isn't who we're supposed to be.
No. I'm Dean Smith, okay?
Director of Sales and Marketing.
I went to Stanford.
My father's name is Bob,
my mother, Ellen, and my sister, Jo.
When's the last time you talked to them?
-To any of them?
-Okay, you're upset. Upset, confused--
Yeah, I only moved here because
I broke up with my fianc?e, Madison.
But I called her number
and I got a damn animal hospital.
Okay. What are you saying?
Are you trying to say
that my family isn't real? Huh?
That we've been injected
with fake memories? Come on.
All I know is, I got this feeling in my gut.
And I know.
I know that deep down,
you gotta be feeling it too.
We're supposed to be something else.
You're not just
some corporate douche bag.
This isn't you.
I know you.
Know me?
You don't know me, pal.
You should go.
[PHONE RINGING]
I quit.
-Got a minute?
-Sure, of course.
How are you feeling, Dean?
-Uh, great.
-You look a little tired.
-Been working hard, I gather.
-Yeah.
Ah, don't be modest, I hear everything.
And I'm pleased with what I'm hearing.
That's why it's important to me
that you're happy.
How's that for a bonus?
-That's very generous.
-Purely selfish.
Wanna make sure
you're not going anywhere.
Wow.
-Are you sure?
-Positive.
You are Sandover material, son.
Real go-getter.
Carving your own way.
-Well, thanks. I try.
-I see big things in your future.
Maybe even Senior VP,
Eastern Great Lakes Division.
Don't get me wrong,
you'll have to work for it.
Seven days a week, lunch at your desk.
But in eight to 10 short years,
that could be you.
Well, thank you. Thank you, sir.
It's, um....
But...
...I am giving my notice.
This is a joke. You're kidding me, right?
No. I've--
I recently--
Very recently realized that
I have some other work I have to do.
It's very important to me.
-Other work? Another company?
-No, I-- It's hard to explain.
It's just that this--
This is-- It's just--
It's not who I'm supposed to be.
-What?
-Dean, Dean, Dean.
Finally.
The hell?
Why am I wearing a tie?
My God, am I hungry.
Welcome back.
Wait. Did I--?
Did I just get touched by--?
-You're an angel, aren't you?
-I'm Zachariah.
Oh, great. That's all I need
is another one of you guys.
I'm hardly another one, Dean.
I'm Castiel's superior.
Believe me, I had no interest in popping
here into one of these smelly things.
But after the unfortunate situation
with Uriel...
...I felt it necessary to pay a visit.
-Get my ducks in a row.
-I am not one of your ducks.
Starting with your attitude.
Oh, so, what?
This was all some sort of a lesson?
Is that what you're telling me? Wow.
-Very creative.
-You should see my decoupage.
Gross. No, thank you.
So, what? I'm just hallucinating all this?
Is that it?
Not at all. Real place, real haunting.
Just plunked you in the middle
without the benefit of your memories.
Just to shake things up?
So you can have fun watching us run
around like ass clowns in monkey suits?
To prove to you that the path you're on
is truly in your blood. You're a hunter.
Not because your dad made you, not
because God called you back from hell.
But because it is what you are.
You love it. You find your way to it in
the dark and you're miserable without it.
Dean, let's be real here.
You're good at this.
You'll be successful. You will stop it.
Stop what?
The apocalypse, huh?
Lucifer? What? Be specific, man.
You'll do everything
you're destined to do. All of it.
But I know, I know.
You're not strong enough, you're scared.
You got daddy issues.
You can't do it. Right?
Angel or not, I will stab you in your face.
All I'm saying is...
...it's how you look at it.
Most folks live and die without moving
more than the dirt it takes to bury them.
You get to change things.
Save people, maybe even the world.
All the while you drive a classic car
and fornicate with women.
This isn't a curse, it's a gift.
So for God's sakes, Dean,
quit whining about it.
Look around.
There are plenty of fates
worse than yours.
So are you with me?
You wanna go steam yourself
another latte?
Or are you ready to stand up...
...and be who you really are?
[ENGLISH SDH]