Lilith is trying to break the
66 Seals to free Lucifer from hell.
RUBY: Girl named Anna Milton escaped
from a locked ward yesterday.
The demons seem keen on finding her.
Pamela Barnes,
best damn psychic in the state.
[SCREAMS]
ANNA:
The angels talk about you.
You were in hell
but Castiel pulled you out.
Some think you can save us.
-So you talk to angels?
-I overhear them.
Now we know
why the demons want you.
This is Uriel. A specialist.
-Hello again, Dean.
-Uhn!
Don't you recognize me?
But we were so close.
-In hell.
-Alastair.
-They're coming.
-Back room.
We're here for Anna.
-Are you gonna help her?
-She has to die.
You want Anna?
-Why?
-Out of the way.
Whoa. Okay, I knew she's wiretapping
your angel chats or whatever.
-But it's no reason to gank her.
-Don't worry.
I'll kill her gentle.
You're some heartless sons of bitches,
you know that?
As a matter of fact, we are. And?
And Anna's an innocent girl.
She is far from innocent.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means she's worse than this
abomination you've been screwing.
Now, give us the girl.
Sorry. Get yourself another one.
-Try JDate.
-Who's gonna stop us? You two?
Or this demon whore?
[GRUNTING]
Cass, stop. Please.
I've been waiting for this.
[GROANS]
[BOTH PANTING]
What the--?
[GRUNTS]
DEAN:
Come on.
[GRUNTS]
DEAN:
Anna? Anna.
Are they gone?
-Did you kill them?
ANNA: No.
I sent them away.
Far away.
You want to tell me how?
That just popped in my head.
I don't know how I did it.
I just did it.
[DOOR CLOSES, DEAN SNIFFS]
What do you think?
Anna's getting more interesting
by the second.
Yeah, I agree. And what did they
mean by she's not innocent?
It seems they want her bad, not just
because of the angel radio thing.
I mean, that blood spell?
It's some serious crap, man.
Something's going on with her.
-See what you can find.
-What are you gonna do?
Anna may have sent the angels to
the outfield but they're gonna be back.
We gotta get ourselves safe now.
[SIGHS]
[TAPPING ON WALL]
Iron walls drenched in salt.
Demons can't even touch the joint.
-Which I find racist, by the way.
-Write to your congressman.
Here.
-Hex bags?
-Extra-crunchy.
Hide us from angels,
demons, all comers.
Thanks, Ruby.
Don't lose this.
So, Anna, what's playing on angel radio?
Anything useful?
It's quiet.
Dead silence.
Good. That's not troubling at all.
We're in trouble, huh?
You guys are scared?
No.
SAM:
Hey, Dean.
Just stay here, okay?
Keep an eye on her.
DEAN: How's the car?
-I got her, she's fine.
-Where's Bobby?
-The Dominican.
-Said we break anything, we buy it.
-Is he working a job?
Hope so. Otherwise, he's at Hedonism
in a banana hammock and a trucker cap.
-That's seared in my brain.
-What'd you find on Anna?
Not much.
Her parents were Rich and Amy Milton.
-A church deacon and a housewife.
DEAN: Riveting.
SAM:
There is something here in the report.
Turns out this latest
psych episode wasn't her first.
When she was 2 and a half, she'd
get hysterical anytime her dad got close.
She was convinced that
he wasn't her real daddy.
Who was? The plumber? Hmm?
Little snaking the pipes? Heh.
Dude, you're confusing
reality with porn again.
Anna didn't say.
She just kept repeating...
...that this real father
of hers was mad. Very mad.
-Like wanted-to-kill-her mad.
-Kind of heavy for a 2-year-old.
Well, she saw a kid's shrink,
got better and grew up normal.
Until now. So, what's she hiding?
ANNA: Why don't you
just ask me to my face?
-Nice job watching her.
-I'm watching her.
No, you're right, Anna.
-Is there anything you wanna tell us?
ANNA: About what?
The angels said
you were guilty of something.
-Why would they say that?
-You tell me.
Tell me why my life has been leveled...
...why my parents are dead.
I don't know.
I swear,
I would give anything to know.
Okay. Then let's find out.
How?
[DOOR CLOSES]
We're here.
SAM:
Pamela. Hey.
-Sam. Sam?
-Yeah, It's me, Sam. Yeah?
-Sam, is that you?
-I'm right here.
Oh. Know how I can tell?
[SLAPS, SAM GRUNTS]
That perky little ass of yours.
Bounce a nickel off that thing.
Ha-ha-ha.
Of course, I know it's you, Grumpy.
Same way I know that's a demon
and that poor girl's Anna.
And that you've been eyeing my rack.
[SAM STAMMERS]
[LAUGHS]
Don't sweat it, kiddo.
I still got more senses than most.
-Anna. How are you? I'm Pamela.
-Hi.
Dean told me what's been
going on. I'm excited to help.
-That's nice of you.
-Well, not really.
Any chance I can dick over an angel,
I'm taking it.
-Why?
-They stole something from me.
Demony, I know. But they're
just plastic. Good for business.
Makes me look extra-psychic,
don't you think?
Ha-ha-ha. Now, how about you
tell me what your deal is?
Hmm? Heh-heh-heh.
Don't you worry.
PAMELA:
Nice and relaxed.
Now, I'm going to
count down from five to zero.
When we're at zero, you'll be
in a deep state of hypnosis.
As I count down,
just go deeper and deeper, okay?
Five, four, three...
...two, one.
Deep sleep.
Every muscle, calm and relaxed.
-Can you hear me?
-I can hear you.
Now, Anna, tell me...
...how can you hear the angels?
How did you work that spell?
I don't know. I just did.
Your father, what's his name?
-Rich Milton.
-All right.
But I want you to look further back...
...when you were very young.
Just a couple of years old.
-I don't wanna.
-It'll be okay, Anna.
-Just one look, that's all we need.
-No.
What's your dad's name?
Your real dad.
-Why is he angry at you?
-No. No.
No! No!
PAMELA: Calm down.
-No, he's gonna kill me!
PAMELA: Anna? You're safe.
ANNA: No!
-He's gonna kill me!
-Calm down. It's all right, Anna.
-Dean, don't.
-Aah! Aah! Aah!
Wake in one, two, three, four, five.
Anna?
[EXHALES]
You all right?
[SIGHS]
Thank you, Pamela.
That helped a lot.
-I remember now.
-Remember what?
Who I am.
I'll bite. Who are you?
I'm an angel.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not like the others.
-I don't find that very reassuring.
-Neither do I.
So, Castiel, Uriel,
they're the ones that came for me?
-You know them?
-We were kind of in the same foxhole.
So, what were they, like,
your bosses or something?
-Try the other way around.
-Look at you.
-But now they wanna kill you?
-Orders are orders.
I'm sure I have a death sentence
on my head.
-Why?
-I disobeyed...
...which, for us,
is about the worst thing you can do.
-I fell.
-Meaning?
-She fell to Earth. Became human.
-Wait a minute, I don't understand.
-Angels can just become human?
-Kind of hurts.
Try cutting your kidney out with
a butter knife. That kind of hurt.
I ripped out my grace.
-Come again?
-My grace. It's energy.
Hacked it out and fell.
My mother, Amy,
couldn't get pregnant.
Always called me her little miracle.
She had no idea how right she was.
So you just forgot that you
were God's little Power Ranger?
The older I got,
the longer I was human, yeah.
I don't think you appreciate
how completely screwed we are.
-Ruby's right. Heaven wants me dead.
-And hell just wants her.
A flesh and blood angel that you
can question, torture, that bleeds.
Sister, you're the Stanley Cup.
And sooner or later...
-...heaven or hell, they're gonna find you.
ANNA: I know.
And that's why I'm gonna get it back.
-What?
-My grace.
-You can do that?
-If I can find it.
So what? You're just gonna
take some divine bong hit.
-And shazam, you're Roma Downey?
-Something like that.
All right. I like this plan.
So where's this grace of yours?
Lost track. I was falling about
10,000 miles per hour at the time.
-Wait, you mean falling, like, literally?
-Yes.
Like the way a human eye can see?
Like a comet, maybe, or a meteor?
-Why do you ask?
-Here, in March '85...
...a meteorite vanished in the
night sky over Northwestern Ohio.
It was sighted nine months
before Anna was born.
And she was born in that part of Ohio.
-Pretty buff for a nerd.
-Look, I think it was Anna.
And here, same time,
another meteor over Kentucky.
-And that's her grace?
-Might be.
All right, just narrows
it down to an entire state.
Look, it's a start.
Sam, I'm sorry.
-For what?
-For bringing you this mess.
If I'd known,
I would've kept my trap shut.
-Well, we'll muddle through.
-Not this time.
You do not wanna get
between these armies.
It's Godzilla and Mothra. If one side
doesn't get us, the other one will.
So, what do you wanna do?
Dump Anna and run?
Forget it. Look...
-...I know angels freak you out--
-Forget angels. It's Alastair I'm scared of.
-Alastair?
-You met him.
Practically, the grand inquisitor
downstairs. Picasso with a razor.
And?
And you should pull him out
and throw him back in the pit.
If you weren't so out of shape.
Your abilities are getting flabby.
-Yeah, so how do I tone up?
-You know how.
You know what you gotta do.
-I'm not doing that anymore.
-Sam....
I said no.
Well, then you better pray
that Anna gets her groove back.
Or we're all dead.
Pamela get home okay?
Yeah, she said she was sorry.
It's just after last time, she....
This is just a little
too rich for her blood.
I don't blame her.
You guys should do the same.
Well, we're not that smart.
Can I ask you something?
What do they want me for?
-Why did they save me?
-I'm sorry.
The angels aren't talking about it.
And it was after I fell.
That's another question.
Why would you fall?
Why would you wanna be one of us?
-You don't mean that.
-I don't?
A bunch of miserable bastards.
I mean, eating, crapping...
-...confused, afraid.
-I don't know. There's loyalty.
Forgiveness. Love.
-Pain.
-Chocolate cake.
-Guilt.
-Sex.
Yeah, you got me there.
I mean it. Every emotion, Dean.
Even the bad ones.
It's why I fell.
It's why I'd give anything...
...not to have to go back.
Anything.
-Feelings are overrated, if you ask me.
-Beats being an angel.
How's that possible?
You guys are powerful and perfect.
You don't doubt yourselves.
Or God. Or anything.
Perfect. Like a marble statue.
Cold. No choice. Only obedience.
Dean, do you know how many
angels have actually seen God?
-Seen his face?
-All of you?
Four angels.
Four. And I'm not one of them.
That's it?
Well, then how do you
even know that there is a God?
We have to take it on faith,
which we're killed if we don't have.
Huh.
I was stationed on Earth 2000 years.
Just watching.
Silent.
Invisible.
Out on the road. Sick for home.
Waiting on orders from
an unknowable father...
...I can't begin to understand.
So don't tell me that--
[CHUCKLES]
-What is so funny? What?
-Nothing, sorry. It's just....
I can relate.
SAM:
Hey.
-Did you find something?
-I think so.
SAM: Union, Kentucky.
Found some accounts of a local miracle.
Yeah. In '85, there was
an empty field outside of town.
Six months later,
there was a full grown oak.
They say it looks a century old,
at least.
-Anna, what do you think?
-The grace.
Where it hit, it could have
done something like that. Easy.
So grace ground zero.
It's not destruction.
-It's....
-Pure creation.
[CHUCKLES]
What?
Nothing. It's just an angel
and a demon, riding in the back seat.
[CHUCKLES]
It's like the setup to a bad joke.
Or a Penthouse forum letter.
Dude, reality. Porn.
You call this reality?
It's beautiful.
It's where the grace touched down.
I can feel it.
-You ready to do this?
-Not really.
Anna, what are we even looking for?
It doesn't matter. It's not here.
Not anymore.
Someone took it.
DEAN: We still got the hex bags. I say
we head back to the panic room.
-What, forever?
-I'm just thinking out loud.
-You call that thinking?
-Hey, hey. Stop it.
Anna's grace is gone,
you understand?
She can't angel up and protect us.
We can't fight heaven and hell.
One side, maybe,
but not both. Not at once.
Guys, the angels are talking again.
-What're they saying?
-It's weird. Like a recording.
A loop. It says:
"Dean Winchester gives us
Anna by midnight, or...."
Or what?
"Or we hurl him back to damnation."
Anna, do you know of any weapon
that works on an angel?
To what? To kill them?
Nothing we could get to.
Not right now.
Okay, wait. I say we call Bobby,
we get him back from Hedonism....
Dean, what's he gonna tell us?
I don't know.
But we gotta think of something.
Hey. Holding up okay?
-Trying.
-Yeah.
Little scared, I guess.
So, Dean.
I just wanted to thank you.
-For what?
-Everything.
-You guys didn't have to help me--
-Hey.
Let's can the "thanks for trying"
speech, you know?
Participation trophies suck ass.
I don't know.
Maybe I don't deserve to be saved.
Don't talk like that.
I disobeyed. Lucifer disobeyed.
It's our murder one and I knew it.
Maybe I gotta pay.
Yeah, well, we've all
done things we got to pay for.
I gotta tell you something.
-You're not gonna like it.
-Okay, what?
About a week ago,
I heard the angels talking...
...about you, what you did in hell?
Dean...
...I know.
It wasn't your fault.
You should forgive yourself.
Anna, I don't wanna....
I don't wanna....
-I can't talk about that.
-I know.
But when you can...
...you have people that wanna help.
You're not alone.
That's all I'm trying to say.
What was that for?
You know, our last night on Earth.
All that.
You're stealing my best line.
Hello, Ruby.
-Alastair.
-I have to say...
...I'm surprised to find you
out in the open like this.
Yeah? Desperate times.
That they are.
You looking for this?
Your gawky human friend
gave it to me.
Keep it. I just came to talk.
About what? About how a demon
is protecting an angel?
We really must revoke
your membership.
Look, I know I'm not
employee of the month. But this?
I never wanted to get
in the middle of this.
-Why are you here, Ruby?
-I'll give you the angel.
-Will you? And in return?
-I walk away.
Me and the Winchester boys,
both of them.
This angel business,
it's none of our business.
Hmm.
You know,
I'd always heard that you were...
...a devious, cowardly little slut.
You don't disappoint.
-So, what do you say?
-It's interesting. Prudent.
[GASPS]
But...
...let me make you...
...a counteroffer.
[DOOR CREAKS]
URIEL:
Look at that.
So cute the monkeys wear clothes.
-I'm dreaming, aren't I?
-It's the only way we could chat.
Since you're hiding like cowards.
Don't normally see you off leash.
Where's your boss?
Castiel? Oh, he's....
He's not here. You see,
he has this weakness. He likes you.
Time's up, boy. We want the girl.
Wouldn't try that if I were you.
See, she got her grace back.
Full-blown angel now.
That would be a neat trick, considering...
...I have her grace right here.
We can't let hell
get their hooks into her.
Why don't you give her back
her angel juice?
-She committed a serious crime.
-What? Thinking for herself?
This is our business, not yours.
She's not even human, not technically.
I guess I just like being
a pain in the pooper.
No.
There's more.
[CHUCKLES]
You cut yourself a slice of...
...angel-food cake.
Didn't you? Huh? You did.
[LAUGHS]
What do you care?
You're junk-less down there...
-...like a Ken doll?
-Hoo-hoo-hoo.
Well, it's your last chance.
-Give us the girl or....
-Or what?
What,
you'll toss me back in the hole?
-You're bluffing.
-Try me.
It's a whole lot bigger than
the plans we have for you, Dean.
You can be replaced.
What the hell?
Go ahead and do it.
You're just crazy enough to go,
aren't you?
What can I say? I don't break easy.
Oh, yes.
You do.
You just gotta know
where to apply the right pressure.
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[SLICING]
[WHIMPERING]
ALASTAIR: You know the problem
with your generation?
Instant gratification.
It's all now, now, now.
No patience, no craftsmanship.
But I do have to say, this knife of yours...
...it's an exquisite piece.
You must tell me where you found it.
[GROANING]
You know, I haven't been up here...
...since Poland, '43.
[SLICING AND SCREAMING RESUME]
Truth is, I loathe it. It's chilly.
No stink of blood or sizzle of flesh.
Or the wet flap of flayed skin.
I don't know how you stand it.
So sooner you cooperate,
the sooner I can finish up...
...with this ghastly angel business
and return home to my studies.
But no rush. Let's take our time.
Relish the moment.
Now, I'm going to remove this...
...don't go smoking out of that meat.
You won't get very far.
[GASPING]
Now you tell me where that angel is.
-No.
-No?
No.
I tell you...
...you kill me.
But I'll show you.
[CHUCKLES]
I don't know, man. Where's Ruby?
Hey, she's your hell buddy.
It's a little early for that, isn't it?
[EXHALES]
It's 2 a.m. somewhere.
-You okay?
-Yeah, of course.
[WIND HOWLING]
Hello, Anna. It's good to see you.
How? How did you find us?
Dean?
I'm sorry.
Why?
Because they gave him a choice.
They either kill me or kill you.
I know how their minds work.
You did the best you could.
I forgive you.
Okay, no more tricks.
No more running.
I'm ready.
I'm sorry.
No. You're not.
Not really.
You don't know the feeling.
Still, we have a history. It's just....
Orders are orders. I know.
Just make it quick.
Don't you touch a hair
on that poor girl's head.
How dare you come in this room...
...you pussing sore?
Name-calling?
That hurt my feelings.
You sanctimonious, fanatical prick.
Turn around and walk away now.
Sure. Just give us the girl.
We'll make sure
she gets punished good and proper.
You know who we are
and what we will do.
I won't say it again.
Leave now or we lay you to waste.
Think I'll take my chances.
[GRUNTING]
Sorry, kiddo.
Why don't you go run to Daddy?
[SCREAMS]
[SPEAKING IN LATIN]
[GRUNTS]
ALASTAIR: Dean, Dean, Dean.
I am so disappointed.
You had such promise.
[BOTH GASPING, GRUNTING]
-No!
-Uhn!
[GASPING]
[GRUNTS]
ANNA:
Shut your eyes.
Shut your eyes!
[SCREAMING]
[ANNA GRUNTS]
[CREAKING]
[GRUNTS]
What are you waiting for?
Aren't you gonna go get Anna?
Unless, of course, you're scared.
This isn't over.
It looks over to me, junk-less.
[FLAPPING]
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
You okay?
Not so much.
-What took you so long to get here?
-Sorry I'm late with the demon delivery.
I was only being tortured.
Well, I gotta hand it to you, Sammy.
Bringing them all together, all at once...
...angels and demons?
It's a damn good plan.
Yeah, well, when you got
Godzilla and Mothra on your ass...
...best to let them fight.
DEAN:
Now you're just bragging.
So I guess she's some
big-time angel now, huh?
She must be happy...
...wherever she is.
I doubt it.
Can't believe we made it out of there.
Again.
[EXHALES]
I know you heard him.
Who?
Alastair. What he said.
About how I had promise.
I heard him.
-You're not curious?
-Dean, I'm damn curious.
But you're not talking about hell
and I'm not pushing.
It wasn't four months, you know.
What?
It was four months up here,
but down there....
I don't know, time's different.
It was more like 40 years.
-My God.
-They....
They sliced and carved...
...and tore at me in ways that you....
Until there was nothing left.
And then suddenly...
...I would be whole again.
Like magic.
Just so they could start it all over.
And Alastair,
at the end of every day...
...every one...
...he would come over...
...and he would make me an offer.
To take me off the rack...
...if I put souls on.
If I started the torture.
And everyday, I told him
to stick it where the sun shines.
For 30 years, I told him.
But then I couldn't
do it anymore, Sammy.
I couldn't.
Then I got off that rack.
God help me, I got right off it
and I started ripping them apart.
I lost count of how many souls.
[SNIFFLES]
The things that I did to them.
Dean, ahem....
You held out for 30 years.
That's longer than anyone would have.
[SNIFFLING]
How I feel....
This....
Inside me.
I wish I couldn't feel anything,
Sammy.
I wish I couldn't feel a damn thing.
[ENGLISH SDH]