You know how I feel about Halloween.
-Who are you?
-Castiel.
-What are you?
CASTIEL: An angel of the Lord.
The Rising of the Witnesses
is one of the 66 seals.
Those seals are being broken by Lilith.
-Last one opens and...?
-Lucifer walks free.
DEAN: So you've been
using your freaky ESP stuff?
SAM: No.
-Well, let's keep it that way.
SAM:
I'm just exorcising demons.
DEAN: With your mind!
SAM: I can send them back to hell.
-Try to see the other side.
-The other side?
I'm pulling demons
out of innocent people.
-Use the knife.
SAM: The knife kills the victim.
What I do, most of them survive.
You should show me some respect.
I dragged you out of hell.
I can throw you back in.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
GIRL 1: Throw them out?
GIRL 2: Yeah, pour it out.
GIRL 1:
Oh, yeah, put that on top. That's cool.
GIRL 2:
Put it on the side.
-How was the store?
-Oh, madness.
Yeah.
Everyone in town was stocking up.
Hi, sweet pea.
Did you get enough?
I had to arm-wrestle
Norma Bleeker for these.
-Honey, she's 74.
-And a lot stronger than she looks.
Eh-eh-eh.
Remember last year? We ran out at 6:30.
-It's just one piece.
-Eh-eh-eh. You can have...
...as much as you want after Halloween.
-Come on.
-No.
Who needs a bath?
Huh? Huh?
There we go. You coming?
Yeah. I'll be up in a minute.
Okay.
Where's Mommy?
Luke? What's taking you so long?
[SCREAMS]
Now, how many razor blades
did they find?
Two on the floor, one in his stomach...
...and one was stuck in his throat.
He swallowed four of them.
How is that even possible?
The candy was never in the oven.
We just have to be thorough,
Mrs. Wallace.
Did police find razors
in the rest of the candy?
No. I mean, I don't know.
I don't think so.
I just....
I can't believe it.
You hear urban legends about this stuff,
but it actually happens?
SAM:
More than you might imagine.
Mrs. Wallace, did Luke have any enemies?
Enemies?
Anyone who might've held a grudge?
-What do you mean?
-Coworkers, neighbors.
Maybe a woman.
Are you suggesting an affair?
-Is it possible?
-No.
No, Luke would nev--
I'm very sorry.
We just have to consider all possibilities.
If someone wanted to kill my husband,
don't you think...
...they'd find a better way than a razor
in a piece of candy he might eat?
Really?
After that guy choked
down all those razor blades?
It's Halloween, man.
Yeah. For us, every day is Halloween.
Don't be a downer. Anything interesting?
Well, we're on a witch-hunt,
that's for sure, but this...
...isn't your typical hex bag.
-No?
-Goldthread.
An herb that's been extinct for 200 years.
And this is Celtic.
And I don't mean
some New-Age knockoff.
It looks like the real deal,
like 600-years-old real.
And that is the charred
metacarpal bone of a newborn baby.
-Oh. Gross.
-Relax, man.
It's at least a hundred years old.
Oh, right, like that makes it better.
Witches, man, so frigging skeevy.
Yeah. Well, takes a pretty powerful one
to put a bag like this together.
More juice than we've ever dealt with.
Find anything on the victim?
This Luke Wallace, he was so vanilla,
that he made vanilla seem spicy.
I can't find any reason why somebody
would want this guy dead.
[MUSIC PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
[CHATTERING]
Hey.
This party blows.
We should just go tp somebody.
-Hey, Justin.
-Yo.
TRACY:
You break into the booze yet?
It's triple-locked.
So you guys going to the
mausoleum party tomorrow night?
Are you gonna be there?
It's gonna be rad.
I'm gonna get so baked.
Well, it's gotta be better
than this G-rated ass-fest.
Oh, come on, it's not that bad.
Oh, check it out.
Okay, bobbing for apples is lame.
-Oh, come on. It's Halloween.
-Eh.... Lame.
I stand corrected.
Well, I wanna try.
Wow. She can really hold her breath.
Jenny?
Help me.
Jenny, what's wrong? Help!
Come on, let's go.
-What is happening?
-Jenny, come on!
[SCREAMING]
Help. Jenny!
Jenny. Jenny.
JUSTIN:
Oh, my God.
-Have you been drinking tonight?
-Yes.
-I got this one.
TRACY: The water started boiling.
Two words: Jail, bait.
I would never.
TRACY:
You know, it's just so weird.
The water in the tub, it wasn't hot.
I had just been in there myself.
Your friend didn't happen to know
a man named Luke Wallace.
Agent Seger, FBI.
Um, who's Luke Wallace?
He died yesterday.
I don't know who that is.
I'm telling you,
both of these vics are clean.
There is no reason
for wicked-bitch payback.
Maybe because it's not about that.
Wow, insightful.
Maybe this witch isn't working a grudge.
Maybe they're working a spell.
Check this out:
"Three blood sacrifices over three days.
The last before midnight
on the final day of the final harvest."
Celtic calendar, the final day
of the final harvest is October 31st.
-Halloween.
-Exactly.
What exactly are the blood sacrifices for?
SAM: Well, if I'm right,
this witch is summoning a demon.
And not just any demon.
Samhain.
-Am I supposed to be impressed?
-Samhain is the origin of Halloween.
The Celts believed
that October 31st was...
...when the veil was
thinnest between the living and dead.
It was Samhain's night.
Masks were put on to hide from him.
Sweets left on doorsteps to appease him.
Faces carved
into pumpkins to worship him.
He was exorcised centuries ago.
Samhain took a trip downstairs,
the traditions stuck.
Exactly. Only now,
instead of demons and blood orgies...
...Halloween is all
about kids, candy and costumes.
Okay, so some witch wants to raise
Samhain and take back the night?
-Dean, this is serious.
-I am serious.
We're talking heavyweight witchcraft.
This can only be performed
every 600 years.
And the 600-year marker rolls around--
-Tomorrow night.
-Naturally.
Sure is a lot of of death for one demon.
Because he likes company.
Once he's raised,
Samhain can do some raising of his own.
-Raising what, exactly?
-Dark, evil crap, and lots of it.
They follow him around
like the pied piper.
DEAN: We're talking ghosts?
-Yeah.
-Zombies?
-Mm-hm.
-Leprechauns?
-Dean.
Those little dudes are scary. Small hands.
Look, it just starts with ghosts
and ghouls. This sucker keeps on going.
By night's end, we are talking
every awful thing we've ever seen.
Everything we fight. All in one place.
It's gonna be a slaughterhouse.
[PHONE PLAYING ROCK MUSIC]
-Hey.
-How's it going?
Awesome. Yeah, I talked
to Mrs. Razor Blade again.
I've been in front of her house for hours
and I've got a big steamy pile of nothing.
Someone planted those hex bags,
someone with access to both houses.
-Gotta be some connection.
-I hope we find it...
...because I'm starting to cramp like a--
Son of a bitch.
Quit whining.
No, Sam, I mean, son of a bitch.
-Hey.
-Hi.
So? Our apple-bobbing cheerleader?
Tracy, the Wallace's babysitter.
She told me she'd
never even heard of Luke Wallace.
Interesting look for a centuries-old witch.
If you were a 600-year-old hag
and you could pick any costume...
...to come back in,
wouldn't you go for a hot cheerleader?
I would.
Mm.
Well, Tracy's not as wholesome
as she looks.
Did some digging.
Apparently, she got into a violent
altercation with one of her teachers.
Got suspended from school.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING
IN VOICE-OVER]
SAM:
Bring back memories?
What do you mean?
-Being a teenager, all that angst.
-Oh.
-What'd you think I meant?
-Nothing.
MAN: Fifteen minutes.
WOMAN: That's all?
Now, that brings back memories.
Dude, I need a bigger kiln.
HARDING:
You gentlemen wanna talk to me?
SAM: Mr. Harding.
-Oh, please, Don.
SAM: Okay. Don.
-Even my students call me Don.
DEAN:
Yeah, we get it, Don.
I'm Agent Geddy. This is Agent Lee.
We just had
a few questions about Tracy Davis.
Yeah, Tracy. Bright kid, loads of talent.
It's a shame she got suspended.
You two had a violent altercation?
Yeah, she exploded. If Principal Morrow
hadn't walked by when he did...
...Tracy would've clawed my eyes out.
-Why?
-I was only trying...
...to rap with her about her work.
It had gotten inappropriate
and disturbing.
More disturbing than those guys?
She would cover page after page
with these bizarre, cryptic symbols.
And then there were the drawings.
Detailed images of killings.
Gory, primitive.
She would depict herself
in the middle of them, participating.
Symbols? What kind of symbols?
Anything like this?
Yeah. I think that might've been
one of them.
-Know where Tracy is now?
-I imagine at her apartment.
Her apartment?
Yeah. She got here
about a year ago, alone.
As I understood it,
as an emancipated teen.
God only knows
what her parents were like.
DEAN: So?
SAM: Tracy was nowhere I could find.
-Any luck with her friends?
-Luck is not our style.
Friends don't know where she is.
She could be making the third sacrifice.
Yes, thank you, Sam.
Trick or treat?
-This is a motel.
-So?
So we don't have any candy.
-No, we have a ton in the--
-We did, but it's gone.
-Sorry, kid, we can't help you.
-I want candy.
Well, I think you've had enough.
Who are you?
DEAN:
Sam. Sam, wait!
That's Castiel. The angel.
Him, I don't know.
Hello, Sam.
Oh, my God. Or, uh.... I didn't mean to--
Sorry. It's an honor.
Really. I've heard a lot about you.
And I you.
Sam Winchester,
the boy with the demon blood.
Glad to hear you've ceased
your extracurricular activities.
URIEL:
Let's keep it that way.
Yeah, okay, Chuckles. Who's your friend?
This raising of Samhain,
have you stopped it?
DEAN: Why?
-Dean, have you located the witch?
-Yes, we've located the witch.
-And is the witch dead?
-No, but--
-We know who it is.
Apparently, the witch knows
who you are too.
This was inside the wall of your room.
If we hadn't found it,
surely one or both of you would be dead.
Do you know where the witch is now?
-We're working on it.
-That's unfortunate.
DEAN:
What do you care?
The raising of Samhain
is one of the 66 seals.
So this is about your buddy Lucifer?
URIEL:
Lucifer is no friend of ours.
It's just an expression.
Lucifer cannot rise.
Breaking of the seal must be
prevented at all costs.
Okay, great.
Now that you're here, tell us
where the witch is. We'll gank her.
We are not omniscient.
This witch is very powerful.
She's cloaked even our methods.
Okay, we already know who she is.
-So, if we work together--
URIEL: Enough.
Okay, who are you
and why should I care?
This is Uriel.
He's what you might call a specialist.
What kind of a specialist?
What are you gonna do?
You, both of you, need to leave
this town immediately.
-Why?
-Because we're about to destroy it.
This is your plan?
You're gonna smite the whole town?
We're out of time. This witch has to die.
-The seal must be saved.
-There are a thousand people here.
One thousand two hundred fourteen.
-And you're willing to kill them all?
-This isn't the first time I've...
...purified a city.
Look, I understand, this is regrettable.
-Regrettable?
-We have to hold the line.
Too many seals have broken already.
And now this town has to pay the price?
It's the lives of 1000
against the lives of 6 billion.
-There's a bigger picture here.
-Right.
Because you're "bigger picture"
kind of guys.
Lucifer cannot rise.
He does, and hell rises with him.
Is that something
that you're willing to risk?
SAM: We'll stop this witch
before she summons anyone.
Your seal won't be broken
and no one has to die.
We're wasting time
with these mud monkeys.
I'm sorry, but we have our orders.
No, you can't do this.
You're angels.
I mean, aren't you supposed to--
You're supposed to show mercy.
Says who?
-We have no choice.
-Of course you have a choice.
I mean, come on. What, you've
never questioned a crap order, huh?
-Are you just a couple of hammers?
-Look, even if you can't understand it...
...have faith.
-The plan is just.
-How could you even say that?
Because it comes from heaven.
That makes it just.
Well, it must be nice
to be so sure of yourselves.
Tell me something, Dean.
When your father gave you an order...
...didn't you obey?
Well, sorry, boys.
Looks like the plans have changed.
You think you can stop us?
No.
But if you're gonna smite
this whole town...
...then you're gonna have to smite us
with it because we are not leaving.
You went to the trouble
of busting me out of hell...
...I figure I'm worth something
to the man upstairs.
You wanna waste me?
Go ahead.
See how he digs that.
I'm gonna drag you out of here myself.
But you'll have to kill me.
Then we're back to the same problem.
I mean, come on.
You're gonna wipe out
a whole town for one little witch?
Sounds to me like you're
compensating for something.
We can do this.
We will find that witch
and we will stop the summoning.
-Castiel, I will not let these--
-Enough.
I suggest you move quickly.
Astronaut!
What?
Nothing.
I thought they'd be different.
-Who? The angels?
-Yeah.
I tried to tell you.
I just....
I mean, I thought they'd be righteous.
Well, they are righteous.
I mean, that's kind of the problem.
There's nothing more
dangerous than some A-hole...
...who thinks he's on a holy mission.
But, I mean, this is God and heaven?
And this is what I've been praying to?
Look, man,
I know you're into the whole God thing.
You know, Jesus on a tortilla,
and stuff like that.
Just because there's bad apples
doesn't mean the whole barrel's rotten.
I mean, for all we know,
God hates these jerks.
Don't give up on this stuff,
is all I'm saying.
Babe Ruth was a dick,
but baseball's still a beautiful game.
You gonna figure out a way to find this
witch or sit there fingering your bone?
You know how much heat it would take
to char a bone like this, Dean?
-No.
-A lot.
I mean, more than a fire
or some kitchen oven.
Okay, Betty Crocker,
what does that mean?
It means we make a stop.
So Tracy used the kiln to char the bone.
What's the big deal?
Dean, that hex bag turned up
in our room not after we talked to Tracy.
After we talked to the teacher.
Hey.
My God. Those are all from children.
And I'm guessing
he's not saving them for the dog.
BOY:
I'll do it.
CASTIEL:
The decision's been made.
[URIEL LAUGHS]
URIEL:
By a mud monkey.
CASTIEL: You shouldn't call them that.
-That's what they are.
Savages.
Just plumbing on two legs.
You're close to blasphemy.
There's a reason
we were sent to save him.
He has potential. He may succeed here.
At any rate...
...it's out of our hands.
It doesn't have to be.
And what would you suggest?
And that we drag
Dean Winchester out of here...
...and then we blow
this insignificant pin prick off the map.
You know our true orders.
Are you prepared to disobey?
WOMAN: Hold my hand, okay?
GIRL 1: Let's go, let's go, let's go.
BOY:
--messed up over here.
GIRL 2: Alien.
GIRL 3: Come on.
WOMAN:
No, we don't. Let's try this one.
MAN:
Push. Push.
GIRL 4:
That one.
Nelson, hurry up.
[MAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[GRUNTING]
Thank you. He was gonna kill me.
Ugh! That sick son of a bitch.
I mean, did you see what he was doing?
Did you hear him?
How sloppy his incantation was?
My brother always was a little dim.
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[GROANING]
He was gonna make me
the final sacrifice.
His idea. But now that honor goes to him.
Our master's return?
The spellwork's a two-man job,
you understand?
So for 600 years, I had to deal
with that pompous son of a bitch.
Planning, preparing.
Unbearable.
The whole time,
I wanted to rip his face off.
Then you get him with a gun.
Uh. I love that.
You know, back in the day...
...this was the one night
you kept your children inside.
Well, tonight you'll all see
what Halloween really is.
[TRACY SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
What are you doing?
Just follow my lead.
My love.
You've aged.
This face.
I can't fool you.
Your beauty is beyond time.
Whore.
What the hell was that?
Halloween lore.
People use to wear masks
to hide from him.
So I gave it a shot.
You gave it a shot?
-Where we gonna find this mook?
-Where would you go...
...to raise all the dark forces of the night?
-The cemetery.
-Yeah.
-So this demon's pretty powerful.
Might take more than the usual weapons.
Sam, no.
You're not using your psychic whatever.
-But--
-Ruby's knife is enough.
-Why?
-Because the angels said so, for one.
-You said they were fanatics.
-They happen to be right about this.
I don't know, Dean.
Forget the angels. You said yourself,
these powers-- It's like playing with fire.
Please.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYS
OVER SPEAKERS]
JUSTIN:
Dude, I'm tripping balls.
Yo, shh, be quiet. It's the cops.
[MUSIC STOPS]
Mr. Harding?
I mean, Don?
WOMAN:
Really funny.
Uh, Don, you locked us in.
MAN:
Did he lock it?
[RUMBLING]
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
-Help them.
DEAN: You're not going alone.
Do it.
DEAN:
Stand back! Stand back!
Come on, come on. Get out.
Move!
Bring it on, Stinky.
Yeah, that demon-ray-gun stuff?
Doesn't work on me.
[GRUNTING]
Zombie-ghost orgy, huh?
Well, that's it. I'm torching everybody.
Tomorrow. November 2nd.
-It's an anniversary for you, right?
-What are you doing here?
It's the day Azazel killed your mother.
Then, 22 years later, your girlfriend too.
Must be difficult to bear.
Yet, you brazenly use
the power he gave you.
His profane blood
pumping through your veins.
-Excuse me?
-You were told not to use your abilities.
What was I supposed to do?
That demon would've killed me,
and my brother, and everyone.
You were told not to.
If Samhain had gotten loose in this town--
You've been warned twice now.
You know,
my brother was right about you.
You are dicks.
The only reason you're still alive,
Sam Winchester...
...is because you've been useful.
But the moment that ceases to be true...
...the second you become more trouble
than you're worth, one word-- One.
--and I will turn you to dust.
As for your brother...
...tell him that maybe he should
climb off that high horse of his.
Ask Dean what he remembers from hell.
Let me guess.
You're here for the "I told you so."
No.
Well, good,
because I'm really not that interested.
I'm not here to judge you, Dean.
Then why are you here?
-Our orders--
-Yeah, I've had enough of these orders.
Our orders were not to stop
the summoning of Samhain.
They were to do
whatever you told us to do.
Your orders were to follow my orders?
It was a test...
...to see how you would perform under
battlefield conditions, you might say.
It was a witch, not the Tet Offensive.
So I failed your test, huh?
I get it.
But you know what?
If you were to wave that magic
time-traveling wand of yours...
...and we had to do it all over again,
I'd make the same call.
I don't know what's gonna happen
when these seals are broken.
Hell, I don't know
what's gonna happen tomorrow.
But what I do know is that this here...
...these kids, the swings, the trees...
...all of it is still here
because of my brother and me.
You misunderstand me, Dean.
I'm not like you think. I was praying
that you would choose to save the town.
You were?
These people,
they are all my father's creations.
They are works of art.
And yet, even though you
stopped Samhain, the seal was broken.
And we are one step closer
to hell on Earth for all creation.
And that's not an expression,
Dean. It's literal.
You, of all people,
should appreciate what that means.
Can I tell you something
if you promise not to tell another soul?
Okay.
I'm not a hammer, as you say.
I have questions. I....
I have doubts.
I don't know what is right
and what is wrong anymore...
...whether you passed or failed here.
But in the coming months
you will have more decisions to make.
I don't envy the weight
that's on your shoulders, Dean.
I truly don't.
[ENGLISH SDH]