Lilith is trying to break
the 66 seals to free Lucifer from hell.
- Lucifer will bring the apocalypse.
Mom.
- Sam, I'm sorry.
- For what?
Does this mean
I have demon blood in me?
I don't wanna be the freak for once,
Dean.
I wanna be normal.
Your brother is headed down
a dangerous road, Dean.
Do you even know how far off
the reservation you've gone?
How far from normal? From human?
If I didn't know you,
I'd wanna hunt you.
You wanna know
if I know about the demon blood.
You didn't tell Dean?
Where are you, Ruby?
I'm all out. Call me. I need more.
This is for your own good.
Guys?
Hey, hey. What-?
This isn't funny. Hey!
Okay. Let me out. This is not funny.
Damn straight.
Dean, come on.
- This is crazy.
No.
Not until you dry out.
Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
- Just open the door.
- You don't have to apologize.
It's not your fault.
It's not your fault that you lied to me
over and over again.
- I get it now. You couldn't help it.
- I'm not some junkie.
Really? I guess I've just imagined
how strung out you've been lately.
You're trying to twist this...
...into some kind of ridiculous
drug intervention?
If it smells like a duck.
Dean, I'm not drinking
the demon blood for kicks.
I'm getting strong enough to kill Lilith.
- Strong?
- Yeah.
This is about as far away from strong
as you can get. Try weak.
Try desperate. Pathetic.
Killing Lilith...
...is what matters.
Or are you so busy being self-righteous
you forgot about her?
Oh, Lilith's gonna die.
Bobby and I will kill her,
but not with you.
- You're not serious.
- Congrats, Sammy.
You just bought yourself
a benchwarmer seat to the apocalypse.
Dean, look- No, wait-
Come back here.
Dean!
Let me out of here!
Let me out!
Dean!
Guys, get down here!
Something's coming!
Hello, Sam.
It's a pleasure to see you again.
Looks like I have you
all to myself here.
Goodness.
How will we pass the time?
Don't. No, no, don't. Don't, don't.
No-
Stop! Stop!
Alastair, unh...
...please.
Please.
So polite all of a sudden.
Very nice.
I appreciate that.
No. Alastair, please. No, no-
No. No.
God, no!
Please! Please, please.
God!
Stop! Stop!
How long is this gonna go on?
Here, let me look it up
in my demon-detox manual.
Oh, wait. No one ever wrote one.
No telling how long it'll take.
Hell, or if Sam will even
live through it.
Hello.
Suck dirt and die, Rufus.
You call me again, I'll kill you.
- What's up with Rufus?
- He knows.
I'm busy, you son of a bitch.
This better be important.
The answer's yes.
You're hallucinating.
That's right, it's me.
Or I mean, it's you.
- I'm losing my mind.
- Definitely.
- What do you want?
- An explanation.
How could you do this to me?
I thought we were gonna be normal.
I tried. I did.
It didn't pan out that way.
Sorry, kid.
"Sorry, kid"?
That's what you have to say?
It's all we ever wanted.
We were so close.
You got away from Dad.
You quit hunting, you were gonna
become a lawyer and get married.
- Why'd you blow it?
- Look.
They killed Jessica.
Yeah.
And if you hadn't run off with Dean...
...if you'd been there to protect her,
she'd still be alive.
- I know.
- You think Jess...
...would want you to turn into this?
She loved you.
You think she'd be happy
you using her as an excuse?
I'm sorry...
...I am...
...but life doesn't turn out the way you
thought when you were 14 years old.
We were never gonna be normal.
We were never gonna get away.
Grow up.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe there's no escape.
After all...
...how can you run
from what's inside you?
The news.
The news ain't good.
This is what Rufus called about?
"Key West sees
10 species go extinct. "
Yep. Plus Alaska.
Fifteen-man fishing crew
all stricken blind, cause unknown.
New York, teacher goes postal,
locks the door, kills exactly 66 kids.
All this in a single day.
I looked them up.
There's no doubt about it.
They're all seals.
Breaking, fast.
- How many are left?
- Who knows? Can't be many.
Where the hell are your angel pals?
You tell me.
I'm just wondering.
What?
The apocalypse being nigh and all...
...is now really the right time to be
having this little domestic drama of ours?
What do you mean?
Well, I don't like this any more
than you do...
...but Sam can kill demons.
He's got a shot
at stopping Armageddon.
So what?
Sacrifice Sam's life...
...his soul, for the greater good?
Is that what you're saying?
Times are bad,
so let's use Sam as a nuclear warhead?
Look...
...I know you hate me for suggesting it.
I hate me for suggesting it.
I love that boy like a son.
All I'm saying...
...is maybe he's here right now...
...instead of on the battlefield
because we love him too much.
Poor baby.
Mom.
Sam.
You look just awful.
Let's hear it.
- Go ahead.
- What do you mean?
You're disappointed.
You never thought...
...I'd turn out this way.
I'm...
...a piss-poor excuse for a son.
Your heart is broken.
Am I close?
Not at all.
You're doing the right thing, Sam.
What you're doing is brave.
You're not being crazy,
you're being practical.
Sam, I am so proud of you.
But-
- But Dean-
- Your brother doesn't understand.
I was raised a hunter from a long line.
We understand
that there are gonna be hard choices.
And we do what we have to
to get the job done.
Yes, our family is cursed.
But you-
You have the power
to turn it into a gift.
You can use it against them.
For revenge?
No, for justice.
I know how scared you are.
What's...
...in me...
...Mom...
- ... it's-
- Evil.
And you know it.
What if it's stronger than me?
Look at me.
What if Dean's right?
Dean can never know
how strong you are...
...because Dean is weak.
Look at what he's done to you.
Locking you in here?
He's terrified.
He's in over his head.
You have to go on without him.
You have what it takes.
- You have to kill Lilith.
- Even if it kills me.
Make my death mean something.
I'm counting on you, Sam.
Don't let anyone or anything
get in your way.
Not even Dean.
Well, it's about time.
I've been screaming myself hoarse
for two and a half hours now.
What do you want?
You can start with what happened
in Illinois.
What do you mean?
Cut the crap.
You were gonna tell me something.
Well, nothing of import.
You got ass-reamed in heaven
but it was not of import?
Dean, I can't.
I'm sorry.
Get to the reason you really called me.
It's about Sam, right?
Can he do it?
Kill Lilith, stop the apocalypse?
Possibly, yes.
But as you know...
...he'd have to take certain steps.
Crank up the hell-blood regimen.
Consuming the amount it would take
to kill Lilith...
...would change your brother forever.
Most likely,
he would become the next creature...
...that you would feel compelled
to kill.
There's no reason
this would have to come to pass, Dean.
We believe it's you, Dean.
Not your brother.
The only question for us
is whether you're willing to accept it.
Stand up and accept your role.
You are the one who will stop it.
If I do this...
...Sammy doesn't have to?
If it gives you comfort
to see it that way.
God, you're a dick these days.
Fine, I'm in.
You give yourself over wholly
to the service of God and his angels?
Yeah, exactly.
Say it.
I give myself over wholly...
...to serve God...
...and you guys.
You swear to follow his will
and his word...
...as swiftly and obediently
as you did your own father's?
Yes, I swear.
Now what?
Now you wait...
...and we call on you when it's time.
Guys! Help!
Bobby! Dean! Help!
Hey! Hey! Guys!
Guys, help! Dean!
Correct me if I'm wrong...
...but you willingly signed up
to be the angels' bitch?
I'm sorry. You prefer "sucker"?
After everything you said about them,
now you trust them?
Come on, give me a little credit,
Bobby.
I've never trusted them less.
I mean, they come on
like shady politicians from planet Vulcan.
- Then why in the hell-?
- Because what other option do I have?
It's either trust the angels
or let Sammy trust a demon?
I see your point.
You hear that?
Yeah, that's a little too much nothing.
- What if he's faking?
- You really think he would?
I think he'd do anything.
That ain't faking.
We're gonna have to tie him down
for his own safety.
Dean? You with me?
- Dean! Before he has another fit.
- Yeah, yeah. Let's just get it over with.
We had to.
The demon blood was flinging you
all over the room.
Tell me something, Sam.
Why did you do this to yourself?
You know why.
Right.
"Kill Lilith. " The big excuse.
But why?
What, revenge? Right?
Of course.
Revenge for what?
For sending me to hell?
Did you happen to notice I'm back?
Alive and kicking.
- So, what's the point?
- Point?
How about
"stop the damn apocalypse"?
My gig. Not yours.
The angels said so, remember?
God picked me, man.
So you got any other fantastic excuses?
Hmm?
I'm gonna ask one more time.
Are we absolutely sure
we're doing the right thing?
Bobby, you saw
what was happening to him there.
The demon blood is killing him.
No, it isn't.
- We are.
- What?
I'm sorry.
I can't bite my tongue any longer.
We're killing him.
Keeping him locked up down there.
This cold-turkey thing isn't working.
If- If he doesn't get
what he needs soon...
...Sam's not gonna last much longer.
No.
I'm not giving him demon blood.
I won't do it.
- And if he dies?
- Then at least he dies human.
I know why you really drink that blood,
Sam.
Just leave me alone.
Makes you feel strong.
Invincible.
- A big, bad wolf in a world of little pigs.
- No.
You're wrong, Dean.
It's more than that, isn't it?
It's because your whole life,
you felt different.
Am I right?
Stop.
Oh, I hit a little close to home, huh?
Not different
because you were some lonely kid...
- ... or because of your weirdo family.
- Stop it.
- Because you're a monster.
- Shut up!
- Just- Unh. Shut the hell up.
- You were always a monster.
And you only feel right...
...when you're sucking down
more poison and more evil.
I would die for him in a second...
...but I won't let him do this
to himself.
I can't.
I guess I found my line.
I won't let my brother
turn into a monster.
Monster, Sam. You're a monster.
- Dean, no.
- And I tried so hard to pretend...
...that we were brothers.
That you weren't one of the filthy things
that we hunt.
But we're not even the same species.
- You're nothing to me.
- Don't say that to me.
Don't you say that to me.
Hello?
Someone here?
What did you do?
- You shouldn't have come, Anna.
- Why would you let out Sam Winchester?
- Those were my orders.
- Orders?
Cass, you saw him.
He's drinking demon blood.
It's so much worse than we thought.
Dean was trying to stop him.
You really shouldn't have come.
Uh-uh, Sam.
The only place you're going
is back inside with me.
No.
Damn it, boy.
You won't shoot me, Bobby.
Don't test me.
You won't do it.
You can't do it.
We're trying to help you, Sam.
Then shoot.
How the hell did he get out?
Maybe he had help.
Room full of busted devil's traps.
Demons?
- Ruby.
- That'd be my guess.
How did she even touch the door?
- You think she's got the mojo?
- I didn't think so.
- I don't know, man.
- What difference does it make?
How he got gone ain't as important
as where he got gone to.
Well, I'll tell you one thing,
I hope he's with Ruby.
Why?
Killing her's the next item
on my to-do list.
I thought you were on call
for angel duty.
I am on call in my car,
on my way to murder the bitch.
- One thing.
- What?
Sam don't wanna be found...
...which means he's gonna be
damn near impossible to find.
Yeah, we'll see.
Honeymoon suite, really?
I'm flattered.
- Did you bust me out of that room?
- How could I, Sam?
The whole thing's engineered
to bite me in the ass.
Then how did I get out of there?
I don't know. I don't wanna know.
You're out.
That's all that matters.
I'm glad you're here.
Yeah?
- Where have you been?
- Got here as quick as I could.
I mean the past three weeks.
- I've been calling.
- I've been trying to dig out Lilith.
Sometimes I can't sit around
and check my voicemail.
I'm sorry you're hurting.
Really.
I had no idea
that Dean would do that to you.
You and me both.
You didn't book this joint
just to impress me, did you?
Dean's gonna come after me.
And he knows my habits...
...my aliases, everything.
He knows exactly
which motel I'd pick.
Hence the room.
Whatever it takes to shake him.
It won't be easy. I mean,
he knows you better than anyone.
Not as well as he thinks.
You know, it's sad.
What?
That things have gotten this bad
between you two.
Police found my car.
Abandoned in an alley
in Jamestown, North Dakota.
He's switching up.
Any other cars stolen in Jamestown?
Two. 1999 Honda Civic, blue.
- Nice and anonymous, like Sam likes.
- What was the other one?
White '05 Escalade with custom rims.
- It's a neon sign.
- You're right. He'd never take that.
Which is exactly what he did.
You think?
I know that kid.
I'll head in that direction.
You stay here,
ride the police databases.
We gotta find him quick.
Your appetite's gotten much bigger.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Sam, relax. It's okay.
It's good.
Just means you're getting stronger,
that's all.
It means you're strong enough
to kill Lilith.
Just in time, too,
because the final seals are breaking.
How many are left?
- Three? Two?
- What?
- Where are the angels?
- Screwing the pooch, wherever they are.
The point is, it's looking more and more
like we're getting down to the final seal.
And I found out something big.
- What?
- Seal 66.
It can't be broken by just any demon.
Apparently,
only Lucifer's first can do it.
Lucifer's first?
Demon Sunday school story.
God prefers humans to angels.
Lucifer gets jealous
and then he gets creative.
And he twists and tempts a human soul
into the very first demon...
...as a "screw you" to God.
It's what got him locked up
in the first place.
That was Lilith?
She's way older than she looks.
Wait. So...
...if Lilith is the only one
who can break the final seal...
...if I get to her in time-
Then Lucifer never busts out of his cage.
Exactly.
Great.
- You figure out where she is?
- The bitch can hide.
But I finally have a lead on someone
who might be able to help us.
I closed in on a member
of Lilith's entourage.
You might call her...
- ... a personal chef.
- Chef? Seriously?
What does she eat?
You don't wanna know.
X- ray head to Radiology.
Hear about that horrible thing
at St. Paul's?
No.
One of the neonatal nurses walked
right off the unit with two babies.
- You are kidding me.
- Swear to God.
Worked there 17 years. Then one day,
out of the blue, she just does it.
That's just horrifying.
Now, she's saying that she doesn't
remember what happened.
Like she was possessed.
- Heh, nuts.
- I know.
- Who could ever lay a finger on them?
They're just delicious.
So our demon gourmet nurse. Heh.
You sure?
She'll be there.
Graveyard shift tomorrow night.
Meantime, if you're gonna be
strong enough to kill Lilith...
...you're gonna need more
than I can give you now.
Sam.
Come on. It's okay.
I know I need more. I get it.
I know it's okay.
I just-
I wish he'd trusted me, you know?
Sorry.
I just hope...
...you know, when all this is over...
...I hope we can fix things.
Cops found the Escalade
in a ditch outside Elk River.
- How far away am I?
- A couple of hours.
I pulled up a weather map...
...made some calls.
There's a town not far, Cold Spring.
- Lighting up with demon sign.
- A good place to look.
- Hey, listen.
- What?
Us finding Sam?
It's gotta be about getting him back,
not pushing him away.
Right.
I know you're mad, Dean. I understand.
You got a right to be...
...but I'm just saying.
Be good to him anyway.
You gotta get through to him.
No.
Let her go.
Just take it easy.
Well, it must've been some party
you two had going...
...considering how hard you tried
to keep me from crashing it.
Well, solid try...
...but here I am.
Dean, I'm glad you're here.
Look. Let's just talk about this.
Soon as she's dead,
we can talk all you want.
- Ruby, get out of here.
- No, she's not going anywhere.
- She's poison.
- It's not what you think.
Look what she did to you.
She vanishes weeks at a time,
leaves you cracking out...
- ... for another hit-
- She was looking for Lilith.
French for manipulating your ass
10 ways from Sunday.
You're wrong, Dean.
Sam, you're lying to yourself.
I just want you to be okay.
You would do the same for me.
You know you would.
Just listen.
Just listen for a second.
We got a lead on a demon
close to Lilith.
Come with us, Dean.
We'll do this together.
That sounds great.
As long as it's you and me.
Demon bitch is a deal-breaker.
You kiss her goodbye,
we can go right now.
I can't.
Dean, I need her to help me kill Lilith.
I know you can't wrap your head
around it but maybe one day...
...you'll understand.
I'm the only one
who can do this, Dean.
No, you're not the one
who's gonna do this.
Right. That's right. I forgot.
The angels think it's you.
- You don't think I can?
- No.
You can't.
- You're not strong enough.
- Who are you?
I'm being practical here.
- I'm doing what needs to be done.
- Yeah?
You're not gonna do a single
damn thing.
Stop bossing me around, Dean.
Look.
My whole life...
...you take the wheel,
you call the shots...
...and I trust you
because you are my brother.
Now...
...I'm asking you, for once...
...trust me.
No. You don't know
what you're doing, Sam.
- Yes, I do.
- Then that's worse.
Why? Look, I'm telling you-
Because it's not something you're doing,
it's what you are!
It means-
What?
No.
Say it.
It means you're a monster.
You don't know me.
You never did.
And you never will.
You walk out that door...
...don't you ever come back.