Good morning, Leonard.
Yeah. We're gonna have to stop by
Pottery Barn on the way to work.
I bought these Star Wars sheets, but
they turned out to be much too stimulating
to be compatible with
a good night's sleep.
I don't like the way
Darth Vader stares at me.
I'm not going to work.
Oh, just because your career's
been stagnant for a few years,
that's no reason to give up.
Sheldon, I was up all night
using the new free-electron laser
for my X-ray diffraction experiment.
Did the laser accidentally
burn out your retinas?
- No.
- Then you can drive. Let's go.
Didn't I tell you I'd be working nights and
that you'd have to make other arrangements?
- You did.
- And?
I didn't.
Let's go.
Good night, Sheldon.
But how am I going to get to work?
- Take the bus.
- I can't take the bus anymore.
They don't have seat belts, and they won't let
you latch yourself to the seat with bungee cords.
You tried to latch yourself
to the seat with bungee cords?
I didn't try. I succeeded.
But for some reason, it alarmed the other
passengers and I was asked to de-bus.
Oh, you're a big boy.
You'll figure it out.
Don't talk to me like I'm a child.
Now, take me to return
my Star Wars sheets!
Penny? Penny? Penny?
Sheldon. What is it?
Leonard's asleep.
- Thanks for the update.
- No. Wait.
You have to drive me to work.
Yeah, I really don't think I do.
But I don't drive, and
I can't take the bus.
Honey, you'll be fine as long as you
don't do that bungee cord thing, okay?
Penny.
Didn't you recently state
that you and I are friends?
Yes, Sheldon. We are friends.
Then I hereby invoke what I'm given to understand is
an integral part of the implied covenant of friendship.
The favor.
Oh, dear God.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize I was
interrupting your morning prayers.
When you're done, we'll go.
Thank you for driving me to work.
You know this is my day off, Sheldon.
Oh, good. I'm not
keeping you from anything.
Your "check engine" light is on.
Typically that's an indicator
to, you know, check your engine.
It's fine. It's been
on for, like, a month.
Well, actually, that would
be all the more reason to...
you know, check your engine.
Sheldon, it's fine.
If it were fine, the
light wouldn't be on.
That's why the manufacturer installed
that light, to let you know it's not fine.
Maybe the light's broken.
Is there a "check the
'check engine light' light"?
What?
Studies have shown that
performing tasks such as eating,
talking on a cell phone or drinking coffee
while driving reduces one's reaction time
by the same factor as
an ounce of alcohol.
Do you have any alcohol?
- Of course not.
- Too bad.
You're going up Euclid Avenue?
Leonard takes Los Robles Avenue.
Well, good for Leonard.
Euclid Avenue is shorter as the
crow flies, but it has speed bumps,
which appreciably increase point-to-point
drive time, making it the less efficient choice.
But you have the conn.
Of course, if you're not going
to slow down fothe speed bumps,
I withdraw my previous objection.
Here's a fun question.
Do you know what the most
common street name is?
- No.
- The answer's tricky.
It's Second Street.
You see, you'd think it would be
First Street, but in most towns,
First Street eventually gets
renamed to something else.
You know, like Main
Street, Broad Street.
Michigan Avenue.
See, Leonard and I often use our commute time to
exercise our minds with brain-teasers like that.
We also play games.
- Would you like to play one?
- No.
Oh, come on. It's fun.
Another bump.
Okay. I'll say an element,
and, and you say an element
whose name starts with the last
letter of the one I said, okay?
I'll start.
Helium.
Now, you could say "mercury."
That would give me a "y." Very
clever. That's a tough one.
So I go with "ytterbium,"
which gets you back to "m."
So you go "molybdenum,"
and I say "magnesium."
You say "manganese."
I say "europium," and, then, you're
left with "mendelevium," and...
there are no more m's because I believe that
meitnerium should still be called ekairidium.
So, congratulations. You win.
Do you wanna go again?
Why don't we just have
a little quiet time now?
All right.
I'm sorry.
I'm finding your reckless nonchalance regarding
the check-engine light to be very troubling.
Get out.
Well, I have to tell you that
while I do have a theoretical understanding of
the workings of an internal combustion engine,
I'm not sure I'm capable
of performing diagnostics.
I said, "Get out."
Okay. I'll give it a shot.
Oh, Leonard. There you are.
I'm ready to go home.
- I just got here.
- Good. Perfect timing.
Sheldon, I told you, I only have access
to the free-electron laser at night.
I can't drive you for
the next few weeks.
No, you said you
couldn't drive me to work.
This is from work.
Howard, help me out here.
No, just for the fun of
it, I'm gonna take his side.
Now, how do you propose I get home?
How did you get here in the first place?
Penny.
But I sense that's no longer an option.
Look, I need to get to the laser lab.
You're just gonna have to find
someone else to take you home.
Ah, damn, I picked the wrong side.
Oh, God, not Euclid Avenue!
Why did Howard leave you in
the middle of the road anyway?
We had a difference of opinion.
Over what?
Whether or not he was trying to kill me.
For the record, I maintain he was.
Where are you going?
I'm taking you home.
Oh, but I'm not going
home. It's Wednesday.
Wednesday's new comic book day.
We have to go to the comic book store.
And then, we have to stop at Soup
Plantation; it's creamy tomato soup day.
And Radio Shack. There's a
sale on triple-A batteries.
Plus, we have to go to Pottery
Barn and return my Star Wars sheets.
I have a better idea.
You want to go to Pottery Barn first?
Can you drive me to Pottery Barn?
Maybe if I turn off the
night-light, I can keep the sheets.
Good morning.
Sheldon, sit down.
She's in my spot.
Don't look at me like that.
Everybody knows that's my spot.
Sheldon, you know
that we care about you.
And it's because we care about you
that we've decided we have to speak up.
You're hurting the people
around you, sweetie.
So we made you an appointment,
and we want you to keep it.
Department of Motor
Vehicles New Driver Handbook?
But I don't have a problem.
Sheldon, you need to learn how to drive.
This madness has to stop.
Penny's taking you to
the DMV. I'm going to bed.
Why Penny?
Because rock breaks
scissors. Good night.
All right, come on, Sheldon.
Hold on. I have one condition.
What?
We have to stop at Pottery Barn.
Okay.
And Radio Shack.
Fine.
- And the comic book store.
- All right!
Ooh, I want to go to
the comic book store.
I like comic books.
I just don't see why I
need a driver's license.
Albert Einstein never
had a driver's license.
Yeah, but Albert Einstein didn't make
me wet myself at 40 miles an hour.
Yeah, and I never wanted to
kick Albert Einstein in the nuts.
You know, I gotta ask, why didn't you just
get a license at 16 like everybody else?
I was otherwise engaged.
Doing what?
Examining perturbative amplitudes
in N=4 supersymmetric theories
leading to a re-examination of the ultraviolet
properties of multi-loop N=8 supergravity
using modern twistor theory.
Well, how 'bout when you were 17?
Take this to the testing
area, put your name at the top,
sign the bottom, answer the
questions, bring it back. Next.
Application?
I'm actually more of a theorist.
The application in your
hand. Give it to her.
Take this to the testing
area, put your name at the top,
sign the bottom, answer the
questions, bring it back. Next!
Excuse me, but I have some
concerns about these questions.
Look at that sign up there.
Yes?
Does it say "I give a damn"?
No.
That's because I don't.
Just look. See, this first
question makes no sense.
"How many car lengths should you
leave in front of you when driving?"
There's no possible way to answer that.
A "car length" is not a
standardized unit of measure.
Look at the sign.
Sheldon, it's "C." Just put down "C."
I don't need your help, Penny.
Listen to that little
girl, honey. Put "C." Next!
No, wait! No, hang on.
Look at this next question.
Sheldon, why are you
arguing with the DMV?
How else are they going to learn?
Look... question two: When
are roadways most slippery?
Now, okay, there are three
answers, none of which are correct.
The correct answer is "when covered by "a film of liquid
sufficient to reduce the coefficient of static friction"
"between the tire and the
road to essentially zero,
but not so deep as to introduce
a new source of friction."
Here's your learner's permit. Go away.
But I'm not done. I have many additional
concerns about these questions.
Don't make me climb over this counter.
Come on. Let's go.
Next!
Aced it.
Okay, that's it. Let's boot it up.
Booting.
This is a
state-of-the-art simulator.
I adapted it from something a
friend of mine designed for the army.
Is that why I appear to be in downtown Fallujah
behind the wheel of an up-armored Humvee?
I haven't configured it yet.
Let's see... Bradley tank...
transport truck... Batmobile...
No.
Here we go. Red 2006 Ford Taurus
on the streets of Pasadena.
What?
Statistically, red cars are stopped by
police far more often than any other color.
I don't want any hassles with the fuzz.
Fine, what color do you want?
You know the pale blue of
Luke Skywalker's lightsaber?
Before it was digitally remastered?
Black, it is.
Okay, now, what you want to do first is
turn on the ignition and shift into drive.
I haven't fastened my seat belt yet.
Okay, fasten your seat belt.
"Click".
Now, are there air bags?
You don't need air bags.
What if a simulated van rear-ends me?
I'll hit you in the face with a pillow.
Okay, now shift into drive.
Pull out slowly into traffic.
Watch out, watch, watch
out for the pedestrians!
Oh, God. Wait-- slow--
Hit the brakes! The brakes!
Thank you.
Sorry. Excuse me.
My bad.
Student driver.
How did you manage to get on the
second floor of the Glendale Galleria?
I don't know. I was on
the Pasadena freeway.
I missed my exit, flew off the
overpass, and one thing led to another.
Maybe you want to give it a
rest and try again tomorrow.
No. I quit.
Aw, the pet store.
Remind me to compliment Wolowitz on
the software. It's amazingly detailed.
So wait, you're just gonna give up?
No, I'm not giving up. I never give up.
So, what is it you're doing?
I'm... transcending the situation.
I'm clearly too evolved for driving.
What does that mean?
Leonard, have you ever wondered why
my little toes and lateral incisors
are significantly smaller than
the average for someone of my size?
I wonder a lot of things about
you, Sheldon. But not-not that.
Well, those are indicators that I'm farther along
the evolutionary scale than the average human.
- No kidding.
- Well, no, no.
I'm not gonna go so far as to say that I
represent a distinct new stage in humankind--
you know, a homo novus, if you will.
No, that's for
anthropologists to decide.
But I am convinced that the reason I
cannot master the plebeian task of driving
is because I'm not meant to.
Yes, you are. You're meant
to learn how to drive.
- Please learn how to drive!
- No, no.
Leonard, I'm meant for greater things, like
unraveling the mysteries of the universe,
not determining when it's safe to pass
a stopped school bus on a country road.
- It's never safe.
- Yeah, well, I know that now.
Fine. Assuming that
everything you say is true,
how does the biologically superior
homo novus get to work tomorrow morning?
Homo novus doesn't know.
Well, hang in there.
Maybe you'll evolve into
something with wings.
Good morning, gentlemen.
Good morning.
Is there some new kind of
casual Friday I don't know about?
No, he lives here now.
Really? Why?
Well, since he won't take the
bus and he's too evolved to drive,
he decided it would be easier
to just sleep in his office
and shower in the radiation lab
until I'm finished with my experiment.
But you finished your
experiment a week ago.
Yep.
You saw nothing!