That was close.
God, I love the smell of
paintballs in the morning.
Yeah, still funny, Raj.
There's no way we can get to the ridge.
The Chemistry Department
has us completely cut off.
But what about the creek bed?
The Pharmacology Department controls that, and
they're all hopped up on experimental steroids.
That's it then. We're doomed.
I think the time has come to acknowledge
that we are paying the price for some of us
failing to attend my Physics
Department paintball strategy meeting.
I told you my mom has spider veins.
I had to take her to the laser clinic.
And I told you I wante
to see a doctor's note.
We need a plan.
How about Operation Hammer of the Gods?
I forget. Which one
is Hammer of the Gods?
We hide behind the Dumpsters in the parking
lot and ambush people when they come to pee.
No go. The Dumpsters are deep in
Astronomy Department territory.
That shouldn't be a problem.
Venus is up during the day.
They're probably just
all staring at the sky.
All right, what we need
now is a tactical retreat.
Did you see the episode of Stargate
where they found themselves on a planet
with a culture based loosely
on Earth's Athens and Sparta?
Not important.
Leonard, Raj and I are going to
burst out the door and run away.
Howard will cover us.
Why don't I run away and you cover me?
Because you chose your
mother's veins over victory.
On three. One, two, three, go!
I had to take her! It's
almost bathing suit weather!
I surrender! Don't
shoot! They went that way!
Howard, I'm on your team.
Oh, Leslie, thank God.
Where's the rest of your squad?
Ah, they left me here to die.
What about yours?
Dead, all of them.
Sorry.
Don't be. It was friendly fire.
They just wouldn't listen.
Well, we're surrounded, so I
guess there's nothing for us to do
but wait to be captured or killed.
Hmm, that's the worst part, the waiting.
All the while knowing that there's a
paint pellet out there with your namen it.
Yeah, the big wet ball of death.
Kind of makes you feel
more alive, doesn't it?
It kind of does.
I say we make every moment count.
I agree.
How exactly do we do that?
Howard, why aren't you covering us?
We're getting slaughtered out here!
War is hell.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:???
The Big Bang
Theory Season02 Episode16
Did you guys see the new budget
memo that went out this morning?
Yeah, more cutbacks.
Unacceptable.It baffles me why
they don't simply let some of you go
so that there's money
available for my research.
You know what baffles me, Sheldon?
Based on your academic record,
any number of things, I imagine.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Leslie.
Howard, I got the approval for
the rapid prototyper you wanted.
That's great, Leslie. Thanks.
You scratch my back, I scratch yours.
What was all that about?
Oh, uh, no big deal. They gave Leslie
control of some unrestricted grant money.
Yeah, okay, but what's with the back
- scratching and the meow!
I believe the back-scratching metaphor
generally describes a quid p quo situation
where one party provides goods or services to the
second party in compensation for a similar action.
Thank you.
The meow, that sounded to
me like an African civet cat.
Are you done?
No.
Despite what the name suggests,
the civet cat is not a true cat.
Now I'm done.
You know what I'm thinking?
I'm thinking Howard wasn't
making a back-scratching metaphor.
I'm thinking there was some
actual scratching involved.
What about it, Howard?
Okay, I didn't want to say anything 'cause
I know you and Leslie have a little history.
I don't care about that.
Great, 'cause I've been
dying to say something.
You and Leslie?
In the paintball shed! Twice!
Is that why you didn't cover our escape
and let us get cut down like animals?
Oh, yeah, sorry about that.
My good man, dereliction of duty in the
face of the enemy is a court-martial offense.
Court-martial, schmort-martial, Leslie Winkle
is the fifth girl I've ever had sex with.
I mean, for free.
And plus, you got a rapid prototyper.
That's an expensive
piece of equipment, dude.
And the rest of us have had
our budgets cut to the bone.
Okay, one way to look at this is
that I'm getting new equipment,
and you're not, and that's unfair.
But a better way to look at this is that I'm
getting sex and you're not, and that's delightful.
The whole thing froze. I
don't know what happened.
Calm down. We'll figure it out.
How can I calm down? I'm gonna
lose my whole shopping cart.
That's three hours of picking
out shoes just shot to hell.
- Hello, Penny.
- Hello, Sheldon.
You're in my spot.
Are you planning on sitting here?
No, I'm going to the comic book store.
Then what difference does it make?
- What difference does it make?
- Here we go.
That is my spot.
In an ever-changing world, it
is a single point of consistency.
If my life were expressed as a function on a
four-dimensional Cartesian coordinate system,
that spot at the moment I first sat
on it would be zero-zero-zero-zero.
What?
Don't sit in his spot.
Fine. Happy?
I'm not unhappy.
Boy, I love him, but he
is one serious waadoodle.
Okay, that should do it.
Oh, thank you. You are a lifesaver.
That's a lot of shoes you ordered.
Yeah, you know the sad
thing is, it's really not.
Ooh, is thisne of those paintball guns?
Yeah. You ought to come
out with us sometime.
Oh, no, thanks. I'm from Nebraska.
When we shoot things, it's because we want to
eat them or make them leave our boyfriends alone.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Boy, your heart's racing. I
must've really gotten you going.
Well, it's partly you, partly
my transient idiopaic arrhythmia.
Sexy.
Can I assume that you likewise
found the experience...
Satisfactory?
That wasn't quite the word I was looking
for, but sure, I'll do this pass-fail.
Hey, are you enjoying
that prototyper I got you?
Oh, it's great.
Everybody in the Engineering
Department is eating their hearts out.
Isn't it nice when your good
fortune makes others miserable?
You know, most people don't get that.
Howard, I'm home!
Oh, great.
Book club was cancelled!
That thing on Phyllis's
neck opened up again!
I'm busy, Ma!
Too busy to help your
mother with her zipper?
Don't come in, Ma!
Why not?
He's got company!
Oh, there's the arrhythmia.
Is she Jewish?
- Are you Jewish?
- No.
Yes!
Okay, then you kids have fun!
Use protection!
You think he'll notice?
There's a chance.
Oh, what are we gonna do?
We?
No, no, you had your chance to be
"we" for, like, a year and a half now.
Right now, you are "you,"
and you are screwed.
Why do we have to tell him I did it?
Well, we're not gonna tell him I did it.
Okay, okay, how about this?
We tell him somebody broke in.
Just to shoot the couch
with a paintball gun?
I'm sorry, Iuy it. All
those people are on drugs.
We could him they wanted the couch
to stay away from their boyfriend.
Okay, fine. What if
we just flip it over?
There. Looks fine, right?
Mm, butt print. There's
no discernible butt print.
Oh, come on.
There, butt print.
It's too small and too... perfect.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Act normal.
Sheldon!
How was the comic book store?
Fine. e new issue of Flash is out.
Great, great. Did you walk the
whole way? It's a little chilly.
Koothrappali picked me up.
Isn't that terrific?
He is such a good friend.
You know what the best
thing about friends is?
They don't talk incessantly
for no particular reason.
No, no, friends forgive
the little things.
You know, I gotta go
home and wash my hair.
Don't you dare, missy.
Hello, fastest man alive.
Want to see me read
your entire comic book?
Want to see it again?
Something's wrong.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure.
It doesn't feel right.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, that. Penny did that.
Excuse me.
Why don't you just
eat in your desk chair?
Why don't I just eat in my desk chair?
Here we go.
That is my desk chair.
That is where I work.
I don't eat in my desk chair
and I don't work in my spot.
I work in my desk chair
and eat in my spot.
Wackadoodle.
You know, there's kind of an
obvious solution here. Get up.
There. Problem solved.
Nobody cares where you're
going to sit. You're not crazy.
Excuse me, but the
problem is not solved.
If your head had been accidentally amputated,
and we transplanted a dog's head in its place,
would that be "problem solved"?
If it were your head, it would be.
Sheldon, I am really, really
sorry, but it's only for a week.
Can't you be a little bit flexible?
Yeah, sorry. I didn't
really think that through.
You claimed it's going to be a week,
but I have no faith in your dry cleaner.
Why not?
Did you notice the sign on his counter?
He's not a full-time dry cleaner.
He also makes keys.
Oh, for God's sake, Sheldon.
Focus is important.
Was Michael DeBakey a wedding
planner in between heart transplants?
Did Alexander Fleming
moonlight as a hairdresser?
"Thanks for discovering penicillin.
Now how about we try a bouffant?"
Ooh, looks like I'm
gonna have sex tonight.
Hey, baby...
His right hand is calling him?
No, it's Leslie Winkle.
It's a long story.
I'll pick you up in ten minutes.
Gentlemen, adieu.
I thought we were going
to play Halo tonight.
What am I supposed to do, Leonard?
There's a woman out there
anxious to have sex with me.
You understand, right?
No. Not at all.
Nevertheless, I must depart.
By the way, did I tell you?
Leslie pulled some strings and got me on the research
trip to Geneva to check out the CERN Supercollider.
That's not fair. You're
not even a physicist.
Okay, there are two ways
of looking at this...
- Get out.
- Bye.
You're improving.
Thank you. It helps when I get
to practice with a real woman.
Hey, listen. Saturday my
sister's getting married.
I-I want you to come
with me. It's black tie.
Yeah, gee, I'd really rather not.
Why not?
When I go to weddings, it's
to scam on chunky bridesmaids.
I don't know what I
would do with a date.
Oh, all right. I understand.
Thanks.
Hey, I'm really sorry
about that Geneva trip.
What about it?
Oh, didn't you hear?
I had to reduce the number of people
going, and you didn't make the cut.
When did that haen?
About 12 seconds ago.
Well, hold on. Are you saying if I don't
go to the wedding, I can't go to Geneva?
Actually, I'm trying not to say it.
Okay, I'm sorry, but that
makes me a little uncomfortable.
How so?
Because it's like you're controlling me
with new equipment and research trips.
Well, if I weren't controlling you with new equipment
and research trips, then I'd be uncomfortable.
How so?
'Cause then we'd be in, like, a real
relationship with feelings and all that crap.
So, bottom line, I'm just a
bought-and-paid-for sex toy.
No. No, noat all. You're also arm candy.
So? What do you think?
Hey, Ma, you got to rent me a tux!
Right now?
What kind of sex are
you having up there?
Why are you crouching there?
This is my spot.
Where else am I supposed to crouch?
I don't know. Texas?
Here you go. Fresh from
the cleaners, good as new.
Really? Great. Sheldon,
look. Good as new.
From that key maker, I highly doubt it.
Come on, Sheldon. Just give it a try.
All right.
There, nice and comfy
cozy. Zero, zero, zero.
There's one more zero.
You forgot the time parameter.
Sit on the damn couch.
Nope.
What do you mean, "nope"?
What's wrong with it?
Nothing, it's what's wrong with him.
- It's exactly the same...
- Penny, Penny,
I think I know what to do.
Sheldon, I have some bad news.
More?
I'm afraid so.
You know the cashew chicken
I get you Monday nights?
Yes. From Szechuan Palace.
Szechuan Palace closed two years ago.
What? Whe did my cashew
chicken come from?
Golden Dragon.
No.
No, this isn't right.
Our food always comes in
Szechuan Palace containers.
Yeah, well, before they went out of
business, I bought 4,000 containers.
I keep them in the trunk of my car.
But... Oh, this changes everything.
I thought that might take
his mind off the cushion.
What's real? What isn't? How can I know?
You did make that up, right?
Oh, God, I wish I had.
- Leonard?
- Yeah, buddy?
I still don't like this cushion.
ll, Penny, thank you for coming.
Thanks for the shoes.
Penny is an amazing shot. I think we
have a real chance to win this week.
- What's the plan?
- Okay. Now, we all run out.
Sheldon and I will cut to
the left behind these trees.
Raj, Howard and Leslie flank
to the right behind the rocks.
Then we'll all have a great view as Penny
runs out and kills everyone else in sight.
Just one thing before we start.
What is it, Sheldon?
What the hell?
That was for my cushion.
Sheldon, Penny was our only hope.
I'm sorry, Leonard. But revenge
is a dish best served cold.
Screw that.
She can't shoot me. She's dead.
He's right. You can't.
Well, if we're going to
descend into anarchy...
Okay, see you.
Where are you going?
Surrender, then Denny's.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:???
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org