I don't see anything at all,Sheldon.
Well,you're the doctor, but I am
constantly hearing this annoying sound.
Me,too.
Is it a high-frequency whistle?
No,it's more of a relentless,
narcissistic drone.
Yup,there's no
inflammation at all,Sheldon.
Then it must be a tumor.
Seriously doubt it.
Maybe it's a lingering bacterial infection
from all those childhood toilet swirlies.
Is that possible?
I used to get those all the time.
Even in church.
Well,if it is from a swirly,
there something I can do.
Okay,circle, circle,dot,dot,
now you have a cootie shot!
- I'm going to bed.
- Okay,I'll be right in.
It's not enough that she mocks me,but that isn't
even the correct procedure for a cootie shot.
Do you understand that Stephanie's not
here to treat your imaginary ailments?
How is it imaginary that I keep
hearing an octave above Middle C?
Is that imaginary?
I don't think so.
- Good night.
- Another thing.
Under Article One,Section
Three of our Roommate Agreement,
I'm calling an emergency meeting.
No,you're not.
Leonard moves the meeting
not occur. Is there a second?
None heard,the motion fails.
I'd like to begin the meeting by congratulating you on
the progress in your relationship with Dr. Stephanie.
Thank you.
That being said, we have to discuss the
implementation of the agreed upon "cohabitation" rider
which has been activated now that
the two of you are living together.
We're not living together.
I beg to disagree.
"A girlfriend shall be deemed
quote living with un-quote Leonard
when she has stayed over
for A:ten consecutive nights,
or B: more than nine nights
in a three week period,
or C: all the weekends of a
given month plus three weeknights.
That's absurd.
You initialed it. See? L.H.,L.H.,L.H.
Wait,I only initialed it because
I never thought it would happen!
I initialed another clause naming you
my sidekick in case I get superpowers.
Hmm,yes,you did.
Now,to review,the following
provisions are hereby activated:
In the refrigerator, as opposed to us having
two separate shelves and one communal shelf,
the three of us now get individual
shelves and the door becomes communal.
Next,apartment vacuuming shall be
increased from two to three times a week
to accommodate the increased
accumulation of dead skin cells.
Third,the bhroom schedule.
Now,I'm given to understand women have
different needs,so, we'll have to discuss that.
I'm going to bed.
At least take this with you.
Look,and have Stephanie
initial here,here,here,here...
and... here.
This states that she does not now nor does she
intend to play a percussive or brass instrument.
Sure sounds like a tumor
pressing on the auditory nerve.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:??????
The Big Bang Theory Season02
Episode10 The Vartabedian Conundrum
No,absolutely not.
It's not a big deal.
We have latex gloves.
I don't care what the symptoms are, my girlfriend
is not going to give you a prostate exam.
Hi,Sheldon.
Good morning, Dr. Stephanie.
I ust Leonard satisfied
you sexually last night.
Sheldon,we don't ask
questions like that.
I heard you ask it over and over.
How is it inappropriate
for me to ask it once?
He did very nicely.
See? She's not offended.
And now you finally have an answer.
Out of coffee. Need coffee.
Oh,hello.
Stephanie,right?
And-And-
And you are?
Penny,I live across the hall.
I've heard a lot about you.
Really?
I haven't heard a thing about you.
Leonard?
Why haven't I heard a thing about
this woman who lives across the hall
and comes into your
apartment in the morning...
in her underwear?
She's heard about you because
we're,you know, involved
and you haven't heard
about her because...
I never slept with her,I swear!
In Leonard's defense,it
wasn't for lack of trying.
Thank you,Sheldon.
You're welcome,Leonard.
Look,I'm just saying,um...
Penny is one of our many neighbors,you
know, and in our building,
neighbors come and go,it's
very casual,no dress code.
In fact,some mornings I'll just mosey
down to the third floor in my pajamas
and have cereal with Mrs.Vartabedian.
Really? I have never once been invited
to have cereal with Mrs. Vartabedian.
She doesn't like you.
You have a gall bladder to remove
and I have to get in the shower
and Penny has clothes to put on,so...
Well,it was very nice meeting you.
Nice to finally meet you,too.
- And I'll see you
tonight? - Okay,bye-bye.
What could I possibly have
done to offend Mrs. Vartabedian?
So,that's Stephanie,huh?
Why do I feel like I'm the one
that just got the prostate exam?
You know,she seems very nice.
Oh,she is. She's terrific.
And she's proving to
be a valuable roommate.
Roommate? You guys are living together?
Like hippies.
We're not living together.
Do I have to pull out
the paperwork again?
We're not living together.
Are you sure?
How could I not be sure?
Well,let's find out.
Don't you think if a woman was living with
me I'd be the first one to know about it?
Oh,sweetie,you'd be the
last one to know about it.
Hmm,cute dresses.
I bet this looks great on you!
We're not living together.
Okay,hmm...
Scented candles, fuzzy
slippers, Floral bed sheets?
We're not living together.
Okay,moving on.
Now,who are these guys at Disney World?
Uh,the big dog is Goofy,
but the older couple with
the mouse ears,I have no idea.
We're not living together!
You're going to go down swinging,huh?
All right,well,we got your body lotion,
your InStyle Magazine,your jewelry box.
We're
not--
Where's my Bat Signal?
You have a Bat Signal?
I did.
It was right here.
She
must've--
Oh,my God,we're living together.
Really? What was your first clue?
New pants?
Yeah,Stephanie got them for me.
Nice. Cotton?
Actually,I think it's more
of a wool,fire ant blend.
So,the girlfriend's
buying clothes for you,huh?
- Sounds serious.
- It is actually.
In fact,I gave it a lot of thought and I
decided it was time for us to live together.
Oh,Leonard,huge mistake.
There's a whole buffet of women out there
and you're just standing in the corner
eating the same deviled
egg over and over again.
At least I have an
egg. What do you have?
A veritable smorgasbord of
potential sexual partners.
See the blonde over there?
I can hit on her and you can't.
So,go hit on her.
She's not my type.
Too bad,'cause she was
checking you out before.
- She was?
- Of course not. Look at her.
I don't care what you guys think.
Stephanie and I are very
happy living together.
I will give either of you 20
dollars,right now to trade pants with me.
Sheldon,what are you doing here?
Hang on.
130 over 80.
A little high.
We can attribute that to the stress
of sneaking past the security desk.
Where did you get the stethoscope
and the blood pressure cuff?
My aunt Marion gave them
to me for my 12th birthday.
She thought if I failed at theoretical physics
that I should have a trade to fall back on.
And by the way,the blood pressure
cuff is called a sphygmomanometer.
I know.
Didn't they teach you
that in medical school?
- I'm busy here,Sheldon.
- I understand.
All I need is for you
to authorize these tests.
A cardiac stress test,a full body MRI,an
electromyogram,a CBC,baseline glucose.
Upper GI?
Oh,and an exploratory laparoscopy.
Last time I had hiccups,it felt like my
diaphragm was just going through the motions.
Go home,Sheldon.
Can I at least have the upper GI?
I already drank the barium!
Oh,good. Do you have
any fabric softener?
Yeah,sure.
What are you washing? A crocodile?
No,the pants that Stephanie got me.
Oh,sweetie,you can't machine
wash these. They'll be ruined.
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
Oh,no. I wish you'd told me that sooner.
Are you guys having problems?
No,everything's fine.
Really?
Yeah,it's wonderful.
Okay,maybe this whole living together happened
kind of suddenly,but it's fine,it's great.
Okay,Leonard,honey,you know,if you're
uncomfortable with the way things are going,
you're allowed to say something.
Are you sure? That doesn't sound right.
Believe me,your feelings are
just as important as hers.
No,that doesn't sound right either.
Just tell her you need the relationship to move
at a pace that you both are comfortable with.
Yeah,I could say
something like that to her.
I'll go do that.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
You ve a really good grasp on this.
Maybe you could talk to her?
You're kidding,right?
No,but that's okay.
I'll go talk to her.
Want to come with?
Go!
- Oh,no.
- Whaa?
You were right. ur larynx
is terribly inflamed.
I mean,I've never seen anything like it.
I knew it!
What do I do?
You're going to need to
stop talking immediately.
- For how--
- Dut-dut-dut.
Immediately.
- Oh,hi,honey.
- Sheldon.
What's going on?
I just performed a "Sheldonectomy."
Careful,if you don't get it
all,it'll only come back woe.
Gotcha.
Listen,we need to talk.
Do we need to talk or
"do we need to talk"?
I don't know what that means.
Okay,why don't you just tell me
what it is you have to tell me?
Okay,um,well,look,it's just that...
things between you and me
have been going pretty quick.
And...
It's just a little scary.
Well,yeah,but scary good,right?
Sure...
When is scary not good?
But...
okay,um,I have feelings,right?
Okay,and it's perfectly okay
to express those feelings,right?
Of course,honey,why don't you
tell me what it is you're feeling?
Okay,we,I ju...I think it's important
to remember that we move at a pace
that is our
speed and--
Oh,shoot,I had it!
Okay,how about this? How about
I tell you what I'm feeling?
What's that?
Really? Right now?
Why not?
I just ate,aren't you
supposed to wait an hour?
I think that's for swimming.
Oh,okay.
I just hope I don't get cramps.
- Oh,I put your clothes in the dryer.
- Thank you.
- Your pants are ruined.
- Good.
So,how did the talk with Stephanie go?
Well,um,on one level,really,really well.
So,you told her you
wanted to slow things down?
Not specifically,but,uh,I did
tell her that I had feelings.
Good,good.
And then what?
And then,uh,the subject
got changed somehow.
You had sex,didn't you?
little bit.
- What?
- Nothing.
Okay,well,it sounds like
things are going to work out.
Yeah,it's all good.
Everything's going to work out.
One way or another.
God,come on,Leonard,You are entitled to try
and make things go the way you want them to.
- Really?
- Yes!
You don't always have to go
along with what the woman wants.
- What?
- Nothing. Just...
rethinking my whole life.
Okay,here's the thing.
I'm afraid that if I ask her
to move out,she'll just dump me.
Well,it's a chance you have to take.
I mean,look,if it's
meant to be,it'll be.
Very comforting.
Okay,so what do I say to her?
I don't know.
I mean,what have women said to you when
they wanted to slow a relationship down?
I really like you,but I want
to see how things go with Mark?
Yeah,that'll slow it down.
I'm sorry,I totally inteupted
you. What we you sang?
Oh,right,yeah,um.
So,Stephanie,hereththing.
I really like yo
Oh,God,here comes the speech.
What speech?
"I really like you but maybe we sh
spend a little less time together"
"'cause I need mspace but
I'll call you on Tuesday
and then you never
call me so I call you,"
but you don't call me back and then
when I run into you at the coffee shop,
you pretend like you've been
having problems with your voice mail
and I know that you're lying,
but I pretend like I don't care
even though I'm dying inside!
No!
No,no!
I wasn't going to say any of that.
I was just going to say...
I really like you.
Oh,good!
'Cause I really like you,too.
Terrific.
Nice sweater.
Yeah,Stephanie got it
for me. It's kind of fun.
It's got a big bird on it,dude.
Yeah,yeah,that's the fun part.
We're also getting new curtains
for my bedroom,and a dust ruffle,
and a duvet,and I don't
even know what a duvet is,
but I'm pretty sure if I
did I wouldn't want one,
but every time I talk
to her about moving out,
she cries and we have sex.
You're lucky. With me,it's
usually the other way around.
You know,if you can't talk to
her,why don't you just text her?
Isn't that kind of cowardly?
Oh,yeah. It's beyond contemptible.
It's true,but on the other hand
you are wearing a bird sweater.
Sold.
"I think it would be better for our
relationship if you moved back to your place."
There. It's done.
Good for you.
Yeah,good for me.
I'll never have sex again.
Hmm,I was wrong. See ya.
Penny.
Sheldon?
I have an inflamed larynx.
Okay?
We're out of herbal
tea. Do you have any?
Okay,let me check.
Some hiney would be nice,too.
Hiney?
Honey.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:??????