[PLAYING RED HOT CHILI PEPPERS'
"UNDER THE BRIDGE"]
[SINGING "UNDER THE BRIDGE"]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
[SINGING IN FALSETTO]
[SQUEALS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Fellas, please.
Penny, come on.
We were just finding our sound.
You found it. It's the sound of a cat
being run over by a lawn mower.
Well, I'm really very busy.
Is there any way we can put this off
until I have more time to prepare?
Of course,
but, uh, you understand my trepidation.
- What's that about?
- Not a clue.
Can't we just postpone it till the spring?
Maybe next summer?
This should be fairly easy to deduce.
He's holding the phone to his left ear.
Ears do not cross hemispheres.
He's using the analytical,
rather than emotional side of the brain...
...suggesting that he has
no personal relationship with the caller.
No, I didn't realize it had been so long.
Sure. I guess there's no other choice
but to go ahead and do it.
He's referring to an activity
he has done before.
It's unpleasant and needs to be repeated.
This suggests some sort of invasive
medical test, like perhaps a colonoscopy.
Aren't there any other options?
There's not a lot of room.
- It's gonna be uncomfortable.
SHELDON: Yes, yes.
I'm definitely going with colonoscopy.
Okay, bye.
My mother's coming to visit.
How about that? You were right.
It's out of order.
Yes, I can read the sign.
I'm just pondering the implications.
I think it implies
that the elevator doesn't work.
Again, I can read the sign.
But the sign and tape are covered
with a layer of dust which indicates...
...the elevator has been nonfunctional
for an amount of time...
...which suggests either a remarkable
passivity among the...
...I assume 24 to 36 residents
of this building...
...based on the number of mailboxes and
given typical urban population density...
...or a shared delusion of functionality.
You must be Leonard's mother.
Oh, I don't know if I must be, but yes.
- Uh, I'm Penny, I'm his neighbor.
- Oh, Dr. Beverly Hofstadter.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Oh, you're a hand shaker. Interesting.
Uh, come with me,
I'll walk you to the apartment.
Oh, all right. Would you like
to exchange pleasantries on the way?
- Yeah, sure, I guess.
- All right, you start.
I've always been curious.
What was Leonard like when he was little?
BEVERLY: Oh, I think you mean young.
He's always been little.
Right.
What was he like when he was young?
You'll have to be more specific.
Oh, um, okay, like five or six.
- Five.
- Oh, well, at that age...
...he was in what Freud would call the
phallic stage of psychosexual development.
An outmoded theory, of course.
But the boy did spend most of his waking
hours with a tight grasp on his penis.
Oh, yeah, Leonard mentioned
you were a psychiatrist.
Well, that is one of my degrees.
My primary field is neuroscience.
Oh. Well, I'm an actress.
[GIGGLES]
Why?
Ha. What do you mean, why?
There were studies that suggest
many who go into the performing arts...
...suffer from an external locus
of identity.
Yeah, I don't know what that means.
Well, it means you value yourself
only as others value you...
...which is often the result
of unmet childhood emotional needs.
Oh, well, I had a wonderful childhood.
Tell me about it.
I know my dad wanted a boy.
[SOBBING]
l-- I just-- I tried being good at sports,
but I hated getting dirty.
And then, I'm assuming,
you entered adolescence.
Uh-huh. He called me slugger
until I got my first training bra...
...and then he just stopped
playing catch with me.
I wasn't slugger anymore.
Your mother's here.
If you want to have intercourse with that
girl, find out what cologne her father wore.
Good to see you, mother.
Here's your tea, mother.
- Oolong?
- Yes.
- Loose, not bagged?
- Steeped three minutes? Two-percent milk?
- Yes. Yes.
- Warmed separately?
- Yes.
- One teaspoon sugar? Raw sugar?
- Yes. Yes.
It's cold.
I'll start again.
I have the same problem with him.
My theory is that his lack of focus
stems from an over-developed sex drive.
Oh, I don't know where he got that.
Aside from a pro-forma consummation
of our marriage...
...his father and I only had intercourse
for the purposes of reproduction.
That seems a fairly efficient arrangement.
Yes, we think so.
We've both done papers on it.
Mine from a neuroscientific point of view
and his from an anthropological.
Mine, of course,
was the only one worth reading.
Of course.
I would very much like
to read about your sex life.
Well, it's all online or you can order it
from the Princeton University Press.
Here's your tea, Mother.
So, what are you guys talking about?
The frequency with which your parents
had intercourse.
Swell.
If you're lucky, maybe she'll show you
the PowerPoint presentation.
I'm sorry, it's on my other laptop.
[GROANS]
So, Mother...
- ...what's new?
- You'll have to be more specific.
All right. Uh, what's new with you?
Oh, well, I've been having some fascinating
menopausal symptoms recently.
Maybe something less personal?
Oh.
Your Uncle Floyd died.
Oh, my God. What happened?
His heart stopped beating.
I have to urinate.
What a remarkable woman.
Yeah, l-- I thought
you guys might hit it off.
I envy you your childhood.
I hate to tell you...
...but the only warm memories I have
of my childhood are of my Uncle Floyd.
You're clearly misremembering. Your mother
is brilliant, analytical, insightful.
I'm betting she never hit you with a Bible
because you wouldn't eat Brussels sprouts.
Sheldon, you don't give
your mother enough credit.
She's warm, she's loving,
she doesn't glue electrodes to your head...
...to measure your brain waves
while potty training.
You were lucky.
When I was a kid, if I wanted an EEG,
I had to attach my own electrodes.
So, Dr. Hofstadter...
...Leonard rarely talks about his
incredibly successful brother and sister.
- Please don't go there, Howard.
- You know, I understand...
...that unlike Leonard,
they're at the top of their respective fields.
Boy, you suck.
Leonard's younger brother, Michael,
is a tenured law professor at Harvard...
...and his sister just successfully grew
a human pancreas in an adolescent gibbon.
So she's close to curing diabetes?
Why else would you grow
a pancreas in a teenaged gibbon?
Wow, you must be very proud.
Why? They're not my accomplishments.
I have to urinate.
- Why are you doing this?
- You know the rules.
You brought your mom to work.
You must suffer.
[HOWARD CHUCKLES]
Leonard, I had no idea your siblings
were so much more successful than you.
[RAJESH CHUCKLES]
Yeah, you're like the Jar Jar Binks
of the Hofstadter family.
[AS JAR JAR BINKS]
Oh, meesa think yousa looking so, so sad.
Rather than mock me...
...my friends might realize this is difficult
and try to help me through it.
Nope, I think mocking you is more fun.
Next time, don't yousa bring mama to work.
Okee-day?
That was fast.
Oh, the middle stall was occupied.
I'll have to try again later.
It's totally understandable.
In bladder voiding, as in real estate...
...it's location, location, location.
So where were we?
Howard lives with his mother and Raj can't
speak to women unless he's drunk. Go.
Oh, that's fascinating.
Selective mutism is quite rare.
On the other hand, an adult Jewish male
living with his mother is so common...
...it borders on sociological clich?.
It's just temporary. I pay rent.
He lives in the same room
where his bassinet was.
Both selective mutism and an inability
to separate from one's mother...
...can stem from a pathological fear
of women.
It might explain why the two of you have
created an ersatz homosexual marriage...
...to satisfy your need for intimacy.
Say what?
[WHISPERS INAUDIBLY]
That's basically what I just said.
You brought your husband to work,
you know the rules.
[AS JAR JAR BINKS]
Meesa thinking yousa looking pretty sad...
...now too, betcha, betcha.
Leonard, it's 1:00. Weren't you going
to show me your laboratory at 1:00?
No hurry, mother. Tell them more
about their secret love for each other.
But it's 1:00. You were going to show me
your laboratory at 1:00.
Her reasoning is unassailable. It is 1:00.
Fine. Let's go.
I think you'll find my work
pretty interesting.
I'm attempting to replicate...
...the dark matter signal found
in sodium-iodide crystals by the Italians.
So no original research?
No.
BEVERLY:
What's the point of my seeing it?
I could just read the paper
the Italians wrote.
Okay, just for the record, we're not
in an ersatz homosexual relationship.
Well, then, why didn't you say that to her?
- Why is it always my responsibility?
- Oh, it's not always your responsibility.
I swear, this is the same thing you did
at the comic book store last week.
I can't believe you're bringing that up.
- I didn't bring it up. You did.
- We'll talk about this later.
Well, you always say that,
but we never do.
You went to the comic book store
without me?
- Hey.
- You got alcohol?
- Mom still here?
- Yep.
Come on in.
She's not gonna come here
looking for you, is she?
Oh, relax. She took Sheldon to the hospital
to get a brain scan.
- Oh, my God. What happened?
- Nothing.
Mother likes looking at brains
and Sheldon likes getting his brain scanned.
Jeez, what a fun couple.
Ugh. She's only here a day and a half...
...and I'm seriously considering alcoholism
as a new career path.
I talked to her for five minutes yesterday
and I've been half bombed ever since.
You can't let her get into your head.
- My head, what about yours?
- It's too late for me.
My head is her summer house.
She was right, you know.
The locus of my identity
is totally exterior to me.
Oh, yeah, there she is. Hi, mom.
Do you know where I was all morning?
Auditioning with 50 other blondes
for some stupid antidepressant commercial.
And for what?
So I'll finally get my daddy's approval?
Did you get the part?
No, they said I was too perky.
Wanna talk about not getting
love from a parent?
You know what I used to do when I was
little to have sensation of human contact?
Yeah, you grabbed your penis
and wouldn't let go.
Your mother told me.
[LEONARD SCOFFS]
Of course she did.
That's not what I was gonna say.
Uh-- Uh, when I was 10-years old,
I built a hugging machine.
- A hugging machine?
- Yeah.
I got a mannequin, stuffed it
with an electric blanket so it'd be warm...
...and I built two radio-controlled arms
that would hug me and pat my back.
Oh, that is so sad.
- Know what the saddest part was?
- What?
My father used to borrow it.
Your scan data
will be very helpful to my research.
You have a remarkable brain.
I know.
Although I've always hated
how my right frontal lobe looks in pictures.
Common complaint among men.
Nothing's ever big enough.
Except when they get a tumor.
Then you never hear the end of it.
Yeah, I'd love to see
a scan of your brain sometime.
Oh, I'll send you a link,
but its physiology is fairly unimpressive.
Oh, I can't believe that.
Your unwillingness to accept empirical
evidence suggests an attempt at flattery.
My apologies.
I've been living with your son too long.
Gotten into some bad habits.
Understandable.
Can I make you a cup of tea?
I doubt it, but if anyone has a chance,
it's probably you.
I feel very comfortable around you.
I feel very comfortable around you too.
It's surprising because I generally
don't feel comfortable around--
Well, anyone.
Nor I.
What are the odds...
...that two individuals
as unique as ourselves...
...would be connected by someone
as comparatively workaday as your son?
Is that a rhetorical point
or would you like to do the math?
I'd like to do the math.
I'd like that too.
[PENNY MOANS]
BOTH:
Aah!
[LEONARD GIGGLES]
[PENNY MOANS THEN COUGHS]
PENNY:
Mm.
- Oh.
- Heh-heh-heh.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
- Okay, now this time...
- Uh-huh.
...you're gonna lick the salt...
...off my neck...
...do the shot-- Whoops!
--and then bite the lime.
[CHUCKLING]
I'm sorry,
I didn't hear anything after "lick."
Neck.
Shot.
Lime.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
- Okay, shot, lime.
- Right.
Dah! Where's the lime?
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Oh, okay, we're sharing.
So, what do you think?
I'm very tempted.
I'm just not sure it's appropriate
with my son's roommate.
Normally, I'd feel the same way.
But based on everything
I've observed about us...
...I can't help but speculate
we'd be very good together.
True. I've had a similar observation.
It's certainly something
I could never do with my husband.
I was hesitant the first time I tried it...
...but I experienced an unanticipated
and remarkable release of endorphins.
- It's quite satisfying.
- Mm.
I see what you're doing.
You're appealing
to the neuroscientific researcher in me.
You see right through me, don't you?
Only when you're in a CAT scanner.
[SNORTS THEN LAUGHS]
[BOTH MOANING AND LAUGHING]
This is actually gonna happen.
Honey. Shush, shush, shush.
You shush. I'm happy.
I wanna talk about it.
[LEONARD CHUCKLES]
You know what my mother would say?
She'd say...
...because you were not loved by your
father and I was not loved by my mother...
...that having sex is our way of making up
for intimacy we didn't get as children.
Why would you bring that up right now?
I don't know. Foreplay?
So you're saying
you're not having sex with me...
...you're having sex with your mother?
Um, I'm gonna go with no.
That is the sickest thing I have ever heard.
Uh, come on, you're trying to have sex
with your father, and I'm okay with that.
PENNY:
Get out!
She said shush. I should have shushed.
[BOTH SINGING JOURNEY'S
"ANY WAY YOU WANT IT"]
All right, Mother.
- Um, have a nice flight.
- That's not really in my control, is it?
Oh, uh, yes.
- Oh, good morning.
- Morning.
- I was just coming over to talk to you--
- You don't have to.
Ever.
Gotcha.
- Goodbye, Mother.
- Goodbye, Leonard.
So, slugger, shall we pick up
where we left off last time?
[PENNY SOBBING]
I mean, my mom could've just said,
"Bob, get over it, she's a girl, move on."
But she didn't. Not one word.
Interesting. Would you be willing
to fly to New Jersey...
...and discuss your relationship
with your parents during a brain scan?
- Would it help?
- Well, it would help me.
[ENGLISH SDH]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org