Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
Holy Franken-fuck!
Snakes!
This is no amateur.
What the fuck?
Debra Morgan,
will you--
Are you insane?
What is that holy
piece of shit doing here?
Brother Sam?
One big, bad ex-con
turned minister.
Runs an auto body shop using
former inmates.
That can't be a man
of the cloth.
That's a killer.
It's why I'm making you
Homicide's new lieutenant.
Fuck balls.
You're serious.
I couldn't be happier.
It's about time a real cop
had that job.
How come if Matthews hates you,
I'm always the one
paying the price?
I can't tell if I'm seeing
a man who's changed
for the better
or just a better cover.
So that darkness inside
is gone?
Still there, but I'm
fighting its ass every day.
Please get off the property.
Not without our boy Nick.
You deaf, pendejo?
I can't marry you.
I'm sorry.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you lieutenant
Debra Morgan.
Hey, you all right?
No.
Really?
Yeah, I think I heard
something snap.
How about we wind up
the Kentucky derby
and we focus on breakfast?
- Yummy, okay?
- No.
- No, Harrison.
- Mine.
Horsey mine.
When you're Harrison's age,
everything's important.
Everything has meaning,
even a piece of molded plastic.
Well, how about we can play
with the horse afterwards, okay?
Took me 20 minutes
to decide what to wear.
Really?
What?
Do I look okay?
Oh, yeah.
You put on a jacket...
Over your regular clothes.
Yeah, well,
I don't want to overdo it.
I still want to look like me,
just lieutenant me.
Smart.
It's dispatch.
Probable homicide, 930 Euclid.
It's about ten minutes away.
I'll meet you there.
You're going
to the crime scene?
It's just Laguerta never went
into the field
unless she knew the case was
gonna be high-profile.
Yeah, well, I'm not Laguerta,
am I?
Hey, it's totally your call.
Shit.
You're probably right.
It's my first day.
I should probably be
at the station
working the snakes killing...
in my fucking office.
Okay, buddy.
Be good to Jamie today.
And no fruit roll-ups.
They make you fart.
Don't we know.
Good luck today.
You're gonna be great.
Thanks.
Why are you doing this to me?
Please just let me go.
You're not going anywhere
until you've repented
for your sins.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
Not to me.
To God.
Beg forgiveness, Nathan.
If you're sincere,
all of this will end.
If not, it will get much worse.
But I am sincere.
Please don't--wait.
0 to 60 in 7.2.
A full 800 RPMs
over the red line.
In high school,
that was my dream car.
Didn't Smokey drive
one of those?
Or was it the bandit?
Burt Reynolds.
Yo, guys!
Body's down here.
Any idea who she is?
Uh, from her tight mini
and a 24-pack of Trojans
in her pocket, I'd say she's
a working girl.
No driver's license?
Haven't found
a purse or an I.D.
We need to roll her over.
Easy.
Guess she lost her
gym membership.
- Where the hell's Quinn?
- He's on his way.
Well, multiple
blunt force trauma,
or manual strangulation.
Take your pick.
Are you crazy?
Okay, okay.
I'm late. I'm sorry.
Not that.
The girl.
What are you doing, man?
What about Deb?
Deb and I broke up.
You broke up?
Yeah, three days ago.
We're over.
I'm sorry I didn't know that.
What happened?
Lieutenant Morgan happened.
She ditched you
because she got promoted?
- That doesn't sound like Deb.
- Yeah?
'Cause this is the same Deb
that stole your job.
She didn't steal my job.
It was never mine
to start with.
That's always been
your problem.
You're too nice.
You let these fucking people
walk all over you.
That's bullshit.
Keep telling yourself that,
Mrs. Laguerta.
You're lucky we got work to do.
What's so interesting?
Tooth is chipped.
Well, no surprise there.
She really got worked over.
It's probably from the beating.
Or someone tried to rip it out.
You'll be leading your first
briefing soon,
so make sure you scan all
the field reports.
It's next on my list.
I just want to finish going
through these resumes.
Resumes?
I need to pick a new detective
to take my place.
I can't afford to be down
a man right now.
Well, I can help you with that.
Sam Harmon from Narcotics.
He's a real up-and-comer,
and the fact
that this father's a district
judge could come in handy.
Yeah, I know Sam.
He's a solid cop.
Great.
Happy to help.
There are a lot of other names
on this list.
You know, there's this guy
from Chicago--
Forget him.
With everything
on your plate right now,
the last thing you want
to worry about
is a transfer situation,
trust me.
Harmon's your guy.
Do you want me to start
the paperwork?
No.
I've--I've got it.
Go ahead.
Morgan.
Don't let her shove something
down your throat,
not unless you're ready
for seconds or thirds.
Take it from Mrs. Laguerta.
Got it.
Thanks.
Deb, one of the most important
things about this job
is knowing how to marshal
your resources.
Take the help
when it's offered.
Remember,
we're in this together.
I remember when
I found that under your bed.
I would have rather it had been
a stack of Playboys.
Most kids in the eighth grade
were obsessed
with their favorite
baseball players.
You tried serial killers.
Only certain ones.
The Tooth Fairy was smart...
and arrogant.
They never caught him,
even when he left a body
on a deputy sheriff's lawn.
15 women--prostitutes--
all dumped on the roadside,
all missing
their lateral incisors.
You really think there's
a connection
to the victim
from this morning?
Her lateral incisor was cracked
like someone tried
to rip it out with pliers.
There was damage to her gums.
Probably a result
of the beating,
like Masuka said.
Maybe someone was trying
to relive old times?
The Tooth Fairy killings
were in the '80s, Dexter.
He'd be 70 years old at least.
What would he be doing
in Miami?
Why do most 70 year olds
come to Miami?
They say old age is like
a second childhood.
There are primary colors...
tricycles...
and ball chasing.
I barely made it through
my first childhood.
I guess no one makes it
through the second.
This place is one block from
where the victim was found.
A short walk for a retiree
on a mission.
- Can I help you?
- I hope so.
I'm, uh, thinking about moving
my dad down here.
He's 81, but still sprightly.
Bless his heart.
Coral Island's
a great facility.
I'm happy to answer any
questions you have.
Do you have any other
residents here from Oregon?
My dad's kind of shy and it'd be
nice to have people around
with something in common,
besides hearing loss.
Well, let's see.
We have three residents
form Oregon.
Fine people.
I'm sure your dad will get along
with them famously.
That's good to hear.
Here are some brochures
with everything
you need to know about
Coral Island.
There's some forms to fill out
in case you're interested
in having your dad join us.
Thanks.
Hey, I hate to trouble you,
but that coffee
really looks good.
I was gonna get some earlier.
I feel a caffeine headache
coming on.
I know what that's like.
I'll fetch you a mug.
Be right back.
I appreciate it.
One woman...
Another in a wheelchair.
That leaves...
Walter Kenney.
Moved here from Grants Pass,
Oregon, five years ago.
How are you spending
your second childhood?
What's that?
Oh, you've been doing
such a good job,
I put together a little surprise
for your viewing pleasure.
Is this what I think it is?
Evidence from the Ice Truck
Killer investigation.
You said in class how
you were really into this case.
Are you kidding?
I was obsessed with this case.
I have followed it
night and day.
This is really sweet.
This is the Ice Truck Killer's
hospital I.D.
And the holy of holies.
Oh, wow.
Whoa.
You know...
When the details of this case
were made public,
I painted my nails like this
for a whole week.
Is that just wrong?
Is it wrong
that it makes me hot?
Uh...what do they do
with all this stuff?
It just sits here
in evidence...forever.
That's a shame.
I mean, this is a piece
of history.
It's time for the briefing.
Oh, there you are.
I've sat through God knows
how many briefings.
Why am I so fucking nervous?
Because everyone will be
looking to see
if you know what you're doing.
Do me a favor.
When you get back to your desk,
look up the word "rhetorical."
You'll be fine, Deb.
Okay, everyone,
we've got a lot to cover,
so let's get started.
First up is the homicide
on Euclid.
Where are we on identifying
the victim?
Her fingerprints
gave us a name.
Rosalia Davolos.
Several priors
for solicitation.
We talked to a local merchant.
It seems that strip
was practically her office.
Did we run her cell phone?
That turned up
a long list of numbers.
Mostly johns.
Uh, we're working through
the names now.
What about a tox screen?
Trace amounts of cocaine
in her system and...
doughnuts.
Let's, uh, check the area
for known pushers.
Maybe she got caught up
in a bad deal
or she got behind on a payment.
I'm hoping five
or six people will volunteer--
They'll never tie this
to a quarter-century-old
serial killer case from Oregon.
Not sure I have either,
but I can dream.
That takes us
to the snakes killing.
It's looking like this wasn't
a drug cartel hit after all.
As much as I hate to admit it,
maybe Brother Sam was right
about our victim.
Maybe he cleaned up his act.
That doesn't mean there wasn't
someone out there
looking to settle an old score.
What if we made some of
the details of the case public,
like the snakes?
Might scare up a lead.
Uh, no.
That may compromise the case
when it goes to court.
If we don't catch anyone,
this will never go to court.
I think detective Quinn
has a point.
We let word out about
the snakes.
The press will eat it up.
Who knows?
Maybe something
will shake loose.
What about the trial?
Well, Quinn's right.
There'll never be a trial
unless we get someone
into custody.
I think it's worth a try.
Angel, get started
on the statement.
Have it on my desk
by this afternoon.
I don't think you
really believe
what you are saying, Nathan!
You need to believe
what you are saying!
I do.
I swear.
I just--I don't know what it is
you want from me.
I want to hear you tell God
that you are sorry.
Okay.
Please, please, God...
I'm sorry for--for--
for everything I've ever done.
Just forgive me.
Forgive me.
For...give me.
No, no.
Wait. Wait.
Where are you going?
Let me go!
He's telling you what you
want to hear.
He thinks we're gonna
release him.
How much longer do we
have to make him suffer?
You really have a good heart,
Travis.
That's why I picked you.
But there's much more
at stake here
than one man's suffering.
Don't we have to be strong?
He has to be pure
or we can't proceed.
Yes.
Hey, he's coming around.
It just takes time.
Good morning, Walter.
Keep saying that and one day
you might be right.
Sam's group is about
to tee off.
You can join them.
Hey, I'm short a partner.
Dan.
Walter Kenney.
I'm a little rusty,
but I'll try
not to slow you down.
Just get a cart, will you?
Worst mistake I ever made
was moving down
to this piss-butt
corner country.
How bad can it be?
It's the Sunshine State.
Only sunshine around here is
what they blow up your ass.
The rest is mosquitoes,
humidity,
and people that don't
speak English.
So what's a young guy like you
doing around Coral Island,
or do you get off hanging out
with corpses?
I'm checking it out for my dad.
You want to help your dad?
Take him to the end of the pier
and push him off.
You'll be doing him a favor.
If I was any more in the rough,
I'd need a fucking machete.
This is like being trapped
in a toxic cloud...
that cheats.
Oh!
Son of a bitch!
You okay?
Oh, I always scream in pain
when I take a swing.
Don't just stand there.
I need to sit down.
All right.
Oh, I ruptured my back
two years ago.
It hasn't been the same since.
Okay, just take it easy.
Jesus fucking Christ!
Listen, I'm done here.
Just drop me off
at the club bar.
I need something
to kill the pain.
You got it.
So what'd you used to do
up in Oregon?
I was a pipefitter
for 25 years.
Shit job, but I managed
to work up a pension.
All I want to do now
is play golf.
Mmm.
Maybe you should find something
else to pass the time.
I tell you, it's hell not
being able to do what you love.
Is he talking about golf
or his failure
to rip out Rosalia Davolos'
tooth?
Walter Kenney may be
the world's oldest asshole,
but that doesn't make him
a killer.
On the other hand,
maybe I gave up too soon.
He wears a dental implant
for the lateral incisor.
The same one the Tooth Fairy
pulled from his victims.
Excuse me.
Hello?
This is Sam from
Good Shepherd Auto.
I was just calling to
let you know your car's ready.
Great.
When can I pick it up?
Well, if you get here
before 6:00,
you won't have to fight
the dog off this time.
- I'm on my way.
- Okay.
This is on me.
I got to go pick up my car.
Well, you know,
I've got a shit-load of errands
to run tomorrow and
with my back the way it is,
I'm gonna have
a real hard time on the bus.
You wouldn't want to give me
a ride, would you?
Perfect, now I won't have
to make an excuse
to run into you again.
I'm in 72.
Pick me up at 9:00.
Actually, I'd rather
have my teeth pulled.
Happy to do it.
People don't put no oil in it
and then wonder why they--
Hey.
Hey, man, yeah.
She's right down here.
I'll be right back, Nick.
Hey, God bless him.
Nick has been busting his ass,
man.
Off the drugs.
Cut his ties with the gang, man.
I--I really think he wants
to change.
You must be relieved.
I'm proud of him is what
I am, man.
It's not easy turning your
life around, man.
It could go south
at any minute,
but I'll take the blessings
as they come.
This looks like the day
I bought it.
You do good work.
Well, it's--it's all these
repair jobs
that pay for that good work.
Listen.
You got any plans this Sunday?
Like service?
What would I
be getting serviced?
Uh, like a church service.
No.
Not much of a churchgoer.
Yeah, I figured that.
Well, we having something
like a company get together,
like a beach party.
It'd be great
if you could come.
Well, this Sunday's tough.
I don't have a sitter
for Harrison.
Oh, that's your boy?
Yep.
He's two.
Yeah?
Bring him along.
It's a kid-friendly environment.
He'll love it.
Play some ball,
put the grill on,
have a little beach
barbecue baptism.
- Baptism?
- Yeah. Nick.
He's taking the big leap,
praise God.
He's taking the holy spirit
on right there
in the waters
of the Biscayne Bay.
Sounds like you're trying
to get me to go to church.
So what?
What, you afraid you
gonna catch something?
I'm just not sure I fit in.
Sure you do.
Listen.
I just think it'd be great
for you
to take a stand with someone
whose life
that you helped turn around.
And if you do happen
to find God,
a lot worse ways you could
spend your day off.
Only one mention
of Walter Kenney
in the criminal database
and he's identified as a victim.
Walter Kenney's mother,
charged with felony child abuse
against her son.
I have to vent or my head's
gonna explode.
- What's wrong?
- Everything.
I'm my ex-boyfriend's boss.
I don't know how to act.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know who to hire.
I have a stack of paperwork
on my desk
that's taller than I am.
Well, take a breath, sit down.
I think I really fucked up
taking this promotion.
I was a fucking great detective
who loved her fucking job.
I traded it all in for politics
and paperwork and Laguerta
up my ass.
Deb, you're too smart to think
that this was gonna be easy.
Well, I didn't expect this.
I didn't expect people
sitting around
waiting for me to fall
on my face.
No one wants you to fail.
Okay, Laguerta probably
wouldn't lose any sleep
if you stumbled a bit.
She'd pop a bottle
of champagne.
But guess what.
You're new at the job.
You're gonna stumble.
You think Laguerta
never messed up?
Shit yeah.
Cut yourself some slack.
You've been lieutenant one day.
If a couple months go by,
you still hate it,
you can demote yourself,
but until then,
just go with your gut.
And when you screw up,
just don't take me down with you.
I need the paycheck.
Okay.
My panic needle's swinging out
of the red.
Good.
How are you
with the Quinn of it?
I miss being with him.
Really?
Quinn's a good guy.
We had fun together.
It was easy.
No expectations.
That's one decision
I know I made right.
Quinn and I were never meant
to get serious.
I have to go.
I have to put people
on the snakes killing.
Thank you for talking me
off the ledge.
You're the best.
Is it a good time for me
to ask for a raise?
- Terrible.
- I'm serious.
Fuck off and die.
Maybe she shouldn't have
taken the promotion.
She might not be cut out
for it.
I think there's very little
Deb's not cut out for.
Kenney's mother
was taken into custody
for repeatedly hitting her son
in the face in public.
I'm not seeing the connection.
Maybe that's how he
lost his tooth.
So Walter Kenney
has mother issues.
Sounds familiar.
Doesn't mean that he is
the Tooth Fairy.
Ah, but it's another reason
for me
to spend my day off
with Mister Sunshine.
You said 9:00.
I just need
a couple of seconds.
TV, barcalounger,
and a view of the parking lot.
This wasn't on
the Coral Island brochure.
My son.
Gave him everything in life
and now I can't get him
on the phone.
You have kids?
You're lucky.
Ungrateful little pricks.
They suck the life out of you
and then they vanish.
Where are my fucking
house keys?
He's completely alone.
Alienated everyone around him.
Ah!
Here they are.
I'm losing my fucking mind.
Abrams in 23.
Dumb as a bag of dog shit.
Looks like a space just opened
up for your dad.
Aw, shit.
Uh...
Here's my prescription.
Just pick it up for me,
will you?
Sure.
Oh, hey, hey, hey!
And a six-pack of beer
from the liquor store
and the latest Teen Ass,
Nipple Parade, and Spanked.
Teen Ass, Nipple Parade,
and Spanked.
Can this really be the man who
inspired me to keep a scrapbook?
Can I get...
Teen Ass, Nipple Parade,
and Spanked?
Ah!
Some needs just don't
go away...
Even if the equipment
is on life support.
Does that hold true
for killing?
Just one more stop and then
I'm out of your hair.
I'll take the bus home
from here.
What about your back?
Got my remedy.
See ya.
What wrong turns do you take
to lead to this at the end
of your life?
An 8x12 storage shed,
a 6-pack of beer,
and a stack of porno mags.
I need those rundowns
on the interviews you did
with the victim's johns.
Yeah, I'm still working on 'em.
Anything I should know?
You know,
they're all sketchy characters,
but their alibis check out.
Uh, final forensics report
on the snakes killing.
Nothing new, but if you notice
the grammar's improved,
it's because Ryan typed it up.
So...Ryan, right?
You've been here a week now.
How you liking it?
- It's heaven.
- Heaven?
- Even with Vince around?
- Ha-ha, good one.
I love Homicide.
I've always been fascinated
by people who do bad things.
Maybe that's 'cause you
got a little bad in you.
You think?
Oh, I think you got
a lot of bad in you.
You may be right.
Yeah.
But you'll never know.
Can I talk to you for a second?
We're, uh, still interviewing
Rosalia's johns.
- So far, nothing.
- Not about the case.
I want to know how you're doing
with the whole situation.
Right.
Uh, I'm good.
Uh, matter of fact,
I just got done
packing up your stuff.
You didn't have to do that.
You know, I figured you're
busy with your new job and all.
You know, might not have time.
Kind of wanted it out
of the house.
So, um, if you want
to pick it up,
it's in the garage right next
to the big bag of fertilizer.
Quinn, I know you're pissed.
You're doing a great job
of letting me know that.
But this wasn't easy
on me either.
I'm sure.
You know, from what I hear,
that promotion
just came out of the blue.
You think that
my becoming lieutenant
had anything to do with
what happened between us?
No, I'm sure it was just
a big fucking coincidence.
Quinn, that is so
fucking unfair.
There seems to be a lot
of that going around.
I got my share.
Maybe you're getting yours.
Ah!
Don't hurt me.
You have to make a choice,
Nathan.
Are you going to be saved?
- It's up to you.
- Yes, please!
Please.
Dear God, cleanse me
of all my sins.
Forgive me for all the evil
that I've done.
Forgive me for--
Forgive me.
He's ready.
Two hours in that
storage facility.
I'm guessing he wasn't
organizing his
Penthouse collection.
It's like my box of slides.
Dried blood on the roots.
These are from all
of his victims.
He's the Tooth Fairy.
The man who terrorized the
Pacific Northwest for 20 years.
All he has left
is a box of teeth.
Is this what happens
to serial killers
at the end of their lives?
Everything's ready.
Kenney's apartment will make
the perfect kill room.
No one ever visits him
and the maid
won't show up until
the morning.
Tonight, Walter Kenney
will have his final tee off.
- Hello?
- It's Walter.
I'm really fucked!
What is it?
I got off at the wrong stop
and now
I don't know where
the hell I am.
I've been riding around
for hours.
- Fucking hell!
- Okay, okay.
Just calm down.
I'll swing by and pick you up.
What's the street name
and number of the bus stop?
321...Alatka.
Got it.
Just stay where you are.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
He made it easy for me
to vet him.
Now he's making it easy
for me to kill him.
Kenney's a monster,
but at least he's considerate.
I don't know what
the fuck's wrong with me.
Sometimes I get so confused.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
I'm just glad I was
in the neighborhood.
I don't know what
I would have done
if you hadn't answered.
You're a good kid.
As if I wasn't starting
to feel enough pity for him,
now he's throwing gratitude
at me?
Keep your eye on the road...
or I'll blow your head
out the window.
Drive until I tell you to turn.
How did you get on to me?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You're Miami Metro, Dexter.
I checked your car registration
when you were filling
my prescription,
and then I "goggled" your name.
Yeah, that's right, dickwad.
Maybe I haven't taken a decent
shit in ten years,
but I'm not fucking stupid.
Turn right at the next light.
Okay.
Where are we going?
To settle our business.
And you're gonna tell me
how you figured out who I am.
And then you're gonna kill me?
You haven't left me much
choice, have you?
Left into the next parking lot.
Okay.
Just for kicks,
I might rip out all your teeth
before I shoot you.
What the fuck are you--
Uh, those are, uh,
ready for cataloging.
Hey, um, after work tonight,
you want to grab some pho?
Grab some what?
Uh, it's Vietnamese food.
It's basically a large bowl
of noodles.
And broth.
So you're asking me out?
As in a date?
Well, you don't have
to call it that
if you don't want to.
I want to.
So that's a yes?
Yeah.
Wow.
What?
It's just that I ran
the conversation
through my mind
and bunch of times.
It always ended in rejection
and bodily harm.
You should be more confident.
You know, in the right light,
you're actually kind of cute.
I'm about to interview
my top pick
for the detective slot.
I thought you might
want to sit in.
Oh, no point.
Sam Harmon and I go way back.
Harmon's not my top choice.
He's not?
It's Mike Anderson,
the transfer from Chicago.
He's got ten years on Homicide,
a ridiculous solve rate,
recommendations coming
out of his ass.
We'd be lucky to have him.
I really put a lot
of thought into this.
If that's true,
then I'm seriously
worried about your judgment,
because this is a huge mistake.
I don't think it is.
Look, I know I'm new
at this job.
And it's not that I don't
value your advice,
but sometimes I have
to trust my gut,
and right now my gut
is telling me Mike Anderson.
It's your decision, lieutenant.
You can do whatever
the hell you want.
But understand this.
You're on your own.
If this doesn't work out,
don't look to me
to have your back.
Mike Anderson.
I'm here to see the lieutenant.
That's me.
It's great to meet you.
Debra Morgan.
- What's funny?
- You...The lieutenant.
- That a problem?
- Listen.
I just got off
a three-hour flight
and I'm really tired,
which means I'm not in the mood
for any cute department
razzing.
So will you take me to your
boss, please?
Maybe score me some coffee
on the way, no cream.
You listen.
Right now, you're my top choice
for this job,
but that can change
real fucking fast.
I put my ass on the line
even considering you,
so stow the attitude,
or the only job you're gonna
find in this city
is guarding a landfill
as a rent-a-cop.
Look, I apologize.
I didn't mean any disrespect.
It's just the other lieutenants
I've served under had, um--
Dicks?
Been around the block.
Trust me.
This is just as weird for me
as it is for you.
Moving on.
Let's talk.
You know, I just
got my car out of the shop.
What the hell is this?
This is the end, Walter.
You pulled your last tooth.
How did I get here?
Service entrance.
I think I tweaked my back.
Fuck me.
You could have spent your
final days relaxing,
enjoying life, but then
there was Rosalia Davolos.
She's the first one
in ten years.
Wasn't she?
Why now?
I got tired of staring
at a box of teeth.
Took me ten minutes
to kill the whore.
Lost another 20 trying
to pull the goddamn tooth.
You know,
when I was in high school,
it seemed you were all
the country was talking about.
The Tooth Fairy.
Too clever for the police.
They couldn't catch you.
Like Burt Reynolds
with his Trans-Am.
I still can't believe you
are the same man
that dumped a body at
a deputy sheriff's house.
Total fucking accident.
I downed a few too many...
And didn't feel like driving
out to the highway
to get rid of the bitch.
That's disappointing.
Well, I'm very fucking sorry
to let you down.
Does that mean you
don't want my autograph?
No.
Just...this.
I--I took teeth.
You take blood.
You're the same kind
of sick fuck, aren't you?
At least I'm never gonna
end up like you.
Oh, yeah?
When you can't do this anymore,
what do you have then?
More.
You're kidding yourself,
asshole.
All I ever cared about
was killing,
and I can't even
do that right anymore.
That's what you've got
to look forward to.
This is your future and it
includes adult fucking diapers!
You are not my future.
I will not spend my
final days getting drunk
and staring at
a box of trophies.
Keep telling yourself that.
Make sure they know who I am.
I wish I could see the look
on my son's face
when he finds out.
He won't be able
to ignore that!
I never want my son
to know who I was.
You said you didn't have a kid.
I also said my name
was "Dan."
What are you doing?
You're not gonna die
as the Tooth Fairy.
You're gonna die as a sad,
old man...
of a heart attack.
No!
The latest resident
to check out
of the Coral Island
retirement village.
Walter Kenney's son
will never know
his father was a monster.
Or at least not a killer.
We all want life to have some
kind of meaning.
Seems like the older we get,
the harder we look for it...
And the harder it is to find.
And some of us just look
in the wrong place.
But if our lives
don't have meaning...
Horsey, daddy.
What can we leave behind
for those we care about?
There you go, buddy.
Walter Kenney wanted
to pass on the ugliness
that his life had become.
What will I pass on?
Ah!
I don't know which slide
goes where, who's who.
There's no order anymore.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com