Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
James Gellar.
The professor from
the University of Tallahassee.
Gellar disappeared three years ago
after he got fired.
You can't get in touch with him...
'Cause he went underground.
You said Gellar does the killing.
He's so much stronger than me.
Gellar is pulling you
toward the darkness, Travis,
not the light.
What you said to me made me think.
Think what?
That I don't have to do what he says.
You're free.
So when Jessica Morris
O.D.'d,
there was definitely someone
in that hotel room with her.
No doubt.
Then why is Laguerta on my ass
to close this thing?
My God!
What the fuck?
Gellar hasn't seen wrath
until he's seen mine.
Travis.
Gellar.
He's been dead all along.
Travis acted alone.
He killed all those people.
Travis is the only Doomsday Killer.
And I've made a terrible mistake.
Same kill wound as the other victims.
Which means--
Travis.
You killed Gellar?
Professor Gellar.
It is not true.
I did not kill you.
No! No.
You did, Travis.
It's time you faced the truth
about yourself.
He thinks Gellar is still alive.
Talking to someone who isn't there.
Huh.
I remember I came to your office.
I brought you
the John the Revelator sword.
Yeah, you'd stolen it.
University blamed me
and they fired me.
I told you we needed it.
Because we are the two witnesses...
from Revelation 11.
And I told you you were delusional
and needed help.
I convinced you.
I made you see...
that we are the chosen ones.
I proved it to you
that you couldn't be hurt.
You stabbed me with the sword
three years ago.
And it couldn't pierce your flesh.
No.
I didn't do that.
You killed me, Travis.
And then you stuck me in the freezer.
That didn't happen.
It was him.
The false prophet.
He killed you.
He's trying to stop
what God has commanded us to do!
And I will carry on without you.
I will finish what we started.
You were wrong, old man.
I'm in control now.
I will make new disciples
that will help me.
I don't need you anymore.
Travis!
I have to stop him.
What happened to saving him?
Travis' Dark Passenger
is a part of him.
He can't be saved from it
anymore than I can from mine.
I should've never listened
to Brother Sam.
He was right about one thing.
If you put your faith
in the wrong thing--
It can really fuck you up.
It was a mistake
to put my faith in Travis.
From now on, I'm only
putting my faith in myself.
It's Deb.
The cops are canvassing
a one-mile radius
around the IP address
from Gellar's blog.
They're closing in.
Maybe it's time to let this one go.
No!
The only way to kill a Dark Passenger
is to take out the driver.
After everything
Travis put me through,
he's mine.
What are you doing?
If the cops find Gellar,
they'll focus the hunt on Travis.
It'll make it that much harder
for me to get to him.
I have to keep Gellar alive.
This is ghoulish, even for you.
Well, if the cops found
only Travis' prints,
they'd get suspicious.
This way, they'll find
Gellar's fingerprints too.
Once I'm done here, I just have
to strike the kill room,
dump Gellar's body in the swamp,
and head to Travis' motel.
You really think he's there?
No, but it might help me
get in touch with him.
What about that?
Well, it's helped me once.
Maybe I could use it again.
I'll stash it in the morgue
for a rainy day.
Gellar's blog.
You mean Travis' blog.
And now that I have Travis' laptop,
I can post as Gellar too.
Batting the beehive?
You sure that's a good idea?
Travis is unstable.
I need him to engage.
This should get his attention.
I'll do...anything...for you,
Dr. Gellar.
It's cool what you're doing,
killing all those people.
That's creepy.
Hey, Gellar.
It's the end times, huh?
Time for God's wrath.
Well, I got some God's wrath...
Right here!
Oh, yeah!
End times!
God's wrath.
Dr. Gellar,
I've read all your stuff.
But I felt like you were
just cracking the surface.
Glad to see you man up,
take the next step.
People are always being killed
in the Bible.
But I'm with you...
Till the end of days.
Doomsday Killer's
in an abandoned church.
It's too fucking perfect.
Holy fucking shit.
Is this it?
Are these Gellar's paintings?
It looks that way.
And this has to be where
Gellar and Travis
prepared their tableaus.
And held their victims.
Holy Christ on a stick.
Sorry.
Deb.
You okay?
I'm fine.
I just need to...
get some air.
What?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be there.
The cops may have found his hideout,
but that won't stop Travis.
That's up to me.
I can't wait for him to respond
to the blog.
I have to figure out his next kill.
Dex, thank God you're here.
You okay?
You look kinda...sweaty.
I was fine until I went
into the church,
and all of a sudden...
my heart started racing
and I couldn't breathe.
What the fuck?
I've been to a million crime scenes.
You remember that Ice Truck
Killer crime scene
when he filled the motel room
with blood?
- Yeah.
- I had a panic attack.
Is that what this is, a panic attack?
Uh, I don't know.
Maybe.
Well, what was yours about?
Reminded me of when my mom died.
Oh, right.
Fuck, obviously.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
But that makes sense,
you freaking out about your mom.
Me, panicking at a crime scene?
I'm the fucking lieutenant
for Christ's sake.
I can't get all woozy here every
time I go to a crime scene.
Maybe you're pregnant.
First of all, fuck you.
And second of all,
that would be the immaculate
fucking conception,
since I haven't been with anyone
since Quinn.
And lastly, fuck you.
Sounds like you're feeling better.
Let's go.
Travis and Gellar were
busy fuckin' bees, huh?
Makes you wonder where God was
when they were up to all of this.
It was a mistake to think
that any of this religious garbage
could be an answer
to my Dark Passenger.
There's no solution here.
Only clues to finding Travis.
The paintings.
We got the seven-headed
serpent...
the four horsemen...
the angel.
Quinn, nice of you to join us.
The Whore of Babylon,
the Bowls of Wrath.
And the sixth one...
Wormwood.
What the fuck's a wormwood?
Perhaps how I find Travis.
It's the next sacrifice.
Something about a star
that crashes down to the earth
and poisons mankind.
Mankind?
Think this one'll be bigger?
Well, they used one body
for the four horsemen
they're not exactly going for literal.
All right, we need to find
the who, the what,
and the where of this A.S.A.P.
Lieutenant Morgan.
Who are you going to poison, Travis?
Hey, Dex, there's blood.
Think these could be from
the Bowls of Wrath?
Could be.
Let's test it
against the samples
we took from the crime scene.
Thank you, sir.
Everything okay?
Matthews wants to set up
a dinner sometime this week.
Someplace fancy.
It sounds like he's inviting
you into his inner circle.
Congratulations.
You're big time.
Yeah, right.
Now that I've done my job,
I can get on with my work.
That looks promising.
There's some more jars over there.
I'll get it.
Travis Marshall.
Dr. Benjamin Carlson,
from Miami.
What do you got?
Just some paint thinner.
What the fuck is chlorpromazine?
Hey, Anderson.
Okay, I'll get back at you.
Get a line on
Dr. Benjamin Carlson.
Think Travis was a patient of his.
Got it.
At least I still have Gellar's blog.
The prodigal son has returned.
"False Prophet."
He's talking to me.
I listened to you once
and I made a mistake,
but never again.
I'm going to fix it.
What's his mistake?
Was it straying from Gellar
and listening to me?
I'm psyched you could do breakfast.
One of the perks of being a nanny.
Two hours off while Harrison's
in preschool.
I need a little advice.
I really want to show Dexter
my video game, you know,
find out what a real blood
spatter analyst thinks of it.
Good idea.
I have never seen the guy
make a mistake, like, ever.
- So you want to impress him.
- Yeah.
I mean, he's--
he's kind of intense.
Babe, I don't know
what he's like at work,
but once you seen him reading
Everybody Poops to Harrison,
you realize he's a big softie.
Just talk to him.
Lieutenant?
I have the personal effects
of Jessica Morris.
You asked for them.
Oh, right, fuck.
The dead call girl.
Um...
Just put 'em in my office.
I'll look at it later.
Okay.
Still looking into that case.
We've been through this.
I'm just doing my job.
You're not.
That's the problem.
I need to figure out
what Travis needs to fix.
What exactly is wormwood...
and who will his victim be?
Okay, people, big day,
so let's get started.
Are you running the briefing?
Doomsday is our most
important investigation,
and the more I help out
the more time you'll have
to focus on other cases.
You're the boss.
- You okay?
- Peachy fucking keen.
So I understand that
we found Doomsday's hideout.
Where was it?
- In an abandoned church.
- Great.
Bring me up to speed.
I, uh, found a hidden cellar.
I was sure it was gonna be
filled with body parts
but there was just some church
crap and an old freezer.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Dexter?
Masuka?
Place was covered in prints
from Travis and Gellar.
What about the blood in the jars?
What jars?
We found bloody jars
in the trash. Dex?
Same type as Travis',
and it matched some
of the samples we took
from the Bowls of Wrath.
I was thinking Holly Benson,
the girl who escaped.
She thought they made her drink blood.
Maybe it was from those jars.
Holly Benson didn't escape.
Travis let her go because of me.
Anderson, what do you got?
Anything else?
Could she be the mistake
Travis was talking about?
The mistake he needs to fix.
Travis is already back
on Gellar's path.
Will Holly be his victim
in the Wormwood tableau?
If I find Holly,
hopefully I'll find Travis.
Dexter. Hey!
Jamie and I went
to your donut shop this morning.
Not now, Louis.
It's--it's you.
And you're Doomsday Adam.
It's just I--
I never...imagined--
Steve Dorsey.
This is such an honor.
It's nice to meet you too, Steve.
Do you mind if I come in?
I'm kind of being hunted.
Oh, right!
Yep, please.
Come on in.
Beth, get in here and meet our guest.
Well, I hope he's hungry.
I have snacks.
Oh, my--
How about that?
Travis Marshall.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Beth.
Oh, I know who you are.
I've seen you on the news.
Is Professor Gellar coming too?
No. Not today.
We were just so confused by his blog.
He said this was all
the Devil's errand.
Professor Gellar didn't write that.
It was a false prophet
trying to throw a monkey wrench
into God's plan.
I knew it.
Well, please sit down.
Sorry I just have, um,
Velveeta and crackers.
Steve's been out of work lately and...
I know how it is.
Sometimes it feels as if
God has forgotten us.
But I'm here to tell you
that your time has come.
The faithful will be given
untold riches in God's new kingdom...
If you trust and obey.
We're ready,
Mr. Marshall.
We'll do whatever you say.
Good.
But first, I need to know
that you're fully committed.
Holly Benson's apartment--
the victim who would've been.
I can stake the place out.
Wait and see if Travis shows up.
Aren't you putting a lot
of eggs in the Holly basket?
I'm trusting my instincts.
Something I should've done
a long time ago.
Doesn't look like she's here.
What if Travis got to her first?
There's no signs
of a struggle or a break-in.
Not an ounce of makeup.
No hairbrush, no toothbrush.
She could've packed a bag,
gone out of town.
She still won't be safe.
Travis is determined to find her
wherever she is.
Which is why I have to
make sure I find her first.
Come on, Holly.
Give me something I can use.
Something else.
Who would she be with?
Family? Friends?
Boyfriend.
I bet he knows where she is.
Peter Grant.
I'm guessing this is him.
Hi, I'm looking for, uh, Peter Grant.
Oh, my dad.
Is he at home?
Does it look like I have
parental supervision?
He's off in Spain...
Or Portugal maybe.
Can you tell me if he knows
a woman named Holly Benson?
She's my dad's "sex-retary."
Why?
I, uh--I'm a friend.
Can't seem to get in touch with her.
Yeah, well, no offense,
but your friend
is a total slam-pig.
Right. Slam-pig.
Any idea where I can find her?
I don't know.
The yacht maybe?
Yacht?
My dad has this boat
that he refuses to get rid of.
Probably some kind of fuck pad.
- Where is it?
- I don't know.
On the water somewhere.
Thanks.
If you do find her, though,
will you give her a message for me?
Nice kid.
But if she's right and Holly's
out on a boat alone,
she's a sitting duck for Travis.
Time to play
"Find the Fuck Pad."
He's in Spain with his wife.
If he was lying, would he
let me crash on his boat
while he's away?
Who asked you anyway?
I got to go.
Hello?
Who's there?
Hello, whore.
Shh.
We're going for a little cruise.
What the fuck?
- You're a fucking asshole.
- I'm an asshole?
Doomsday's out there searching
for his next victim
and you're asleep on the job.
What are you, fucking SuperCop?
No.
I give a shit.
Maybe you should try it for once,
instead of going out drinking
every night
and coming to work while messed up.
- Give it a fucking rest, man.
- So what...
Your girlfriend broke up with you.
- Get over it.
- Fuck that.
I'm just being
a single guy having fun.
- You should try it for once.
- Hey.
Any leads on a Wormwood victim?
We're going over to Gellar's
and Travis'
friends, relatives, and acquaintances.
Figure the last two victims
were personal.
Good thinking.
Keep at it.
Any luck
on the Dr. Carlson front?
Turns out he passed away
a couple years ago,
but I got a court order
releasing Travis Marshall's
psych eval.
Drugs were antipsychotics.
Apparently he had some
breaks with reality.
Jesus. Violent tendencies
since childhood,
a lack of empathy,
master manipulator,
delusions of grandeur.
It makes sense.
Fucker wants to end the world.
What's that?
Travis' psych file.
More like psych-o file.
The guy was complete sociopath.
Shit, it says here the shrink
thought he killed his parents.
I thought it was a car accident.
Or not.
Apparently Travis attacked his father
and grabbed the wheel.
Turned it right into a tree.
Any signs of parental abuse?
Mm-mm.
It's so weird.
His sister seemed so convinced
he was a good guy.
Maybe she didn't know.
Anything's possible.
He's been a monster from the start.
He's using Gellar
to justify his kills.
A lot of people justify their kills.
You mean me?
You justified my kills.
You taught me the code.
I kept you from becoming your brother.
Making me a killer
was the best you could do.
You were already gonna be a killer.
I guess we'll never know.
There it is.
The fuck pad.
The Ricochet Rabbit.
Where you going?
I know this marina.
I had a freak-out
at a crime scene today.
Is that unusual?
Yes, that's unusual.
Seen a lot of fucked up shit
and it usually just rolls right off.
But not today.
You know what's even weirder
is the stuff that usually fucks me up
- didn't even phase me today.
- Like what?
Like Laguerta trying to swing
her dick around
in the briefing room.
I handled that like a champ.
Well, that's fantastic.
So why did I lose my shit
when I walked into that church?
Did the church have some kind
of significance for you?
I don't know.
The only time I go to church
is to go to a funeral, you know?
My mom, my dad...
boyfriends,
my sister-in-law.
So you associate church with loss.
I guess.
Whatever.
Doesn't matter.
My brother showed up,
he calmed me down.
Dexter?
Was it something that he said?
Um...
I guess.
Not really.
It was more just him being there.
Come to think of it...
Every time the shit hits
the fan, I go to him.
I've even moved in with him
a few times.
- He's your safe place.
- Yeah.
Since we were kids.
I used to have these nightmares,
and...
I would sneak into his room
and I'd curl up on the floor.
He wouldn't even know I was there.
Is that weird?
I don't know.
Do you think it's weird?
Not really.
He's my brother.
I think it's sweet.
What are you gonna do?
You mean, what are we going to do.
We're going to kill her, Beth.
Oh!
He's testing our faith.
Like Abraham.
You've got it easy.
He was asked to sacrifice his son.
You just have to pitch in
and help kill a whore.
I don't think I can do that.
I understand, Beth.
But you'll be purifying her sins.
Her soul will know paradise
because of your strength,
your love.
Come on.
Let's show her some love.
Oh. Hey, Dexter!
Louis got here a little early
to pick me up for our date.
You have a date?
I was hoping you could stay.
Sorry.
I don't supposed you'd wanna
have your date here.
We can't.
Louis bought us tickets
to go see the Avett Brothers.
Can't go another time?
They're only playing tonight.
Hey, Dexter.
Uh...I was wondering
if maybe
you could take a look at my game
before we go.
I mean, if it's not a bad time.
I should probably put Harrison down.
Oh, I got him.
You take it easy.
Looks like you had a long day at work.
Daddy.
So...
Looks like you have a minute.
- Looks like I do.
- Awesome.
I'll just--I'll bring the game
up on my laptop.
Uh, so...the game...
is about homicide.
And I know there's, like,
a million video games out there
about that.
But the secret
to this game is--
and I haven't even told Jamie
this yet--
but in my game...
you can be...
the serial killer.
What?
See, you have these character choices.
You can be, uh, Dahmer,
Jack the Ripper,
the Bay Harbor Butcher.
I am the Bay Harbor Butcher.
So...
What do you think?
I think this is offensive.
Who would choose
to be a serial killer?
Well, I mean,
it's like a vicarious thrill.
Vicarious thrill?
How could you possibly know
what it's like to take a life?
Why would you even want to?
It's a bad idea.
Do something else.
So?
I'm not--
I'm not feeling well.
I think I should go home.
And miss the show?
I'm sorry.
I'm not, uh--
I'm not up to it.
Still need a sitter?
This is the spot, but no boat.
Which means Holly is probably on it.
Unfortunately, Travis may be with her.
Only one way to know for sure.
Check the security camera footage.
I guess we all tell lies
about ourselves.
Security video archives.
Travis.
It's got sea tracker
and the password is...
Neptune.
Thank you, Mr. Grant.
How can I help you tonight?
Yeah, I kinda have a problem.
My girlfriend and I got into a fight
and she took off with my boat
and I don't know where she went.
I have the coordinates right here.
I'll notify the police.
Any way around that?
Sorry, sir, it's protocol.
I know...
It's just...I don't think
my wife would be too thrilled
to find out about my girlfriend.
I understand.
She's got a bit of a jump on you.
I've got her location right here.
This...is Wormwood.
I thought it would be bigger.
- So we're ready?
- Not yet.
We have to cover our tracks.
Police will find this place.
What difference does it make?
The world's ending in four days.
It doesn't--
It will only end
if we complete our work.
That can't happen if we're in jail.
God never said this would be easy.
Jessica Morris.
Guilt trip from beyond the grave.
"Meet me at our usual spot tonight.
Love and hot kisses,
T."
Sal's Flowers.
Sal speaking.
Hi, this is lieutenant Debra Morgan
from Miami Metro Homicide.
I need to know if you recently
delivered flowers
to a Jessica Morris, sent by
someone with the initial "T."
Jessica Morris.
Here it is--dozen red,
delivered morning of the 18th.
Uh, that was the day she died.
Who sent them?
Oh, my God.
Uh, it was Thomas Matthews.
I'm sorry,
did you say Thomas Matthews?
Uh, what's his phone number?
305-454-8537?
Jesus Christ.
Thank you.
Hey, Deb, what's up?
I have a situation.
Can we talk?
What is it?
Not on the phone.
When are you coming in?
Um, not for a while.
I have some personal stuff
to take care of.
- Before you get mad--
- It's okay.
- It is?
- Yes.
You have your own life to deal with.
It seems to be filled with a fuckload
of mysterious personal stuff, but...
whatever.
Well...thanks for being
so understanding.
Well, I'm sorry I wasn't before.
You've got my back when it counts.
- I know that.
- Okay.
By the way, you were right
about that whole
panic attack thing, so...
thank you.
I'm gonna get off the phone now
so that I can have another one.
I'll see you when you get in, okay?
Louis.
You're here early.
Uh, I couldn't sleep.
I...got a lot on my mind.
Um, I think I found a new lead.
This guy--Doomsday Adam.
He keeps posting on Gellar's blog.
To all of professor Gellar's
faithful followers.
I can now tell you without a doubt
that his prophecies are real.
My wife Beth and I have been chosen
to be soldiers in the final battle.
And with God's help,
we will prove worthy.
This will be our last post.
See you in Paradise.
You think maybe Gellar
and Travis got to this guy
and enlisted his help?
I know it's a long shot,
but--
It's worth checking out.
You think you could track down
Doomsday Adam's real name and address?
His name is Steve Dorsey.
Here's his address.
Good work.
I'll call Quinn, go check it out.
At least someone around here
appreciates me.
Hey, it's Quinn.
For the fourth fuckin' time,
answer your phone.
I'm not calling again, just get here.
Sergeant Batista,
Miami Metro Homicide.
- Are you Mrs. Beth Dorsey?
- Yes, that's right.
Is your husband home?
No, he's not.
Is there something wrong?
I'd like to ask you a few questions
if you don't mind.
Are you aware that your husband
has been posting on a blog
by a Professor Gellar?
Mm, gosh, maybe you should
talk to him when he gets back.
How about we start with you
and we take it from there?
Found the fuck pad.
Travis.
Why is he in a Hazmat suit?
You're too late.
Wormwood can't be stopped.
No!
This was supposed to set things right.
So you're telling me
that this was all a joke?
The videos your husband posted
as Doomsday Adam,
the whole...chosen thing?
My husband has kind of
a strange sense of humor.
Yeah, I would say so.
Steve's been out of work lately.
He was hoping the videos
might go viral
and get him some attention,
and I just wanted to be supportive.
Mrs. Dorsey,
these murders are nothing
to be joking around about.
Your husband wasted valuable
police time
and resources that could've been spent
catching the Doomsday Killers.
I am so sorry.
I will talk to Steve--tell him
to get those videos down.
This will not happen again.
I'd appreciate that.
If this was all a joke,
why do you have all these books
by Professor James Gellar?
What are we gonna do?
He's a cop.
He doesn't enforce God's law.
We do.
It's a sign.
Miami Metro Homicide.
That's where God wants us
to stage Wormwood.
Nothing to tell you
what Wormwood is going to be.
I don't care what it's gonna be,
I wanna know where it's gonna be.
I have to fix this.
Holly.
But this doesn't look like Wormwood.
She was stabbed, not poisoned.
You're still too late.
She's already dead.
Travis is gone and you killed
the wrong guy.
When you gonna let this go?
When I kill Travis.
Are you sure you can make that happen?
Isn't that what you taught me to do?
I didn't have a choice.
According to you,
I don't have one either.
Well, you have a choice
to make right now.
Maybe you should call the police.
I told you, I don't call the police.
Travis is mine.
Dexter, don't make this personal.
Methylphosphonyl difluoride?
And isopropyl alcohol.
Mix them together, they're lethal.
Poison gas.
This is Wormwood.
This could kill
who knows how many people.
Dexter, you have to call the police.
Why would I listen to you?
I'm only here because of you.
Now I'm supposed to trust
your judgment?
- I'll make my own decision.
- Dex.
Leave me alone!
Brother Sam said it.
Sometimes you have to surrender
to something greater than yourself.
9-1-1.
What's your emergency?
The Doomsday Killers
are hiding out on a yacht
at 114 Bleaker Canal Road.
And who's calling please?
I'd rather not leave my name.
Hurry.
They have poison gas.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com