Last season on Dexter...
The butchered bodies were
submerged inside these garbage bags...
Did you hear that?
30 bags. Do you know what that means?
There might be
a new mass murderer out there
- way worse than the Ice Truck Killer.
- Uh-oh.
Eight confirmed victims
of the Bay Harbor Butcher.
That's what the press is calling
whoever dumped those bodies offshore.
Last thing Miami needs
is another serial killer.
- Any idea who the FBI is sending?
- Some guy named Lundy.
We have positive IDs
on all 18 of our complete bodies.
All 13 were either tried for murder
or at least suspected of murder.
Bay Harbor Butcher? Give me one
shot, I'd put a bullet in the fucker's head.
You really feel that way?
If Dad taught us one thing,
it's the value of human life.
Yeah, but I think we had
different homework assignments.
Tell me the truth.
Are you an addict?
Yes, I have an addiction.
- I'm Dexter.
- Hi, Dexter.
There's my sponsor.
So tell me, exactly how full of shit are you?
This woman sees me.
Somehow she's able to make me feel OK
about what I am.
You're going to tell me
all your deepest, darkest secrets.
Laura Moser, my mother,
she was murdered.
I've never told anyone that before.
Did you find out what happened to the
men responsible for your mother's murder?
Santos Jimenez. Turned state's evidence,
went into witness protection.
- Where are you?
- I've decided to look up
someone from my past.
1976!
You slaughtered her
cause she stole cocaine.
She was a snitch for a cop.
She was fucking him.
It seems my foster father and
my biological mother were having an affair.
Did he blame himself for her death?
Is that why he took me in?
Or was he just using her?
Was he using me?
But there ain't no paper trail
on the early years of Dexter Morgan.
Your past is a bigger mystery
than fucking Jimmy Hoffa.
Back... off.
Ow! Fuck!
If Dexter files a complaint,
you will be kicked off the force.
He's hiding something, Maria.
I can feel it.
I need some blood slides analyzed.
I'm about to be found out
at work for what I really am.
- You don't understand.
- Why don't you make me?
- Who the fuck are you?
- Oh, pardon my tits.
How could you do this to Rita,
not to mention her kids?
You and Lila
stayed in a hotel together.
It's over, Dexter.
I'm sure that you heard we have a suspect
in the Bay Harbor Butcher case.
Sergeant James Doakes.
He had the slides.
Carefully hidden in the trunk of his car
at the airport.
Jesus Christ, Morgan.
You're the Bay Harbor Butcher.
You sure about that?
You might want to check with Lundy.
What's it gonna be, Morgan?
Kill me now or set me free!