Previously on Dexter...
Dexter Morgan,
good suburban husband,
happy father of three.
Living the dream.
(Whispers) Daddy kills people.
It's always the same
three kills with Trinity -
a young woman in a bathtub
followed by a mother
falling to her death
and ending with
a man getting bludgeoned.
Trinity... He doesn't belong here.
It doesn't make sense.
- Hi, honey.
- Trinity's a husband.
A father. He's...
like me.
Lundy came to Miami to hunt this guy.
I think he got too close,
and I think it got him killed.
(Gunshot)
I need a partner, Dexter.
Someone I can trust.
Unless you can be
completely honest with me,
I don't want to do this anymore.
I'm married.
Stay the hell away from my wife.
There's only one person
who can help me.
- Arthur Mitchell.
- Kyle Butler.
Four Walls, One Heart.
We build homes for the homeless.
Still so much to learn
about handling the kids and the wife.
- Choose your weapon.
- Or maybe not.
(Motor revving)
Kill him now.
No more confessions,
no more good deeds,
and no more fucking remorse.
This isn't how you die.
(Jonah) It's been my dad's baby for years.
Fucking hate you!
Fucking asshole!
(Grunting)
Get the fuck...
off of him!
I should have fucking killed you
when I had the chance.
Did you and my father
have a romantic relationship?
I was one of his girlfriends,
if that's what you're asking.
There were others?
Laura Moser, my mother.
- You remember now?
- I have a brother.
Watching mom die...
(Harry) It's all right, little guy.
You're safe now.
(Boy grunting)
Arthur!
Oh, my God.
The boys begin the cycle.
If I can make the police think the Trinity
Killer is someone else, Arthur's all mine.
Stan Beaudry.
(Harry) A decoy.
I just need to make sure
the police find Arthur's DNA.
Stan Beaudry
is now the Trinity Killer.
- I killed Lundy.
- Wait, no! Don't, don't!
(Gunshot)
(Arthur) Who are you, Kyle?
What is it you want?
Hello...Dexter Morgan.
He knows my name, occupation.
He can find out about my family.
My family.
What the hell have I done?
I'm sorry, sir.
You're on the wrong floor.
No, it's exactly the right floor.
We should talk somewhere else.
Somewhere private...
so you can extort money
from the Trinity Killer?
So what do you want?
I want you to disappear from my life.
Like a ghost.
A really annoying ghost.
And you'll disappear from my life?
I couldn't care less about your life.
Or death.
Unless you get in my way.
If I were you, I'd give up vigilanteism.
You're not very good at it.
Goodbye...
Dexter Morgan.
He's right. I screwed up.
I let it come to this.
But no more.
No fucking more.
Morgan.
Come on, Quinn. Not today.
Jesus, Morgan, middle of the day,
you're out again?
Yeah, I have some
secondary analysis to do
- on the Kyle Butler case.
- There's a spatter report
on Christine Hill's suicide sitting
on your desk - you even look at it?
I don't need to.
It's a cut-and-dry suicide.
Yeah, but you have to sign off on it.
That's how it works - you sign off,
case closed. It gets put in a file cabinet
so I don't have to think about it
or hear about it
- or be fucking reminded of it...
- I'll get to it.
What, when you're done chasing tail?
You do not want to question
my loyalty to my family, Quinn.
Not today.
Do your fucking job!
Great. Fucking mess.
(Tires squealing)
Do you even have a plan here?
Follow him and look
for an opportunity.
What if he keeps on driving?
- Then I keep on driving.
- (Cell phone rings)
- It's Rita.
- Don't answer it.
Could be important, about the baby
or something. Hey, you.
(Rita) I have something
very important to say.
Everything OK?
(Car honking)
I want my honeymoon
with you this weekend.
Uh, it's not really a good time.
It's a perfect time. Astor and Cody
will be in Disney World.
With Paul's parents.
I know, I remember.
And Harrison will be with us,
but it'll still be romantic.
I think it's...fantastic.
Great. I'll start booking
flights and a hotel and...
- (Man) Hey!
- Gotta go.
What the...fuck, man!
(Sighs) Told you not to answer it.
I'll deal with it later.
The messes are piling up.
Isolated. No security. Perfect.
Gotta risk it.
May be the only opportunity I get.
Three postcards
don't have a match.
Trinity sent these
to Christine from Cheyenne,
Topeka, and Bloomington, Illinois.
- Morgan...
- Lundy never uncovered
Trinity killings in these cities...
which means there could be
as many more as nine murders.
- Go home.
- I'm gonna call Homicide
in each of these cities.
Christine Hill just committed suicide.
In front of you.
Four hours ago.
Now, take a personal day.
Get some closure.
- That's an order.
- These cities...
I'll call their Homicide departments.
- Stan Beaudry is...
- Is our number one Trinity suspect.
We're on it.
What's she still doing here?
She's going.
Closure, huh?
Some of the cities
on these postcards...
What?
You're my husband.
And I have a wife.
So...what do we do now?
We find the Trinity Killer.
No. I mean, do we...
move in together?
Married people do that.
My house?
Your house sounds fine.
Valerie? Debra Morgan.
Yeah, fine.
You said my dad left you
for another CI?
You followed him to her house?
Any chance you remember
where she lives?
Really? Great.
My day just got wide open.
You up for a road trip?
(Car alarm chirps)
(Grunting)
(Exhales)
Finally, it's over.
Savings account closed.
Checking account closed.
You were gonna leave town,
weren't you?
And probably leave
your family destitute too.
Eventually the police
will see through Stan Beaudry,
and they'll get on to you.
But you'll be missing
with all your money,
and everyone will assume...
that you skipped the country.
Luck is finally working with me.
(Chatter)
(Man) That's the car right there
that swiped me over on Riverside.
Seriously? Fuck!
(Chatter)
Hey, that's him! That's the prick.
- Who, me?
- You fucking hit my car!
Learn how to drive, you idiot.
'Cause being rude always helps
in a tense situation, right?
- Calm down.
- Look, I'm sorry.
I was on my way
to a crime scene.
Miami Metro, Forensics.
Come on, he's working
the whole cop brotherhood angle?
No one's above the law, pal.
OK. Be cool.
Diplomatic.
Look, obviously, I'll pay
for whatever the damage is.
- You fled the scene of an accident.
- I didn't flee. I was in a hurry.
- To solve a crime.
- So you stop at a bank?
That's bullshit!
I'm just asking for a little
professional courtesy here.
You might pull that shit
down at Miami Metro,
but here at the Sheriff's Department,
we don't put up with that shit.
- Come on!
- Caught on tape, asshole.
Don't fucking point that thing at me.
All right, come here.
OK, buddy, we're taking you in.
So much for diplomacy.
- You sure this is the right block?
- Pretty sure.
- Want one?
- Quit.
Ugh. I remember when
your dad stopped, cold turkey.
If Harry said he was gonna
do something, he did it.
- He was a good man.
- He was a man-whore.
Yeah, but he was a lot
of other things too.
Like he always made me feel safe.
And the crowd I ran with -
that meant a lot.
Here it is.
What's wrong?
- Fucking can't be.
- No. This is it.
I remember the porch.
Why, what is it?
I've been here before.
(Grunting)
Aah!
Oh, God!
He brought me here.
Who did?
The Ice Truck Killer. Brian Moser.
That was her name!
Laura Moser.
She had two little boys.
Dad, who the hell were you?
(Exhales)
I don't have time for this shit.
Why are you even in here?
Because of Arthur fucking Mitchell.
Wrong.
All right, I'm here because
I didn't follow the code.
Everything you taught me
was to keep me out of here.
- What else?
- What do you want me to say?
I'm here because I lost it?
Yes. I fucking lost it.
On a fucking cop!
- Like a fucking amateur.
- Fuck you!
It's your number one rule -
don't get caught.
They were gonna find him.
They were gonna find me
with an unconscious man.
That's not why you lost it.
That's not why you're in here.
I couldn't just let them
find him, God damn it.
I have to be the one to kill him.
I have to know he's gone.
For my family.
Exactly.
You can't think clearly
because of them.
They've done this to you.
No, my dark passenger
has done this to me.
It's ruining my life.
It is your life.
I don't want it to be.
I don't want it.
- You said you had something?
- Nothing good.
Been back-checking
Stan Beaudry's trucking routes,
dug up a couple of past employers.
They put him 3,000 miles away
from Pittsburgh in '89
and Sacramento in '92.
And Beaudry's only been
connected to a prostitute kill.
Nothing ritualized about it.
I told Matthews it was too soon
to release Beaudry to the press.
If he's not our guy,
we're gonna look like fools.
I knew it wasn't Beaudry.
What? I'm smarter
than the rest of you.
Then how do you explain
Trinity's DNA showing up
- in Beaudry's rig and shack?
- Yeah, smart man.
Well, I can't...yet.
(LaGuerta) Sergeant, you find something?
I spoke with Bloomington Homicide.
I asked about the dates
on this postmark.
Summer of '92,
there was a bathtub murder,
a jumper, and a bludgeoning.
I see a big "but" on your face.
What?
Guy said it was
the worst month of his life.
In addition to those murders,
there was a ten-year-old boy missing
five days prior to the bathtub kill.
Last week, that ten-year-old boy
went missing here.
- Scott Smith.
- Exactly.
So I called a few cities.
Ten-year-old boys missing?
Every time.
Five days before
each cycle began.
And Lundy was only looking
at homicides, not missing persons.
Get Scott Smith down here.
Let's check every Trinity city
for missing ten-year-olds.
We may be looking
at a whole new pattern.
(Computer beeps)
"Brian and...
"Dexter Moser"?
Dexter Morgan?
Yeah.
It's your lucky day.
Yeah. It feels like it.
We're outta bunks for the night.
There's a shot
Arthur's still unconscious.
Bummer.
Yeah, well, budget cuts
are gettin' worse and worse.
But since you're Miami Metro,
we figured we could at least
do you the favor of calling your wife,
- have her come pick you up.
- My wife?
How is it I can kill people
and feel no regret...
but disappointing Rita makes me feel
like the scum of the earth?
I'm sorry.
I know.
I just had a...
bad day and...
let it get to me, I guess.
First it was smashing that light,
which was...weird.
And then you punched Elliot,
which I actually liked.
But now you...
pick a fight with a sheriff?
I don't understand.
I want to, but...
I wish I could explain.
Try. Please.
Sometimes I'm just goin' along,
and everything seems OK,
and then this...
darkness creeps in,
and it takes over.
Makes you sound crazy.
Maybe I am.
No.
No, I don't believe that.
I'll be right behind you.
Shit.
Well, you actually think Dad'll let you
go to the winter prom?
- He doesn't have to know.
- We can figure something out.
(Thud)
Arthur! We didn't know
when to expect you.
Bring me your jewelry -
gold, silver, anything with a stone in it.
And all the cash in your purse.
- Why? What's wrong?
- And your wedding ring.
No. This is mine.
- Arthur!
- Hey!
Don't, Jonah, no!
- OK.
- Daddy, what's happening?
I need the money you keep
behind your headboard.
Don't pretend. I know it's there!
- No, Daddy! Daddy, why...
- The silver pendant I gave you.
- Now!
- What the hell is goin' on?
- What did you do?
- Arthur, please, no!
You're lucky I don't pull
the fillings out of your teeth!
Don't ever question me!
I gave you everything you have.
I will take it all away!
Collect your things.
I've got some business to attend to.
Other than stealing
from your family?
Jonah.
Someone stole something from me.
And I'm gonna find him.
We... We should just go.
Leave and never come back.
He'll find us.
This... This is our chance.
He's... He's in trouble. He's insane.
- Mom!
- What?
Please.
We'll live in fear.
We already do.
Debra. Oh, sorry.
Detective Morgan.
Have a seat.
Thanks for your time,
Deputy Chief.
I know you're busy.
I need to talk to you about a case.
It was one of my father's
old cases from a long time ago.
And you're the only one
still around from those days.
Suddenly I feel ancient.
Look, it was a quadruple homicide...
out at the ports.
In a shipping container.
- You were there?
- No. Wasn't my case.
But I remember Harry's face
when he came back from it.
Said he'd never seen
so much blood.
- (Cell phone vibrates)
- Sorry.
My dad said Dexter's parents
died in a car accident.
That's not true, is it?
No.
My father's CI, Laura Moser,
was murdered
in that shipping container.
She had two boys.
One of those boys was Dexter?
Please tell me the truth.
Harry adopted him.
The other boy was too damaged
by the incident.
(Whispers) No shit.
He grew up to be the Ice Truck Killer.
You knew.
(Cell phone vibrates)
Debra, your father
wanted to protect you.
He didn't want either
one of you to ever know.
And you both turned out
pretty damn well.
So I think he made the right call.
Yeah?
Well, I know now.
What the hell am I supposed
to do with this?
You keep it to yourself.
(Cell phone vibrates)
Oh, fuck! Jesus!
Quinn, what?
I'll be right there.
(Click)
(Chuckles)
We should go
to the Keys tomorrow.
For our honeymoon.
No, I'm not sure that's...
You can fly down in the morning.
I'll follow you after work.
Have a spa day. Indulge.
Please?
- Dexter, uh...
- Look, I know you're upset.
You have every right to be.
Having to pick up
another husband from jail.
You... You think I'm upset
because you're like Paul?
I'm worse.
- I know.
- Dexter.
Whenever they picked up Paul,
it was a relief.
And life got easier.
Without you...
You're the most important
person in our lives.
What's upsetting me
is the idea of losing you.
You have your demons.
I accept that.
Because I know that you don't
have to be a slave to them.
I wish that were true.
It is.
(Chuckles) I know you.
Better than you know yourself.
You can conquer
whatever darkness there is in you.
I know you can.
I want to be that man.
You already are.
Please.
Please fly to the Keys
tomorrow morning.
I wanna meet you.
Truly, there's nowhere
I'd rather be.
Trinity sure went to a lot of effort
to make us think that
Beaudry was our guy.
Planting DNA.
Planting Lundy's murder books.
Have we heard back from
any more Homicide departments?
Almost every town. Ten-year-old boys
missing in all of them.
Quinn is talking
to Scott Smith now.
No, I'm not.
I called in someone who knows
about being kidnapped.
Someone took me once too.
Without my permission.
- Were you scared?
- Most scared I've ever been in my life.
And...as much as I want to forget,
there are all these
little things I remember.
The way his breath
smelled like medicine.
The bad man.
Used medicine on me.
When I was getting in the van.
Do you remember any
little things about the van?
It was empty.
Except for some papers.
There was a picture on it.
Do you remember what it looked like?
Uh...
We're looking for this logo.
(Police radio chatter)
We've got something.
We walked cadaver dogs
over the whole area.
They led us to this spot,
and the guys started digging.
(Quinn) They found something
buried under the patio.
All right, hold up.
(Coughs)
Male victim.
Approximate age...
ten years old.
Badly decomposed.
Looks to be wearing pajamas.
They found Scott Smith
wearing pajamas.
I'll call Judge Morales at home,
have her get a warrant started.
(Debra) I'll get the names of everyone
who volunteered on this build.
(Batista) Make it everyone who volunteered
for Four Walls nationwide.
Cross-check 'em
with Trinity's cities.
We'll find Trinity's real name,
then we'll take this motherfucker down.
You're a little piggy, Dexter Morgan.
"Debra Morgan."
Debra Morgan!
Fucking Debra!
Astor and Cody,
Disney World awaits.
They'll be safe there
with Mickey, Minnie,
and their goofy grandparents.
Now for the rest of my family.
Found it!
(Rita) Oh.
(Chuckles)
Wish I could go with you right now.
Me too.
I just got a few loose ends to tie up at work,
and I'll see you tonight.
Can't wait.
Me either.
Can't wait to be with my family.
Can't wait to be done
with Arthur Mitchell.
I just need a clue where he's headed.
Receipts.
Drug store.
Auto shop estimate.
Dry-cleaner, groceries, gas.
No bus, train, or plane tickets.
Only one other place I can check.
(Ringing doorbell)
(Knocking)
- Mr. Butler, what...
- Jonah, have you seen your father?
Yeah, he blew through here last night
looking for anything he could sell.
Jonah! Who is...
- Kyle.
- He's asking about Dad.
Can you tell me
what's going on?
(Sighs) I'm not sure.
I hope he stays gone this time.
He took...everything.
It's gonna be OK. I promise.
I'll make sure you get Arthur's money.
Did he say where
he was headed?
- He never does.
- Did he take his tools?
Pack a bag?
Does he have a passport?
I don't know. When we got up
this morning, he was gone.
(Helicopter overhead)
Shit.
Aah!
Get down! Down on the ground!
(Overlapping yelling)
We create our own destiny
every day we live.
- Freeze! Hands up.
- Forensics.
All right.
(Sirens)
Dexter.
Where's your flak jacket?
I left it in the car.
Do you see this?
Cabr?n.
And over here...
(Breathing heavily)
Look. It's a framing hammer.
I'll get Masuka in here,
get some DNA.
(Dexter sighs)
- What?
- How'd you get here so fast?
Word's everywhere.
You found Trinity.
Yeah, the Four Walls national database
led us to Arthur Mitchell.
Can you believe that fucking
monster had a family?
And he abandoned them?
He's gone?
Yeah, he emptied out his bank accounts
and disappeared.
He's probably halfway
around the world by now.
Probably.
Deb, what's...
Why don't you get your fucking flak jacket
so everyone knows you're one of us?
Hey. It's the fucking Karate Kid.
Yeah, about that, uh...
You pull that shit again, next time
I won't be the one who's on my ass.
(Sobbing)
This is their future, Dexter.
We both know it's inevitable.
No. Arthur abandoned his family.
I would never do that.
Arthur left his family too late.
The damage was already done.
You can still save your family.
By leaving them?
You'll always need
someone on your table.
If you stay,
sooner or later you'll be caught,
and they'll pay a terrible price
for what you've done.
Because long after
you're executed...
they'll still have to go through life
with your name branded
across their foreheads.
(Debra) Dex.
I have something to tell you.
- And maybe I shouldn't. I don't know.
- OK.
I found another CI
Dad was sleeping with.
A woman named Laura Moser.
Harry was right. This is it.
Does that name
mean anything to you?
- Should it?
- It doesn't?
Look, she died,
but she left behind two little boys.
And one of those
little boys was you.
Laura Moser
is your biological mother.
Don't say the rest. Don't know it.
The other little boy, your brother,
was named Brian.
Brian Moser.
The Ice Truck Killer.
She knows who I really am. It's over.
I wasn't gonna tell you,
but then I saw Trinity's family,
and I thought that it's better
for you to know the truth.
The truth?
The truth...
That's a lot to take in.
I know.
And that's all she knows?
Do you think Brian knew about me?
I don't know.
He must have glommed
onto you as a way to...
get to me.
Don't you see, it wasn't your fault.
He wasn't your fault.
If I'd never been in your life...
Fuck you.
Fuck me?
If you hadn't been in my life,
I wouldn't be who I am.
You've given me confidence...
and support.
And...
you've been the one constant.
The one constantly good thing
in my life.
I've been good for her.
And Rita says I'm good
for her and the kids.
No one would ever say that
about Arthur.
Maybe Harry's wrong.
Maybe things could turn out
differently for me.
Morgan.
Debra Morgan. Need you inside.
I'll be right there.
I love you.
I'm so thankful.
The Mustang.
Arthur brought it in two days ago.
Should have known
he wouldn't leave it behind.
Here. Take the rest of this.
Mr. Mitchell, this gonna be nice.
Ah, it's beautiful work, Julio.
Especially on such short notice.
(Engine starts)
Por favor, the paint.
The paint. It needs more dry!
iTres horas m?s!
(Julio) Shit.
(Batista) The wife had no clue
what the husband was up to.
Do we believe her?
She threw up when I showed them
the pictures of what he did.
That can be faked.
This is the team
that broke the case.
Lieutenant LaGuerta,
Special Agent Davis of the FBI.
First-rate job. Congratulations.
It was Detective Morgan
who brought these killings
to the department's attention.
- Building on the work of one of your own.
- Special Agent Lundy.
Fuck yes, Special Agent Lundy.
- He told you guys...
- It's been a long day.
No disrespect, but she's right.
I agree. In retrospect, the Bureau
should have proceeded differently.
Well, your retrospect
cost a man his life.
We'll be taking over from here.
So after we do all the heavy lifting...
You get all the credit.
I'm sure they're grateful
for all your hard work.
We are.
(Whispers) Motherfuck.
I know.
But it is what it is.
(? Music plays on car radio)
(Bang)
(Engine chugging)
Damn it to hell.
(Hissing)
(Groans)
Where's my fucking oil cap?
(Grunts)
Hello, Arthur Mitchell.
Ah!
(Grunting)
Guess you were picturing
a different scenario.
I was following my path.
So was I.
God led you to me.
Hardly.
(Metal clinks)
(Whimpers)
Is this who you are?
Ta-da!
Oh, look at you.
I never took pride in what I did.
No, you're a very special
kind of monster.
You destroyed your own family.
- I gave them everything!
- No, you took everything.
Their future. Their dignity.
Their hope.
Christine...
even killed herself.
No!
Because of you.
She was weak.
I can't believe there was a time
when I actually thought I could
learn something from you.
You think you're better than I am?
No.
But I want to be.
You can't control
the demon inside of you
any more than I can control mine.
Did you ever actually try?
(Chuckles) Oh, my God, yes.
I prayed to be changed.
To be made...different.
That's not trying.
That's waiting to be stopped.
It worked, didn't it?
Case in point.
So what's the alternative, Arthur?
Leave? Disappear?
Fake my own death
and start over again?
No.
You'll still be you.
I have a family too, Arthur.
And I'm good...for them.
(Chuckles)
You're like a child.
Mm, a child with a big knife.
You dream of a heaven
you'll never see.
- I don't believe in heaven.
- Oh, but you do.
This isn't your doing.
This is God's plan.
I accept that now.
You have to do the same.
I accept...nothing.
Nothing is inevitable.
It's already over.
Could you...
Thank you.
(? Frankie Avalon: Venus playing)
? I'll give her all the love
I have to give
? As long as we both shall live ?
Now it's over.
(Crunch)
(Splash)
I wonder if Rita's looking
at this same moon
at this same moment.
I like that -
connected by light.
The dark passenger's
been fighting against it,
trying to keep me all to himself.
But it's my turn now...
to get what I want.
To embrace my family.
And maybe one day
not so long from now...
I'll be rid of the dark passenger.
It all begins with a getaway.
Time away from the old me.
(Sighs)
It's OK.
Life doesn't have to be perfect.
It just has to be lived.
(Cell phone beeping)
- Unheard message.
- (Beep)
(Rita) Hey, sweetie, I'm a dope.
I was in such a rush
to get Harrison organized
I forgot my ID for the plane,
so I'm zooming home for it.
Means I'll be on a later puddle jumper,
but we'll still be there waiting for you.
Oh, and I know you're not
into this stuff, but...
the moon tonight
is gonna be amazing.
So take a moment.
You deserve it.
We love you. Bye.
(Ringing tone)
(Cell phone ringing)
(Ringing)
(Harrison crying)
(Crying)
Rita?
No.
(Harrison crying)
Born in blood...
both of us.
Harry was right.
I thought I could
change what I am,
keep my family safe.
(Harrison crying)
But it doesn't matter what I do,
what I choose.
I'm what's wrong.
This is fate.