Sync by honeybunny - www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
It's always the same
three kills with Trinity.
Young woman in the bathtub...
followed by a mother
falling to her death.
And ending with a man
getting bludgeoned.
Trinity's likely someone
who's gone his own
solitary way through life,
foregone all but the most rudimentary
of human connections.
A lone wolf.
If we can find where he
bludgeoned back then...
Lobby's open 24 hours, guard on duty.
Too much foot traffic.
Trinity would have
to choose another floor.
Ooh, so sorry.
Wasn't watching where I was going.
White male,
eyes blue,
something in them.
Super agent Lundy has a
hunch that the dead woman
is connected to this
big serial killer case.
You still dating that she-bag reporter?
After she put Lundy's name in the paper?
Tell me, is this conversation
going to end up in the paper too?
'Cause you have no idea
the shit storm you've gotten me into.
Find yourself another source.
Just unsealed the juvie
records of Johnny Rose,
our vacation murder suspect.
Shoplifting with his high
school girlfriend Nikki Wald.
Get down!
I think we should inform the brass
about our relationship.
It's none of their business.
I get a gig in town to
spend more time with you,
and you spend all your time
with your ex.
Don't go disappearing on me again.
Not a...
- Deb.
- Hey, you.
- Back behind the line.
- No, I was called here.
I'm Dexter Morgan.
That might be my sister.
I understand, Sir, but
right now I need you
to step back and let
our people do their job.
No, no, I'm with Miami Metro Forensics.
My laminate and my
wallet are in the car.
Until I see some ID,
I need you to step back.
And I need you to fucking listen.
My sister was shot,
No one can tell me
what her condition is,
and that's a dead body.
Sir.
You want to let me go.
Hansen. Hands off.
He's one of us.
Deb's alive. Okay?
They're taking her to the hospital.
I have to see her.
How bad is it?
Lost a lot of blood.
If Deb dies,
I'll be...
lost.
Paramedics think the bullets
are through and through.
She's gonna be okay?
It's looking good.
Who did this?
We got here just before you did.
Quinn was first on scene.
He says it's smelling like
the vacation murders' MO.
Then that's...
Lundy.
What was Deb doing with
Lundy at 5:00 in the morning?
Oh.
Dexter, I swear to you,
we will find who did this.
My kit's in my car.
Hey, hey, hey.
You got better places to be.
Like with your sister.
Go. That's an order.
You'll know the minute we know anything.
Lundy was a worthy adversary.
He deserves better
than to be face down
in a hotel parking lot,
a random victim of a senseless crime.
Sorry about Deb, man.
Did she say anything?
She was in shock,
didn't see who pulled the trigger.
Batista said you think
this looks like the vacation murders.
Deb's cash and credit cards are gone.
So's Lundy's watch and wallet.
Anything, Vince?
Surgeon general wouldn't
have been able to save him.
GSWs to the neck and chest.
He bled out in seconds.
Lundy was shot twice?
Deb was vulnerable and
a potential witness.
The shooter could have easily
finished her off like Lundy.
I should get to the hospital.
Deb, she knows.
Even though we go at it all the time,
We're still...
Yeah, she knows.
We're gonna get these fuckers.
Not if you're looking
in the wrong direction.
Detective Quinn.
Not now. Really.
I didn't come here for a quote.
You all right?
My partner's been shot.
The last thing I am is all right.
I know this can't be easy,
but if you need anything,
I'm here for you.
Thanks, Christine.
That means a lot.
I got to...
- It's okay.
- All right.
Sergeant Batista.
No comment.
Come on, sergeant.
Is this the work of
the vacation murderers?
I said no...
On the record.
It's too early to tell,
but one of 'em, Johnny Rose,
we found out has syphilis,
and it's real bad. Untreatable.
Multiple partners.
Print that.
With pictures.
I call it in now,
it'll be online this morning
and on the stands this afternoon.
With pictures.
While my colleagues
are working the vacation murder theory,
I'm gonna follow Lundy's theory
and check his hotel room for clues.
Lundy devoted his life
to hunting Trinity.
He left word for me
he'd had an interesting encounter
two days ago.
You think it was Trinity?
Every crime scene is a jigsaw puzzle.
So many pieces.
Assemble them right,
A picture forms.
If it was Trinity,
It'd explain why Deb is
alive and Lundy isn't.
Trinity's a monster.
If he was the one who hurt your sister,
you need to kill him.
That was my blood down there too.
You can't let these be
logged into evidence.
Not until I have a complete picture.
Police so far are refusing to comment
on the murder of a former FBI agent
and the shooting of a Miami Metro
homicide detective.
But Channel Nine has learned
there may be a connection
to the so called vacation murders.
Sources tell us that...
All right. Denver
omelet, side of rye toast.
Can I top that off for ya?
Coffee's fine,
but there are no diced
tomatoes in my omelet.
I'm sorry about that.
Cook is slammed today.
I'll bring you a side of tomatoes.
How's that coffee?
My coffee's not the issue.
My breakfast, on the other hand, is.
You need to start over.
Denver omelet... with tomatoes... diced.
Coming right up.
You're a dear. Thanks.
Astor, will you get that?
But it's Dexter's.
Oh, it's okay.
He was in such a hurry
he probably forgot it.
Could be the hospital.
Is aunt Deb gonna die?
Oh, no, honey. No, she's gonna be okay.
Some man. He says
he's Dexter's landlord.
There's something wrong
with Dexter's apartment.
Oh, there's got to
be a misunderstanding.
Uh, yes, hi. This is Rita Morgan?
How long have you been there?
Not long.
You're sitting up.
It's a good sign.
I'm fine.
I didn't even need surgery.
Couple stitches.
Looks like more than a couple.
You have any pain?
No. Just tired.
Whatever they gave me has some kick.
You want me to come back?
It's okay. I'm fine.
You remember anything at all?
You see anything unusual?
It's all still a blur.
Who was hit first?
You, or-
Jesus, Dex.
Am I squeezing too tight?
I expect those kind of questions
From Batista or Quinn,
but not my brother.
You said you were fine.
Twice.
Doesn't matter, anyway.
Just tell me what you want me to do.
That's just it.
You can't do anything.
No one can.
I didn't feel anything.
I didn't even know I'd been hit
until I was on the ground.
And then two more shots.
So much blood.
You're safe.
I'm here.
Lundy had this look in his eyes.
Like he was apologizing.
I couldn't do anything.
I was helpless.
Fuck, I can't even walk
three feet to the bathroom.
Do you need to...
Yeah. Bad.
Come on.
Okay?
Mm-hmm.
I may not know who shot my sister,
or why her life was spared,
but I do know I won't
be returning the favor.
Oh, god. Deb, is she
Peeing.
I'll just-uh...
be outside.
Hey.
How's Deb?
She's lucky to be alive.
I was so worried.
Can I see her?
Uh, she's peeing.
With Anton.
I would have been here sooner,
but I got hung up on the phone.
Your landlord called.
A pipe burst in your kitchen...
at your apartment?
Oh.
I was just hanging on to the place
until the lease ran out.
So I could get the
security deposit back.
Why'd you tell me you got rid of it?
I said that?
Talk about this later.
This isn't the time or the place,
Not with Deb here.
Family comes first.
I'm just so sorry I wasn't here.
You don't have to keep saying that.
So glad you're all right.
I'm not.
Babe, what is it?
I slept with Lundy.
I thought you were happy.
I thought I was too.
I can move out.
No. No. No.
Listen, I'll see you through this, okay?
You did the same for me.
Anton, stop.
You deserve so much better.
Is that what you want?
Sorry I hurt you.
Anton?
Gracias.
Just hung up from
notifying Lundy's daughter.
Then you could really use
a shot of whiskey in there.
I get that the guy's
personally invested in this,
But Matthews hovering
around like a vulture
isn't gonna help us catch bad guys.
Angel...
I made official disclosure yesterday
that we're seeing each other.
We talked about this.
I know.
But it was the right thing to do.
I said I was uncomfortable
with the disclosure stuff,
and you go ahead and do it anyway?
I made a judgment call.
The problem, Maria,
is that you made it for the both of us.
You shouldn't keep the
deputy chief waiting.
What do we got?
Not much.
No witnesses, no security cameras.
Took a statement from Deb,
she can't remember seeing anything.
Forensics.
Waiting on trace and
ballistics from the lab.
APBs out on Rose and Wald.
County's increased
patrols at the airport
and the higher profile tourist hotels.
If my face was all over the media
for shooting a cop and a fed,
I'd be digging a fucking hole
all the way to China.
No one fuckin' go there.
Or you'd be watching the press
to try and stay one step ahead of us.
It's a Hail Mary,
But I planted a story
with Quinn's girlfriend.
She's not-
We're not-
You're the paper's unnamed online source
about Johnny boy's drip?
I figure if Johnny has syphilis
and Nikki wasn't listed by the county
as one of his sexual partners...
She may not know.
Exactly.
Maybe we turn these
two against each other.
Rita was right.
Family does come first.
Finding who did this to
my sister comes first.
Is this a new page of the code?
Revenge?
My sanctuary.
It's private and... sacred no more.
If I have to give up this place,
What will I do about my roommate,
the dark passenger?
This apartment is the only thing
that's helped me keep the mask in place.
Without it...
I'll burst.
They're letting me out tomorrow.
That's great.
Any chance you can give me a ride?
Of course.
I'm also kind of gonna
need a place to stay.
I broke up with Anton,
and, no, I don't want to talk about it.
We can make room for you.
Rita won't mind?
Don't worry, Deb. I'll
take care of everything.
Trinity's a lone wolf.
Unable to connect.
Except with his victims.
He never deviates.
Bleeds out a young female in a bathtub,
forces a woman to jump to her death,
and five days later
bludgeons an older male.
I'll look at potential sites.
This may be the closest
to Trinity I've ever been.
Lundy got closer than he thought.
He just couldn't see how
all the pieces interlock,
what they form.
A sacred ritual.
If there's anyone who knows
the importance of ritual,
it's you.
Lundy underestimated
how far Trinity would go
to make sure his ritual
wasn't interrupted.
Lundy was an obstacle.
And Trinity killed him.
If anyone has ever deserved
to be on your table,
it's this son of a bitch.
Can I help you?
I'm taking on a project.
How big?
Almost more than I can handle.
And I don't have a lot of time.
Maybe you need another hand or two.
There's plenty of laborers out there.
No, no. I work alone.
Sounds like you need the
right tool for the job.
So much work.
But I have to finish
what I started, right?
Yeah, I-I guess.
What would you do?
Me?
Oh, I'd go with the framing hammer.
Got a lot of heft.
It's versatile.
You can't go wrong.
I see what you mean.
You've been very helpful.
Lobby's open 24 hours.
12-story building, hundreds of rooms.
Trinity could strike anywhere.
He'll have to set up shop
in the surveillance room.
Trinity's the perfect predator -
camouflaged, waiting for
his victim to be alone,
and then he strikes.
Trinity struck here 30 years ago.
A bartender, father of two,
was found bludgeoned to death
in the men's room of a tavern
at this same address.
If history is going to repeat itself,
this is where Trinity will be.
Problem is, you have no
idea who you're looking for.
Lundy was so methodical,
He would have commented on
Trinity's physical appearance
if their paths had ever crossed,
but there's nothing in his tapes.
I've listened to them all.
You sure about that?
That's your recorder.
Where's Lundy's?
It wasn't in the hotel,
because Lundy had it on him.
Must have been logged
into evidence. Shit.
Dexter, you need that tape.
You need to be certain
it's Trinity on your table.
There's still time.
He won't complete the
cycle until tomorrow night.
And I'll be here.
Waiting.
Oh, god!
Oh!
That was, uh...
unexpected.
That's not an adjective I usually hear.
I'm not complaining.
I'm just-
I'm just wondering
why you're really here.
My way of saying I appreciate
you running that story
for my boss.
Okay. Hmm.
You fucked me to thank me?
Technically, I went down on you
to thank you.
I thought you said this
was just too complicated,
you being a cop and me being a reporter.
I guess I like complicated.
Look who's here.
Sorry, Astor.
I promise it won't be for long.
It's okay. I get Cody's room.
Sorry, Cody.
Come on, guys. It's
time to go to school.
Check in later.
Everything all right
between you and my brother?
We just need to have a talk.
It isn't about me staying here, is it?
No, you're family. You're
always welcome here.
I'm gonna let you get settled in,
And I'm gonna get you some water
for these pain pills, okay?
Rita.
Thank you.
Thanks for letting Deb stay with us.
It was either here or your apartment.
Look, we can't keep putting this off.
It's still not a good time.
I need to get to the station.
So when do you suppose
it'll be a good time
to discuss why you lied to me?
I'm really trying here, Dexter.
Dexter.
I'm just asking for a
little patience, all right?
Not for me, but for Deb.
Right now I need to focus
on finding who did this.
Okay.
You didn't come over last night.
So little time to sleep lately.
I thought I'd get more
rest in my own bed.
I'm sorry I went behind
your back to Matthews.
It was wrong, and I apologize.
If you haven't noticed,
I'm a bit of a control freak.
You mean like how like to
guard the remote control
with your life?
Or how you need to be the
first one in the shower.
Or how you like to-
Look, the reason I went to the brass
was because it'd be
one less thing to worry
about ruining what we have.
The only thing that
would ruin what we have
is if we're not honest with each other.
No more secrets.
Then I'm not going anywhere.
That's everything collected
from the parking lot and the hotel rooms
back there on the right.
Thanks for doing this.
My father gave Deb the ring,
and it means the world to her.
I checked the inventories.
Masuka never logged it in.
Yeah, Deb doesn't remember
if she was wearing it or not.
The shooting has her pretty messed up.
If my coming down here to double check
helps ease her mind,
so be it, right?
Yep.
Ah, fuck.
Damn it.
You Morgans and that mouth.
Do you mind?
Oh, yeah. Don't sweat it.
There's plenty more
where those come from.
Thanks.
Here you go.
Guess who just found her ring.
Sorry for the trouble.
Thanks a lot, though.
No problem.
I appreciate the personal tour.
Any time I can do rounds
with a fellow human being is a win.
You're alone every night?
Yeah, economy's a bitch.
There used to be two of
us on every shift, but now-
Oh, say no more.
I'm recently laid off myself.
From here on out I'm
gonna be my own boss.
Well, there's plenty
of office space here.
You know, more tenants means more money.
Then maybe I won't have
to do these double shifts
and I can see my kids once in a while.
Oh, you end up setting up shop here,
I guarantee this'll be
your favorite destination
come lunch time.
Right on schedule.
And you brought me a customer.
It's a future renter.
Well, possible future renter.
Can I get you any?
No, no.
Caffeine makes me a different person.
Appreciate the offer, though.
So you say you walk this whole place
every two hours?
That's quite a workout.
My wife calls it low-impact aerobics
or some shit like that.
It takes about 45 minutes,
give or take a smoke break.
Well, we all have our vices.
So how'd you like the building?
It's perfect.
Great.
Thanks a lot.
Mm-hmm.
Rita, I think something's
wrong with Harrison.
I know that cry.
Someone's wet, isn't he?
Good.
Thought it was me.
Oh, no.
No, Harrison loves his aunt Deb.
Can I ask you something?
I don't do diapers.
Did Dexter tell you
he kept his apartment?
What the fuck?
Are you kidding?
He told me he got rid of it.
Me too.
Just thought he might
have said something
since you two are so close.
Not a word.
God, it's like a Morgan
family curse or something-
Make the worst choice possible.
At least Dexter's
don't get people killed.
You think you're responsible
for Lundy's death?
He never would have been
anywhere near that parking lot
if it weren't for me.
Is that why your pain
pills are in the trash?
Punish yourself?
What happened to Lundy isn't your fault.
You had no control over it.
This isn't about choices
or even about you.
Sometimes bad things just happen.
That's the answer to this?
Bad things happen?
Life happens.
I've yet to find Trinity's signature
at any of his crime scenes.
Trinity moves from state to state.
Law enforcement never
links his kill cycles
to one another.
Over 30 years of killing.
The cycle, the ritual,
they tell me where Trinity will be,
But I have to know who I'm looking for.
I have to be sure.
Lobby's open 24 hours.
Guard on duty.
Too much foot traffic.
Trinity'd have to choose another floor.
Ooh. Sorry.
Bus number 432.
Male.
Maybe 6'4".
190 to 200 pounds.
Age around 60.
Hair gray, eyes blue.
Something in them.
Lundy saw a ghost.
Okay, listen up, everyone.
I just got word there
was a shooting at a motel.
You all need to get there
as soon as possible, guys.
So Quinn's already en route.
Angel, you're with me.
Masuka, grab your stuff.
What's going on?
Motel shooting.
Body's a match for Johnny Rose.
I'm going with you.
You can't work this.
You're next of kin.
I've got it.
Let's just hope Deb
is finally gonna get some justice.
That's the plan.
Karma.
What a fuckin' concept.
Uno, dos, tres.
The first bullet didn't
quite make her point.
Lieutenant, we've got Nikki Wald
cornered in the alley
behind Al's liquor store.
Let's go.
Prick.
Son of a bitch. God.
What do we got?
Found her in the alley.
Altered, agitated.
Every time we get near the gun goes up.
- We good?
- Yeah.
Why? Why?
Nikki!
Damn it.
He fuckin'-
He fuckin' cheated on me.
We need you to put the gun down.
He ruined everything.
You fuckin' ruined everything.
She's wasted.
She doesn't even know where she is.
Cover us.
Nikki.
No one's gonna hurt you.
We just want to talk.
The alley's sealed off.
You can't go anywhere.
Did you hear that, Johnny?
What about the boat?
What about Bermuda, Johnny?
Wasn't that the plan?
You piece of shit!
Aah!
We got 'em, Morgan.
Got who?
Nikki Walden, Johnny
Rose. Well, we got Nikki.
Johnny's on his way to the morgue.
What happened?
She fuckin' shot him. Long story.
Look, I know this doesn't
change what happened,
but hopefully you'll
find some peace of mind
knowing this thing's over.
Yeah.
Peace of mind.
I got to take this
skank down to booking.
Congratulations, partner.
Such a waste.
Lundy, those other tourists.
For what? A boat to Bermuda?
Hell hath no fury like
a meth addict scorned.
Your office, lieutenant.
Was-Was that a smile?
I don't know.
Congratulations, Maria.
That was really good
police work out there today.
Thanks.
But it was sergeant
Batista's good police work.
Yes.
Well, I know he's an asset to your team,
but this department can't risk
a defense attorney turning
your romantic involvement
into a courtroom sideshow
every time you work a case together.
What are you saying?
I am saying I need you to
transfer sergeant Batista
out of homicide.
Tom, this is bullshit.
We followed protocol.
Christ, he made this bust.
Which is why I'm going to make sure
That sergeant Batista gets a promotion
along with his transfer.
Have the papers on my desk by Monday.
Sergeant.
Fuck. What is it?
While everyone's chasing
their tails over Nikki Wald,
I'm going after the man
who really shot my sister.
In a few hours, the
enigma that is Trinity
will be on my table.
A riddle wrapped in plastic.
Morgan.
I need to see you.
I'm kind of in the middle of something.
Can it wait?
No.
Well, I'm way over on
the other side of town.
It'll take me at least
an hour to get there.
I'm not home.
I'm where Frank was shot.
You can't even see our blood.
It's like it never happened.
Deb?
What the fuck's your problem?
I got here as fast as I could.
You have everything,
And you're doing your goddamn best
to throw it all away.
Rita told you about the apartment?
What the fuck were you thinking?
You have to make this right.
I'm not sure I know how.
You figure it out.
I'm the fuck-up in the family. Not you.
Don't say that.
You have a choice.
To be a good husband.
To be a good father.
I know.
It's just, uh...
Sometimes I feel trapped.
By what?
Three kids?
A wife who adores you?
Yesterday, I had Lundy and Anton.
And now they're gone because of me.
You didn't do anything wrong.
It doesn't matter what I do.
Or what I choose.
I'm what's wrong.
There's nothing I can do about it.
If I'm not hurting myself,
I'm hurting everyone around me.
There's nothing I can do about it.
I'm-I'm broken.
I'm-
No, you're not.
I am.
Why don't we go back to the house?
Don't! Don't.
I need to be here.
Where Lundy died.
I can't do a fucking thing about it.
My sister doesn't deserve
to be in this kind of pain.
But I know who does.
Trinity hurt my sister,
and I'm going to hurt him back,
And it's going to feel-
-uh-oh.
Your manager let me in.
He had no idea we were married.
Funny thing is, I'm
getting to wonder myself.
Rita, you're upset.
I actually convinced myself
that by coming here
this would all make sense...
Why it was so important
that you keep this place a secret.
As I was coming over here,
all I could think about-
that you were using drugs again.
That you were having an affair again.
That will never happen.
I went through your cabinets,
rifled through your desk,
looking for anything
that would explain
what would be so horrible
that my husband would
have to keep a place
to hide it from me
or his own sister.
And?
I was gonna break the lock,
but I was too scared
of what I might find.
And you know why?
'Cause you put me in
this position, Dexter.
This is not the type of person
or wife that I want to be.
You really want to know what's inside?
Yes.
It was Harry's.
I wasn't comfortable having
it in the house with the kids,
so I kept it here.
See?
I have nothing to hide.
Except for the syringes,
scalpels, and bone saw
hidden in that secret drawer underneath.
Nothing to hide.
Like your car accident
and your concussion and this apartment?
The most disturbing thing
about your lying is that...
I'm beginning to see
just how good you really are at it.
You should sleep here tonight.
When you're ready to come home,
we have a lot of work to do
if this marriage has any hope.
Hey. Pulling an all-nighter?
Yep. No rest for the wicked.
Have a good one.
Always do.
It's almost poetic-
One serial killer
ending the 30-year reign of another.
Trinity could be
anywhere in this building.
I've got to get
to the security surveillance room.
Huh. Where's that security guard?
He was here last night.
I've been so focused on Trinity,
I've neglected who his victim might be.
The bludgeoning victim 30 years ago,
didn't he have two kids?
It's the security guard.
If he's here...
then where's Trinity?
Aah!
Take the bait.
Oh, no.
Please.
I'm a father!
You were no father.
Aah!
You made me...
The recording disc is gone.
Where are you, Trinity?
Oh, my god.
You made me do this.
Trinity.
Shit.
The elevators aren't moving.
He's using the stairs.
Which one?
I can't risk picking the wrong exit
and miss Trinity.
His car has to be here.
No way I lose you again, Trinity.
In Miami, nobody sees.
He's scurrying back
to whatever hole he crawled out of.
The lone wolf thinks this is over.
Asshole!
What the hell's he doing?
Where are you going, Trinity?
Stay with him.
He's not getting away.
He doesn't belong here.
It doesn't make sense.
Hi, honey.
Mmm. Missed you.
Hey, kids.
Daddy.
Hey, dad.
Lundy was wrong.
I was wrong.
Neither of us
knew pieces of the puzzle were missing.
Trinity's a husband,
a father.
He's...
like me.