Previously on Dexter...
Do you know where you are?
- Ambulance. What happened?
- You were in an accident.
Bad news is that
you sustained a concussion.
I'd like to keep you
here for observation.
Dexter, oh my God!
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
Just a little fender bender.
Doc says I'm good to go.
You got a minute?
I'd, uh,
like to pick your brain.
Lisa Bell?
The girl in the bathtub.
Of course.
The Trinity killer's
most recent victim.
Trinity is going to kill again.
Another woman,
older than Lisa Bell this time.
But the person that you should really
be talking to is my sister.
She's lead on Lisa Bell.
You sure that's a good call?
Given our history.
I wouldn't want to mislead you.
What I have with Anton...
It's-It's great.
I fucking love you.
The reason I'm in Miami
is because I'm convinced
these bathtub murders are
connected to a series or murders
all over the country.
Christ.
I'm an idiot.
Debra!
Tell me again this isn't crazy.
Crazy good.
I brought you a copy of my article.
A string of robberies turned
deadly in what authorities
are now calling
the vacation murder.
I found your guy.
Name's Johnny Rose.
Briefing room in five minutes.
Strategy meeting.
Dexter's turned up a lead on our shooter.
Don't sweat it, Quinn.
I've got much bigger things to worry about.
I thought it was a fender bender.
I'm sure there's a bent fender
somewhere in this mess.
Oh, my God.
Rita,
what are you doing here?
You lied to me, Dexter.
[latin music]
Dexter s04e03: "Blinded By The Light"
The backyard barbecue.
It's a holdover from the last ice age
when food was scarce,
and men had to work together
to take down such a large beast.
Those who worked well with others survived,
and their genes have been passed
down through the centuries.
Until they landed here-
In this...
My community.
[latin music]
[drumming]
Soda?
Whatever.
How 'bout you?
I'm good.
Ah, wasted youth.
Hey, can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah.
I just got off the phone
with Dr. Montgomery,
the doctor that took care
of you after your accident.
Oh, right.
Why didn't you tell me
you had a concussion?
I just wanted to keep you from worrying.
You already have so much to deal with.
The doctor also told you
that you weren't supposed to drive
for the next ten days,
and you didn't listen.
So I will now be doing
all your driving.
I will take you to work
in the morning,
and I will pick you up
at the end of the day.
- Rita, I'm perfectly capable-
- Dexter.
The past few weeks, you have not been
the most present father and husband.
Remember.
We're a team here, right?
Okay, we work together.
She's right.
Maybe now's the time to turn that around.
Score a few points.
Which will then make Rita
more likely to say yes
when I need a little time for myself.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Let's go eat.
So I guess you saw somebody
bashed in Kate's birdbath.
I know, that's awful.
Poor birds.
And poor Kate.
Why would someone do such a thing?
The same reason he knocked over
the Andersons' water fountain,
pulled down the Garcias' basketball hoop
and spray-painted
the Schwarzs' trash cans.
'Cause he's a dick.
He knocked the sea horse
off my mailbox, too.
I hated that sea horse.
Well, your mom picked it out.
- You know Andy.
- Uh, yeah, of course.
Hi, how are you doing?
Hey, Jess, Jess, Jess?
Do you really need to be doing that?
Yeah, I really do.
His wife passed away last year.
So, uh,
so about this neighborhood vandal.
We all need to work together
to deal with this guy.
The last thing we need
is a dangerous presence
in our neighborhood.
You know,
it's a funny thing, Dexter.
This all started to happen
time you moved in.
A little suspicious,
don't you think?
I'm just busting your chops.
Oh.
[chuckling]
My chops are busted.
The danger of community is that
the people who don't belong
are looked upon with suspicion.
Those of us who prefer to work by ourselves,
the lone wolves,
risk being singled out.
Cody. what's that?
Waah!
[laughing]
I'm gonna get you!
Oh, I'm scared!
So I become an expert at blending in,
camouflaging myself,
becoming one of the guys.
Astor, what's that?
Ahh!
Oh, my God.
Dexter!
I'm so humiliated.
What were you thinking?
She was wearing a bathing suit.
This blending in thing
isn't as easy as it looks.
[eerie music]
[indistinct sobbing]
We're here.
Stop right here.
That's okay.
Oh!
Oh, God, please.
Don't hurt me!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
Don't do anything stupid.
Careful, now.
Wouldn't want to hurt yourself.
It's pretty, isn't it?
Okay, now.
It's time for you to jump.
What?
God, no.
Yes.
It always ends like this.
No, but-
Shh.
It's already over.
Why are you doing this to me?
You know
I'm not to blame here.
[sobbing]
Come on, now.
Please, no!
Now you just need to let go...
and fall.
Please, I'll do anything.
- Good. Jump.
- No, I can't!
- You can.
- I have children!
I know.
Jason and Susie.
[groaning]
If you like,
I can swing by your house,
Put an ice pick in your husband's head,
and bring your kids back,
and throw them off one at a time
until you finally decide to jump.
Is that what you want?
Please...
What?
Please.
Just push me.
It doesn't work that way.
Jump.
[screaming]
[thud]
Oh... Mommy.
You've only been here a month,
and they've already got you tagged.
It's not just me.
There are other houses.
Dex, we've been through this before.
11th grade.
Bunch of kids T. P.'ed the house.
And you made me clean it up.
Because it raised questions, Dexter.
It would have made people
think, "Why this kid? Why him?"
You can't afford to have people
asking those questions.
No one's asking questions.
Getting married,
having a kid,
moving here-
I know you're under a lot of pressure.
Yeah, I am.
But you can't let things slip.
I'm not slipping.
But somebody is.
[guitar music]
How come you never make the coffee
even if you're up first?
'Cause I don't want it
bad enough to make it.
I don't even know what to say to that.
Well, baby,
if there was chocolate cake here
I would eat it, but I sure
as hell don't want to bake one.
- Hey! Good news!
- Yeah?
Yeah, the Sandpiper Hotel
wants to book my band
for a one-month gig.
Three nights a week.
Wow, that's great.
No more cruise ships.
And best of all it means
no more time away from you.
Really?
Yeah, I'll be here every day.
Going to bed with you every night.
Waking up with you every morning.
Waiting for you to make me coffee.
[laughs]
# Karma karma karma karma
karma chameleon #
# You come and go #
OK, if I count yesterday.
then this is day two of me being
the best husband in the world.
I can last another five days.
I really need to stop
for a coffee someplace.
You already had a coffee.
# Red, gold and green #
# Every day is like survival #
# Survival #
Really, I started Saturday afternoon,
So it's actually been
more like 21/2 days.
# Every day is like survival #
Only 41/2 to go.
I'm never gonna make it.
As far as our vacation murder suspect,
Johnny Rose,
we've still come up with nothing.
We've spoken to his mother,
his sister,
his past two employers-
Everyone in his apartment building,
his mailman,
the liquor store guy across the street.
So no one's talking.
We have his immediate family members
under surveillance,
but we're still not getting any hits.
Well, expand the search.
Draw up a new list of subjects.
Morgan, where do we stand
on the Lisa Bell murder?
Uh, somewhere in the middle
of Shit Creek.
Well, you better find a paddle,
or I'm moving you
onto the vacation murder
with the rest of us.
Finding Johnny Rose is
our number-one priority.
Yes, Ma'am.
Dexter. Hey.
Uh, hi.
Quick question: Do you like the Dolphins?
I'm really more of a Manatee guy,
but sure.
Club level seats.
- Enjoy.
- Why?
I can't go.
And I asked myself,
who's a friend that I could give 'em to?
So I thought of you.
Miami Dolphins.
Football.
Club level?
Jeez, who do I gotta fuck
to get those kind of tickets?
Here.
No fucking.
Dude.
All right, listen up.
We got a report of a female body
found at the old port.
It looks like a jumper.
Who wants it?
Sounds exciting, Sarge,
But I think I'm gonna hold out
for a cat stuck in a tree.
Huh, I wonder if that's
the woman Lundy predicted.
- We'll take it.
- Okay.
Unless she landed
on a pile of marshmallows,
there's gonna be blood.
Grab your kit.
Sure, I'll follow you there.
Ha ha, not a chance, concussion-boy.
Rita said no driving for you.
You're coming with us.
[sighs]
[hip-hop music]
Climb in the back, Dexter.
You'll be right on the subwoofer.
You can feel the bass in your spine.
Loud.
Female. Caucasian.
Mid-30s, I'm guessing.
If this is the latest victim
of Lundy's Trinity killer,
then he's a very different
monster than I am.
Cause of death?
Gravity.
Why her?
Why here?
What is Trinity's code?
Does he have one?
No sign of a struggle.
No pre-mortem bruising.
No ligature marks.
It's looking like a suicide to me.
Oh, well, if it isn't
Special Agent Grandpa.
- Shut up, Quinn.
- Detectives.
- Morgan.
- Agent Lundy.
Masuka.
Cool hat.
You have a name yet?
Driver's license in her car
says Tarla Grant,
from Fort Lauderdale.
So what brings you
to our little suicide?
Just observing.
You're a little quick
to decide it's a suicide,
aren't you?
Still has her jewelry,
money in her wallet.
Wasn't robbed.
Well, why would she drive down
from Fort Lauderdale
to jump off this abandoned warehouse?
Maybe she liked seagulls.
Well, until we know
one way or the other
I'd like to treat this
as a homicide
If that's okay with you.
All right.
You two, on the sixth floor.
The rest of you,
search the grounds.
Victim: Tarla Grant.
30s...
So listen...
I want to apologize
For being such a douche the other night.
No need.
We're all allowed to be
the occasional... douche.
Thanks.
It was pretty embarrassing.
Debra, if we're being
completely honest here,
Then, yes, I did come to Miami
to follow a case.
But I have to admit
that I'm glad the killer chose this city,
knowing I'd find you here.
So is Dexter right?
Did you predict this jumper?
What I did was suggest that
if Trinity held to his pattern,
we could expect to see
another woman die soon.
Is this her?
Little early to tell.
But you might want to check
your missing persons reports.
I wouldn't be surprised
to discover that she's married
with two kids.
What else?
I'm very curious to know
if there was a similar death
at this site 30 years ago.
I make my bodies disappear.
Trinity leaves his out in the open,
supremely confident that no one
will ever trace them to him,
Decade after decade...
after decade.
[upbeat country music]
Thanks for the ride.
Anytime, partner.
Great,
security lights.
Just what every serial killer needs.
What are you looking at?
- Oh.
- Dexter!
Did you get my message about
the neighborhood watch meeting?
Actually, no, I didn't.
Hey!
This is my community.
I am one of you.
Uh, great.
Love having the neighbors over.
Are you ready to fight crime, Dexter?
You betcha.
That's good.
Be aware of your neighbors.
Know their schedules.
That way you'll know if
something's different,
If anything seems off.
We don't want that.
Here, have a whistle
and a head flashlight.
It'll keep your hands free
when you're out patrolling.
Patrolling?
We're patrolling?
Your job is to watch and report,
watch and report.
- Watch and report.
- You got it.
[laughing]
Community college for me now.
Hey, Dexter, our neighborhood
beautification association
Asked me to give this to you.
I'm the secretary.
It's a warning against
the graffiti on your gate.
I know it's silly,
but they want you to repaint.
Hey, Dex.
I guess you saw the new
motion-detector lights
I just put in.
Sure are bright.
Yeah, brightest I could get.
Made sure I angled one
right on your place, too.
That's very neighborly of you.
We have to look out for each other.
Yeah, this guy started off small,
a few broken windows,
Andy's mailbox,
but yesterday he broke into
the Walkers' guest house
and trashed the place.
Yeah, next thing he'll be
stealing our women.
Can't let him steal our women,
now, can we?
No, they're our women.
[laughing]
- Is that the sign-up sheet?
- Yeah, yeah.
See, we're setting up patrols
for every night of the week.
I'm good for every night
but Wednesday.
I got a poker night at the Lodge.
Great.
No one will come in or out
of this neighborhood unnoticed.
Including me.
It's not the neighborhood vandal
I'm worried about.
It's the neighborhood watch.
Hmm, graffiti.
Excuse me.
So I was all set to go to the
University of Miami next year
till my dad decided
to get himself laid off.
That blows.
How about you, Jesse?
You want to sign up for
the neighborhood watch?
Sounds kind of lame.
So lame.
Paint can, soda can...
I'm thinking fingerprints.
Let me get that for you.
And I know one little lady
who is up past her bedtime.
Mom!
Dexter, you can't treat her
like a little girl anymore.
I can't?
Hey, Dex.
Hey, Elliot.
Have a nice day!
You knew this day would come, Dexter.
You've always been good with kids,
but eventually they grow up.
They become more mature,
develop complex emotions that
just aren't in your skill set.
Astor's becoming a whole person,
and you're...
Something less.
I hope you're not taking
any of this seriously.
The wife, the kids,
the house in the 'burbs.
It's all great camouflage,
but that's all it is.
It's gotten more complicated than that.
Then uncomplicate it.
You need to realize your limitations.
Remember exactly who you are.
Probably should have used
something a little darker.
It's fine, dad.
Nothing's gonna show through.
I hope not, Dex.
For your sake.
Hey, you ready to go?
Almost.
I've got the best of Bananarama.
It's a cruel summer.
As long as the neighborhood vandal
keeps my neighbors on edge,
I will have no privacy.
And I'm not going to let you
do that to me, Jesse.
Tarla Grant, married, mother of two.
It fits.
- It fits what?
- Lundy's theory.
That she's another victim
of the serial killer.
Yes.
What?
His whole life is about serial killers.
That's all he thinks about,
so of course he thinks
she was killed by a serial killer.
I think he's
a little smarter than that.
I'm sure you do,
otherwise you wouldn't be
sitting at your desk going
through 30-year-old files
all afternoon.
Oh, yeah, guess what.
So are you.
Just unsealed the juvey
records of Johnny Rose,
our vacation murder suspect.
Anything?
Shoplifting with his high
school girlfriend, Nikki Wald.
That was like, what,
ten years ago?
You think they're still in touch?
Since she testified against him back then,
I'd say extremely unlikely.
Well, at this point, I think
we need to take any shot we can.
She lives in Oakland Park.
I'll drive out there with you.
Let's go.
That seem accidental and unplanned to you?
Even I believed it.
I was thinking we could stop
somewhere for lunch first.
I know a little place where
we can order some room service.
Okay, here we go.
30 years ago to the week.
Female, caucasian, 36, mother of two.
Jumped to her death off the same warehouse.
The woman's family insisted
she was the victim of foul play,
but it was ruled a suicide.
Doesn't mean fuck-all.
Someone fell or jumped off
the same warehouse eight years ago.
Someone else jumped off
a ship loading crane
on the same Pier back in '86,
and another body washed up on the rocks
right in front of the warehouse
only two years ago.
Nobody knows how it got there.
This is Miami, Deb.
People die.
And sometimes it's by murder.
I want to follow up on this.
Okay, Tarla Grant seemed to have
a pretty decent life.
No apparent reason for suicide,
so keep it open for now.
Fuckin' a we'll keep it open.
I'd know that foul mouth anywhere.
Anton, what are you doing here?
I love you too, baby.
Come on, let's have some lunch.
I have a fuckload of work to do.
All right.
All right, but it's a working lunch.
Ah, solitude.
Something I won't enjoy again
until I deal with Jesse,
the neighborhood shithead.
- Hey, Dexter.
- Hey.
Dexter, I was looking for you.
Hello, Debra.
- Hi.
- May I?
Yeah.
Frank Lundy.
Anton Briggs.
My lover-
Friend.
My boyfriend.
All of the above.
So, Dexter,
I was wondering if you'd gotten
the blood tox results back
on Tarla Grant yet?
Yeah,
I should check on that right away.
Please, finish your lunch.
All done.
Tarla Grant,
just like you said: 36 years old,
married, mother of two.
That's a shame.
I found the matching 30-year-old case.
What's that?
Big case we're working on.
I'm afraid I've enlisted Debra
in another of my mad theories.
Ah.
What's it all about?
Finding out who killed her.
Oh.
I don't suppose you happened
to bring the, uh-
30-year-old file?
Read the husband's statement
from 30 years ago.
Family never believed it was a suicide.
But since Trinity never leaves a trace,
there was nothing to investigate.
You give good room service, Angel.
You know, we should do
lunch out more often.
Missed one.
[giggles]
No arrests since she got busted
with Rose back in high school.
Spotty job record,
but that's about it.
It's a stretch, I know.
[knock on door]
Nikki?
Nikki Wald?
I'm not sure Miss Nikki Wald is home.
Okay.
Hey, I'm Sergeant Batista
from Miami Metro homicide.
It's Rose.
Get down!
[gunshots]
Shots fired, 41st and Andrews.
We need backup!
- Good?
- Yeah, I'm good, let's go.
Suspects Johnny Rose
and Nikki Wald going northbound
on 41st street in a white sedan.
- I think it was gray.
- A light-colored sedan.
Make? Model?
Suspects are armed and dangerous.
Rita thinks I'm with
the neighborhood watch.
Truth is, I'm gonna do
a little more than watch.
There's dad,
off to his weekly poker game.
[car ignition starts]
And if I were the delinquent son,
I would take advantage
of my father's absence.
Going after him feels very familiar,
except it won't have
its usual satisfying ending.
The best I can do is scare
a little sense into this kid.
Hey!
Come on, it's the vandal.
Let's get him!
Oh, fuck.
It's watch and report, assholes.
Not watch and chase.
This is so humiliating.
Go that way.
This neighborhood's gonna kill me.
Already? I mean, the kids
aren't even dressed yet.
I know, I know, I'm early.
Just wanted you to see
the latest work of the vandal.
Happened in the middle of the night.
He obviously smashed the window,
released the emergency brake,
Gave it a shove, and,
uh, let it roll.
So dangerous.
Is that Cody's bike?
Oh, my God.
What if he had been out here playing?
These dummies share the same
size and weight distribution
as our victim.
At this height,
any variant in trajectory
resulting from a simple jump
or being pushed off the building
will be evident in where they land.
What if she took a running leap?
People don't kill themselves that way.
They just let go.
Oh, hey, either of you
interested in buying tickets
to the Dolphins game?
Club level?
I'll let them go for 500 bucks.
- Where'd you get those?
- Dexter.
Son of a bitch.
Come on,
we have dummies to drop.
Is he gonna pay me for those?
Must be weird for you-
Lundy coming back.
Why would it be weird?
You're weird.
None of my business, I know.
But... if I loved someone,
and that person was gone,
and then I moved on,
and then found someone else,
and then that first person
all of a sudden showed up again,
I don't know-
I've never had that problem.
But it's gotta be a little confusing.
Maybe.
A little.
So then maybe if you know
that it's supposed to be
weird and confusing,
then maybe it's
a little easier to handle.
Thanks.
It's always the same
three kills with Trinity-
A young woman in a bathtub,
followed by a mother
falling to her death,
and ending with a man
getting bludgeoned.
I put her in a short shirt
so that we can see her panties
while she's falling.
Specific.
How many times that you know of?
I've got the bits and pieces
that add up to at least 15 cycles.
Since we just turned the clock
back another 15 years,
I'm sure there are considerably more.
Wow.
That's impressive.
In a very evil way.
What's really impressive
is that I can't prove a thing.
Could never get anyone
at the Bureau convinced.
He's that good.
Why do you think he's so successful?
Trinity's likely someone
who's gone his own solitary way
through life,
So preoccupied with his own obsessions
that he's foregone all but
the most rudimentary
of human connections.
A lone wolf.
Exactly.
It's a little bit disturbing.
Yeah.
I mean...
I could just as well
be talking about myself.
Sure, I've been married.
Was married for 29 years, happily.
But even so,
the only thing that
really got my heart beating
was the hunt.
I'm sure you can't relate.
No, sorry.
And now here I am at 60,
watching dummies fly off a roof,
still on the hunt.
It sounds like Trinity
is a worthy prey.
What's really got me intrigued
is the notion
that he's returned to Miami.
He's come home.
I'm not sure "home"
is the right word.
People like us
don't really belong anywhere.
We just pass through.
Drink up.
You're next.
The vacation murders.
Word is, you know who
Johnny Rose's accomplice is.
Forget it, you'll get
the press release same time
as everyone else.
But my Sergeant and Lieutenant
were almost killed yesterday,
So if you put any negative spin on it,
I'll be very angry.
When you're angry, you're very sexy,
so this could be
sort of a win-win for me.
Let's just say I'll be angry
in a very withholding
sort of way.
Okay.
- The bathtub murder?
- Still under investigation.
The jumper at the old Port building?
Ditto.
I gotta run.
See you tonight?
Sure.
Can you just go over
the figures one more time?
They're not gonna change.
The test results indicate that
Tarla Grant jumped,
rather than was pushed.
I don't buy it.
I think we're looking at a murder victim.
Deb, we also got the autopsy report.
She had a small tumor.
Talked to the husband.
They just found out last week.
Maybe she was taking the easy way out.
Maybe she was determined to fight it.
That doesn't mean she killed herself.
I checked her cell phone records.
No text messages,
no suicide note.
Not everyone leaves a note.
I just got word.
We will be debriefed
on our shooting incident
in the morning.
Okay, good.
We need to get our stories straight
about why we left the precinct at 12:30
and didn't get to Wald's
apartment until after 3:00.
We grabbed some lunch
and then we had a flat tire.
Flat tire it is.
You okay?
I've read Masuka's notes.
That, along with the autopsy reports,
leads me to believe that
there's no reason
to keep Tarla's case open
as a murder investigation.
Lieutenant, I think
it's premature to close it.
- Lundy has this theory-
- You don't work for Lundy.
You're welcome to pursue this,
but between the vacation murders
and Lisa Bell, I think
you're gonna be very busy.
You're on your own with this one.
Poor Cody.
Ouch.
Where'd the glass come from?
That car on Elliot's lawn.
Cody was coming back from their pool,
and he stepped on a piece.
Does he need stitches?
No, he's fine,
he's just scared.
First his bike, now this.
Poor guy.
Give him a hug for me.
Hi.
Help me out here, Dexter.
I've been going out of my way
trying to make things good
with you,
but no matter what I do,
you just throw it back in my face.
You don't need to make
things good with me.
Come on,
what's it gonna take?
Quinn...
I don't care if you're a dirty cop.
If I didn't take that money,
it would just sit
inside a locker until some fatass
who sits behind a desk
grabs it to buy new carpet
for his office which he never leaves.
I put my life on the line every day.
I give this job everything I've got,
and I can't even afford
a down payment on a condo.
I thought you had family money.
Had, and that has nothing
to do with anything.
Just don't fucking call me dirty.
The last thing I need
is a cop mad at me.
Look, you're right,
I take it all back.
I honestly
don't give a shit.
Just keep my sister out of it,
okay?
You don't understand any of this,
do you?
You can't,
'cause you're not a cop.
You're not one of us.
[sigh]
Cops... Another community I'm not part of.
[exhales]
What?
It's so crowded in there.
Well, I guess so.
A wife and three kids.
They're always there.
Tell me about it.
It was easy living with Anton
when he was never home.
I'd come back to a quiet apartment
and unwind without having
to deal with anybody.
Now, as soon as I walk through the door,
he's there,
waiting to engage.
There's no escape.
And now Lundy shows up.
Is that good or bad?
I have no fucking clue.
- [giggles]
- What?
We're complaining because
people want to be with us?
How lame is that?
You think Tarla Grant killed herself?
No, I don't.
Masuka said she wasn't thrown
or pushed from the building.
She jumped.
What would make her do that?
Fear is a powerful motivator.
You should go inside.
You're home.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
- Hi.
- Hi, sweetie.
Where is everybody?
I'm in here.
Fort Cody.
Hey, buddy, how's your foot?
It's better.
Good.
Keep holding down the fort.
Okay.
And I'll take care of my end
once you guys go to sleep tonight.
You may want to talk to Astor.
This is one of those moments
when I wish
I was like everyone else.
I'm sure other people
would know what to say.
Hey.
I know you're not a little kid anymore.
Duh.
I'm sorry.
It's just...
Sometimes I'm...
Dumb.
It's okay.
You can be dumb.
[sighs]
Thanks.
What?
It's funny.
A few months ago,
after a shoot-up like this,
people saw me leaning against you,
they wouldn't think twice.
They still wouldn't think twice.
They don't know anything about us.
I know.
But I think twice.
I'm constantly worried that
people will misinterpret.
Let them misinterpret.
Hey...
I need this as much as you do.
This Dexter guy.
First of all, who the fuck
is named Dexter?
[groaning]
Oh, that feels good.
What, did his parents know
he was gonna grow up
to be a fucking egghead?
I met him.
He seems okay.
He's a lab geek.
Fuck, that feels good.
What else?
I'm exhausted.
I spent all afternoon in the sun
throwing dummies off a warehouse,
'cause Super Agent Lundy has a hunch that
the dead woman is connected
to this big serial killer case.
Hmm, really?
Oh, yeah.
Lundy always gets his man.
Yeah?
Well, so do I.
This is where
I first noticed the pattern.
Raleigh, North Carolina, 1993.
That got you curious?
Then I found
San Francisco, Louisville,
Detroit, Richmond.
Eight different cities in all
that I know of.
Never the same place twice.
Until now.
Ready for another?
Oh. yeah.
So now this is your little
retirement project?
You're completely incapable
of relaxing, aren't you?
That's just it.
This is how I relax.
I get the scent of a bad guy,
I can feel my blood pressure go down.
And here I thought I was bad.
You are.
You're exactly the same as me,
just in a much prettier package.
Are you flirting with me,
Agent Lundy?
Simply stating the truth, miss.
[phone vibrates]
Thank you.
[cell phone rings]
Excuse me just a second.
Hey.
Hey, so you want me
to order some takeout?
I'm still working,
so I'll just grab something here.
Okay, well,
I love you, babe.
Me too.
[glass shatters,
car alarm blaring]
Ah, Jesse, hard at work.
Big surprise.
I'm gonna wait in your room
and scare the shit out of you.
Jesse!
If you're in here...
Andy!
Apparently I'm not the only one
who isn't exactly what he seems.
Is that the wrench you use
to break windows?
- What the heck?
- Don't move.
Okay, what's going on?
Who are you?
You're gonna stop breaking things,
stop rolling cars down the street.
Stop everything you've been doing.
If you so much as touch
another window,
I will come back here,
and I will leave
with your head in a bag.
I already have the bag.
Fuck you!
Let go of me, you fucking asshole!
Fuck!
You really don't know
what you're doing here.
I know exactly
what I want to fucking do,
Piece of fucking shit.
You should've seen their faces.
Those boxes in their driveways
with their big fucking
flat-screen TV's.
"Oh, look at us, aren't we so fucking rich?"
They're lucky the only thing I broke
was their fucking windows.
And you're lucky
I don't break your fucking neck.
- It's over.
- Fuck you, it's over.
[groaning]
- Give up.
- No!
I played by the rules my entire life.
And look what it got me.
My wife's dead.
I lost my job.
My son hates me, and now...
The bank wants to take my house away.
So if you want to take my fucking head,
you take it.
I said stop.
You want me to come back
for your son's head too?
What? No!
Not my boy!
It's all I have!
You're gonna save
what's left of your family,
save what's left of yourself.
Because all that other stuff
is over.
Say it.
Yeah, it's over.
Bad news for Andy is
he's lost his house.
Good news for me is he'll
be out of the neighborhood.
But why should I care about him?
It's his world.
People like him made it this way.
At least he had a chance to belong.
It's still there, Dex.
A stain so deep it can't be erased.
[grunts]
[sighs]