All right, stand here.
You're just tall enough.
I- I don't-
I don't think I am.
It just goes around. There's
nothing to be scared of, all right?
I didn't say I was scared.
It'll be fun. Come on. When I was a kid,
this was my favorite thing ever.
I don't like rides.
All right, all right.
I just-I thought it'd be fun.
I shouldn't be making you do this.
Let's go home. We can have fun at home.
No, Daddy, wait.
The ride does look like fun.
Oh, this is awesome!
Alice, are you all right?
Honey, you all right?
Alice!
Alice, are you okay?
Transcript: FRM - Synchro: jh26
Nothing happened.
Something happened.
It was a little kiddie ride.
She hates those rides. I don't
understand why you insist on making-
Okay, I appreciate the
fullness of your answers, but
I just wanted to know if she
had any history of abdominal problems.
- No.
The admitting doctor
noted no family history of-
I have an aunt with Crohn's Disease.
You didn't mention that?
I forgot what it was called. Your aunt
has got a million things wrong with her.
If you paid attention for five minutes-
I doubt it's Crohn's.
She has none of the other symptoms.
You're alone with her for eight hours,
she ends up in the hospital.
I'm wondering if we can focus on
answering the questions, Mrs. Hartmann.
I'm not Mrs. Hartmann. We're divorced.
I suspected.
And your past generosity
made me think of you.
We're half a million
dollars from our goal.
Of course, this is a naming
opportunity for your foundation.
Is-is there a problem?
There's something on your face.
It's, uh-
Excuse me.
I'm sitting in there
hoping it's a sniper
because at least then the
sociopath isn't my employee.
This baby won me second
place in the clinic's weekly
"weirdest thing pulled
out of an orifice" contest.
I am this close to putting
a new lab in Oncology.
You do not want to
know what came in first.
- House.
- Rhymes with "fucchini."
Give me his pills.
- Where's my prescription?
- No more free floating prescriptions.
Princeton PD has already
forced Wilson to shut down.
A cop says boo, Wilson shuts down.
Every doctor in this place is afraid
to make a move without covering his ass.
Do you think maybe you're
shouting at the wrong person?
Tritter's obviously out to get me.
He doesn't care-
- Your forged prescriptions!
- Allegedly.
Your pain has become my pain.
From now on you get reasonable
doses at reasonable times.
But I hurt in an unreasonable way.
- Then dip into your secret stash.
- Tritter took it.
Then move onto your secret secret stash.
I ran out.
Then move onto your
secret secret secret stash.
Parents say she's not on any med.
If the pancreatitis wasn't set
off by drugs, and she hasn't been sick,
that leaves trauma or
some kind of structural defect.
Put up the CT.
- What's that density there?
- Shadow. Looks normal to me.
- We got a referral from-
- Excuse me.
You stash your drugs
in a Lupus textbook.
It's never Lupus.
Who's got gallstones,
and why do we care?
- Gallstones?
- Biliary duct is dilated.
Probably from a stone lodged in it.
Must've caused a nasty
case of pancreatitis.
She's six.
Six-year-olds don't get gallstones.
So she didn't have pancreatitis.
Your theory is an invisible gallstone?
His theory correctly
predicted pancreatitis.
You might want to wait until
he actually tells us his theory
before you start kissing
his theory's ass.
My theory is...
vanishing gallstone.
She had it, and it passed.
Those things travel in packs.
The rest of them are probably hiding out
in her gall bladder. Do an ultrasound.
If I'm right, we'll take out
the organ so we can analyze the stones.
I wasn't kissing his ass.
It must've just looked that way from
our angle. You on your knees,
House bending over.
He predicted the pancreatitis.
- It's his dad's fault.
- My dad was an ass.
But you did everything he wanted you to,
and in return
- you got everything you wanted.
- Yeah, it's that simple.
The strategy worked.
Dad got him a cushy job.
Paid for his cushy life.
Cut me out of his cushy will.
I told you.
It's just his nature.
Poor guy's hardwired to kiss ass.
House was right.
Gallstones.
I didn't know a kid
could get gallstones.
It's unusual. That's why
we need to see what's causing it.
We'd like to remove Alice's
gallbladder and analyze the stones.
- Sure.
- No.
- Just 'cause I said sure?
- I am capable of my own thoughts.
It's a simple procedure.
The gallbladder isn't essential-
If the doctor thinks we should do it,
we should, Edie.
You think maybe we
should get a second opinion
before we start removing
our child's organs?
That's an effective
use of taxpayers' money.
I'm actually off this week.
I'm guessing you don't have a family.
Most people have enough going on
in their lives that they don't have
to personalize every slight.
This isn't personal.
Not anymore.
My head of oncology had to shut down.
My entire staff are afraid to
make a move without covering their ass.
I think you're angry
at the wrong person.
You think Dr. Wilson deserved
to have his assets seized?
- His entire practice ruined?
- No.
So you just don't care?
This is how I get what I want.
I put pressure on people.
And if it doesn't work on Wilson,
it'll work on you.
You punish the innocent.
None of you are innocent.
Not one of you.
Not one of you has told me the truth.
about Dr. House.
The pills allow him
to cope with the pain.
No, the pills distort reality.
He is an addict.
He's not out robbing a liquor store or-
No, he's treating people.
He needs to find a different
way to cope before he kills somebody.
If he hasn't done that already.
If you're right,
he has a medical problem.
It should be dealt
with by doctors, not by-
Well, it's not being dealt with
by doctors. Doctors are covering it up.
The whole point of
the criminal justice system
is to make things right
when everything else fails.
With all due respect...
you have failed.
Sorry. Didn't know you
wanted your kid dead. Although,
for a couple of G's I
could still make it happen.
- Who the hell are you?
- I am complete stranger
who apparently cares more about
whether your kid dies than you do.
- You're Dr. House.
- You've seen my stage show.
She's not dying. She has pancreatitis.
Once you've treated that,
I'm taking her home.
And do what, burn sage?
I want you to do the surgery.
My father had gallstones.
They were totally harmless.
Alice had one bad one, but it passed.
For all we know this is over.
And for all we know she
could get sick again tomorrow.
Then I'll take her to her pediatrician.
She's six, Rob.
She shouldn't have unnecessary surgery.
Or a moron for a mom,
but what can you do?
You're the doctor. I'm the mother.
I outrank you. Live with t.
I've read the file.
You've got 15 minutes.
It's like people like
this who killed Copernicus.
- Galileo.
- Either way.
And they just locked Galileo up.
They killed his spirit.
Nobody likes a showoff.
Luckily, Alice Hartmann has
a dad who's willing to see reason.
Reason as defined by
slavishly deferring to you.
Their doctor.
Your Honor, I've had no
opportunity to consult my attorney.
There's no time.
- All I want is a second opinion before
- No time!
Your testimony is their child will die
if I don't grant this motion right now.
Am I under oath?
Let's say yes.
My testimony is that
this child might
die if you don't grant
this motion right now.
Literally no time for a second opinion.
Wouldn't be as good
as the first opinion.
- Dr. Cuddy, what do you think?
- She's not a specialist in this area.
Her opinion is worthless.
Dr. Cuddy,
what do you think of Dr. House?
Is he as big a jerk as I think he is?
Bigger.
But he knows what he's talking about.
Got a page.
She's complaining about her stitches.
Nurse just said that's
completely normal. Did you get
- the test results for the gallstones?
- Any minute now.
No time for a second opinion
but the test takes three-
My skin hurts.
I know I no longer have
the right to demand it,
- but could you please take a look?
- Sure.
She's pissed, now she's just
looking for things to go wrong.
You're right, I'm so petty I hope
she dies so it vindicates my opinion.
I didn't mean that, sweetie.
Mommy was being sarcastic.
She's a few years away from
grasping sarcasm, don't you think?
Guys.
I already gave you that number.
Simple surgical procedure turns
a little girl into The English Patient.
What gives?
Must be allergic to something
we used in the surgery.
C ameron.
C- a-m-e-r-o-n.
This is my office. I'm talking.
There are people here who work for me.
They're not listening.
Explain this to me.
Tritter froze my account.
They're checking theirs.
I'm on hold with a lawyer.
Call Wilson's lawyer. He'll tell
you exactly how and why you're screwed.
This kid has no history of allergies.
You've gotta talk to Tritter.
You gotta make this go away.
Yeah, great plan.
The man's obviously open to reason.
Well, here's the plan. We do nothing.
We wile away the time
diagnosing the patient.
The stones were calcium bilirubinante,
pigment stones.
Which are non-conclusive.
Kid presented with low-grade fever,
mild anemia.
That plus the stones
indicate bacterial infection.
Bacterial infections
don't cause a vesicular rash.
And doing nothing is not a plan.
It's specifically a lack of a plan.
We cut into her belly. Bad boys escape.
They swarm over, colonize the wounds,
and... ka-plow! Vesicular rash.
Allergic reaction is 100% more
likely with or without a history.
Fever and anemia could've
been symptoms of pancreatitis.
Hello?
Thank you for your help.
They froze my accounts.
- Thank you for your help?
- It's not her fault.
He hasn't gotten to mine yet.
I'm gonna withdraw and much as
I can as fast as I can. Lunch is on me.
Do a scratch test. Check for allergies.
When it comes up negative,
start broad-spectrum antibiotics.
Bullies bully. They don't
get a reaction, they lose interest.
No go do what I ask before
I stick your heads in toilets.
- How'd Otter get here?
- Daddy got him last night.
It was at the dry cleaner.
They close at 6:00. How'd you get it?
I drove over there. I knocked
for about ten minutes. And then I
I begged.
How about some ice cream
for when this is through?
- My tummy hurts.
- Ginger ale?
Yeah?
- I'll take over.
- Be right back.
He's already been really good at
the big romantic gestures, but ask him
to do the dishes or show
up for a meal on time or drive her-
Almost done here.
- What are you doing here?
- I work here.
Passively-aggressively
you gave up your practice.
I have clinic hours.
Now, you're passively-aggressively
spreading peanut butter
with a big sign around your neck saying,
"Wilson doesn't have enough
cash for the cafeteria."
You know, before Lenny
Bruce died of a drug overdose...
If you're gonna confront me
with everyone who ever abused narcotics,
I think I'm gonna have
to get something to read.
...he was arrested
on obscenity charges.
He went through a series
of arrests and trials
because he just couldn't
stop challenging the police.
He became obsessed with
his own legal problem.
And his act turned into long,
humorless rants about fascist cops
and the violation of his rights.
I get it, I get it.
I need to change my nightclub act.
You think more props?
House, scratch test is getting results.
A lot of results.
How could she be allergic to everything?
She can't be.
It has to be an infection.
You see a positive allergy
test and decide it's infection?
The bacteria got into
the scratches in her back.
Infections radiate.
That shape of this isn't-
- Eat this.
- I don't feel like eating.
- It'll make you better.
- A sandwich?
- Magic sandwich.
- There's no such thing-
Just take a damn bite, okay, kid?
Amazing how she didn't
go into anaphylactic shock.
That's diagnostically ridiculous.
Right, she's allergic
to everything except peanuts.
If she is allergic, antibiotics
could cause a massive systemic reaction.
If she's allergic, but she's not.
Chase, you're right. The shape indicates
allergy. The tests indicate allergy.
Just because she's
not allergic to peanuts
doesn't mean she's not
allergic to lidoca?ne or-
Chase, hang the bag!
You can grow a backbone tomorrow.
No, I'm not giving my daughter
drugs that could shut her system down.
You know what else shuts down systems?
Death.
Sorry.
I can't let you do this.
Luckily, Alice Hartmann has a mom
who is willing to see reason.
You were in here yesterday
telling me her father's
guardianship was best for her.
I honestly figured I'd
get a different judge today.
- You agree with Dr. House now.
- Now my kid actually is sick.
- She was sick yesterday.
- Her pediatrician doesn't know
what's wrong with her,
says House is the best.
She loses guardianship.
Then, House is a hero.
- It's got nothing to do with me deci-
- Hey, zip it! I've heard enough.
- This lawyering thing is easy.
- You shut up too.
Arguing over every decision
is a waste of her time and mine.
Since her parents can't or won't agree,
I'm awarding temporary
guardianship to a doctor
who will place the health
of the child above all else.
I don't think Dr. House is capable-
- Dr. Cuddy.
- Yes, Your Honor.
No, I was finishing my sentence.
The kid's all yours.
3:00. Give me the pills.
I don't even know this kid. How am I
supposed to decide what's best for her?
Fine, I'll choose. I'm gonna
side with the angry doctor's opinion.
Give me my pills.
We're not gonna go broad-spectrum. If
there's any chance that she's allergic-
- There is no chance.
- Of course there's one.
- I'm appealing.
- No, you're not.
If you think it's bacterial,
pick one antibiotic.
Not gonna be enough.
We need to go broad-spectrum.
It kills bugs. That's what you want.
We'll go with metronidazole.
You don't have to testify
he's broken any laws.
Though I'm sure you could.
Just how many pills he takes in a day.
Because I'm fairly confident
I can prove that he didn't, uh,
have that many legitimate prescriptions.
I really hope no one dies while
I'm sitting here not talking to you.
I- I had a, uh-
I had a buddy at Trenton PD
do some digging.
Your brother locked up for drugs.
Your own flesh and blood,
and you don't even visit.
But your boss practices
medicine on drugs,
time to start lying to the cops.
If I run out for coffee, will
I get back before you make your point?
You, um, you testify...
I can make sure that
Marcus goes free on parole
in less than two months.
My brother and I...
We grew up in the same home.
But...
I made something of myself.
He didn't.
Dr. Foreman, the way you talk,
you'd think you never
committed any crimes yourself.
You and Dr.
House. You are both cold bastards.
You don't give a
damn about your brother,
and you can't stand House.
But I do expect you to take this deal
because you hate hypocrisy more.
House has had a thousand chances.
You had two chances.
Why is your brother stuck at one?
Well, if she was allergic to this
antibiotic, we would've seen it by now.
I think we are out of
the woods as far as that goes.
Guess they occasionally get one right.
You're gonna be glib about this?
- You almost killed her.
- I made a choice.
The same choice you made yesterday.
Only when I make it, I'm an imbecile.
Every decision you
have made has been wrong.
When this over,
I'm suing for sole custody.
Because I trusted
doctors when you didn't?
Because it's not just
about the past two days.
Like you have the hotline on
what's best for Alice. She loves me.
She never does her homework when she's
with you. She never brushes her hair-
Her heart's racing. Pressure's rising.
The two of you, get out.
I'm her mother. You can't just-
You fight. She has an anxiety attack.
The two of you are making her worse.
Get out and don't come back.
How's the kid doing?
Much better as of about two hours ago.
You got any money for lunch?
If you like parsley and croutons.
Tritter finally froze my accounts.
- Really?
- You surprised?
Why wouldn't he?
I figured if he was singling you out,
you must've done something different.
What, like talking?
Yeah, and now that he's frozen
your accounts, you probably will.
You need the cash, right?
He doesn't freeze my accounts,
I'm guilty.
He does freeze my accounts, I'm guilty.
Is Alice having some procedure done?
- She's fine. She's resting.
- Where?
In her room,
where you're not supposed
I was just at the window.
There's no one in there.
Her backpack wasn't there either.
You don't think her father could've-
Call security.
- Get a gurney.
- She's stiff. She can't move.
I don't know what happened.
I mean, she seemed fine.
Help her, please.
On the plus side,
she could medal in luge.
Muscle rigidity is almost
exclusively neurological.
Neuroaxonal dystrophy.
She's the right age.
Except that her liver's starting
to shut down. No dystrophy would-
M etronidazole.
Great idea. Let's not go broad-spectrum.
Let's not take any chances
of actually curing her.
House, can you focus on the case?
No! Because I'm in pain.
Because you think that compromise
is the answer to everything.
I need more pills.
Muscle rigidity plus liver
involvement means Wilson's.
No, no corneal ring. No mental changes.
Then what?
I need more pills!
- No, you are on a reasonable-
- What the hell does "reasonable" mean?
Keep it quiet.
Her B.P. reacts to stress,
and yelling is not gonna-
If you think that I'm not in pain,
then don't give me anything.
Keep me away from the aspirin.
But If I'm in a buttload of pain,
I need a buttload of pills.
Fine. You need more pills.
You're not getting them.
You can have all the aspirin you want.
I say we draw straws.
Loser drives down to Trenton,
scores him an eight-ball.
- Which one of you gave her an aspirin?
- What?
Her symptoms fit Reye's Syndrome,
which doesn't make any
sense unless she took aspirin.
Rob?
No way. She's a kid.
I've read the 800 warning labels.
I'm not even angry.
I just want her to be okay.
She's lying. She's angry.
Because you kidnapped her kid.
She'll be angrier if the kid dies.
- I didn't.
- One aspirin
combined with a pre-existing
infection is all it takes
- to set off an attack.
- I'm not lying.
Well, sure,
you've certainly earned our trust.
Where was Alice the
night before she came in?
With me. Well, at my house. I went out.
She stayed with a babysitter.
- Where were you?
- None of your business.
You hired someone that
might've poisoned our daughter.
- She's 15. She's very responsible.
- Is she a 15-year-old pharmacist?
Or just some kid from down the
street who needed 20 bucks for lip gloss
and couple of Tiger Beats?
Put your kid on charcoal hemoperfusion.
Shouldn't we see what
the babysitter has to say?
I know what she's gonna say.
She's gonna lie to save her business.
I need more pills.
We are gonna use this
machine to clean your blood.
It goes out of you and through
a filter like the filter in a fish tank.
It's kind of cool actually.
I'm scared.
It won't hurt.
It takes a while,
so it'll be boring.
But it won't hurt.
It's gonna make you better.
They hate each other, don't they?
We're never gonna be together again.
Well, you never know.
You gonna break out the rubber hoses,
the bright lights?
I'm not gonna testify just
because I have to borrow lunch money.
I know.
Women don't give up guys that
they're in love with.
I'm not in love with House.
The guy is unhinged and unethical.
Does what he wants
with no concern for others.
But you stand by him.
It can't just be loyalty and respect.
No.
I'm a girl,
so I must be in love with him.
Not because you're a girl.
Because ten years ago
you got an "A" in calculus
until you ratted yourself out.
Showed your professor
a mistake he missed.
- Because you married a man-
- Don't go there.
You used to be someone
who did the right thing.
House has changed you.
Do you think it's
all been for the better?
How's it going?
- Boring.
- Told you.
So far, so good. Just like five
minutes ago, ten minutes before that.
What's the matter?
She must've thrown a clot.
Let's get her out of here.
I'll call the O.R.
You said it wouldn't hurt!
- Found it.
- She's burning up.
- Give me a sec.
- Foreman, she is on fire.
- Almost there.
- Get me some cooling blankets now.
Right away.
Every time we touch this kid,
something goes wrong.
Bad mojo is not a diagnosis.
You really had to flash
your private stash in front of me?
You find it easier to
lie for me if it's more subtle?
Fine.
Your told your associates
that I had frozen your accounts.
- Yes.
- Smart lie.
You figured they'd think there was
a reason that you'd been singled out.
Like that
you had agreed to testify against House.
Yeah, I assume that's why you did it.
You have a reputation
as a bit of an opportunist.
You already gave your boss
up once from what I've heard.
To save my job.
He goes down now, I lose my job.
You lose your job, you fin another one.
You get fired...
Chances don't look so hot.
- Why would he fire to me?
- Because you rolled on him.
- I haven't rolled on him.
- I think you will.
And he's gonna think you already did.
As far as he knows, my accounts
are frozen just like everyone else's.
In 24 hours, all three of you
will have access to your accounts again.
- Why would you-
- See,
if I was looking at this
as an outsider,
I would say
it was because Detective Tritter had
what appeared to be a very
pleasant lunch with Dr. Chase.
Yeah.
The two of them
appeared to be
working together.
How the hell are there
no ice packs in the O.R.?
Clot's out. Ice packs aren't gonna hold
her for long. Where are the blankets?
In the E.R., they're dealing
with a four-car collision.
We need to cool this kid
down before her brain melts.
What are you doing?
She got a major dose of heparin
to thin her blood for the procedure.
Could've induced thrombocytopenia.
That's unlikely. The charcoal
would've absorbed a lot of the heparin.
She's been anemic.
- Could be a primary blood disorder.
- Or we never cured the infection.
Are you saying she never had Reye's?
We just put that little
girl through excruciating pain.
The pain wasn't House's fault.
Even if the clot was a reaction
- to what we gave her we still had-
- I don't need you to cover my ass!
What I need is my Vicodin!
Two pills every six hours.
Like I'm on an allowance.
She's a given a cop leverage
over medical decisions.
What the hell? Why don't we
get a plumber in here, ask his opinion?
Hey, Cuddy, you know any
rodeo clowns who can weigh in-
Where the hell is she?
Look at her arm.
- I told you it was an infection.
- We fixed the infection.
Well, apparently not.
I asked you for broad-spectrum.
You put her on the bare minimum.
It's a good thing you failed
to become a mom because you suck at it.
What's good about this rash?
Good guesses, but no.
It's on parts of her
body that we haven't touched.
She's got a fever of 103.
She's in and out of consciousness.
But it's not a reaction to anything
we did. Her mojo is off the table.
Which means?
Oh, so close!
Means that thanks to
Cuddy's candy-ass approach
broad-spectrum antibiotics
are no longer an option.
This thing has grown horns and fangs.
We gotta figure out what species it is.
Go in with a spear to the heart.
Okay, you guys are sulking.
I don't really care why, but apparently
I can't do my job without finding out.
- Tritter released our bank accounts.
- Horrible, horrible news.
Wow, I'm glad we didn't let that fester.
If she did have Reye's, then it
could be varicella. They're associated.
He released our money.
You do know what that means.
The correct question is
"how could it be varicella
given that she's not itchy?"
Rickettisal pox causes rash,
fever, and muscle pain.
Pain, not paralysis. Rocky Mountain
spotted fever on the other hand.
Rash, fever, anemia, paralysis.
- And I didn't say anything to Tritter.
- Neither did I.
Maybe he wants us to
think that one of us talked.
- It worked.
- You were with him.
- We were all with him.
- We weren't laughing with him.
Maybe he just gave up.
Start the kid on chloramphenicol
for Rocky Mountain spotted fever.
- Can we talk?
- Nope.
- I really think-
- Either you screwed me
and you want absolution,
or you didn't and you want applause.
Either way I'm not interested.
Busy.
You okay?
Yeah, sure.
What I meant by "are you okay?" is
what the hell did House do?
- Nothing.
- What did he say?
I've seen House be rude a thousand
times, usually to achieve something.
I have never seen him
be mean just because he can.
Seriously?
- What did he say?
- Nothing. Doesn't matter.
Well, I've seen House be
rude to you a thousand times,
but I've never seen it get to you.
People think
House has no inner censor.
But the fact is he holds himself back,
because when he wants to hurt, he knows
just where to poke a sharp stick.
I have been trying to get pregnant,
and House knew.
He told me I would fail as a mother.
And you're this upset
because you think he's right?
I've had three separate implantations.
The first two never took.
The last one I lost.
I'm sorry.
You didn't fail.
Those where physical events.
A little girl is...
scared and in pain.
I was awkward,
terrified of doing the wrong thing.
- That's normal. That's-
- I didn't hug her.
I didn't even reach out and hold her
hand. I told her it was gonna be okay.
She needed reassurance.
I told her her folks
might get back together.
When I see people with their kids,
it's so natural.
It's like they have an instruction
book imprinted on their genes.
Maybe I just didn't get a copy.
Maybe my wanting
to be a mother is like a
tone deaf person wanting to sing
opera or a paraplegic who wants to-
Well, I see what you mean
about House poking in the right spot.
Chloramphenicol isn't working.
- What dose did you give her?
- Yeah, maybe Chase screwed up.
We always end up there.
Just getting a jump on it.
I doubled her up.
The infection's morphed.
- It's moved into her muscle sheath.
- Necrotizing faciitis?
That's impervious to drugs.
The only treatment...
is to cut away the infected area.
- So we amputate.
- Arm and leg?
We can't cut a six-year-old kid
in half without a confirmed diagnosis.
Moves too quickly and we waited too
long. We don't have time for a culture.
We can at least observe her for a few
hours. Confirm the rash is spreading.
It spreads, she dies.
You're talking about crippling her.
We're not even certain
this was an infection.
Right! She's six! She's cute!
She can't have flesh-eating bacteria!
It's just wrong!
Let's cure her with
sunshine and puppies.
Cute kids die of terrible illnesses.
Innocent doctors go to jail.
And it because cowards like you
won't stand up and do what's required.
You can sit around and moan
about who's the bigger weakling.
I'm gonna go do my job.
What kind of quality of
life will she have without-
Great thing about life.
It's got qualities.
And if we can't agree?
I don't know.
He's yelled at us before.
Because he thought our theories
were dumb. Not because our theories
- were sending him to jail.
- He's going through withdrawal.
Could be causing mild paranoia.
It'll pass,
we just have to suffer thought it.
We never ruled out allergy.
We gave her drugs.
She had no negative reaction.
We cut open her belly.
She got a rash on her belly.
We did a scratch test on her back.
She got a rash on her back.
I know House ruled out mojo,
but it can't be a coincidence-
Too late to be playing
differential games, isn't it?
Get that thing away from me.
I don't want to get burned.
Laser pointers don't burn you, genius.
- Skin, no. Retina, yes.
- You don't trust my aim?
Maybe you should cover any sensitive-
He was wrong about the puppies.
House,
you gotta stop the surgery.
She doesn't have necrotizing faciitis.
Oh, good.
She's got erythropoietic protoporphyria.
She's allergic to light.
It's genetic,
either parent could've carried it.
I know what it is.
Infection fits better.
She gets worse every time
she goes under surgical lights.
- Dad takes her outside-
- Liver's shot too.
- She swallow a flashlight?
- Stop the surgery.
- Get the hell out of my way.
- No, I'm-
Light damages the blood cells.
The damaged blood cells
contain protoporphyrin.
The protoporphyrin
builds up in the liver.
That's why the liver's shutting down.
Stop.
How can she be allergic to light?
She's never had this problem before.
The negative reaction starts at birth.
It reaches critical
mass around this age.
Her blood cells create
chemicals in reaction to light.
When they reach the liver,
it tries to filter out the bad cells.
The chemicals damage the liver,
and one byproduct is gallstones.
So she'll just keep getting worse?
EP can be managed.
We'll give her beta-carotene.
She's gonna need special light bulbs
and filters on the windows. She's
probably gonna need to be home schooled.
Her life will be complicated,
but she will live.
How do you get something like this?
- It's genetic.
- So one of us...
Both of you must be carriers.
She's gonna want to see
you when she wakes up. So...
don't screw it up.
So, what's new?
- House missed one.
- That's happened before.
He nearly maimed a little girl.
I got it right.
And I told him, and it didn't matter.
Chase, you solved one. You helped a
patient. That better be enough for you.
Beckett was gonna call his
play "Waiting for House's Approval" but
decided it was too grim.
Trust me.
I'm not waiting anymore.
I'm gonna need 30 pieces of silver.
Transcript: FRM - Synchro: jh26