I'm okay,
let's just go home.
You're getting checked out.
I tripped on the ice.
Eight other kids tripped.
This is embarrassing.
You said you were just gonna
hang with your friends.
I turn around
and you're out there on the ice.
I'm fine.
You don't know that.
You fell.
Awkwardly.
No, I didn't.
You don't know
how to fall.
I'm 16,
I've been falling a lot.
I think I'm getting
the hang of it.
And I checked.
And now the doctors
are gonna check.
You don't think
that you're overreacting?
I don't need you
to fix every boo-boo.
Then stop getting them.
I was just playing around
with my friends.
I was having fun.
You know you can't do that.
Oh, I can't have fun?
You know what I mean.
I'm gonna have a talk
with your friends
No!
and tell them that they need to stop...
No.
I don't want you
freaking them out.
Fine.
Fine, we'll go
to the hospital,
but they're gonna tell you
that I'm fine.
and they're gonna tell you that
you don't need to worry about...
Mom!
Mom?
Mom.
Hello!
Mom, you gotta wake up.
No one's coming.
Mom!
911, what is your emergency?
We got into an accident
along the canal road
just outside Kingston.
My mom's unconscious.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mom.
www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@MAOREN
Sync:FRM@????·???
HOUSE 314
Where's Foreman?
He's down here somewhere.
Somewhere.
Very helpful.
Do you have any idea
when he's getting out tonight?
Sometime.
I realize you can't predict,
I just thought you might
be able to estimate.
It's Valentine's Day.
I've planned
a surprise getaway.
Getaway.
Get away.
Is my mom okay?
She's gone to surgery.
Foreman.
Your girlfriend
wants to know
if you're available
for Valentine's.
Act surprised.
What are you doing DOWN HERE?
There's a snowstorm.
E.R.'s short staffed.
We're all
supposed to be here.
You're supposed
to be here.
And you're an ass.
Act surprised.
This could sting a little.
Ow!
Can we hurry this up?
Make sure that... Take your time.
What's your name?
Hannah Morganthal.
You have CIPA,
No, I don't.
We have to do x-rays
to make sure
you don't have
internal injuries.
Blood tests to make sure
no infections.
EEG for
neurological anomalies.
And...
biopsy a spinal nerve.
Whoa whoa whoa.
Congenital insensitivity
to pain
is one of
the rarest conditions on the planet.
There's only been about...
60 documented cases...
Yeah, and I have
seven reasons
to think she's one of them.
She says she's not.
That's reason number one.
She knew what it was
without us telling her.
Two, she's still wet
from the snow,
but she's not shivering.
That's odd.
Unless she can't sweat
or feel hot and cold.
The ambulance was warm.
I want
to see my mother.
Three, scarring around
the lips and tongue.
When she was a baby, she chew on herself
without feeling it.
I fell through a window
when I was a kid.
Four, when you cleaned
the wound,
she flexed into the cleaner
instead of away from it.
It's hard to fake pain
when you've never felt it.
Takes an imaginative leap,Ms. Morganthal.
That's one of
them Jew names.
Ashkenazis
are a higher risk group.
One the other hand,
she says she doesn't have it.
And she'd be dead by now
if she'd never been diagnosed.
They killed our Lord.
You gonna trust them?
She wants
to see her mom.
If she admits
having CIPA,
she knows we're not
letting her go anywhere without a battery of tests.
You said
you had seven reasons.
I pulled a number
out of the air.
What, five isn't enough?
Five lame reasons aren't.
I'm taking her
to see her mom as soon as--
I can hit her again
if six isn't enough.
Do the tests.
Need to bail on the E.R.
I got a case.
Why are you
wearing perfume?
Is this a real case or one of those
imaginary cases
that happen
when you're bored?
CIPA.
CIPA is a diagnosis.
Diagnoses happen
at the end of cases.
She's got no idea
what's going on In her body.
There's gotta
be something wrong.
In other words, she could
be perfectly healthy,
but you're curious
about someone
who can't feel pain
because you always feel pain.
So you wanna go exploring.
She was
in a car accident.
She needs x-rays,
blood tests, EEG,
nerve biopsy.
I also note that,
althounow was coming down in sheets this morning,
you left your hat at home
and used ear muffs.
Do your tests
except for the--
So while everyone else
was just worrying
about getting in,
you were concerned with hat-head.
Blind dates are never
a good idea.
Only reason to wear
a scarf like that
is as a beacon
to identify you in a crowd.
Do your tests.
Except the nerve biopsy.
I need the nerve biopsy.
You'd risk
paralyzing her.
But it's neurological.
You have no evidence of that.
She tripped.
Do you have any evidence
other than the fact
that a typically clumsy
CIPA patient
tripped on an icy day?
If the EEG
reveals a problem,
we can talk then.
You could have
left the scarf at home
and just told him you'd be
wearing a look of desperation.
Spiking on leads C3
and O2.
She could
be going into a seizure.
I'm fine
I think there's
a simpler explanation.
You're not gonna ???
I'm fine I wanna see my mom!
So sedate her.
She won't consent.
She's a teenager.
No dad,
mom's still in surgery.
What do you want us to do,
hold her down?
Only until you inject her
with a sedative.
Then you can let her go.
We tried.
Seriously?
She's strong
and doesn't care.
We'd have broken something
before we could get her
to sit still enough to inject her.
So break her arm.
She won't mind.
You're cranky.
I'm in pain.
Come on,
let's go break her arm.
Nurse Shortie,
your biz-nitch.
How long
you gonna waste her time?
So glad
we're walking somewhere.
Another 60 feet
and this conversation is over.
When you guys
are out of this program,
Cameron will find somebody,
Chase will find
eight somebodies,
and you'll be alone.
30 feet.
You'll date and you'll date.
But you're
the ultimate Darwinian.
You've got to fight
for everything.
Anybody else
would just slow you down.
Yeah.
I'm still with her,
aren't I?
Yeah.
I can only imagine
it's because she hasn't given you an excuse
to break up
and you don't have the guts
to recognize your own reality.
I wanna see my mother!
Hi again.
Not sure I can say this
without being condescending,
but then you'd get
the false impression
that I respect you,
so...you're a kid.
You're scared,
you're stalling.
Grow up.
I'm not scared.
I'm never scared.
See?
How juvenile was that?
You can't feel pain.
Nothing left but pleasure.
Why don't you tell me
how wonderful that is?
It sucks.
Better than being in pain
all the time.
Get in the chair.
Every morning
I have to check my eyes
to make sure I didn't
scratch a cornea in my sleepmy
Oh, God, stop.
I'm in a pool of tears here.
I can't cry
Neither can I.
Every morning,
I check my eyes
for jaundice.
In case the Vicodin's
finally shot my liver.
I can't run anywhere
without examining all my toes for swelling.
I can't run.
Boys can't hold me
for too long because I can overheat.
Girls can't hold me
for too long
because I only
pay for an hour.
(Hannah)
I need an alarm on my watch
to remind me
to go to the bathroom.
You know how many
humiliating experiences before I thought of that?
The bathroom's
50 feet from my office.
Every drink of water,
I weigh the pros and cons.
After everything I do,
I self-check.
Mouth, tongue, gums,
for cuts.
Count teeth,
check temperature.
Fingers, toes, and joints
for swelling.
Skin for bruises.
I got shot.
I sat on the stove
when I was three.
Wanna see the coil marks?
Yeah.
You think I'm lying?
You think I just wanna
check out your tuchus,
as your people would say?
Get in the chair
and run the damn tests.
If she moves again,
give her nitrous.
You weren't shot
because of lege ain,you were shot
because you're a jerk.
Some think the two
are connected.
He didn't have to do that.
Yeah, he did.
I'm sick?
No, you EEG was normal.
X-ray showed no breaks.
Blood test
showed no infections.
Urine indicated no...
Hannah?
Call a code!
Oh, God.
Need ice packs
and cooling blankets.
Got saline in there?
She's not flush,
she's not sweating.
You must be--
She has a temperature of 105.
Wow, she's actually sick.
We got her temperature
down below boiling.
Could be infection.
No, LP showed normal proteins
and no white blood cells.
High bilirubin.
Could be a liver problem.
Nope, transaminases
were normal.
Could be drugs. She's smoked pot
since she was 11.
No again.
Tox screen was clean.
We're doing this case
backwards.
We do the tests
and then she gets sick?
Maybe we did something
to her.
Maybe she got sick
after the tests.
We should re-run them.
And biopsy a spinal nerve.
You wanna risk paralysis because she's got
a fever?
I want to risk paralysis
because I don't know
what's causing t fever.
???
It's a fever!
In a CIPA patient.
Obviously, things
are a little different in her upstairs wiring.
And have been
since the day she was born.
Yeah.
It's much more likely
that whatever it is
was cleverly waited in hiding
until you guys
were done testing.
Were are you going?
You're all
against this, right?
And you're all gonna stand on principle
and refuse to do it, right?
I'm going
to get Cuddy's approval.
(Cameron)
How long are we gonna
keep Hannah in the dark about her mother?
(Chase)
Long as possible.
Side airbag
should be standard.
I'm sure she'll agree.
(Cameron)
She should know
her mother's situation.
Breaking that news
is that surgeon's problem.
Any word from House?
No.
Maybe Cuddy will say no.
[laughs]
Cuddy never says no.
That's not true.
Nobody ever says no.
We don't say no.
You don't say no.
He'll come back,
he'll browbeat us,
he'll give us seven reasons,
and eventually we'll fold.
We all will,
not just me.
The only way we can avoid
biopsying this kid's spine
is to find the answer
some other way.
All the tests were negative.
We need a better history.
How much more paperwork
do you need?
We've got pediatric records,a few dozen E.R. records,
our own
admission questionnaire.
What's the first question?
Insurance coverage.
Okay, second question.
Just make your point.
Where does it hurt?
If we knew where it hurt, we could diagnose her.
You do know CIPA means
she can't feel pain.
No, CIPA means
she's insensitive to pain.
She still has scattered
nerve fibers that could conduct pain,
but the signals don't make it to the brain.
What if we give her
more pain signals?
A lot more pain signals.
Maybe some of them
will make it through.
You wanna torture her?
No.
Yes. We do this
to anybody else, it's torture.
Doing it to her
is no different than pricking her finger.
We keep poking sharp sticks
into her,
eventually
we'll find the part that's already tender.
So what does
a Dean of Medicine do?
Oh, can we please
not talk about that?
I will
talk about anything else.
I'm just trying
to get away from work.
Metaphorically.
Because geographically, the coffee place
around the corner
from the hospital
probably isn't the furthest you could get.
Well, the snow.
Roads are clearing.
But it's a good place
to beat a retreat from.
You usually expect
your dates to go wrong?
Experience has taught me
to have an escape route.
Well, low expectations,
that's in my favor.
Whatever happens...
I need you to understand
that there are certain aspects
to my life
I'm no happy about.
I need the nerve biopsy.
And you had to come here
personally to tell me that.
And how did you even know
I was here?
I had to bring the file.
This was the most noncommittal location
in walking distance.
You left your car keys
on your desk.
Greg House!
You two must have met
online.
Either that or you've got
a friend who secretly hates you.
Uh, Don Herrick.
Yeah, we connected through
singleballroomdancelovers.com
Why would he volunteer
that information?
Why would I hide it?
You didn't tell him
that anything he said
would be held against you.
So what line of work
are you in?
Oh, auto maintenance.
Changing oil and filters.
Great, my place overcharges.
Can't trust anything
you guys say.
Where're you located?
In 14 states.
I own Eastern Lube.
Most CIPA complications and she's got a fever.
LP? Urine?
Clean, normal.
Same with
the white blood cell count.
Cancer?
Nothing on the scan.
I think it's her nerves
messing with the temperature control.
Amyloid, sarcoid.
There's a lot
of candidates.
I want a biopsy.
Fine.
If that's what you need,
go get it.
He seems a lot nicer
than that one
from Wicca need a daddy figure
dot com.
One of these is warm,
the other is very hot.
Start here,
move to the hot one.
Just a few seconds.
Then back.
We're gonna monitor
activity in your brain while you do it.
If you feel any response
to the heat,
it could indicate
a vascular problem.
How's my mom doing?
(Chase)
She's okay.
do you feel anything?
No.
What does okay mean?
She's still in surgery.
They tell me
it's going okay.
You can
take your hand out.
And you didn't
ask anything else?
Take your hand
out of the water.
What's going on
with my mother?
Hannah.
You just got
second degree burns.
I'll be fine.
What's going on
with my mother? Is she gonna die?
They said she's okay.
Surgery this long
is typical when there are
internal injuries.
Naloxone and kinase
proteins in.
And 27at's gonna
make me feel pain?
didn't feel anything
when you guys screwed this thing
into my head.
It'll repl'le missing chemicals
in your nerves.
Heighten sensitivity.
We'll be drilling
directly into your skull.
A response
could indicate sarcoma.
What does it feel like?
It...hurts.
Um...sorry.
Bone pain
is the worst there is.
So you need to let know
as soon as you feel anything.
She's ready.
So what... I just sit here
while you guys drill a hole in me?
You wanna talk?
Just you and your mom, huh?
You two
must be pretty close.
We were.
Until I got arrested.
The third time.
Drugs?
Fights.
You got an advantage.
Not really.
Never know when to stop.
You piss a lot of people off or are you just trying
to piss off your mom?
Those are pretty much
the only two choices you have.
Hannah?
You want us to stop?
Stop the drill. Stop the drill.
It's okay.
What'd you feel?
Where did you feel it?
Hannah, I need to know
how it hurt.
Hannah!
I am so tired of this.
Did you know
that the new nurse
from cardiology
is sleeping with
that weird lawyer
from the board?
The guy with 11 fingers?
He has 11 fingers?
How do you
not notice that?
The nurse
used to be a man.
She's not anymore?
But we can't
talk about that.
I thought we were.
We were supposed
to talk about that.
I came here
But on the way up,
I ran into Cameron.
You've got
a CIPA patient.
Mmm.
Tranny nurse
is more interesting.
Oh, it's way
more interesting.
But instead, I've gotta
be your damn conscience.
I'm tired of being
your conscience.
I don't enjoy being
No one enjoys...
You're studying her.
She's actually sick.
Which you found out
after you took her on.
I was curious.
Since I'm not a cat,
that's not dangerous.
I don't think that metaphor
was designed to actually warn cats.
You don't care
about her illness,
you care about CIPA.
Which means your focus
is gonna be on getting your answers,
not hers.
Thank you.
Forewarned is forearmed.
What do you think
you're gonna figure out?
You think her lack of pain
is somehow the answer to your pain.
I think if you'd stop talking
to Cameron,
then right now,
we could be ranking nurses
in order of do-ability.
Need you.
What did the nerve
biopsy show?
Never did it.
Then do it.
Can't.
Why?
She's gonna jump off
the lobby balcony.
You think
I can catch her?
Get away from me!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Yes, you are.
You're just jealous
that I can do anything.
Hannah, you're having
a paranoid delusion.
I don't believe you.
Think she would
This is real.
You want me to be in pain.
You even said so.
If we wanted to hurt you,
we'd let you jump.
Just let me see my mother.
Fine, we'll take you
to her O.R. observation room.
I don't believe you!
Your mother is fine.
I just spoke
to her surgeon.
I don't believe you!
Hannah, what do you want
from us?
What do you want us
to do?
I can't feel my legs.
If you're trying to pull
the same stunt twice in ten minutes...
I'm not pretending.
???
WALK ???
Anything?
We're not
looking for pain.
Anything at all, pressure?
Nothing.
You have
six br bones,
a fever, a concussion,
erratic heart rhythms,
and a complete lack
of sensation below the waist.
I feel fine.
Is my mother
out of surgery yet?
Not yet.
This is excellent.
The paranoia
seems to have dissipated.
But her vitals
keep getting worse.
She could be dead in hours.
But...if you're gonna die
a miserable, lingering death,
pain-free is the way
to do it.
You sure the fall
didn't cause the paralysis?
The paralysis
caused the fall.
Spine's clean.
No veritable fractures
or spinal cord compression.
Even better.
The nuttiness and paralysis
mean there's definitely
a neurological component.
Could be a nerve disease.
Which is why we need
to look at the nerve that you didn't biopsy.
There are other tests...
HIV? Syphilis?
She's negative ???
Vascular?
No.
ANA was negative.
Cerebral clot?
No, MRI was...
Thyroid storm.
Makes sense, given her glucose reaction
was slow
and potassium's down.
Yeah.
I'll check
with an endocrinologist.
Bennett's on call.
Perfect.
No.
Need a consult.
I already okayed
your nerve biopsy.
Need an endocrinologist.
Bennett's on call.
Won't pick up.
His cell phone
must be broken.
Mine's working.
Had to give you the file.
I assume you're thinking
thyroid storm.
Have you done
a hormone panel?
Normal. TSH was on the low side.
Is that a cheery fire
I hear crackling nearby?
No.
What about CPK enzymes?
Elevated.
275.
People light fires
for themselves.
But then
they don't deny it.
He's here.
CPK isn't high enough.
Potassium's
what you'd expect
because of
the bronchodilators.
Oh, my God!
You're not
wearing a bra.
It's not thyroid storm.
You just met him.
I like him.
And I like sex.
Do I need to stitch a letter
on my tops?
No.
But it might be worth
taking out an ad in the local papers.
Do you like me, House?
I was on the phone
with Bennett 15 minutes ago.
His cell phone's working.
You're M.O. is to avoid me
at all costs.
And suddenly,
you need my input on every move you make.
I can only assume
it's because I'm on a date.
When we met,
I noticed--
You noticed he was a Shriner
because the way he parted his hair.
You noticed he was
a mama's boy
because of the way
he blinked his left eye.
I'm not interested.
I'm not impressed.
There are only two reasons
anyone would want
to screw with me tonight.
Either they're an altruistic,
decent person who is worried
about my well being...
Or they want me FOR THEMSELVES
You left out
the third option.
Evil bastard who just wants
to mess with other people's happiness.
Good night, House.
We won't be bothered again.
It's late.
I should go.
HMWhy?
I part my hair on hae left
and I'm a Shriner.
You heard the conversation.
I'm not interested in him.
I don't blame you.
I only said those things so that
he wouldn't come back.
I don't really
care about my job.
I do it well,
I provide a service.
But my goal was always
to make enough money
to do the things
I really like.
Music, travel...
I like those things too.
You like them, but they're not
really important to you.
I don't know
whether it's House,
your job, or if you just
thrive on conflict, but...
you should hear yourself
when you're talking to him.
Nothing else in the world
is going on.
You're focused,
confident, compelling.
Don't take this
the wrong way,
but I'd like
to go out with that woman.
I can get her
on the phone.
Where did you go?
She's getting worse.
???
Get me spinal nerve.
There are still
r tests.
She just said
the girl was getting worse.
You ???
We'll be risking infection,
maybe make
the paralysis worse.
It is worse.
We're making it worse
than worse.
Do the biopsy.
We could paralyze her
and get no useful information.
Do the biopsy.
If you're thinking
peripheral neuropathy,
we should a take a nerve
a little further away from the spine.
A little further
from the truth.
We're talking paralysis.
Good chance
the spine is relevant.
And if this thing
is progressive,
it'll kill her in hours.
Give me back my papers.
Is he asking
for a spinal nerve?
How did you know?
Give us a venute.
Did you know they recently
found a protein
that speeds up
nerve growth?
Fascinating stuff.
If you put that protein
with the insulationfrom a spinal nee,
you could grow your own
little garden.
If that spinal nerve...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If it happened to come
from a person with CIPA,
I could grow
pain-free nerves
and graft them
into my own leg.
What an evil plan.
You'd have to be
on immunosuppressors for life.
Risking infection,
shorter life span...
Shorter.
But normal.
Usually jealousy
expresses itself
by trying to destroy
what someone has.
You're more ambitious.
You actually wanna
change medical fact to get this thing...
Medical fact
changes all the time.
You're risking
your patient's life.
That's how
medical fact changes.
A doctor risks--
To serve
their patient's health.
Not their own.
This is medically justified.
Are you sure?
Are you sure...
that you're the right one
to be making this call?
Biopsy whatever nerve
you figure
you can safely get at.
GOd, Wilson's annoying.
(Cameron)
Past 3:00 AM
on Valentine's Day night.
I assume you
had a date with Wendy.
She'll survive.
She knows the deal.
You're lucky.
I know.
Someday, when thers time,
I would like
to actually have a social life.
Someday?
Come on.If there's one thing
a good-looking woman
can have when she wants,
it's a social life.
You mean a sex life.
There's nothing wrong
with a little companionship
'til the real thing
comes along.
I had the real thing.
Forgive me
if I don't want to settle.
Right.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
You think I didn't
have the real thing?
I have no idea
what you had.
And yet you're judging it.
It's late, I'm cranky.
Sorry.
You think
I didn't have the real thing.
How could you even know?
You married a dying man.
You thought...
six months, a year,
it'll be tough.
But then I'll recover
and I'll have the rest of my life.
It's like willy-nilly
getting the flu
or joining the Peace Corps.
Short term.
Wow, you nailed it.
It's basically
like a wasted weekend.
The sacrifices you made
were huge.
But they were at the height
of your love for him.
A commitment
is only commitment
because it has
no expiration date.
You stand next to someone
and watch them floss
for 30 years,
like my parents have,
then ask for sacrifices.
That's how
you know the real thing.
Cameron...
I wasn't criticizing you.
People who avoid commitment
are people who know
what a big thing it is.
This isn't right.
CIPA can't cause
this much degenetion.
(Chase)
A few nerve fibers
we teased out ofthe center
have some insulation left.
But the insulation
around the bundles
has been stripped bare.
Means the damage must be
coming from the outside in.
Which means
it's secondary demyelination.
Which means the source
is somewhere else.
Which tells us
it's not a nerve disease,
it's something systemic that's affecting the nerves.
Which means
that we need to--
Where are you going?
Kid's mom is finally
out of surgery.
I'll be right back.
So what?
Hannah should see her.
Yes, immediately after
we're done chatting
about saving her life.
Most likely
causes are metabolic.
They found brain swelling.
They're prepping her mother
for another surgery.
Again, so what?
Get a nurse
to take the kid.
There are more than 60
different metabolic conditions
that could account
for what she's got.
There's only
three of you guys.
She's scared.
She should be.
She'll die if we don't
diagnose her.
So diagnose her.
Mom.
How bad is it?
Are u OK?
I'm okay, Mom.
I'll get better.
I always get better.
Are you checking yourself?
Your temperature?
Mom, could you
just let it go?
You shouldn't be worrying.
Oh, baby, I'm sorry.
I should have
seen that car coming.
No.
I did this to myself.
I screwed up.
You were right
You were right and I was wrong.
No.
I...I shouldn't have
gone out on the ice.
I shouldn't have
fallen down.
And I shouldn't have
made you rush me
to an ER for the tenth time
this year.
Mom?
You okay?
We gonna have to take her
back to surgery.
Hannah, your BP
is way up.
We need to get you
some rest.
My hand's wet.
You're crying.
I can't cry.
My head is killing me.
So what does the pain
tell us?
No tingling, no itching,
so we can rule out--
It tells us nothing.
It wasn't physical pain,
it was emotional.
Exactly.
What were they doing
when she got the headache?
Saying good-bye.
You said
they were arguing.
They weren't really arguing.
She was just frustrated.
What were they arguing about?
Whose fault it was.
Peripheral neuropathy,
fever,
and intermittent paranoia.
Lots of metabolic conditions can explain those things.
But what if we add guilt?
Guilt as a symptom?
Alzheimer's can
cause euphoria,
pain causes depression,
and B12 deficiency
causes guilt.
Along with
all that other stuff.
If she felt guilty,
she wouldn't be making
her mother's life miserable.
She wouldn't be
getting in fights,
getting arrested...
Maybe she's fighting
because she feels guilty.
She's showing her mom
she can take stupid risks and still be safe.
Means mom can let go.
(Foreman)
Which is rational.
If guilt is a symptom,
it's caused by the illness,
not by a thought process.
And it would
have to be new.
Couple years ago,
she was a model student.
This is pointless.If the headache
was caused by guilt,
she has a B-12 deficiency.
If it's just because
she was sad,
it's meaningless. How the hell
do we test for that?
(House)
We don't.
We give her
a shot of B12.
When she gets better,
I was right.
We already did.
ER gave her B12
when she was admitted.
Part of a multi-vitamin
supplement.
Apparently,
she's just sad.
Why are you still here?
Trying to get
a couple patients into a drug trial.
Paperwork's due tomorrow.
Why are you here?
Still haven't
figured out why...
No, I meant here.
In my office.
Just dumped
a cool B12 theory.
Moved on to leukemia.
Very pedestrian.
I'm not happy.
Her white blood cell count
was low.
But the one she's got...
A whole lot of eosinophils.
The immunoglobin E level's
borderline.
If you wanna be
100% sure,
check the bone marrow.
Team's doing
a biopsy right now.
So it turns out...
the weird lawyer...
knew that she used
to be a man.
And he's cool with that?
Turns out that
his previous girlfriend
also used to be a man.
Ho-ho!
Yeah.
Is it possible
for you to just watch me eat?
Or do you get
some primeval thrill
out of beating
the other hunters to the food?
See ya later.
You still haven't figured out
that I don't need sedation?
It's so you don't move
during the procedure.
Is that nitrous?
You trying to kill her?
You gave her nitrous
during the EEG.
That's what made this thing
rear its ugly head.
What thing?
B12 deficiency.
Are you having deja vu?
We've had this conversation.
She was given B12.
She didn't get better.
Because someone else
ate it.
Get an abdominal MRI.
What?
What are you doing?
Don't touch me!
See, there she goes.
Another paranoid delusion.
Come on. At the rate
she's going downhill,
forget the MRI,
we need an O.R.
Leave me alone!
Occupied!
Her hernia can wait.
Help!
They're trying to kill me!
Okay, you can either believe
that we really are trying to kill her...
Or you can assume
that she's suffering from a medical condition.
Seeing as this is a hospitaland we're all
dressed like doctors,
and there are easier ways
to kill somebody...
Bev, help them.
Gonna need iodine,
scalpels number 10 and 15,
forceps,
and a largish salad bowl.
Okay, hold her down.
Come on, weenies,
she's in a cast.
Swab.
15.
You're not gonna
anesthetize her?
Relax, it's just
a magic trick.
She's faking it.
We're not falling for it
this time.
Okay, keep that retracted.
Forceps.
Lake fishing
can be fun.
It can bring the generations
together.
But if you don't
cook that trout or perch well,
you'll be giving
room and board to this fella.
And by free board, I mean
all the B12 you can take in.
I could have
one of ???
Not likely.
You'd be in a lot of pain.
It's gotta be
25 feet long.
Dammit.
World record's over 60.
Hannah. Wake up.
Somebody here to see you.
She's got limited motion
on her left side.
You might have to take care
of her for a while.
Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
You don't feel it,
but you're about
to rip your stitches out.
Take care of yourself.
Then you can take care
of her.
You haven't gone home.
Sorry I screwed up
Valentine's Day.
I'm dating a doctor.
I'd be an idiot
to expect anything else.
I did get you a gift.
MGH.
Best teaching hospital
in Boston.
You wanna be
a nurse practitioner,
that's as good as it gets.
I made a few calls.
You're in ???
This is why you've been
helping me get
my surgical hours
for accreditation?
I thought you wanted...
Stupid.
You've got ten feet
of personal space around you.
I step forward,
you step back.
I've shared
a lot of things with you.
Which is why
you're breaking up with me.
You can't stand
to be close.
Wendy.
You think I'll stay with you
because you're angry with me?
I'm upset.
Because I care.
Only you'd expect an argument
to be rational.
You and that
ass boss of yours.
You could ask her
for the spinal nerve.
She's got
no reason to give it.
She owes you.
The hospital
will send her a bill.
I'm just saying.
If you wanna do it, do it
while her B12 is still low.
Guilt can be your friend.
Breakfast?
Yeah.
Happy Valentine's Day.
A holiday that only
applies to people who are already paired up.
For everyone else,
it's Wednesday.
Thank you for that
dash of cold water.
Don't get me wrong,
I still think
true love's out there,
it's just very far away.
Possibly in another galaxy.
We may need to develop
faster than light travel
before we can make contact.
So I'm thinking
we should have sex.
That makes sense.
Despite the wisdom
of pop songs,
there's no point
in putting our lives on hold
'til love comes along.
We're both healthy
and busy people.
We work together,
so it's convenient.
Like microwave pizza?
And of all the people
I work with,
you're the one
I'm least likely to fall in love with.
Like microwave pizza.
The point here
is to make things simpler,
not more complicated.
Someday, there'll be time
to get serious about someone.
Meanwhile, we already
had sex once
and didn't get weird
about it.
I get it.
So what if I'm offended
by your judgment?
Then you're not the man
I'm looking for.
welcome to www.1000fr.com