So you want me to
explainhow you just lost?
Or do you wanna stare at the
board your full... three minutes?
Cling to hope?
Come on. It's called speed chess.
Na na na na
na na na na
hey hey hey
good-bye
good game.
I said good game.
Hey!Hey hey!
What are you doing?
Stop that,son!Stop that!
Back away from him. Back away!
Call 911.Get an ambulance!
Tell them to send two!
My head's gonna explode! Aah!
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=-
HOUSE
Season 03 Episode 23
Your head still hurt?
You a moron?
Nate.
I'm clutching my head in
pain, and he asks if it hurts?
What are you, some kind of med student?
You look like you still
have theme birthday parties.
Sorry.
Any problems concentrating
in school lately?
Besides the dreams of running my tongue
along my french teacher's breasts?
No,I'm doing quite great.
The rage and pain could be caused by
a parasite. Does he eat a lot of sushi?
No. Uh,he was a vegetarian
until just a few months ago.
Any changes in behavior
since the new diet?
No.
He's been this way since
he became a teenager.
It doesn't matter how much I yell
or punish, he's still gonna say-
yeah,let's all shed a tear
for poor little nate's mother.
Any more stupid questions?
nate.
I hate this kid.
I like this kid.
- You haven't met hiM.
- I know you hate him.
What more do I need to
know? The kid's not a clich?
Anybody can get into
a fight after losing.
It takes real creativity to
beat up someone you just beat.
The pain's not limited to his head.
The rest is bumps and bruises accounted for
by the 17 fights he's been in this semester.
Concussion?
Mri was clean. No frontal lobe tumor.
And the tox screen showed no
trace of coke or amphetamines.
Nate went medieval on
the other kid. Could be-
hold on. I'm having a moment.
This...
this could be foreman's last time
mistakenly suggesting adrenal gland tumor.
Which could create excess adrenaline.
Causes the head pain and rage.
But not the personality disorder.
there is no personality disorder.
He's a teenager.
Being a teenager excuses the
odd inappropriate comment.
This kid say anything appropriate?
He's having cluster headaches.
Probably been having them for years.
Question is, what's causing them?
If it were just a cluster headache,
he'd have swelling around the eyes.
Er gave him ibuprofen for
the pain. Useless r this pain.
But it could have knocked down the
swelling. Best bet is a vascular problem.
Normal treatment for cluster headaches
is steroids, which the er also gave him.
He's still in pain. Which means-
normal treatment is called normal treatment because
sometimes you have to use abnormal treatment.
Start him on blood thinners and give his
noggin transcranial magnetic stimulation.
Don't you dare...
touch that acerbic wit.
50 bucks to whichever of you
steps up and treats this brat.
Not the kid's fault, he's sick.
Fine. You do it.
No way. He's your brat.
I'll do it. But I've got
a job interview after work.
Anything comes up later,
you guys handle it.
- Need a peer recommendation?
- Thanks.
Cameron's should suffice.
This isn't gonna turn me into some,like,
drooling vegetable that wets his pants,is it?
It's safe. The magnetic pulses activate nerve
cells which will hopefully squelch the head pain.
Is there anything you can
do about the other pain?
From the fights?
Yeah,I mean,my face,
my shoulder. My stomach.
I mean,I can barely bend my fingers.
You're already on pain
meds. Nothing more I can dO.
Sure you can,man. Tell your
homies to quit stomping on me.
I'll get the word out
that you're a great guy.
So,do people watch what
they say around you?
Because I'm black?
No,because you're gay.
cluster headaches can persist for years,
cause irritabilityor even
hostility towards others.
You mean,the illnessis
affecting his personality?
If these treatments work, it could-
change him?
Yeah.
Oh,thank god.
Oh. Oh,you must thinkI'm awful.
Here my son'slying
in a hospital bed and-
I
- I'm pretty sureI get it.
I thoughtI was a bad mother.
And I hated myself.
Because I hated him.
what have you got for
me this fine morning?
Blood thinners and tmshad no
effect. It's not cluster headaches.
You accusing the symptomsof lying?
Could be hemochromatosis.
Wouldn't accountfor the
personality disorder.
What about hypothyroidism?
He's notgetting aggressive and lethargic,he's
getting aggressive and aggressiver.
What aboutruptured dermoid cyst?
Sorry. Just got dizzy there.
I was expectingto turn right.
It's foreman's turnto be shot down.
The thingthat cameron said.
Way to thinkoutside the box.
But no fat in the ventricles.
It's cluster headaches.
normal treatment didn't work.
Abnormal treatmentdidn't work.
Good point,foreman.
The treatments don't always
work. Symptoms never lie.
the only approved treatment left for
cluster headaches is brain surgery.
And that's not even a guarantee.
Back off,foreman!
If the approved treatment doesn't
work, we go withan unapproved treatment.
Hey!
Something on your mind?
Because you totallycan't tell.
I had a job interviewlined up
at new york mercy yesterday.
Hospital for manhattan'sglitterati.
Big coup. Your homies must be kvelling.
Didn't happen,because
apparently I called to cancel.
I don't remember making that call.
You think I haveneurological issue?
- Yes.
- Why are youjerking me around?
- It wasn't me.
- Yeah.
It was oneof the other petty,
socially repressed assesI work for.
Maybe it wasashton kutcher.
If you want me to stay,tell
me you want me to stay.
Would it matter? No,but it'd
bethe adult way to handle it.
If the adult way doesn't
work,why bother with it?
I've beentotally professional! Gave two
weeks notice,continued to work cases.
Scheduled my interviewson my own time.
You have no rightto
screw with my future.
You're gonna be all whiny during
the differentialdiagnoses,aren't you?
It wasn't me.
I only sabotage peopleI
consider worth it.
You are one evil,cunning woman.
It's a massive turn-on.
You girlscan gossip later.
What are you talking about?
You called new york mercy to
haveforeman's job interview killed.
When I said,"you girlscan gossip later,"
I was throwing you out,but in a polite way.
Well,I take it you're
offyour antidepressants.
Ah,you're deflecting.
Only I'm allowedto do that.
Does foremanactually think I did that?
No,just me. But I know somethinghe
doesn'T. I didn't do it.
Why would I do it?
- Do you want him to leave?
- No.
Were you planningon doing something?
I'm waitingfor board approval.
But if he takes the job, there's
nothingto be done. You had to stop him.
Wasn't me.
What are you doing?
Looking for a tell. Rapid
eye blink,twitch of the lips.
Send in nurse ungerwhen you
pass her on your way out.
Almost forgot. I need to give a 16-year-oldmagic
mushrooms to treat a cluster hdache. Is that cool?
Yeah,no problem.
I was being sarcastic.
Wouldn't look that wayin
the court transcript.
Mushrooms have psilocybinsthat
work on cluster headaches.
It's either that,or
cutting into his brain
I assume you've consideredhe could
have a psychogenic experience.
Possibly suffer a fitof severe paranoia.
Well,I have now.
Yeah,it's definitely betterthat the dean of medicine prescribes
it insteadof an unhinged doctor with a history of drug use.
Takes the stink off if the patient
decidesto put on a cape and fly off the roof.
Low dose. No more than ten
milligrams. Tightly controlled setting.
And make sure the mothersigns off on it.
Party on,garth. And don't standin
foreman's way. It's just wrong.
New research showsthat a chemical
component in the mushrooms can be-
yeah,lots of technicalmedical
stuff. So when do I get 'em?
I went to college. I
know about mushrooms.
A friend of a friendshot
himself in the foot.
They're not giving mea gun,enid!
Sign the consent form.
We'll be monitoring him, but
cardiac arrestis possible.
big E...
small N...
and if the mushroomsdon't work?
The next step would bea
type of brain surgery.
Oh,god.
Pain's gettin' worse.
Need 'shrooms now!
In-a-gadda-da-vida,honey
don't you knowthat I'm lovin' you
in-a-gadda-da-vida,baby...
oh,yeah.
Nate,how's the pain?
That I'll alwaysbe true...
hey,hey!It's skippy!
The bush kangaroo!
Your head,nate. We need
to knowhow the pain is.
What I got hereis the opposite of pain.
That means you're sufferingfrom cluster
headaches. Which means,hopefully-
Man,you're hot.
- She's making me horny.
- Deal with it.
Hey,hey,hey,hey.
You can't get me stoned,then
not close the deal.
- Shut up.
- Take it easy. He's not well.
You'll regret saying no.
Check it out.
Oh,for god's sake.
- Hold it.
- What the hell are you doing?
He has undersized testes.
His other secondary
sexualcharacteristics are normal.
If you wanna curry favorwith me, avoid
discussionsof other men's testicles.
Thanks.
Focus on phrases like... "you were
rightabout the cluster headaches. "
But wrongabout what caused them.
Vascular problemin a major artery
wouldn't cause hypogonadism.
Okay,what causes rage,headaches,personality
disorder, and hypogonadism?
Where's foreman?
He's mad at me.
- Why?
- No reason.
Yeah,that makes sense.
The male genitalsare controlled by
the hypothalamusand pituitary gland.
We're not talkingabout foreman anymore.
The kid's being pummeledat school.
A couple blows to the head
could causehypothalamic lesions.
We ever gonna talk aboutwhat
happens when foreman's gone?
If this werean employee-owned
airline in scandinavia,yes.
It's not lesions. His temperature wouldbe
all over the map. Symptoms don't lie.
He's gonein less than a week
and you haven't evenread a r?sum?
Doesn't even need to. The
two of uscan handle it.
Craniopharyngiomafits the symptoms.
Biopsy the brat's pituitary.
And let the record show I was
rightabout the cluster headaches.
Forget it.
It's a straightforwardprocedure.
and cut somethingout
of my brain? No way.
If it's a tumor,it could kill you.
Just give me more
'shrooms,okay? I'll be fine.
You only needmy consent,right?
Yeah,but it'llbe a lot easier if he-
do whateveryou have to do.
You don't touch me,all right? You
can touch me. Just not my brain.
Nate,you gotta do this.
I can't take it anymore.
My god,mom! Save me the
melodramatichand-wringing,okay?
Loosen up! Get yourself coited.
I'm gonna give hima sedative.
You're decent-looking,dr. Skippy.
Why don't you take herfor a ride?
Nate...
Are you in pain?
Nate!
His heart rate's normal.
Respiration's even.
What's happening? What's
the matter with him?
he's jaundiced. His
liver's shutting down.
we started him on sodium
polystyrene sulfonate.
His liver's operating at about
20% and deteriorating fast.
Which means he'll be dead long before
foreman turns in his parking pass.
So,what causespersonality
disorder, head pain,
blah blah blah,and liver failure?
Liver failurecan cause
hypogonadism, head pain.
Altered mental status leads to
thepersonality disorder and rage.
All we needto do is figure out
what causedthe liver failure.
Yes-also,we needto figure out how symptoms
yesterdaycan be caused by liver failure today.
If his liver's failing
now,it wasn't great yesterday.
If it wasn't operatingat
capacity, it could have caused-
ooh-aah!Whoa!
Don't sneak up on a personlike that.
I'm listening.
Well,listeningdoesn't help me.
Okay. Let's go with the
liverand a time machine theory.
Foreman,what causesliver problems?
Wilson's disease.
No. Ceruloplasmin's normal.
No enlargementand no
palpable mass, so no cancer.
Could be a narrowingof the bile
ducts. Primary sclerosingcholangitis.
Most liver damagebegins with what
we put in our bodies. Foreman?
Angry teen... alcohol.
No,blood testswere negative.
no signs of drug use or acetaminophen
poisoningin his tox screen.
Maybe the water was contaminated.
his mother would also be sick.
Cuddy?
Sounded like someonewith back. Go.
We'll tryand muddle through
without your blank stareto guide us.
So if it's not the bad thingshe's
putting in, what about the good things?
he was raised a vegetarian.
Was raised. Means he's all grown up.
Or he's nota vegetarian anymore.
He started eating red
meata few months ago.
Unless he's been buyingcuts of mad cow,
his body wouldhave no
problem metabolizing it.
It would if he hadan otc deficiency.
Body can'tmetabolize
nitrogen, damages the liver.
Run a hamburger test.
It's exactlywhat it sounds
like. Stuff him full of meat,
wait for his ammonia levelsto spike.
I'll double your salary.
Chase and cameronwould
mutiny if they found out.
Chase and cameronwouldn't be heading
up their own diagnostic group.
You'll work in parallelwith
house. It'll be your practice.
Separate staff,separate
cases. Complete autonomy.
I've only been doing
thisfor three years.
Three years under house.
No better training.
And when that case comes
alongthat I can't figure out?
You knowwho I'd have to go to.
Or you canjust let that patient
die. That's completelyup to you.
No.
Why?
He's evil.
He didn't sabotageyour interview.
How do you know?
Because I did.
I didn'T.
You believed me-meansyou're
not sure house did it.
Well,somebody did it.
Somebody here did it.
I can't work here.
This isn'ta medical procedure.
This is just about
doogiemaking me eat garbage.
Need to seehow your liver
processes the proteins.
Then get me a steak,some roast beef.
What if I brought
himsomething from home?
It has to be prepared here
so we knowthere's no chemicals
or preservatives that
couldaffect the test results.
I'm not eatinganything prepared by $5-an-hour
immigrant hospital cooks in hairnets.
Shut up!
Either you start eating,
or I'm gonnastrap you to this bed
and shove thesedown your throat
one by one-got it?
You can't get mad at me.
I'm sick.
You're supposedto feel bad for me.
- Nurse,full setof body restraints.
- yes,doctor.
Trust me.
It'll be a lot less
messyif you do it yourself.
You killedforeman's job interview.
- Why would I-
- somebody did.
Wasn't me,and it wasn't house, which means it hasto
be somebody who thoughthe was protecting house.
Which means it hasto be somebody
who actually likes house.
Which meansit's either you or the weird
night janitor who wearshis pants backwards.
I want foreman to leave.
House has to realizehe needs
someone who stands up to him.
Cameron's in love with him,chase
is afraid of him, and I enable him.
- House needs
limits. - I give him-
you authorizemagic mushrooms.
House is a six-year-oldwho thinks
he's better off without parents.
A few tummy achesafter dinners of ice
cream and ketchupmight do him some good.
You're lying.
An enablerdoesn't conspire
against, an enabler enables.
What?
You're paranoid.
You made that call.
And because of that call, you bacally
guaranteedforeman's out of here.
I thought it would be funto
work on my boat with him.
And you went shirtlessbecause
skin cancer looks cool.
Well,I realizeI got burnt.
I'm not too worriedabout that.
It's these white marks,you know?
Lie down.
I mean,that boathas
all sorts of lead paint,
and there's chemicalseverywhere.
when daddy works on his boat,
does he have a coolerwith lots
of brown bottles with long necks?
And does daddy like to lie down on
his boat and go nap-nap in the sun?
Oh!What-what the hell?
I will give you this for the...
$1.41 in your pocket.
Wait,how could you know...
a psychic once told methat I'm psychic.
Hey,one of these quartersis canadian.
Give me backmy syringe.
Hamburger stress testshowed no
change in his ammonia levels.
Liver's properly convertingthe
ammonia into urea.
He doesn't haveotc deficiency.
Welcome back.
Sorry. I shouldn't have beentaking
my problems out on the patient.
Or on me. Apology accepted.
- Starve him.
- What are we looking for?
Diabetic steatosiswould
screw up his liver.
Starve him overnightand
see if his blood sugar pops.
We mess with his blood sugar,we
could set off another rage.
Not a problem. You can take him.
I want something to eat!
- Honey,please don'T.
I was just tryingto get a
urine sample, and he went crazy.
I need to eat!
You're not stickinganything else in me.
It's justa few more hours.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
I'm gonna hurt you!
As soon aswe get a urine
sample, we can leave you alone.
You want your sample?
Here's your damn sample!
Nate,don'T.
Oh,my god.
Nate,you needto get
back into bed. Right now.
chem panel and urinalysis confirms the
bloody urine was caused by kidney failure.
He's on dialysis. He's gonna
need itfor the rest of his life.
Which is shorteningas we speak.
We are lookingat a chinese menu, and
we've got symptomsfrom too many columns.
They're goingto overcharge us.
Multiple organ failurecould
mean primary hiv infection.
That would meansomeone
agreed to sleep with him.
Plus his serologyis negative.
His uric acid'sslightly elevated.
10% of malesin this
country have elevated-
so we're onlygonna pay attention
to abnormal abnormalities?
We've been stuffing himwith meat and his
kidneys are shot. Of course his uric acid-
could be hepatic fibrosisor mcadd.
The brat'sgot a genetic disorder.
Get the sequencing primers. See if
it's oneof the ones we can treat.
I can draw some blood,but
then I gotta run.
Job interview?
You gonna stop meif it is?
You do the nurse stuff,they'll
do the doctor stuff.
This a blood testfor a marriage license?
Plan on kidnapping meto
massachusetts or canad...
what did you give him?
Are you treating himfor something?
Sedative.
Did he need a sedative?
I did. Just shutting him upso I
can draw some of his bloodin peace.
You walked in with that. You
didn't even give him a chance.
People are what they are.
He's sick.
The rudenessisn't his fault.
If he had tuberculosis, it
wouldn'tbe his fault either.
But I still wouldn't let himcough on me.
- Hi.
- Hey.
where are you going?
The lab. We're testingour
patient's blood for hereditary-
cuddy thinks I
sabotagedforeman's interview.
She's gonna fire me.
I don't believe it.
She saidit was unprofessional and-
no,I mean I literally don't believe it.
Cuddy wouldn't fire
youfor something like that.
Which means eithershe lied to you,
or you're lying to me.
You so would havefallen
for that three years ago.
You werelooking for a reaction. You
were looking for meto feel bad for you.
To save your skin. But
how am I gonna save you?
Unless...
you think I'm the onewho really did it.
Cuddy's logic wasforeman's
valuable to house.
I care about house. Ergo,I
woulddo anything to save him.
And your logic was... I care about
houseas much as you do, ergo...
it wasn't me.
I don't care about house.
I don't believe you.
No one does.
House is nothing morethan my boss.
Foreman's nothing morethan a colleague.
You're lying.
Everyone does. But it wasn't me.
No markersfor hepatic fibrosis.
And nothing for mcadd.
Foreman's interview in
new yorkgot screwed up.
I heard.
Foreman thought it was house,
house thought it was cuddy.
Cuddy thought it was
wilson,wilson thought it was me.
And you think it was me?
You thinkI sabotaged foreman?
- I don't evenwant him here.
- I know.
Then why wouldI do-
I think you sabotaged foreman
just to sabotage foreman.
So everyone's a suspect because
everyonewants to help house. Except for me.
I'm a suspectbecause I'm
a petty, vindictive jerk?
You actually thinkI would
do something like that?
- It was someone.
- It wasn't me.
Negativefor von gierke disease.
And it's tuesday.
I know.
I like you.
See you next tuesday.
Found something.
He's got a partialhprt
enzyme deficiency.
Means he could
havekelley-seegmiller syndrome.
But it'sa partial deficiency. So
it may notbe kelley-seegmiller.
Yes. Those arethe two
options. It is or it isn'T.
Kelley-seegmiller explainsthe
aggressive personality.
If he d kelley-seegmiller, he wouldn't
just be aggressive, he'd be self-mutilating.
Chewing his lips,banging his head.
Lovely disease.
Degenerative,fatal,incurable.
I wonder if that's
whycameron's on the "not" side.
That and the factthat
symptoms don't lie.
kelley-seegmiller carriers
self-mutilatewhen they're stressed.
He's in the icuwith a
failing liver and no kidneys.
Yeah,his life is sweet.
His vegetarian dietcould have
limited the purines in his system,
slowingthe disease's progress.
- So let's speed it up.
- Why?
So you two kidswill stop fighting.
Also,I don't feel likewaiting
for respiratory failurE.
Chase,find some wayfor the
mother to get lost for a while.
I'm going to stress this
kiduntil he bites off a finger.
They move me to geriatrics? Who are you?
Dr. MccaneY.
The man who's gonnakick your
ass all over this chessboard.
- Yeah,well,I'm too weak
to- - bite yourself,yeah.
You need some liquid energy.
Now,if you consent,I'm gonna
give you this shot of adrenaline.
I don't wanna play.
Aside frombeing indicative of pituitary
issuesand certain kinds of genetic disorders,
small testiclesalso indicate...
that you'ra big chicken.
Please don't make medo the sound effect.
You're not gonnagoad me into playing.
Didn't think I'd have to.
Thought you'd justjump at the
chance of humiliating someone.
Age before cripple.
I'm white.
It... is... on!
Bird's opening. Passive approach.
Sign of a coward.
Sicilian defense. Sign of an idiot.
Arrogance has to be earned.
Tell me what you've doneto earn yours.
I can walk.
I don't bleedout of my penis.
Check.
You know,it's a real thin
line between tortured genius
and awkward kid who can't
get girls because he's creepy.
Why are you doing this?
To stress you out.
Check.
Yeah,but why?
I'd tell you,but I figureit's more
stressful if you don't know why.
Yeah,well... I'm not
feeling too stressed.
You knowthat no one likes you,right?
Yeah,well,anybody like you?
You're dying.
Check.
Your move.
Care to lay down your king?
You can't win.
You can pin my queen.
My knight to e7. Your king to h8.
Sacrifice rook takes pawn.
Bishop blocks. Queen to h5. Checkmate.
Save what's leftof your dignity.
Lay down your king.
Crap.
he's having a seizure.
- Four milligramsiv lorazepam.
- Right away.
I hate this kid.
I like this kid.
Did you get the job?
They're gonna let me know.
Kelley-seegmillerdidn't
cause this seizure.
So we've gotone more
symptom, one less diagnosis.
I assume they're gonnacall for
references? Did you give 'em my name?
No.
Amyloidosis can cause seizures, and the
protein buildupcould causorgan failure.
Wouldn't alterhis personality.
Whose name did you give?
My last boss.
Ouch. That can't look good.
I hate this kid.
What if we're notdealing with one
condition? What ifit's multiple conditions?
Uh-uh,it's gotta be
one. It's always one.
Nothing explainsthis
constellation of symptoms.
We've gotta be missing something.
Maybe the kidlied about some medication.
Maybe he's hiding something.
- Why wouldhe be hiding something?
- I don't know,because he's evil?
What if he is?
What ifthe symptoms lied?
There.
Now all we're looking at is a
simple,evil jerkwith amyloidosis.
You're not being objective.
Amyloidosis was your idea.
You were right,it
doesn't fit the symptoms.
Yeah,it does.
Look.
You crossed it off because
you wannahate the kid.
And you can't hate himif he's a victim-
you want himto be a victim because
you wanna believethat people are good.
And if they're not, it's
gottabe a chemical problem.
Except they're not,and it's not.
Flush himwith immunosuppressants,
get a biopsy to confirm,
and find hima marrow donor.
what will happen to him?
substances called amyloid proteins
build upin the body's organs,
shutting them down.
It's a fairly rare disease.
And I'm afraidit can be fatal.
So do you operateor
something to take them out?
He needsa bone marrow transplant.
Dr. Cameron is searchingthe donor bank.
We should test youas well.
when you first told me he was sick...
I was... happy.
Relied.
Now...
nate,I'm gonna takea small
piece of nerve from your ankle.
Let me knowif you feel any pain.
I'm burning up.
Couldn't you justknock me
out like you did last time?
Wish I could. But your
bodyhas to be clear
so it's readyfor a marrow transplant.
hey,dr. X...
I know you've busted
asstrying to save me.
It's all right.
I wasn't gonna thank you.
I was gonna tell youyou
really suck at this.
We're doing our best.
That's sort of my point.
Your best really sucks.
Nerve biopsy was clean.
No evidence of amyloidosis.
It was your idea. Don't
give up on itso fast.
He's running a fever. If it's two conditions,
one of them'sgotta be an infection.
We should start himon antibiotics,
see what clears up,what doesn'T.
Is he having troublebreathing?
Yeah,he has mucusin his
chest from an infection.
Could alsobe an amyloid buildup.
Keep him on immunosuppressantsand
biopsy somewhere else, his sinuses.
Look,you got two choices.
Engage me in a futile argumentthen do
what I asked, or just do what I asked.
You're not ready.
There was a third choice.
Don't do what I asked.
You could have defied me,stuck the
kid on antibiotics. But you didn'T.
Because you stilltrust my
judgment more than your own.
You sabotagedforeman's
job interview, didn't you?
Foreman's alreadybeen
over this. It wasn't me.
Everybody's chasing ghostsover this.
Which meanseither nobody did it, or
somebody wants everybodychasing ghosts.
Now,who does that sound like?
And why would I do that?
Because as long as
foremanthought you were guilty,
he was gonnabe useless around here.
You know,sometimes I
forgetwhy I hired you.
You cost hima good
opportunity and gained nothing.
I cost hima crappy opportunity.
New york mercy'swhere you go to
treat boils and cystsand build a 401k.
If you want him to stay,tell him.
I don'T.And there'd be no point.
You do.
And the point wouldbe to make
him feel like he's wanted.
He doesn't need that.
All right,then. It'd make him
feellike maybe you weren't evil.
He needs that.
Talk to foreman.
We dumped one symptom.
But forgot to add one.
Revenge time,nate.
- Are you...
- yes! I am.
Black or white?
Just limp away.
He doesn't wanna play. Leave him alone.
Pick one,or this comes out.
And for all you know,this
is really important.
Ow!Stop it!
That hurts,right?
Which is odd, because
I'm reallyenjoying this.
You hold the piecesthat way
because you can'tbend your thumb.
Because your boneshave
formed abnormally.
Thanks to all the crap that's been
pushing its wayin between them.
Actually,this stuffisn't
important at all.
Your doctors saidhe
needs immunosuppressants.
They're idiots. It's not amyloidosis.
It's iron. He's got hemochromatosis.
The body absorbs iron from food, but
can't process it. Can't get rid of it.
And idle iron is the devil's playground.
It builds up in the organs and joints,
whacking them in the process.
Caused all of the symptoms.
Including somethingthat
wasn't a symptom.
Those body aches,they
were notfrom the fighting.
His personality issues?
Sorry.
The iron's innocenton that count.
Your kid's a jerk. And
yeah,it's probably your fault.
Although,if you'd stayed off
the meat like your mom said,
you'd havehalf as much iron,
and be twice lessalmost dead.
Oh,nurse!
This patient is bleedingfor some reason.
Is he going to be okay?
He'll need dialysis.
And he'll haveto get his blood drained
every few monthsfor the rest of his life.
But my condolences. It's going
to be a longand annoying life.
And I wouldn'thave taken your bishop.
I'd have moved my queen
to d6,defusing the threat.
Then rook to e8,attacking
the king's pawn.
I'd have lost the
exchange,but won the game.
I know.
I was bluffing.
And that's why...
You lost.
Little jerk.
You just here to watch,or
you got something to say?
Still runningthe new
biopsy for amyloidosis?
Yeah,but still nothing.
Run the test again.
Recheck your results.
Looks like you're infor an all-nighter.
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-
HOUSE
Season 03 Episode 23