What are you doing down here?
I thought you usually
had lunch with coma guy.
This is vegetative state guy.
Better company.
Hey, tell him about those sherpas
you dropped acid within st.Patrick's cathedral.
You stole my prescription pad,
and you forged my name.
- What did you tell the cop?
- I lied.
They'd have put you away for ten years.
After they took your license
to practice medicine.
- So everything's good, then.
- I lied to the cops.
There is no case unless they can prove that either
I gotthe drugs illegally or I sold them illegally.
I didn't do the second.
You lied about the first. Game over.
Yeah.
Tritter's just playing.
He's gonna seehow clever you are
and then just walk away.
The important thing is that you keep
prescribing the same amount of drugs to me,
or it'll look suspicious.
Here's another way to look at it.
Having forced me to lie to the police,
your first concern is securing your drug connection.
Joining my father for lunch?
I should've called ahead for a table.
- Dr. House was just--
- enjoying a reuben.
It's okay.
After ten years, anything that'll
get doctorsin the same room as--
- what are you doing?
- Nothing.
What are you doing?
Chips?
Wanna see something really cool?
I saw you leaving last tuesday.
Practically tripped over two guys on your way out,
but you had no problem opening doors.
It's called akinetopsia.
You can't see things when they move.
And since you haven't been hit by a bus,
I assume that it's intermittent.
It's probably accompaniedby seizures,which made me
think that I could set one off by flashing them
god, I love this family!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-colleen3684
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
House
Season 3 Episode 07
I can see fine now.
I've had seizures before.
Most of the time, they're small.
Doctors ran me through all the tests.
Couldn't find anything.
Any history of epilepsy in your family?
The only things I know that
run in my family are a lot of chutzpah
and the ability to sleep for ten years.
Although i'm not really an expert.
Dad never really liked my mother's side of the family,
and after she died and he came here,
I was raised by a guardian.
I wouldn't even know
how to get in touch with him.
How 'bout your father's side of the family?
Any relatives we could speak with?
My father was an only child.
And my grandparents are dead.
Well, who did you put down as the person
the hospital should contact in an emergency?
- I left it blank.
- there's gotta be someone.A friend?
Oh, plenty of friends.
Just...
no one that would care if I was here.
Say, do you mind passing me my backpack?
Hair of the dog.
- could be infection.
- or a brain tumor.
Says he had a ct.
What's wrong with the
simplest explanation?Trauma.
He didn't report any injuries.
He didn't report
being an alcoholic, either.
Drinking equals falling down,
equals trauma, equals
maybe it's inherited.
How would you jump to
genetics from his eeg?
All you've got are some
vaguely epileptiform waves.
It's not his eeg.
It's his father'S.
When it comes to cortical seizures,
like father, like son.
Small seizures aren't unheard of
in a patient in a vegetative state.
Similarities are interesting, though.
What caused the vegetative state?
His house burned down.
Went back into get his wife.
Firefighters found him unconscious
three feet from the bedroom, asphyxiated.
Not an inherited condition.
Test his dna.
Start with a drenomyeloneuropathy.
Check out the home.
- He has a single bed.
- They still make single beds?
Could mean he just doesn't have sex--
though there were condoms in the apartment.
House asked you to check out the home for toxins.
No mold, no leaks, no pets.
mri and lp are both inconclusive.
Infection's still possible.
- Tumor's less likely, but--
- dna?
Adrenomyeloneuropathy test was negative.
Dna test again.Try unverricht-lundborg
and late-onset lafora'S.
genetic tests take forever.
You can't just keep testing for every
inherited condition you think it might be.
Well, not me.I'll be leaving early.
But you guys can.
You said no one's been sick,
but what about delivery people,repair guy?
I wouldn't know.
I work from home.
Haven't been to the office
in over a month.
- visitors?
- Haven't had any.
The only person I've seen in the last week
was the pizza delivery guy.
And he looked pretty healthy.
There's gotta be someone you're close to.
Actually, the person I see most oftenis my father.
He's asleep,so he can't stop me.
- What is it?
- Just feeling a little nauseous.
- I--I think his liver's failing.
- Oh, god.
Does--does that mean that I'm--
I need a central line kit.
Two units of packed red blood cells,type o negative.
He's unconscious and heading for a coma.
He's at a four on the rlas scale.
Stop all treatment.
You think this is a reaction to our meds?
Well, they're obviously not helping.
Given the fact that he's an alcoholic,there's a good chance
his liver wasn't so hot when he came in.
Anti-seizure drugs could have
just pushed him over the edge.
We take him off those meds,
what do we put him on?
I was hoping you'd know.
May be academic,
but I just started him on dialysis.
Kidney and liver failure.
Not too many people
come back from that.
trauma's out of the picture.
It could still be infection.
- Or neurological.
- Or genetic.
We needa better history.
did you miss the part
where the patient lost consciousness?
L-dopa?
You're not waking kyle.
You're waking his father.
I commend your observational skills.
You have no reason to think any amount
of drugs will wake a man from a coma.
Vegetative state.
Much easier.
This guy's no terry schiavo.
His brain's all there.He moves around.
His muscles have barely atrophied.
Just waitingfor a fairytale kiss.
After I do that,
stick a needle in him.
The amount of amphetamines alone
would be dangerous,
besides whatever the hell else
you've got in there.
There are reports out of south africa
about a pill that would temporarily revive
someone in a vegetative state.
We've all seen awakenings.
Made me cry.
I wanna cry.
put the syringe down.
I can out-draw you, mysterious stranger.
We don't experiment on helpless patients.
Be reasonable.
There's no way this is gonna work.
Even if you woke him,
it would only be for a few hours.
A day, two at the most.
You're risking his life.
I'm risking getting sued.
That's the only objection here.
You'll be torturing him.
And his family.
Good news for legal.
The only family he's gotis upstairs dying.
Hey!
I want this patient monitored
for the next 24 hours.
I want someonewith him at all times
to make sure you didn't kill him.
I want your ass in my office--
god.I'm starving.
I could really go for a steak.
do you know your name?
You know where you are?
Gabriel wozniak.
I don't know the name of this hospital.
- How much are three and five?
- Eight.
Also known as 1/2 of 16,1/4 of 32,
two to the third power.
Coolest thing ever.
- Any history of seizurein your family?
- No.
- Liver disease?
How long have I been here?
I--I got the feeling it's,
um,been a long time.
interesting.If your internal clock
kept ticking,how deep does that awareness go?
Pick up scraps of conversations?
You have the vague sense that the hospital
administrator dresses like a trollop?
Or that the new star wars movies
were a disappointment?
I know my wife is dead.
I don't know how longit's been.
Ten years.
What's the last thingyou remember?
The fire.
My wife was in the bedroom.
She had takena sleeping pill.I got...
kyle out.
Went back in for her.
- I knew I didn't make it.
- I'm sorry.
What about your wife's side of the family?
Any history of seizures there?
Your son kyleis a patient here.
I'm afraid his conditionis serious.
He may be dying.
No seizure issues on my wife's side, either.
What about that steak?
Nobody ever answered me.
Rumor in the cafeteria was
caustic guy was waking up coma guy.
Technically,vegetative state guy
was woken by...
- yeah, caustic guy.
- So what happened?
Gotta get him a steak before I can
ask himany more questions.
He doesn't want to talkabout his son?
Didn't seem to emotionally register
that his son is sick.
Brain issue? He was asphyxiated,
spent ten years as asparagus.
- Who knows what damageis in there?
- It's possible.
'Course, there's alwaysthe simple explanation.
Maybe he just doesn't like his son.
Only in your world would that be simple.
The delusion that fathering a child
installs a permanent geyser of unconditional love--
maybe your father's feelings
were conditional.Not everyone's--
yes, well, of course,that would play
into yourromantic vision of human--
in terms you would understand,we have an
evolutionary incentiveto sacrifice for our offspring.
Our tribe,our friends.
Keep them safe.
Except for all the people who don'T.
Everything is conditional.
You just can't always anticipate the conditions.
Mind if we talk for a few minutes?
How many pills would you say
dr. House takes a day?
I'm uncomfortable setting a number.
Mm, try.
Six.
A day.
Has he ever had you...
write prescriptions for him?
No.What is ityou want me to say?
That he takes too many pills
and is a danger to the hospital?
Or he takes too few
because he's selling them on the side?
Either one is ridiculous.
- I meant the former.
- You're wrong.
Can I ask whatdr. House has done
to deserve your loyalty?
He's not knownas a great boss.
He's not even much of a friend.
I mean, look how he left
dr. Wilson holding the bag.
It's odd.
You don't know about that.
You defend him, and he won't even
tell you what's happening in his life.
- I was paged.
- Saw you with a cop.
What'd he want?
How many pills does house take,did I
ever write him a prescription,that sort of stuff.
- I told him six.
- A day,or in a mouthful?
I was just hoping you guys
would stay consistent with--
- he wants to talkto us, too?
- You're next.
We've gotta tell house what's going on.
- Tritter says no.
- Then no it is.
Cops have a thousand ways
to make life difficult for you.
Quick, what's the kid's status?
I gotta get back to our sleeper
before he goes looking for the orgasmatron.
See, if that were rhetorical,
it would mean that I could just turn around
and leave now.Which I'm not doing.
From which you should deduce--
he's off all drugs except the antibiotics.
His liver's just managing to hang in there.
He's still sliding into coma.
Your barber sucks.
Hey.
Coma diet.
I could makea fortune.
Vegetative state diet.
- Who gave you your clothes?
- Dr. Cuddy.
I guess I'll needall new ones anyway.
Everything went in the fire.
Ah, don't worry about it.
We use recyclable clothes now.
Wear them once, then eat them.
Your son's measles vaccination.
Do you remember if he had it
and what type it was?
Man, you're a piece of work,you know that?
You weren't gonna tell me,were you?
I don't need new clothes.
Dr. Cuddy says my body will adjust to the drugs.
That I'll be a vegetable againby tomorrow.
If I'm really lucky,the day after.
Yeah.
If I got a day to live,I'm not gonna spend it
in a hospital roombeing grilled.
come on, where you gonna go?
Your house burned down.Your wife's dead.
Business was sold off.
The only thing you have left
is down the hall heading for a liver biopsy.
Used to be this little,
um,hole in the wall.
Run by a guy named gian carlo.
Made the best hoagies in the world.
Real italian rolls.
Prosciutto. Provolone.
How far is atlantic city from here?
You have one day to live.
And you want a sandwich.
- People on death row get a last meal.
- State provides it.
Who's providing for you?
You got a car? Money?
You're negotiating with me.
Take out another hundred for me.
And I need your car.
I'm not doing you any favors.
You'll get it back tomorrow.
Two days, max.
Road trip.
This is like trying to control the weather,
but I'd prefer it if you didn't eat in the car.
- I just had it detailed.
- I drive.
- Oh, the hell he does.
- Sure.
Aside from the fact he just woke upfrom a
vegetative state,the guy doesn't have a licensE.
How 'bout this?
Cops stop us, we lie.
You know how to do that.
Chips.
It's all the drugs
pumping through his system.
Right now, his reflexes
are better than dale earn hardt jr.'S.
Hey, what's this?
It says, "ipp-odd."
I'm coming.
so let's talk about toxic exposure.
what was wrong with the old colors?
I trusted brown.
Do the purple ones
have chocolate inside?
Raspberry cocaine.
This house that burned down.
Where was it?
Moorestown, new jersey.
Listen, I really need to know about the candy
because I'm allergicto berries.
- You didn't mention that.
- Is it significant?
No.
So where else did you live?
List everywhere,including vacations.
Start with when your wife got pregnant.
We lived in jersey.
Then we moved to jersey.From there, jersey.
What are you waiting to hear?
About the little cottage in the amazon
with the mosquitoes and the lead paint all over the walls?
Yes.
You know what?
I didn't let you come along so you could
suck all the fun out of my one day of life.
Well, you're outta luck,
'cause that's totally why I'm here.
Okay.
Rule change.
Person with the money makes the rules.
Or in this case,the person who's friends
with the person with the money makes the rules.
Well, you want answers
more than I want money.
All right, so here's the game.
Ask whatever you want.
But for every question I answer,
you have to answer one first.
And why would you care about
anything I have to say?
The day before I died,
I was a successful man.
I had a factory with over 200 employees.
People listened when I talked.
I liked power.
Now the only power I have left
is the power to annoy you.
Took wilson's assistant for coffee.
- Why?
- Something tritter said.
She told me the police think that house stole
wilson's prescription pad and forged his name.
You...believe it?
- Do you?
- Oh, absolutely.I do.
I'm just checking
how naive you are.
He's not gonna steal his best friend's pad,j
eopardize his career.
Until his best friend says no to him.
house is a junkie.
Junkies do whatever they
have to do to get what they need.
Kyle's down to a three on the rlas scale.
He's only showing localized response.
I'll call house.
Tell him we're gonna need an answer soon.
Get in your right lane for 295.
And pass me the twizzlers.
- I'm curious.
- No, you're not.
Why would a man's first instinct be
to drive away from the only family he's got?
No!This is no time for you to do your thing.
We don't care about his state of mind.
We don't care if he's happy.
This factory of yours.
What did you make?
- So ask me a question.
- I'm thinking.
Only six left, by the way.
So sign my name.
You don't need a doctor.You need a pen.
What is upwith you two?
Wilson lied to the bulls
to keep me out of the big house.
- Are you out of your mind?
- Well, who's he gonna tell?
By tomorrow night,he's gonna
bea mindless stalk of celery.
Since I answered that one,
by the way,my turn.
- What did you make in your factory?
- Luxury boats.
- Have you ever been in love?
- Wow.
Going right for the closets
with the embarrassing stuff.
Good move.Yes.
Describe the boats.
35- to 65-foot hulls.Twin engines,parquet floors
in the galleys,staterooms with queen beds.
- How'd you meet?
- She shot me.
These boats.I assume you used
mildew-resistant painton the hulls?
Naturally.
Shot you?
Paintball.
Doctors versus lawyers.
- You ever take your son to the factory?
- Sure.
He used to run all over the place,
but it was perfectly safe.
Ever love anybody else?
No more questions.
I got my answer.
While dad's in the office,
son's watching them spray-paint.
And what kid wears a mask?
Mercury specifically targets
the central nervous system.
Are you sayingthis was my fault?
Mercury poisoning explains the seizures.
The liver is likea big soup strainer.
Soup runs through.
Chicken dumplings stay.
For soup, read blood.
For chicken dumplings--
I get it, I get it.
Mercury.
Sits more or less idle until your kid
pours tequila shooters into his liver.
When the liver goes,takes out the kidneys.
Explains everything.
Yeah, it's me.Foreman, draw blood.
Test for mercury poisoning.
Chase.Start heavy metal chelation
while we're waiting for results.
Chase isn't here.
I'll start the--
where is he?
The lab.
- How many pills does he take a day?
- It's hard to say.
Pain levels vary over time.
Could be six, eight, ten.
Ever write any prescriptions for him?
- Yes.
- Why? Did he tell you to?
He asked me to.
Medicine...attracts people
who are attracted to power.
I know how he hates when he is defied by a patient.
I doubt he handles defiance
from his staff any better.
Now, you correct meif I'm wrong.
But I don't think dr. House asks for anything.
I think he takes it.
And I think that you are stuck lying
to the police to cover up something...
you didn't want to do.
we have been up and down st.James
like a monopoly car.
It's not here.
Giancarlo has left the building.
We could still turn around
and go back to princeton.
No!We've come this far.
I'm getting the hoagie.
If your son does have mercury poisoning,
there's a good chance he'll respond to the chelation.
You might be able to have
a few minutes with him before you lapse.
Why are you so concerned about me?
Deep inside, wilson believes that
if he cares enough,he'll never have to die.
- Your behavior isn't normal.
- And you would know normal.
What could he have done that you won't forgive
after ten years,when this is your last chance?
My son is what he is.
His mother's side?
All drunken losers.
He's gone the same way.
House told you that drinking
had damaged your son's liver.
I just said that.
But you didn't hear him say that
till after we left the hospital.
So why did you leave?
maybe your son takes after your side.
- Seizures and an allergy to emotional connections.
- Okay, okay, okay.Enough.
We're in atlantic city,
and my time's not up yet.
We'll find a hotel with a casino.
Bp's starting to drop.
O2-sat's down to 70.
0.3 milligrams of epi in.
What are you trying to do?
Make him bleed faster?
Check the pulse.
It's not his liver.
It's the heart.
I understand he's a french chef,
but I'm sure he can handle this.
We need a 12-inch italian roll,
oregano vinegar--
no.Not balsamic vinegar.
Oregano vinegar.
Quid pro quo, clarice.
Game's still on.
I thought the answer was mercury poisoning.
What other questions would you care about?
If you each had one day to live,
you'd lookfor one last meal,
and house would lookfor
one last answer.
No, can you just send
the ingredients up here?
And I'll make it myself.
Last ten years.
How much awareness did you have?
I don't know.
I knew it wasn'tthe next day.
I--I knew that--
I recognized your voice.
How often were you in my room?
No.You're wasting a question.
I have a better one.
- Why steal my pad?
- oh, my god.You're right.
I'm an addict.
Thanks for opening my eyes.
No, I mean, why my pad?
Foreman, cameron, and chase's pads
are just as convenient.
But their association with you
is involuntary.They're employees.
I associate with you through choice.
And any relationship that involves choice
you have to seehow far you can push before it breaks.
This is easy.
You ask the questions,answer them,
and make tasty snacks.
Let's go try the casino.
And one day,our friendship will break.
And that'll just prove your theory
that relationships are conditional,
and you don't need
human connection,or deserve it,
or whatever goes on in that
rat maze of your brain.
Sorry.If I'd known
he was gonna be this annoying,
I would've stolen dr. Cameron's pad
and dr. Foreman's car.
At least she appreciates my brooding melancholy.
House's house of whining.
State your complaint.
- Patient's bp just dropped like a stone.
- Do an echo.
- Mercury isn't likely to damage--
- it didn'T.
Mercury test was negative.
Do an echo.
I was wrong.
Your son's still dying.
I need to go over every relative
you ever had again.
This time, forget their diseases.
Just tell me how they died.
We don't have time to take turns.
Gimme the answers.
You get a big one at the end.
You go for whatever you want.
Destroy my privacy,my dignity.
- your grandmother?
- Heat exhaustioN. Fourth of july picnic.
The woman was 92.
Does anyone in the kitchen know the hoagie shop
that used to be on st.James place?
Your sister-in-lawwith the diabetes.
- As far as you know,is she still alive?
- She's not.
Killed in a traffic accident
driving homefrom a phillies game.
I'm sure a lot of beer was consumed.
Phillies lost.
- Your father?
- Old age.Heart finally gave out.
- Your wife's father?
- Hit-and-run.
Walking the incontinent dog.
Uh, hi.
Do you guys deliver?
Let me put it this way.If you deliver,
there'll be a $100 tip in it for you.
Excellent!
Victory.
Ha, ha, the night isfinally going my way.
Wilson, toss me a soda.
Shall we go somewhereto talk?
House is an ass.
But he obviously needs pain medication.
How much pain one person feels
is not a call the government should be making.
So you think I'm a bureaucrat with a badge
following some arbitrary guideline.
- Yeah.I do.
- Oh.
So you're saying I should...
just trust him.Do you?
- You're not qualified to make that--
- I'm not sure you are,either.
I've been a cop for 20 years,and not a day
goes by that someone doesn't try to
sell me someself-serving story.
If you had my job,you'd know.
Everybody lies.
Think you've run out of relatives.
So.
It's my turn.
Why did you become a doctor?
That's the big question?
I gave you complete license to humiliate me,
and that's the best you can do?
Well, okay.Let's discuss
the wonder of the human body.
No, no, no.
You're a curious guy.
You like to figure things out.
Why not go into research?
Why work with people when you...
obviously hate people?
Oedipal fixation.
I was seeking my mother's love,and she thought
that ben casey was just the dreamiest--
okay, fine.You don't think you'll need
any more answers from me?
Give me a hard time.
When I was 14,my father was stationed in japan.
I went rock climbing with this kid from school.
He fell, he got injured,
and I had to bring him to the hospital.
We came in through the wrong entrance
and passed this guy in the hall.
It was a janitor.
My friend came down with an infection
and the doctors didn't know what to do.
So they brought in...
the janitor.
He was a doctor.
And a buraku.
One of japan's untouchables.
His ancestors had been
slaughterers,gravediggers.
And this guy,he knew that
he wasn't accepted by the staff.
Didn't even try.
He didn't dress well.
He didn't pretend to be one of them.
The people that ran that place,
they didn't think that he had anything they wanted.
Except when they needed him.
Because he was right.
Which meant that nothing else mattered.
And they had to listen to him.
Thank you.
Need 20 milligram sof diazepam in a syringe.
Heart beat's irregularand accelerating.
- It's at 200.
- He's gonna crash.
- Allergic reactionto the diazepam?
- Better hope so.
It's either that,or his heart's done.
What happened on the night of the fire?
Yeah, I'm sure it's a
stressful emotional question.
Suck it up.
My wife had takena sleeping pill
and gone to bed.It was christmas eve.
I let kyle pop corn in the fireplace.
He managed to...
knock loose some tinder.
Wrapping paper caught on fire.
Spread.So fast.
I got kyle out.
And when I went back in for--
you're a disappointment.
You act as though
you don't need anybody.
You--you just blame your son
for what happened.
I don't blame him.
He was a 12-year-old boy.
You don't blame a kid for an accident.
Then what are we doing here?
Why aren't you with him?
Because it wouldn't matter!
I failed to keep my family safe!
I couldn't stop the fire.
I couldn't save my wife!
Now you want meto stick around watching
while I fail to save my son.
Thank you so much for waking me up.
How did your son dislodge the tinder?
He dropped the popcorn tray.
He had been complaining it was too heavy.
I should've listened.
And the hit-and-run.
Walking the pissy dog.
- That happen at night?
- I think so, yeah.Why?
Car accident after the phillies lost.
Night game?
Ragged red fiber.
It's an inherited condition.
Dropping things, muscle weakness.
Poor night vision.
Makes people seem uncoordinated,
accident-prone,careless.
It's transmittedin mitochondrial dna.
So it only passes through the mother.
Your wife's family weren't drunks.
They were sick.
- It wouldn't have affected his liver.
- The kid is a drunk.
He thinks that he killed his mother
and turned his father into a vegetable.
You know, I might have a few shots myself.
- Foreman.
- Test his dna for ragged rediber.
- It's not gonna--
- here's a thought.
Why don't we not assume that the test
is negative until we actually do it?
House.
The kid has severe cardiomyopathy.
Alcoholic.
No shot at a transplant.
So yeah, maybe you figured out why.
Good for you, but...
he's gonna die anyway.
I want to give kyle my heart.
This thing--whatever it is--
you said he gets it from the mother.My heart's fine.
And it could go on being fine
for the rest of your life.
yeah.It's not like
he's gonna do anything with it.
Well, you woke him up once.
Maybe someone will come up
with some other answer.
We've both seen breakthroughs
no one expected.
And ragged red fiber's treatable,
but not curable.
Even if he gets your heart,
there's no guarantee.
He's my kid.
No.Did you really expect
a different answer?
We have arranged transplants before
when a patient is near death.
Except he isn't near death.
He's saying,"kill me
and cut out my heart."
Are you out of your mind?
Fine.
I'll think of something else.
I'm sorry.
Wilson.
Get out.
No.
You've lied to the cops enough for me.
Maybe I don't wanna
push this till it breaks.
Pills are the simplest.
Hanging has less chance of damaging the heart.
I'm okay with pain.
Strangulation is better than breaking your neck.
Which means this'll be slow.
I wouldn't get to see him
even if we got in the car right now
and broke the speed limit driving back,would I?
No.
Tell him-
I don't knowwhat to tell him.
Think it's my turn to ask a question, isn't it?
I don't think so.
'Cause you just asked me that thing
about the speed limit.
What do you wanna know?
If if you could hear one thing
from your father,what would it be?
- It wouldn't help you.
- Try me.
I'd want him to say...
"You were right.
You did the right thing."
Yeah.
It doesn't help.
- Hi.
- I'm dr. Wilson.
- I'm mrs. Schaeffer.
I'm from princeton.
My husband and i and our
three children live in philadelphia.
So, uh...
do you like to swing?
No.
Well, if you change your mind,I'm in--
house.House!
Is it room 622? 642?
- 622.
Yeah.
- Alibi.
- I figured.
They found an open bottle
of aspirin by the body.
Lucky he had a headache.
Reduced trauma to the heart in transit.
Lucky.
That can't be all.
Well, you got a heart out of it.
How many organs do you want from the guy?
I mean,my father must have said something.
He couldn't just--he must have given you
some kind of a message for me.
He said you were right.
You did the right thing.
Right about what?
What does that mean?
How would I know?
He's your dad.
You know what I found
interesting about this case?
That it proved that people can love unconditionally,
and you can tell yourselfit's not true,
but you'll just end up in a hotel room
in atlantic city asking someone to cut your heart out?
The hoagie.
You thought this guy was emotionally
confused and that the hoagiewas just a mask
to hide his real feelingstowards his son.
It was.
Did you know tritter was talking
to your team while we were away?
Yeah.
And yet you moved heaven and earth
to get him that mask with mustard and prosciutto.
- Which one of them told you?
- All of them.
Which means that none of them
said anythingI have to worry about.
Back to the hoagie.
You think that my addiction's out of hand.
Your need to be needed is so strong
that you'll give people what they want,
what they need,what they think they need.
I don't think my enablingis anything
you should be complaining about.
Yes, my nameis dr. James wilson.
Accot number 835687.
The atm says I've got zero--
what does that mean--a hold?
Yeah, okay.
Thanks.
My accounts have been frozen
as part of a police investigation.
They can't keep your money forever.
No, they can keep it till I agree
to help send you to prison for ten yearS.
You're getting dinner.