Coming up to 50 feet.
Roger that.
We're light on fuel.
Two minutes to bingo.
Come on, Fisher.
We got places to go, people to see.
- Workin' on it!
- So I?e heard.
What's taking so long?
Let go of the suitcase!
- You're gonna have to hold onto me!
- Es de mi esposa, no puedo!
Sir, whatever it is, it's not worth it!
We're at bingo fuel, sir.
You hear that, Fisher? Bingo.
Either reel him in or
we're leaving you both here.
Roger that, sir.
- Ditch the damn luggage!
- Yo lo puedo aguantar, esta bien.
Marina.
Mi amor.
?estas bien?
Mi esposa esta enferma. Sus
expedientes medicos estaban enla maleta.
Tell him if he's so worried
about his wife's clothes,
he should have stayed in Cuba!
Oye, tenemos que regresar. Dr. House
necesita ver sus expedientes medicos.
He says it wasn't her clothes.
It was her medical records.
Says she's sick and needs to go home.
No home. House.
I need to see Dr. House.
Transcript: swsub.com
Sync: jh26
You don't answer your phone anymore.
I'm world-famous now.
Press won't leave me alone.
- It's Cuddy.
- I know.
If it was the press, i'd be answering.
And since you're not
taking her calls, I am.
Your patient's been waiting for hours.
- She didn't book an appointment.
- No, she risked her life.
You don't reach terra firma,
you don't get any milk or honey.
The woman has ten different
things wrong with her,
including pains all over her body.
Admittedly, not as interesting
as staring uselessly at Foreman.
You know, I find the
good-bye party fascinating.
Isn't it kind of insulting if
you celebrate when someone leaves you?
- What are you gonna do to keep him?
- Nothing.
He really is gonna leave.
You know that, right?
- Yeah.
- So what are you gonna do?
There isn't anything I can do.
He doesn't want more money,
better working conditions.
He doesn't even want a better job.
He wants to not be me.
Because he thinks you're a cold-hearted
bastard without any regard for anyone
but yourself.
- He's right.
You need to show him
that you really do care.
Don't.
Foreman's not the only
chocolate-covered cherry in the box.
House, you play a guitar
you got in ninth grade.
Eighth.
You're living in the same apartment for
15 years. You drive a 10-year-old car.
You are not good with change.
That used to be true, but I changed.
He's not afraid to be you.
He's afraid to be who he thinks you are.
Rheumatic fever would
explain the skin rash.
What about the double
vision or bloody urine?
They were lost at sea for three days.
Severe dehydration
causes kidney problems.
- And the double vision?
- Concussion during the shipwreck.
It all fits as long as each symptom
started when you think it started.
This would be a lot easier
if we had her medical records.
Any of you certified deep-sea divers?
She's from a dirt poor
country in the tropics.
Infectious disease and parasites
are the most likely cause
of unexplained pain,
fever, and skin rash.
We might as well start there.
If there's one thing Castro knows,
it's how to look great in green.
And if there are
two things castro knows,
it's how to look great
in green and train doctors.
Even without the medical records, we can
assume she was drowned in antibiotics
before she risked drowning to see me.
So what doesn't Castro know?
How to lay his hands on
high-tech scanning equipment.
The pain, double vision
point us towards the head.
Cameron, get an MRI.
See what's cookin' in the old cabeza.
- Chase, check out the husband.
- Why? He hasn't complained of any pain.
Basic math... Take all her symptoms,
subtract his sea symptoms.
The remainder equals
her original symptoms.
Are you in any pain?
No. I'm just sunburned.
Any blurred vision?
No.
So my wife...
She is with Dr. House?
She's with another doctor
who is part of Dr. House's team.
No, she's supposed to see Dr. House.
We have permission.
This is the way it works with Dr. House.
- I came a thousand miles to see him.
- He doesn't care.
I'm sorry, but that's who he is.
That's who you risked your life to see.
And you made the right choice.
Any other metal?
Must have been difficult on the boat.
When the storm came, yes, very much.
I pray while my husband, he, um...
?como se dice?
Uh, with the paddles?
- You were on a boat without a motor?
- No, no.
We start with the motor.
But it break on the first night.
My husband, he can fix anything.
A washing machine, a car.
A computer.
But that stupid motor...
And me.
These two he cannot fix.
He got you to us.
He never gave up.
No matter what happen,
he kept saying to me,
"don't worry.
"we will make it.
I'll take care of you."
That's Esteban.
He refuses to worry or pray.
He believe if you don't have one,
you don't need the other.
Husband has a pulled
muscle in his shoulder,
but no other pains or double vision.
Does have a fever, fungal rash,
a cough, and elevated bilirubin.
Foreman's not going anywhere.
He said that to you?
He doesn't really want to leave.
And you don't really want to let him.
You'll cave,
just like you did with Cameron.
Foreman's not as easy as Cameron.
But, of course, who is?
I'm in the room.
He may not want a date,
but he does want something.
Maybe it's something I can't offer.
- Then you'll just lie.
- He'd see through it.
Maybe. Or maybe he'll
just see what he wants to see.
She has MS. Explains the pain,
fatigue, double vision, kidney problems.
The kidney problems aren't connected.
Her husband has the same issues.
It is possible for 2 people to have the
same symptom for 2 different reasons.
If we're gonna take that approach,
then we might just throw out
everything we got from
the husband and start over.
We could do that,
or we could do something productive.
Start her on interferon for the MS,
see if she improves.
I do like being productive.
Well done. Do it.
Well done? Is that what you
think he wants, a pat on the head?
Go do your job.
She does not have MS.
I know it's not a pleasant
diagnosis to hear, but...
No, the doctors in
Cuba would have found MS.
What's that?
It's all right. Pulse-ox just came off.
- Marina, you can't...
- It hurts.
The pain is getting worse.
Your treatment isn't
working because it's not MS!
Does this hurt?
Either Foreman's way stronger
than he thinks he is, or...
Seriously, or...
She's too young for
osteoporosis that severe.
And too old for osteogenesis imperfecta.
- Which leaves bone cancer.
- Cancer's a long shot.
Why? Because metastatic tumors
don't explain the abnormal MRI,
kidney damage,
cotton mouth, double vision?
- Oh, wait, they do.
- Infection could do all that too.
It's not an infection.
Because you know the nonexistent
medical records confirm
that the brilliant doctors
in Cuba treated her for infection?
Or because you're trying
to kiss up to Foreman.
Because an infection
would cause a fever,
and the brilliant doctors who work
in my office have already crossed
that off the list because the husband.
You're the one who said
it's possible for 2 people to have the
same symptom for 2 different reasons.
And you're the one who said
if we do that, we might as well throw
out everything we got from the husband.
Right, and then you said
we should do something productive,
like breaking her arm?
- Foreman didn't break her arm.
- Of course he didn't.
- Cancer did.
Put her in a pet scan.
See what else is breaking.
This isn't gonna work. He's not a moron.
You can't just agree with
everything he says for two days
and hope he forgets the last
three years and how much he hates you.
Anything else?
When you get the results
of the pet scan, let me know.
I don't really care if
Foreman stays or goes, but...
You're fired.
What, because I- I yelled at you?
Because you've been here the longest,
you've learned all you can,
or you haven't learned anything at all.
Either way,
it's time for a change.
Fine.
No tumors in her arm.
Synovial membrane's working fine.
No hotspots, no bone cancer. Maybe
we should be looking for something else.
Is it raining out?
- House fired me.
- What?
Because you yelled at him?
"Time for a change,"
was the official explanation.
It makes no sense.
- Since when does House make sense?
- He always makes sense.
- He's angry.
- Yes, it's all about you, Foreman.
He's upset you're leaving,
so he fires Chase.
Excuse me.
By the humerus.
She's got a hotspot.
- Why'd you fire Chase?
- Sure thing.
First, you tell me the
results of the pet scan.
- Did you fire him for me?
- Would you stay if I did?
You asked him to fire Chase?
- No!
- Yes.
You're frustrated with Foreman,
so you lash out, kick the dog?
He's not gone five minutes,
and the name-calling starts.
- What's on the pet scan?
- Why'd you fire Chase?
- Do you know what's on the pet scan?
- You two, out.
Whoa, wait. What's on the pet scan?
You can't dump your entire department
just because you don't
know how to deal with an issue.
Yes, they are all irreplaceable.
If only this country
had figured out a way
to somehow teach people
to interpret pet scans.
What the hell's wrong with you?
You fired Chase?
I don't suppose you know
what's on my patient's pet scan.
I told you to show
Foreman you have a heart.
How does that translate
into you being a bastard?
So that's a no.
Pick up the phone and
tell Chase you made a mistake.
Un-fire him.
If you know what's on the pet scan,
call me back.
- Cut the crap.
- Chase is a good doctor.
Sorry, you're in the wrong room.
My name on the door.
My team, my decisions.
My building, my floor, my people.
Hold that reprimand.
Dr. Chase.
How are ya?
Thank you.
You are indispensable.
You're still fired.
Sorry.
That was awkward.
Pet scan revealed a blood clot
in my patient's arm, which means...
Good-bye.
Still got two people working for me.
I gotta get one of them to do my job.
A clot means a heart problem.
We have to do an emergency angiogram.
How do you know she has a blood clot?
Pet scan can't determine
that with certainty.
You have no better idea of what's wrong
with her than when we first got here?
- We've ruled out MS.
- I told you it wasn't MS.
- Where's Dr. House?
- Dr. House has left for the night.
He'll be here in the morning to review
the results if you sign the consent.
But,
you know...
You could call him at home.
He doesn't always pick up.
So keep calling.
Thank you.
Dr. House, it's Esteban Hernandez again.
As soon as you get home,
it's very important you call me.
Hello, yes, Dr. House.
It's Esteban Hernandez.
As soon as you get home,
if you can please call me.
- Catheter's in her femoral artery.
- Why are you telling me that?
- Because you're assisting.
- Do I look like I? assisting?
I had nothing to do
with Chase's termination.
Is everything okay?
You're doing fine, Marina.
The dye will take a minute
to work its way through your system.
Why would you tell him
you're leaving cause he's a jerk?
Because it's the truth.
Did you give an angry
cuban my home number?
Why would you do that?
You're not turning into House.
You're worse than him.
Let me get this straight.
Instead of picking up the phone and
talking to a patient for five minutes,
you gave up on sleep and drove in here.
My chest.
She's in v-tach.
- What did you do?
- Nothing.
You must have hit something.
Did you nick an artery?
She has no pulse.
It hurts.
She has no pulse, but she's talking.
Cough.
Cough again.
Keep coughing. It'll push blood
into your head, keep you conscious.
Push 1 milligram epinephrine.
Will...
That...
Help?
No. But it is amazingly cool.
We need to get her on bypass...
We need to keep her here.
If this is a clot,
then the force of bypass will
blow it into her brain, kill her.
If we continue CPR, she'll lose blood
flow, which will cause brain damage.
What caused the heart to stop?
Let's assume it wasn't human error.
I didn't nick an artery.
It just stopped.
I said, let's assume.
The only other option
is electrical instability.
No ST segment changes.
We need to tell the husband.
Tell him what?
We have no idea what happened.
Keep going till I figure this out.
Jeez, at 47 I hope my colon
looks better than this guy's.
Isolating the first transverse.
Help! I'm trapped inside a monitor!
Not a good time, House.
My patient lost her heartbeat during
a routine cardiac catheterization, so...
- Human error.
- It's not human error.
Electrical instability?
Pre-procedure EKG was normal.
No syncope.
Ischemia?
Foreman said no ST segment changes.
Human error is the
only other possible...
It's not human error.
Of course it's human error. You don't
want Foreman to have made a mistake,
because then you'd have to mock him.
And that would put a crimp
in your brilliant plan of keeping him
by having a breakdown and firing Chase.
Did you just spit on a monitor?
You know I can't see you.
Human error would
not explain her symptoms.
You mean her heart stopping?
And her foot pain, her back pain.
House, I? busy. You have a team.
Run your differential with them.
Foreman and Cameron are doing CPR.
Then you shouldn't have fired Chase.
Change is fun, huh?
Five, six, seven, eight.
Go.
Someone's gotta talk to the husband.
He thought this whole thing
was gonna last 45 minutes.
Half an hour more of this,
nothing to talk about.
We won't be able to bring her back.
We've gotta get her on bypass.
House still isn't answering his phone.
You, get in here.
Go.
Excuse me, my wife was supposed
to be back an hour ago...
As soon as we know anything,
we'll call you.
Thank you.
Human behavior finals will also get
into clinical presentations of mania.
And... We'll touch on Stanislas
Dehaene's pet scans...
Excuse me, professor.
House, when we're
done with our rounds...
My patient has no heartbeat.
Stopped when we inserted a
catheter during a routine angiogram.
Anyone tells me why her heart
stopped gets an A in Dr. Cuddy's class.
Anyone.
Human error?
Yeah, I? polling
first-year medical students
'cause I hadn't considered human error.
Marfan syndrome.
Structural abnormalities would
show up on the echo. You get a C.
Yeah?
- Botox injections.
- F.
If the injection was tainted
with live botulism, it'd fit.
B+. Unfortunately,
she missed her last botox appointment
due to a boating accident.
- But send me your resume.
- House, time's up.
Good lord. You smell like musk ox.
Either our patient goes on bypass,
or I call time of death.
- Your patient isn't already on bypass?
- I was worried about a clot.
- How long?
- Three hours.
House. Bypass. Now.
Clear the hall!
Dr. Foreman! My wife...
What has happened?
Her heart stopped.
We have to get her on bypass.
He needs to wait outside.
Dr. House.
You can vacuum later.
I am not the janitor.
I am Esteban Hernandez.
What happened to my wife?
Her heart stopped.
- Wh-why did her heart stop?
- If I knew that, I? be coming to you.
Tell me where you take her.
Tell me what is happen to her.
Happening.
It's the present participle.
Not a particularly interesting form
of speech. Kinda like this conversation.
But I-I risk my life to see you.
I look you up. You fix people.
When everyone else gives up, you don't.
And now you...
Insult me? Ignore my wife?
Helps my process.
You do not ignore my wife, okay?
She's everything to me.
Well, then you do not ignore your wife.
You just sit here.
You don't talk to people.
How do you fix something
if you don't look at it?
Turn on the bypass, please.
Good.
Good distal flow.
- Need to look at the heart.
- Why?
I can't find my wallet.
Pick it up. Turn it over.
I don't see anything physically
wrong with her heart.
- Hearts don't stop for no reason.
- Okay, take your look.
You see anything wrong?
Give her a jump-start.
Clear.
And again.
Again.
Yeah. Seventh time is the charm. Sorry.
I'll keep her on bypass till her
husband has a chance to say good-bye.
I'm not telling her husband anything
until I can tell him why his wife...
It doesn't matter.
Her heart can't start.
She's dead.
I got you something.
I'll miss you.
I know you won't miss me, but...
I just thought it would
be nice for you to have that.
I will miss you.
Can I have a hug too?
Surgeon found nothing.
Can't start her heart.
What a thoughtful gift.
Nice reminder of intellectual theft
to hang at your new place of employment.
You two can go. Say hi to Chase for me.
You're wearing lipstick.
We can stay.
We can run another differential.
You two have no theories
about why the heart stopped,
which means I don't need you... Go.
It's too late for theories.
We need to tell the husband.
- Tell him what?
- That it's over.
- Why?
- Because her heart won't start.
How can we tell him there's no hope
if we don't know why there's no hope?
He's not gonna pull
the plug on his wife.
He risked his life to get her to me.
If he pulls the plug,
it means he's failed.
it means you failed.
And you're okay with that?
Go.
You look great.
You know House firing
you has nothing to do with you.
The why doesn't matter.
Foreman'll end up staying.
House'll call you,
probably yell at you for not showing up.
It's... It's okay.
He's right.
It's time for a change.
You were right too.
The whole "It's tuesday,
I- I like you" was...
It was silly.
Don't give me that look.
Don't feel sorry for me.
Getting this job was the best
thing that has ever happened to me.
Everything about it. And losing it...
Well, I think it's...
Gonna be... good too.
I'll miss you.
You got time for a drink or something?
I think I should go.
Yeah.
How's it going?
The way the security
light hits your legs...
Looks good.
Thank you.
If you're here to yell at me about the
Foreman/Chase situation, it can wait.
When do you plan on telling the husband
it's time to say good-bye to his wife?
Haven't put a clock on it.
Other than your curiosity, do you
have any reason to keep her on bypass?
Patient's husband prefers her not dead.
Or you want a storybook
ending for the young man
who crossed the ocean for his wife.
This is not an act. I don't care.
Then pull the plug.
What if I can fix it,
but I just don't know it yet?
- I know you care.
- I don't care.
I really don't care.
My motives are pure.
If we do an autopsy and we see, oops...
If i'd thought of that crazy idea,
we could have saved her,
then the husband might be upset.
You've done all you can do.
It's time to let go.
I was told you didn't believe in God.
I don't.
I promised my wife I?l
do everything I can to fix her.
If I don't pray,
then I don't do everything.
It's not working.
She's not coming back.
If you want to say good-bye,
you can come down to the ICU,
and then I?l take her off bypass.
I'm sorry. I should have...
I am so sorry.
When you turn the machine off,
that's it?
Yeah.
- Right now is her brain working?
- Probably.
Just not her heart.
She seems like she's just sleeping.
She's not sleeping.
We double-checked.
Her heart.
It beats.
No. It's residual flow from the bypass.
No, I-I can feel it.
Look.
That is her heart, no?
P wave, QRS, T wave.
It's a normal normal.
Holy crap.
Is this heaven?
No. It's New Jersey.
God send you back to me.
It's a miracle.
- It's impossible.
- Apparently not.
Live hearts don't stop for no reason.
Dead hearts don't start for no reason.
Apparently, they do.
She's three hours off bypass
and still stable. And the pain is gone.
No, it's not.
You think she's lying
about feeling better?
Just 'cause it's not there
now doesn't mean it's gone.
Just because it was there
before doesn't mean it's coming back.
Chase was probably right.
She had some sort of tropical
infection that cleared
when we put her on
antibiotics during the bypass.
Antibiotics did not
bring her back to life.
Other than a miracle, it's
the only explanation for her symptoms.
How come God gets credit
whenever something good happens?
Where was he when her heart stopped?
What if it wasn't human error?
What if it was God's error?
A congenital defect
in an artery making it
susceptible to inflammation.
We need to do another angiogram.
We've looked at her heart a hundred
different ways. There was no evidence...
The time we looked inside,
we stopped before we could see anything.
Because it stopped.
Good news.
We think we know what the problem is.
You mean was.
Hey, it's my first language, not yours.
If she wants to outlive Castro,
we need to fix her heart.
?qui quiere?
In case no one's filled you in,
today is monday,
which means you've been dead for a day.
When that kind of symptom comes back,
it can get serious.
I need to do another angiogram.
Wait. Wasn't that what
caused her heart to stop before?
No. God caused that.
He's all-powerful, you know.
Si. Lo es.
He was watching over us in the ocean.
And he's watching over us now.
Your rescuers didn't have wings.
They had a helicopter.
Esteban prayed.
You know how many little
boys are praying for jet packs?
How many priests are praying for...
Well, that one actually works.
You didn't bring me back to him.
And I? not gonna take you away
from him. But if we don't do this test,
God will.
You said there was no chance,
no hope, which means...
Which means I was wrong.
But I? wrong all the time.
My mistakes don't prove there's a God.
You came a long way to see me.
You gonna put her life
in God's hands or in mine?
Ready?
I'd better not see you praying!
I don't wanna have to
fight for credit on this.
Exiting the femoral,
entering the aortic arch.
This is where...
Where we stopped to
have a picnic last week.
- Her blood pressure's rising.
- Mine's rising too.
Of course,
I am doing battle with the deity.
In the heart.
Injecting the dye.
Right coronary flow's unobstructed.
Left coronary flow looks normal.
Looks like you're wrong.
Either I? right,
or this test is about to go very bad.
What's that?
She has one, two,
a third ostium.
How many is she supposed to have?
Dos.
All the third one's doing
is causing inflammation,
throwing off clots,
getting in the way of the angiogram.
No human would screw up that big.
Don't worry.
Just one more surgery,
and you'll be fine.
Thank God.
Don't make me slap you.
It's tuesday.
No, it's monday.
I know. I just...
I didn't feel like waiting.
I hear you got another
satisfied customer.
One more,
and I get a set of steak knives.
Well... This is it.
I appreciate the
opportunity you gave me.
Didn't do it for you.
Thought you were the
best guy for the job.
Thanks. I guess.
Which is why I want you to stay.
You're an important part of the team.
I need you.
I know.
But I don't need you.
And I definitely don't want to be you...
You're miserable.
I just solved a case by predicting
a never-before-seen heart defect.
Case you couldn't solve.
Case you gave up on.
I couldn't be happier.
For two minutes,
maybe, until the next case comes along,
until you're jonesing for your next fix.
This woman talks while
in full cardiac arrest,
and you're more excited about
the talking than the heart dying.
- The two were connected.
- I don't want to solve cases.
- I want to save lives.
- Do you think she cares?
You think the husband cares?
You think the children she can now have
because of me are gonna
care why I saved her?
- I care.
- About yourself.
About your own ego.
You're the selfish bastard, not me.
Which is why you took so much pleasure
drawing out this little good-bye
of yours for the last three weeks.
It wasn't for me. It wasn't for anyone.
Sure as hell didn't help anyone.
Nice try.
Nice tries are worthless.
You now have a bigger office than I do.
Why don't you go enjoy it?
Better be naked pictures.
My resignation letter.
I've gotten all I can from this job.
What do you expect me to do?
Break down and apologize?
Beg Chase to come back?
No.
I expect you to do what you always do.
I expect you to make a joke and go on.
I expect you to be just fine.
I'll miss you.
Genuine american cigars.
You guys can't get them in Cuba.
100% healthy.
Shouldn't you go home?
Patient follow-up. Very important.
She looks great. Like she's sleeping.
She is sleeping.
I double-check.
So...
They all quit.
Two of them quit.
I fired the third.
It's very hard to lose your people.
Must be very upset.
Yeah, I must be.
But you're not?
I don't think I am.
I think I?...
Okay.
What are you going to do?
God only knows.
Transcript: swsub.com Sync: jh26
Last one by me, no sync next year.