Wait. Wait, we shouldn't...
we shouldn't be doing this.
What, you're not having fun ?
It's not that. It's just...
rather be with the boys ?
No.
Well, then, come on.
You kids need any help ?
No. No, we're fine.
- Car trouble ?
- No.
Then why are you here ?
Um... we're just talking.
Does she do all the talking ?
Uh, most of it.
I know what that's like.
I'm gonna come back through
here in ten minutes.
And if you're still here,
I'm gonna call your parents.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Now, where were we ?
Uh, we were going.
In nine minutes.
Wait a minute.
Stevie ?  What's wrong ?
Oh, my god !
Help ! Someone help me !
www. ydy. com
proudly presents
sync:Mina
www. ydy. com
House Season 3 Episode 13
"Needle in a Haystack"
"J. Whitner. M. D"
"House. M. D"
16-year-old with respiratory arrest.
The only thing I hate more than
a thief is a crippled thief.
Yeah, me too. No sign of trauma.
No history of asthma or allerg...
- Who the hell is J. Whitner ?
- No idea.
Stevie lipa's ekg and
echocardiogram were normal, but...
Normal is good. Send him home.
J. Whitner ! Doctor.
Who is he and where do I find him ?
She's a new researcher,
works with ereshevsky.
Is she hot ?
She's in a wheelchair.
Doesn't mean she's not hot.
Just means she can't bend over, so Cuddy
has to bend over backwards.
16-year-old kid. E. R. Work-up revealed
a bloody pleural effusion.
That's odd.
Yeah, that occurred to me.
What took you so long to mention it ?
No tumors or pneumonia on the ct.
He passed out while making out.
If he's into sex, drug and rock and roll
can't be that far behind...
I'm guessing cocaine.
Tox screen was clean.
Just means he wasn't on drugs,
not that he hasn't been using drugs.
Looks like a plumbing problem to me.
Leaky pipes.
If he popped an aneurysm,
he'd be in the morgue, not the E. R.
That's why you're gonna do a venogram
instead of an arteriogram.
This is not a high-pressure burst...
it's a low-pressure leak.
Still could have been drugs that caused
the pipes to corrode in the first place.
So go look under his mattress.
See if he's got any pills or powder
stashed with the hand lotion.
Sweet ride.
I asked for the one with the sissy
bar and the banana seat,
but santa gave me this instead.
Guess that's what I get for being naughty.
You must be Dr.House.
Yeah.
So, looks like there's been some sort
of mix-up at the parking office.
They had to move me closer to the door.
Had to ? You don't look like
the type to pull a weapon.
- Wheelchair.
- Cane.
I think you should do the honorable thing,
let me have my space back.
Oh, well, uh, since you asked
so nicely... wheelchair.
Cane ! Walking long distances
makes my leg hurt.
And it's easy for me ?
'Course not.
Pushing that little lever,
your thumb muscles must burn.
I'm sure the last ten yards are pure torture.
Crossing the parking lot's dangerous...
cars can't see me.
Did you ever hit
a patch of black ice with a cane ?
No, gosh, on account of the
fact that I can't walk !
Maybe you should ask the parking
office for some crampons.
Look, this is about who can most
easily cross the parking lot.
You're the winner.
Oh, and the prize is apparently
a parking space.
there's still no answer at either
one of your parents' cell numbers.
Is there any other way
we might be able to contact them ?
No. They're in a conference.
They probably had to turn
them off or something.
What does it matter where they are ?
I mean, he's in pain.
You gotta do something.
We need them to sign this.
Why can't he just sign the papers ?
- He's 16.
- Still not an adult.
Then call my parents.
They know him.
They'll take responsibility,
do whatever you need.
I can'T. It won't...
You can't just let him sit here in agony
until his parents finally decide...
leah. It's okay.
No, it's not.
I feel like there's an anvil
sitting on my chest.
You win.
We're doing the venogram now.
We'll deal with the fall out later.
My fingers feel wet.
That's just the dye.
Your nerves can't tell
the difference between the cold inside
your body and the wet outside your body.
The nerves can't tell the difference,
or the brain can't interpret the difference ?
It's a little of both.
You like science ?
It looks like a diffusion pattern.
That's because it's the venous side,
low pressure.
So Graham's law applies ?
You've taken physics al ready ?
No. Just sort of read up on my own.
I had to teach myself a lot of stuff too.
Schools sucked where I grew up.
You go to public or private ?
Public.
Leak has to be in the pulmonary
veins to get in my lungs, right ?
- Yep.
- I don't see anything. Do you ?
No. It doesn't make sense.
How can I have a bloo effusion
without any bleeding ?
This is putrid.
Put food-borne parasites and
infections on the list to check on.
I'll take the bedroom.
I'm sorry, I didn't know there
was anyone... we were just...
I have a gun.
Look, you can take whatever you want.
- My wallet's in my suit.
- Freeze !
Oh ! I'm calling the cops.
Okay, you don't have a gun.
And you're not calling the cops.
Oh, no, I'm calling the cops, unless you
two get out of here right now.
Unless ?
Who calls the cops unless
a burglar does something ?
You don't want to have
to explain the affair.
We're not having an affair.
He's got a ring. You don'T.
And judging from the state
of the kitchen downstairs
and the half-vacuumed bedroom,
I'm guessing you're a better
lover than you are a maid.
Maid ?
You son of a bitch.
I'm not a maid, okay ?
This is my house, not his.
Oh, sorry.
And what's wrong with my kitchen ?
Nothing. We're sorry.
We're just here to help Stevie.
Who's Stevie ?
Your... son ?
Huh ?
it was the address you gave.
The E. R. Must have written it down wrong.
Or you lied because you don't
want us to talk to your parents.
I gave you their phone numbers.
You gave us some numbers.
We haven't been able to reach anyone.
I told you, they must be in a conference.
He's lying.
Leah.
He's romani.
A gypsy.
So you don't have a home ?
Of course we do.
Next you're gonna ask me about dancing
around campfires and... Stealing children ?
This is why I don't tell people.
They share everything with each other
and nothing with the gadje... the outsiders.
Sharing information with outsiders
has not gone so well for my people.
I get it, but right now you're making
yourself more vulnerable by lying to us.
You can't go to my house.
You'll pollute it.
All we're gonna do is look around.
Your presence is enough.
My parents take it seriously.
It's spiritual as much as it is physical.
You know where he lives ?
Don't.
Look, I'll tell you whatever
you need to know.
If we can't trust your answers...
I drink sometimes, okay ?
I've smoked pot.
I'll tell you anything.
The truth.
You just... You can't go in my home.
The pot wouldn't cause a bleeding problem.
A pesticide on the pot could.
Where did you get it ?
Some kid at school.
Stevie. He got the pot from me.
He doesn even go to school.
His parents made him drop out.
I'm home schooled.
He reads books.
What else are you lying about ?
Is your father really a professor ?
He's a salesman.
They buy and sell anything
they can get their hands on.
They... so you're with your dad
when he's making these deals ?
He was just in chicagoa week ago.
You fly ?
No. My dad's got a truck.
You can't be serious.
Actually, I can.
See ? It's my space. I want it back.
It's not your space.
It's the hospital's space.
And the hospital thinks that the person
who's worse off should get the better space.
Your application for a handicapped space
says you can walk 50 yards.
And whitner says she can roll
50 miles between oil changes.
I can't change my leg.
The space I moved you to is only 46
yardsaway from the front door.
I measured. You'll be fine.
Great... so I can collapse four yards
into the lobby instead of outside in the cold.
As long as it's not in my office.
You know who won the New York
city marathon six years in a row ?
Guy in a wheelchair.
Then go get yourself
one and leave me alone.
Gimme my space, I'll be
happy to roll around all day.
You couldn't last one week in a wheelchair.
Wanna bet ?
What's wrong with you ?
Nothing that a week off my feet won't solve.
Venogram's negative. No leak.
You mean you couldn't find the leak.
Is your leg worse ?
No, but my parking spot is.
Blood is only made inside
the circulatory system,
which means when we find it outside...
there's no leak. I even checked lymphatics.
So you're gonna spend
a weekin a wheelchair
just to get a parking space
closer to the front door ?
Easier than chopping off my legs.
We've ruled out toxins and drugs.
Kind of. He's romani.
Apparently, they feel
the need to keep secrets,
so it's hard to know anything for sure.
Yeah, he's also a human being,
which means you shouldn't be
trusting him to begin with.
Stop relying on his answers
and find some on your own.
It's a deep veinthrombosis.
The kid spent 16 hours
in the backseat of an old pickup.
Causes a clot and makes
its way to his lungs.
We should do an arteriogram,
find the clot, bust it with tpa.
Or we could find the leak.
There's no leak.
Hey, you can't yell
at a guy in a wheelchair.
It's a slow leak.
You gotta speed it up.
Thin his blood. Redo the venogram.
That could cause a massive bleed.
Excellent... massive'll
be even easier to find.
Pardon me.
Guess you guys are gonna
have to get the next one.
I thought you were
redoing the venogram.
As soon as we're done with the arteriogram.
Okay, you're gonna feel a little poke.
Could you maybe do that ?
Don't worry. It's just your leg.
I don't have to go any further than this.
Take a look at this.
Bones of your Forearm.
Uh, radius and ulna.
How 'bout the wrist ?
Um... lunate... hamate... the...
scared lovers try positions
they can't handle.
It's a mnemonic for the wrist bones.
It's the only way I can remember them.
Are you okay ?
Ow. Ow, my stomach.
You hit something ?
- I barely started.
- Lie flat.
No, I can't. It hurts too much.
I'm getting out.
It's our only chance to see what's going on.
If he moves, I could shred his artery.
Just get it out ! Now !
It's gonna be okay, Stevie.
Just inject the dye.
Dye's going into his liver,
but it's not coming out.
The clot's gonna be constricting
the flow in the hepatic vein.
It's not constricting it.
It's completely blocking it.
His whole liver's fried.
kid's liver's failing because of massive
clots blocking his hepatic vein.
How can he have both a bleed and a clot ?
It's not a clot.
Must have blocked a vein
with a catheter wire.
Not a chance.
Increased pressure downstream
could also stop the blood.
there's no heart failure or cirrhosis.
Means it has to be a clot.
Massive clots block veins.
They don't make them leak.
And since he clearly has some kind of...
you having a little problem ?
Would you mind ?
Boy, that was humiliating.
How does whitner make it through the day ?
"Pride goeth before the fall.
"Lucky for me, I'm sittingin
one of these babies.
So, what other theories can I shoot down ?
Dic would explain both...
his platelets are normal
and his ptt isn't elevated.
Leukemia ?
Normal cbc and differential.
You guys are still thinking like doctors
when you should be thinking like plumbers.
Come on, I wanna see some butt crack.
Something inside the liver
is punching holes in the pipes.
Blood bleeds through the opening,
sticks to the intruder,forms a mass.
- A clot.
- A mass.
cancer. A tumor could erode a blood vessel.
Well, so could a granuloma
from tuberculosisor sarcoidosis.
Do a ct, mri, a sputum, and an ace level.
Excuse me, sorry.
Cripple coming through.
He says his throat hurts.
That phrasing means you think it doesn't.
No, I don't.
Good enough for me.
Where are you going ?
Mothers know best.
Get yourself a sucker on the way out.
Look, I think he's just faking
so he doesn't have to go to school.
How did you know I was a truant officer ?
I told him he had a choice...
go to school or the doctor.
Right... he's wasting your precious time,
so you decided to waste mine.
How thoughtful.
I'm in a wheelchair, so I can't
examine him all the way up there.
Hop down.
My life is just one horror after another.
Open.
Does it look like it hurts ?
Nope.
- What's that ?
- It's a syringe.
I'm with you--make him hate the doctor's
office more than he hates school.
That's okay.
I don't... I don't think that's...
it's just saline... hurts like hell
when it's injected directly into the muscle.
So what do you think ? Arm or ass ?
I think he's learned his lesson.
Oh, I don't know.
We better check.
Jack, is your mommy a big fat idiot ?
Well, what do you know ?
Guess you were right.
Just hold still, Stevie.
This shouldn't take long.
Sorry, i'm guessing the mike
in this thing doesn't pick up nods.
Smart kid.
Too bad it's all gonna go to waste.
Nothing wrong with being a salesman.
He should be able to pursue his own life,
not be stuck helping his parents
sell old toasters.
He's still young...
you never know what he'll end up doing.
Unless he goes back to school,
I know exactlywhat he'll end up doing.
Wait.
Is that a lesion ?
Magnifying times five.
It's a granuloma.
Means wegener's is most likely.
Stevie !
Mom, is that you ?
Hey, hey !
Get him out of this now !
Your son is sick.
The sign on the door...
No, the sign says no metal.
We took everything off.
It says no admittance.
What's wrong with our son ?
We don't know yet.
He's not gonna die, is he ?
Your son is very ill.
We're still trying to figure out why,
which is why we need you to leave the room.
what are you going to do now ?
Oh, now I've gotta slide my butt
from one padded seat to another.
What if I bump my knee ?
Mri showed a granulomain his liver.
Fantastic.
Wanna give me a hand here ?
No... clotting, bleeding,
and a granuloma equals wegener's.
I know. That's why I said fantastic.
I was being sincere.
Now give me a hand.
It wouldn't be fair.
We're gonna biopsy the liver to confirm.
Wouldn't be fair not to.
People are good and kind and gentle
and help people in wheelchairs.
You don't believe that.
- But you do.
- No, I don't.
Foreman.
Forget the biopsy.
His liver'll be gone before
you get the results.
Start treatment with cyclophosphamide
before wegener's punches a hole in another pipe.
What's with the clothes ?
You're not being discharged.
I know. It... it's my parents.
They insist that I wear this stuff.
We insist on our own food,gown,
and furnishings for a reason.
Hey, my... my chest burns.
Are you sure the treatments are working ?
Wegener's causes the body to attack itself.
It doesn't get undone overnight.
Be patient.
Where's your soup ?
It's in the garbage.
It has willow bark extract.
Willow bark extract is basically aspirin.
Yes, for the fever.
He's already on meds... our meds.
We can't risk any adverse interactions.
We need all this stuff to go.
We need to control this environment.
So do we.
People get sick for a reason.
'Cause something in their
life is out of balance.
Dad, he's a doctor.
He doesn't want to hear your talk.
Balance is just starting to be restored
now that that girl is gone.
That girl took pretty good care
of your son while you were away.
Yes, we can see that.
All this stuff may make
him feel more comfortable,
- But it's not...
- How long is this treatment gonna take ?
We should start to see some improvement
in his liver function soon.
"Soon. "Very scientific.
I'm sorry.
Be back in a little bit to check on you.
ah, yes.
If it isn't dr. Ironside.
Ah, if isn't "Dr.
I had no friends when I was growing up,
"so all I did was watch tv by myself,
"which is why I can now make
constant pop culture references
which no one understands but me.
" That's my name.  Don't wear it out. "
Ah, ah. Safe from Cuddy, but I guess not
from her trusted rat-complice.
Reasonable people don't debate
the relative merits of their handicaps.
Reasonable people make
rules based on evidence...
like difficulty covering
a distance, say 50 yards,
not on some pre-ordained
pathetic-ness scale.
Last I checked, pigheadedness
was not the eighth heavenly virtue.
It's only pigheaded if you're wrong.
If you're right, they call
it sticking to your principles.
Give it up. You're demeaning yourself.
That's what they told rosa parks.
Don't stand up in there.
I'm watching your feet.
Get out of our home.
This is not a home.
It's certainly not...
It's our home as long
as our son is here.
Mom, dad, will you just
please just calm down ?
You're not family.
You have no right to be here.
What are you gonna do,throw me out ?
You can't even touch the gadje.
I'll touch you.
What is going on ?
I'm the one who brought him here.
I should be able to see how he's doing.
He wouldn't even need to be
here if it weren't for you.
Right... I'm so unclean, I caused
his liver to shut down.
Enough.
No one is leaving.
He's our son, and we
want her out of here.
It hurts.
Your stomach again ?
No. What ?
his liver's actually improving.
We plug one hole and end up poking another.
We talking about the patient
or how to get a raise from Cuddy ?
The wegener's treatment gave him a
massive hemorrhagein his bladder.
Which means...
It's wegener's.
What did I just say ?
We were treating him for wegener's
when eveverything went wrong.
Not everything.
Yeah, it was a very lovely day outside.
On the other hand,
the treatment made him worse.
Treatment made his bladder
worse, not his liver.
Clot in the liver's breaking up.
And the mri, sputum, and
ace ruled out tb, sarcoidosis,
and lymphoma, which leaves us with...
still could be a cancer with multiple...
A cancer we can't see on mri,
ct, or blood tests ?
It's wegener's.
It's not the wrong diagnosis.
It's the wrong treatment.
We could increase immuno suppression.
Add methotrexate.
we can't give methotrexate to a kid who's
already had lung problems.
Methotrexateis carpet bombing.
Hits everything.
We need a smart bomb.
So we don't suppress the
immune system... we change it.
Immune modulation.
Ft-28.
His antibodies are attacking
his blood vessels.
The irritation causes
them to bleed and clot.
We change his immune system
so the antibodies don't interact
with his blood vessels but
work fine everywhere else.
Ft-28's still experimental.
It's not fda-approved.
It's worked for crohn's disease
and rheumatoid arthritis.
He doesn't have crohn's or arthritis.
Let's say that he does...
and start the treatment.
absolutely not.
My people have been experimented
on before. Never again.
Mr. Lipa, with all due respect,
comparing this hospitalto
auschwitz is ridiculous.
Ft-28's been proven safe in hundreds...
People always say you can trust them.
Why would they say anything else ?
Why do they think we would listen...
Hey, hey, hey. You think I don't
understand what it's like to
come from a people who've been
enslaved, mistreated,
and experimented on ?
Tuskegee went on for 28 years
after world war II.
And the laws that made it illegal
for the romani to even set foot
in this state were still
on the books until 1998.
It's not ancient history.
Conventional therapy hasn't worked.
Your son may be dying.
He needs a targeted approach,
and you need to trust us.
I'm sorry.
A life time of experiences
tells me I can't trust you.
And the past three days have
done nothing to change that.
We want our son treated,
not experimented on.
If you don't know how to do that,
then just tell us
so we can take him someplace
where they do.
they're absolutely right.
Stay away from that unproven,
experimental stuff.
Much better to stick with the "moving
of furniture until he gets better" approach.
Yes, you're right.
We're gonna have to come up
with something else.
You mean another
last-ditch desperation move ?
You got anything ?
Go back and don't take no for an answer.
What kind a salesman are you ?
The kind who avoids the house with the crazy
couple who put tinfoil over their windows.
They got money for tinfoil, they got money
for whatever you're selling.
What's that mean ?
Means that if they don't trust you,
you should earn that lack of trust.
What does paying for tinfoil mean ?
Why should I have to answer
all the questions ?
Oops. Sorry.
Still getting used
to the power steering.
I assume you've heard the news ?
I'm not worried.
From what I hear,what you lack in shame
you also lack in will power.
My will may be weak,
but my backbone is strong.
And pain-free, now that
I've stopped using the cane.
'Course, it's harder
to look down cuddy's shirt.
Then, the vantage point
on her ass is much improved.
That's just me... alwayslooking
on the bright side.
I'm the guy who said that
her c cups are half-full.
They are nice, aren't they ?
Oh... no.
You're not gonna win me over that easily.
You may have a wheel.
It doesn't mean you get the grease.
You gotta squeak.
What's that ?
Cyclophosphamide.
We're continuing the standard
treatment as you requested.
Uh, I have to ask everyone to leave
the room for a few minutes
while I apply some bandages.
Why do we have to leave ?
For his penis.
You lied to them.
The bleeding stopped.
I don't need any bandages.
We need to changeyour treatment,
but your parentswon't let us.
They've got it in their
minds that we want to try
some sort of inhuman experiment on you.
The treatment's experimental ?
Ft-28's been through extensive clinical trials.
It's also been used successfully
for other conditions.
The fact that you're recommending...
experimental treatment means
you haveno other options ?
Sorry.
We stop the pleural effusions,
your liver almost fails.
We save your liver, the bladder fails.
If we don't get ahead of the curve on this...
What do you need me to do ?
Take the medicine,but don't ll your parents.
I don't like lyingto my parents.
The rest of the world,though...
the rest of the world can't trust.
You can trust me.
How do I know ?
Because if you do this,then tell
your parents, I lose my license.
Ow ! God !
Get in here !
Wow. Spleen basically exploded, huh ?
Got another bleeder.
2-0 silk on a stick.
Got it.
I believe you ordered your meat rare.
Keep him open... if I confirm wegener's,
might as well stage the
diseasewhile he's still on the table.
What's taking so long ?
External capsule's ruptured but still intact.
No signs of a clot or bleed.
Normal follicles.
Normal lymphoid tissue.
His spleenis ripped to shreds.
There's gotta be granulomas. Keep looking.
Come on.
Can't leave humpty dumpty like this forever.
I don't see anythingbut normal spleen.
No granulomas.
Means no wegener's.
That's all I need to know.
Let's go, people.
Run his bowel.
No need.
I'm closing.
Suture.
Run his bowel.
Nothing suspiciousin the spleen.
Get him out of here.
You missed it.
He had a granulomain his liver.
No, it was just scar tissue.
Looked like a granuloma
on the mri, but it's not.
Don't know whyI'm debating this.
Pass me the kelly clamp.
I'm closing.
Not unless you're gonna sew my
hand into this kid's stomach.
Get out of there.
He's unstable.
He's got wegener's,
which means he's got granulomas.
I'm calling my lawyer.
It's only 26 feet.
If he were an ostrich,
you'd have a 46-foot wait.
Blood pressure's dropping.
Hang another bag of ringer's lactate.
I'm having nothing to do with this.
- Foreman,hang another bag...
- Ringer's lactate. Got it.
Come on, come on.
It's gotta be in here.
But it's not.
Mind if we close ?
Well, it's a good thing
we never sold him on ft-28.
His parents were right.
There's no way his parents
are gonna let us near him again.
they won't be able to transfer him
until he's recovered from the surgery.
You can add the surgical team to the list
of people who won't let us near him.
Bleeds, clots, bleeds, clots.
Spleen explodes.
We should test himfor von willebrand's.
Or we could just play tic-tac-toe.
Okay, xs are bleeds.
Os are clots.
We started in the lungs, right ?
What did we do ?
Ct, sputum, two venograms.
That's one bleed, one clot.
Then what ?
Liver shut down.
Mri, labs, treated with cyclophosphamide.
Whereupon, he peed out
3 units of o negative.
Another bleed.
Where is this going ?
I don't know yet.
What's next ?
Bladder, kidneys.
high resolution ct scan.
Ua and urine sediment.
Gi tract ?
You ran his small bowel in the or.
The large bowelis fixed
to the abdominal wall.
I didn't run that.
Because there was no reason to.
He hasn't been having
any symptoms in his bowels.
Do a colonoscopy.
Because he's had no symptoms ?
You lose your keys,first
thing you do is look everywhere
you might logically have placed them.
You don't find them, then
you start looking in other places.
The medicine cabinet, freezer, mailbox.
We need to lookin this kid's mailbox.
Why don't we x-ray his feet ?
They're fine too.
Because we need to take
the center square to block.
Okay, even if that did
make sense, it's kind of hard to
do a colonoscopy on
a kid you can't get near.
He's in the icu now.
His parents only have
limited visiting privileges.
I like that kid.
He's got spunk.
Can't talk now.
On guard duty.
You're still in that thing.
What thing ?
Oh, this.
Forgot it was even there.
You know,even if you manage
not to get struck down by
a bolt of lightning and make it a week,
cuy's not gonna give you the space.
She can't.
Bet's a bet.
Yes, and that rule out ranks
the americans with disabilities act.
You think you've got logic on your side,
but whitner's got the legal system.
And legal bets logic every time...
just ask O. J.
You're right.
I am ? Yeah.
So you're doing this even though you know
you've got no legal leg to stand on.
Who needs legs when you got wheels ?
I'm gonna get that spot.
No way cuddyis going to gyp me !
What'd you say ?
I'll see you later.
Gonna have them yelling
at me for the next 20 minutes.
Mucosa looks normal, healthy.
No lonely diverticula.
Blood pressure's dropping.
He's bleeding agn.
not in his colon.
- Hurry up.
- I am.
There's nothing there.
Wait, wait, what's that ?
A reflection ?
No, it's something...
looks like A... toothpick.
Are you sure ?
He must have swallowed it accidentally and
just figured he'd digest it eventually.
When you two were making out in the car,
it must have folded awkwardly
and pushed the toothpick
through the wall of the
intestine and into the lung.
And it moved on to his liver and
made its wayto his bladder and spleen.
So that's it. He's gonna be okay.
Yeah. Small holes.
He shouldn't take that long to heal,
now that we've got it out.
See ?
See what you did ?
Me ?
If you hadn't been kissing him...
that's what you heard ? It was the toothpick !
It was that disgusting habit...
it would have just passed right through
him if he hadn't been writhing around.
Isn't that right...
- That's it ?
- Yeah.
That's it.
Wood absorbs water, becomes the same
density as the tissue around it.
That's why it didn't show
upon the ct or mri.
That's cool.
I mean, not cool for me, but...
lotta damagefor something so small.
You know, the lab here,
they have a paid intern position.
It's usually given to one ofthe
kids from the universities,
but if you want, I could
probably get you an interview.
There's some entry-level
stuff,some gopher work,
but you'd also have access
to a lot of cool things.
Thanks, really, but... I can't.
Yes, you can.
Stevie, you're bright.
You have more curiosity than
90% of the doctors on the staff.
Uh... it's not that.
It's just...
I go to work every day
with my family, you know ?
People I've known my whole life.
I don't want to lose that.
You can have both.
No, I can't.
Because they don't want to let you.
They shouldn't be making you choose.
Maybe not, but they are.
And I'm choosing them.
Look, change is hard.
Trust me, I know.
But it worked out for me.
You're a successful doctor.
Your name is on journal articles.
I would love that.
It's just...
I see you with Drs.
Chaseand cameron, and...
you all got empty ring fingers.
You're alone.
Oh ho ho.
This is my last day
living a life of leisure.
So are you gonna tell dr. Whitner
she's outta my space or can I ?
Why would I do that ?
Because you said that you would.
And lying is wrong.
I said I would give you the space
if you made ita whole week...
- Which I...
- Didn't.
The bet didn't stipulate that
you had to be in the chair
for a week unless you had to
barge into an operating room
and shove your hands in a kid's bowels.
You know about that.
You lost.
I saved a life.
Two minutes out of the
chair to save a kid's life.
You lost, house.
I earned that space.
No, you didn't.
I earn that space every day I limp into
that building and do my damn job.
You lo-o-ost.
Hey !
You were never gonna give me
that space, were you ?
I saw whitner the other day.
She knew about the bet.
Didn't seem that worried.
She knew I'd win.
But she doesn't know me.
In fact, she doesn't know
anything except what you tell her,
and you told her that you were never
gonna give me that space, didn't you ?
Just tell me.
Do you at least feel a little guilty ?
If you wanna teach me lessons, don't make
commitments you can't keep.
How's it going ?
How guilty does she look ?
About an eight.
That space is mine.
Veni, vidi, vici.
House Season 3 Episode 13
www. ydy. com
proudly presents
sync:Mina
www. ydy. com