Mark.Mark!
Mark, would you pleaseask your father if he wants a burger?
I know, you're defendingthe free world.Please ask your dadif he wants a burger.
Dad.
dad.
Mom wants to knowif you want a burger.
Mom, I don't knowwhat he wants.
You want a burger?
the guy drove his wheelchairinto a pool.House would love that.
He'll be bored.It's a great visual,but it's diagnostically boring.
What about post-hair-transplantaphasia guy?
Infection throwing clots.House'll shoot it downand call you an idiot.
Oh, well,I wouldn't want that.
What about yoga girl?
It has a good hook.
Should we lead with it?
His first day backhe might want to flex his sarcasm muscle.
Maybe we open with one of the weaker pitches.
You ran here?
It's just eight miles.
Why did you--
why does a dog lick its workplace-acceptable euphemismfor testicles?
Because he can.
What do you gotfor me, boss?
I thought you said you neededeight weeks of rehab.You should'vebeen back here--
if I'd come back sooner, then I'd only be ableto run six miles.I never would've made it in.
What do you got for me?
You're completelypain-free?
The ketamine treatmentcan wear off.
It's been two months.It's not wearing off.
What do you gotfor me?
-It can takeas long as--
-why are we havingthis discussion?
Nna hear me ank you again?Thank you, dr.Cuddy--
not justfor removing the bullet,
but thank you for putting me in a ketamine-induced coma and changing my life.
Happy?I am.
Middle-aged manhad a hair transplant about two months ago--
infection throwing clots.You're an idiot.
Except you're not an idiot.
And she's holding a filefor a 26-year-old female.
What do you really gotfor me?
Girl was doingan inverted yoga pose.Neck snapped.Paralyzed from the neck down.
Except the x-rays showno evidence of spinal injury.
And she's cute.
Oh, well played, sir.
What about stephen hawkingtrying to do the 500 butterfly?
Forget it.Brain cancer, brain surgery.
There's nothing left diagnose.I would takethe other one.
I'll take 'em both.
You don't thinkhe had brain cancer?
Course he had brain cancer.Even oncologists don't screw upfor eight years.
So if there's nodiagnostic issue, why are you takingthe case?
Treatment can be interesting.
-Not to you.
-I've changed.
-No, you haven'T.
-No, I haven'T.
So why are you takingthe case?
Guy tried to kill himselF.
The guy had cancer.He's a lump.
He hasn't been ableto touch his wife, speak to his kids.
He's been in that chairfor eight years.
His muscles have atrophied.Maybe I can help himwith the pain.
Isn't that enough of a reasonto want to help?
Not for you.
-I've changed.\n-No, you haven'T.
Then why am I takingthis case?
Let's startwith the cute paraplegic.
Welcome back.
You look--
healthy.
Quad with no broken neck.Struck me as odd.
Uh, you could takea whole two minutes to ease into being back.
Wouldn't taken a whole monthto ease back.
But eight weeks isthe maximum rehab time for a gunshot woundto the stomach and neck.
So go.
We heard they neverfound the guy.There's no new leads?
What, you thinkhe might've shot this patient, too?That would explain her symptoms.
Could be M.S.
See?It's not so difficult.
It's not M.S.
She had no symptoms beforeshe climbed onto her head.
Unless she's been upside-downfor the last ten years, M.S.Ain't it.
Could be transverse myelitis,swelling in the disks choking off nerve function.
mri was negative for that.
(?±?»??)
When did this turn into"what did you do over your summer vacation?
"it's a little weird to discuss the casewhile you're staring at your blood on the floor.
I asked cuddyto replace the carpet.
I like the carpet.
What did you doover the summer?
-I--
-redo the tests.
Let's see if the sourceof the problem is in the limbsor the spine.Do an emg.
Got a whole other quadto cover.
This guy's still got fluid in his lungs.
You don't think that'sfrom the pool he drank?
Get him an o-2 mask.His leg muscleshave atrophied.
Tendons have shortened from disuse, causing intense pain.
Tendon surgery will make himmore comfortable.
comfortable?
Scoot.
anks for being here.
not a problem.
My dad wouldn't kill himself.
You haven't spoken to himin over six years.
I know my dad.
Mark, the doctor'sjust trying to--
he wouldn't kill himself.
Fine.I'm wrong.
You obviously havea better understanding of this man who drooin front of your tv set 24 hours a day.
Dr.House.
he must have been confused.
All right?It must have beenan accident.
Hope it wasa suicide attempt.
If he was trying to kill himself, then he knows how miserable his life is.
It means there's stillsomething there to kill.
It means your dad'sstill there.
Sorry.Need you.
Thank you.
We were doing the emg,but we never got past the insertionof the conduction pin.
Did she just say"thank you"?
I loaned her some money.What went wrong?
Nothing went wrong.
If nothing went wrong,then something went right.
You're not gonna tell mewhy she thanked you?
You're not gonna tell mewhat went right?
You did somethingfor which she is grateful, and you're...
embarrassed?
For you.
She saw you coming up, thought you werea 14-year-old boy.I set her straight.
I am not telling youwhat went wrong.Or right.
Until you tell mewhy she said thank you.
Oh, you've got me.
You know I need to know.I am so gonna fold.
Except you're forgettingthere's one thing I can do now.
It's either thator a reflex response or--
what happened?
Okay.
This is dr.House.
-House, this is caren.
-Pleasure's all mine.What happened?
When we insertedthe conduction pin,she flinched.
She flinched!Did you hear?
Does that mean I'm getting better?
How big is a flinch?
Bigger than a twitch?Smaller than a spasm?
You smoke?
Socially.Not a lot.
You do yogaand you smoke?
I know.It's hypocritical.
Not at all.The world sees your legs.
No one's checking out your lungs.
-How would smoking--
-it wouldn'T.
I just needed a lighter.
House!
Oh, my god!
The case was lookingso promising.
Hey, I'm not faking.
You moved.Therefore, you can move.
Get this lunaticout of here before she bores again.
I'm not faking!
I heard youwere watching surgery with a patient's family.
Talking to a patient's family.
It's because of yourhallucination, isn't it?After you were shot.
You chose life.You decidedyou wanted meaning.
So you took a casewith no mystery.
Something any doctor could do.
A case with no upside except the satisfaction of helpinganother human being.
She thanked me.
And...you felt nothing.
I wasn't even surewhat I was supposed to feel.
It's like your leg.It's atrophied.
Keep working it.The feeling will come.
Sorry.
Need you.Again.
I told youto get rid of her.
It's a good thing we didn'T.Tightness in her chest.
She can't breathe.It could bea pleural effusion.
Right.
Either thator she's holding her breath like a four-year-old.
RelaX.
I'm not gonnaburn you again.
I'm going to stab you!
Look, either you're faking or you've gota pleural effusion.
That's a buildup of fluidaround the lungs,which is very serious,
and I'd have no choice but to stab you in the backwith this needle and suck all the fluidout of you.
-So.
-we should give her a local.
That would defeat the pointof me being nasty.
Ready?
-Down.
-She can't breathe if she's down.
-She can't--
down, down, down!Come on!
That's nota pleural effusion.
The problem's in her heart.
Can't fake that.
I've had to relievethe pressure three times In the last two hours.
So either we figure out what's causing blood to build uparound her heart,
or I follow her aroundwith a needle for the rest of her life.
Echo was clean.No structural abnormalities.
Could be aninfectious process, tb.
Or vasculitis would alsoplain the effusion.
but not the paralysis.
Let's assumethat she wasn't faking it.
she moved.Therefore, she could move.
She wasn't paralyzed.
Doesn't mean she was faking.Could have been a delusion.
Either she was faking
and coincidentallygot a real cardiac problem at the exact same time, or it's a delusion.
And the fake paralysisis a real neurological symptom.
You thinking vascular tumorin her spine?
Her platelets are normal.
And she's been scannedup and down.It was all clean.
So open her up and find it.
so what do you want us to do?
Start at her neck and just keep cuttingdown her spine until we stumble on something?
That should work.
His heart rate'sa little high.
Should I be worried?
Probably just meanshe's still in discomfort from the surgery.
I'm gonna up his morphinea little.
You've been so nice to us.
That's the job.
No, I mean,all the other doctors,
all they did was obsess on the cancer, the treatment, the damage.
Just trying to fix him.
You're the first doctor that's ever given a damnabout the quality of his life.
His heart rate'scome down.
Morphine worked.I was right.
What a touching moment.
That's whywe become doctors.
One of those rare momentswhen our hearts are warmed--
would you liketo get a drink?
Are you serious, or are you just tryingto change the subject?
No, I'm serious.
I drink.You drink.
We could do itat the same time.
At the same table.
Do you eat?
We could do that, too.
I mean, if the answer is no, that's cool, but--
no, it's just--
you're just comingoff the surgery, and you're not yourself yet.
And I work for you,and even though last year'S...
You're smiling.I'm saying no,and you're smiling.
Oh, don't take itpersonally.
It's just 'causeyou're full of crap.
You have no interestin going out with me.
Maybe you did...
when I couldn't walk.
When I was a sick puppy that you could nurtureback to health.
Now that I'm healthy,there's nothing in it for you.
You are not healY.
Cuddy wants to see you.
You've been back at work24 hours, and you're alreadyplaying hide-and-seek in a woman's spine.
Who won the pool?
There's no tumor.
Her platelets are normal.
-The scans didn't--
-what's the worstthat can happen?
I paralyze her.
She wouldn't even notice.
Her lawyers might.
You're not doing the surgery.And lower the morphineon your other patient.
Fine, I'll lower it.If you'll let me dothe surgery.
What?
You want to trade?
We're not swappin'a couple of goats for your helpputtin' up a barn.
You want something.I want something.
We compromise.It's the grownup wayto resolve our differences.
There alreadyis a mechanism for that.
It's called the employer-employee relationship.
I get what I want,and you don'T.
You tried to swap?
Ran a few more tests.
Came back negative.Surgery's on.
You really don'tgive a crap, do you?
Does that make me evil?
Yeah.
The girl's lifeis at stake.All we're talking aboutwith the guy is--
all we're talking aboutis the reason you took the case.To help someone.
-Too bad for them.
-Too bad for you.
The reason we crave meaning is becauseit makes us happy.
The first levelof happiness is--
I'm not going away.
the fifth level of happiness involves creation.
Changing lives.
the sixth level is heroin.The seventh level is you going away.
You're saving lives.Which is tantamountto creating lives.
But all you're takingaway from this is the game.
You don't have to listen to them thanking you.
You don't have to change the cases you take or even how you handle them.
You just have to know that you made a difference.
House, you're not--
I'm not an idiot.
house, leave her alone.
close her up.
Wanna know why?
The room's no longer sterile.
True, but that's notthe most interesting reason.
That is not a sexy big toe.
You would neverput that in your mouth.
-What the hellhas that got to do with--
-told youit was interesting.
It gets even better.
Scurvy?
Yeah.Drink.
Like what sailors getwhen they don't eat right?
Aye-aye.
Your arms and leg tissuesare choked with blood.
Makes it hard to move.Also damages your hairand toenails.
But I'm on this great diet.Lots of protein, lots of--
no vitamin C.
Now drink.
Well, thank you.
And thank dr.House.
Send him a note.
The nurse changedhis morphine.I thought you wereworried about the--
it's just post-opdiscomfort.He's ready to go home.
So he won't haveany pain?
Eventually.
Thank you.
Everything elsewill be the same.
Well, you took away his pain,and that--that changes a lot.
Why don't you put himin some sort of facility?
Someplace without a pool.
Yeah, I could dump him there.
Except...
he's my husband.
He's my son's father.
Right.
Kids need a dad.
Someone to play catch with,talk about girls.
Mark's learned that you don'thave to abandon someone--
get a dog.
I'm taking care of him for the same reasonyou helped us.
Some guy shot you,and you hallucinated?
I have a responsibility.
So he's just an anchor weighingyou and your family down.
Sapping your energy,wasting your life.That's the meaningyou take from this.
I want to take care of him.
You enjoy this.
I can't abandon him.
So you don't wantto take care of him.
Taking care of him doesn't fulfill you,make you happy.
But not taking care of himwould make you miserable.
Okay.
Here we go.
I don't need your help.I've done thisa million times.
Lay him back down.
Do that again.
Make that sound.
What was that?
That...
was talking.
you guysare lousy doctors.
You're in such a rush to make the patient feel better, you forgot to checkwhat was wrong.
Yoga girl walked out of heretwo hours ago.You fixed her.
Not her.The other guy.
He had brain canceR.They removed iteight years ago.
His condition's been the sameever since.
Until last night.He spoke.
What'd he say?
He...grunted?
You want us to dissect eight years of medical historywith grunting in the differential?
Sounds good.Call me when you're done.
You're fabricating a mysterybecause you're bored.
I am not bored.
Damn it.
You didn't tell the wifeit was only a grunt?
Of course not.
Because then she neverwould have consented to a bunch of dangerous tests.
I don't remember youbeing this bitchy.
The vicodin dulled it.In the sober light of day,I'm a buzz-kill.
You're giving false hope to a family that's been wrecked.
Don't torture them.
Let it go.Tell the wifeit was only a grunt.Tell her to go home.
I can't let her downlike that.
Pumped her upwith too much false hope.
Oh, I stuck that primo!
How rad am I?
2002, patient had dry eyes.
Dry eyes plus a grunt.
It all makes sense.
Could bea neurological issue.
I get hay fever,I put drops in my eyes.I don't goto a neurologist.
Dry eyes could indicatean autonomic dysfunction.
Goes on the board.
What about coughing?
Or boogers?Should we include boogers?
I'm happy we're doing this.
I'd much rather do this than lengthensome guy's tendon.
Patient's headachesincreased.
Doc scanned his head,found a tumor.
You like wasting your time?
-I'm learning.
-To do what?
Reconsider solved cases because you don't want to deal with the real world?
He's pushingwhere there's nothing.
Cameron, you arean excellent doctor.
You'll get lotsof tearful thank-yous from grateful patients.
Yeah, am I such a bitchfor wanting that?
Well, it's not a bad thing.But it's not why I'm here.
I took this fellowshipto learn from house.
He's teaching youto be a masochist.
Dry eyes goes on the board.
in eight years, the patient experienced 214 symptoms, many of them repeating.
Any patterns?
fever plus frequent urination could mean prostatitis.
Or a urinary tract infection.
-White count was normal.
-No infection.
if you add pain into the mix, fever,
frequent urination could indicate a kidney problem.
I like it.
No.Creatinine and bunwere both normal.
Not the kidney part.The pain part.
Abdominal pain plus all that stuff could equal pancreatic cysts.
perfect.You've managed to pick the one symptom he never had.
Abdominal pain.
It's the first symptomon the board.Grunt.
Grunting isn't pathognomonic for abdominal pain.
No.
The traditionaldiagnostic marker is compression of the diaphragm
and vibration of the larynx, leading to the audible sound.
"I have a painin my abdomen.
"richard's symptoms are culled from eight yearsof medical history.
They're not patterned.These are random, individual events over time.
Illnesses haveincubation periods.
Do an upper endoscopic ultrasound.
his throat will collapse.
Muscle degenerationin his neck won't tolerate the scope.
It's an automatic trach.
You're talking about himlike he's an invalid.
We're insensitive.
Does he drool?Can he hold his neck straight?
Does he chokeon his food?
His neck's fine.His throat'snot gonna collapse.
Cameron, get consentfrom the wife.
Open.
I need you to swallow.
Sorry about that.
Here we go.
Passing through the loweresophageal sphincter,
into the antrum of the stomach.
There's the tail of the pancreas.
Looks clean.
Moving medially,the body and the headof
the pancreas look clean--
get it out.Get it out.
It's stuck.
I can't move it.
His throat's collapsed.
Vitals are all overthe place.
We're losing him.
I'm cutting.
We trached him,endoscopicallyremoved the probe,
and he's breathing again.
So,all in all,great idea.
Did you get a lookat the pancreas
before the world ended?
It was clean.
Which means,barring anything else,
meaning you,he can go home tomorrow.
This man nearly died.
How can you discharge him?
His throat collapsed becauseof what we predicted.
you stick something down someone's throat,
they gag.Spasm.
Which he did.
It took us a half an hourto get that thing out.
Except our patient's throatwas sedated.
Which means the brainshould have sent
a signal in not to do anything.
This could be cancer.
Or some bizarre neurodegeneration.
Even a new typeof vacular--
stop it.
You're enjoying this.
I find it interesting.
It's interestingonly if you're right.
If you're wrong,we're torturing this guy to amuse you.
Half hourto remove the probe?
House.
It's not a spasm.
His throat didn't collapse.
It locked down.
Brain is supposed to tell every muscle in
the body to relax and contract at the same time.
This muscle was onlycontracting,which means
a signal from thebrain was not getting through.
there are no lesions  his brain.
Nothing to interruptany orders.
All it takes is one wire down.
You have no evidenceof any wires down.
A few microtumorson the meninges,
suddenly you're chokingto death.
You wanna lookat the lining of his brain?
the amount of contrast material
you'd need to pump up there just to see--
he'll bleed into his brain.
- No,he won'T.
- Because that wouldn'tbe interesting.
You can get permissionthis time.
The brain is enclosedin a sack
called the meninges.
Does this meanthe cancer's back?
No,no,no,no.
House.
If we found cancer,
it wouldn't bethe original cancer.
It'd be new.
So what?More surgery?
More radiation?
Might not bethe worst thing.
If this isn'tjust ancient history,
maybe it's somethingwe can correct.
Might even get some brain function back.
He could get better?
No.
But understanding whatyou're
saying would be nice.
Maybe you can figure outways to communicate.
Thank god he spoketo you.
Mrs.McneiL.
The test to do this is very risky.
He could die.
He's already dead.
chase,  go slow
already injected into spinal canal
next stop is brain
contrast material entering into
the fourth ventricle.
No parietal bleeds.
Blood pressure's high.
But it's holding.
meninges are intact.
No bleeding.
Oh,god.
Foreman,get in here.
*******
you are lucky he didn't die
I'm lucky? he is the one who didn'y die
we told you he had haemorrhage
you told me he bleed into his brain
not out of his ear
gotta drop this
I'm missing something
we did a dangerous test
and something bad happened
that's all this is
give me tour of the brain Foreman
walk me through the scans
what happened
*******
nothing
next
spec on the superior temporal region
It's regrowth, it's benign
*****
scar tissue from bioposy
House, every spec is not suspect
It's use of surgeon digging around his head
let him go
we do every blood test he's ever had
re-scan his head
no
he's in sick in suffering for 8 years
and I'm not gonna helping make it worse
I'm not gonna help you make interesting
That's okay.
Foreman's better at that stuffthan you are.
We need 5-millimeter cuts through
the occipitaland hypothalamic regions.
No.
How many millimeters?
I can help him.
This is it?
That's your argument?
Seems like a good one.
If I thought for a secondyou wanted
to help him,you'd have carte blanche.
You're doing thisbecause it's fun.
Does nobodyin this hospital have
anything betterto talk about than my motives?
My motives have nothing to dowith the case.
Your motives have everythingto
do with your judgment.
For the first time in years,
I've got no opiates in my body.
Now you question my judgment.
24 times a year you comestorming into my office,
spouting that you can help someone.
Only you never saythose words.
You say something like,
"his pancreas is gonna explodebecause
his brain is on fire."
You come here with medicine,
not with platitudes.
I didn't want to bore youwith the details.
There are no details.
You have a hunch.
House,you don't use hunches.
You always have reasons.
This hospital doesn't exist for your whims.
I'm sorry.
As of 7:00 A.M. Tomorrow morning,
I'm sending your patient home.
The answer is no.
Cuddy called 30 secondsafter you left
and said you'd tryan end around.
My leg hurt.
How bad?
Enough that I'mtelling you.
Did it go away?
Ached for a while.
First time I've felt anythingthere
since the surgery.
But it went away.
It was muscular.
There was some cramping.
What are you smiling about?
You're 40-somethingyears old. You've been
running god knows how many miles a day.
Fallen 100 tim off that skateboard,
and you're shocked to have some soreness?
Just give mea prescription.
For vicodin?
House,people getaching joints,cramps,
they put onan ice pack.They take some ibuprofen.
I know what the pangsof middle age feel like.
No,you don'T.
Because you've been stuffingvicodin every
five minutes since you turned middle-age.
The surgery didn't work.
Don't play me.
Oh,you thinkthis is a scam?
I think you want meto feel sorry for you and either
do the end around on cuddy or give you the drugs.
Either way,you get the highyou
think you need.
House,your surgery worked.
You're fine.
It's just gonna take timefor
it to feel good.
The circumventricular systemsenses cytokines
released in the early stagesof the immune response.
But cvos releases prostaglandinsthat
reset the hypothalamic set point upward,
unless it's countered by anti-pyretic therapy.
So yeah,his brainis on fire.
The suicide attempt was not a suicide attempt.
He drove that wheelchairinto the pool
because he couldn't regulatehis body temperature.
He had hypothalamicdysregulation.
And you discovered this...
when you stepped into the...
university pool?
Fountain.
- I can cure him.
- Cure him.
Even if the fountainproved anything,fixing
hypothalamicdysregulation isn't gonna regenerate brain.
No,but if the scar tissueon his hypothalamus
is restingagainst the pituitary,
the adrenals would shut down.
Addison's disease.
You didn't see anyscar tissue on his mri.
His ct scans--
- his brain is functional.
- His temperature's normal.
There is nothing wrong with his
hypothalamusor his pituitary.
I can make him walk.
I can make him talk.
This is a wild guess that came
to youbecause you were sweating.
Inject him with cortisol.
The guy'll have sexwith his wife again.
He'll hug his kid again.
Hopefully that'sthe combination he was using.
Be a shameif I cured a pedophile.
You're smiling.
That's a bad sign.
You're high.
I told you I haven't hadanything
in three months.
This is as highas you get.
A theory that ties your case up
in a neat little bow.
But you don't have a lickof
substantiating proof.
Your decisiondoesn't make any sense.
There is no risk to a cortisol injection.
If I'm wrong,big deal.
He goes home a vegetable,like he already is.
But if I'm right--
this is not about downsidesor
risk management.
It is a big deal for youto
understand the word no.
I'm sorry,house.
He's on his wayout of here.
Figured you'd beon your scooter racing down the
halls to stab the patient in the neckwith cortisol.
She was right to say no.
I had no objective reason to
thinkthat I was right.
Just needed the puzzle.
Hold on a sec.
Is everything all right?
Yeah,it's just somethingI forgot.
What's that?
This is cortisol.
And it's to fight infection.
Wanna hold onto that?
Put a bandage on it.
Let's see.
Is he okay?
Yes.
Can we go now?
You can go.
Excuse me.
Richard.
Dad,you okay?
Richard?
Richard!
Richard.
You're standing.
Thank you.
he got up.
- I have to go tell house.
- No.
Cuddy.
You can't tell him.
I have to tell him.
He was right.
Why did you do it?
Why did you thinkhe might be right?
Because he's house.
Medically.
What made you thinkhe was right?
- Nothing.
- He got lucky.
That's all that happened.
Telling him nowas a good thing.
Because next time,he won't get lucky.
He'll kill someone.
Just becausehe was right doesn't
meanhe wasn't wrong.
I see him every day.
I can't just...
everybody lies.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-wk120 gagegao
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
House
Season 03 Episode 01