*Gifts I'm preparin'for some christmas sharin'*
*but I pause because*
*hang in my stockin'I can hear the knockin'*
*'zat you, santa claus*
*sure is dark outnot the slighest spark out*
*pardon my clackin' jaws*
*who's there, who is ituh, stoppin' for a visit*
*'zat you, santa claus*
- merry christmas.
- And a happy go to hell.
What's he doing here?
Is he with you?
Detective tritter and I...
we worked out a deal.
Already got a lawyer.
Get out of my office.
I told him I didn'twrite those prescriptions.
I spoke with the da.
He agreed to two monthsin a rehab facility
in exchangefor a guilty plea.
Get out of my office.
- No jail time.
- Right.
I should get locked upin some place I don't belong
in order to avoidgetting locked up
in some other placeI don't belong.
I got you on forgeryand fraud.
- Enough drugs--
- no sanctionsto the medical board.
And you get your car backand your bank accounts
and your precioustumor-ridden patients.
I did this to help you.
Next christmas,buy me a sweater.
You punched outan employee.
You nearly cuta little girl in half
because you weretoo strung out--
I was in pain!
You need to believethat I've got a problem
so that your betrayal hasthe illusion of nobility.
- But you just selfishly--
- knock it off.
Look, I don't carewhy dr. Wilsonis doing this.
And right now, it makesno difference to you either.
You need to dealwith the realityof your current situation.
You want to stand on principle,you end up in a cell.
And you end up neverpracticing medicine again.
So you've got two choices.
Your principlesor your life.
Get out of my office.
The da put a clockon the deal.
You've got three daysto decide.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-colleen3684
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
House
Season 3 Episode 10
house!
Just give me a minute.
- You're afraidof the pain.
- You're not?
You can still havepain meds in rehab.
- Tramadol, gabapentin--
- those don't work.
They will once you'reweaned off the vodin.
Look, there's jesus.
Better go tell the romans.
Fine, run to cuddy.
You don't think she'sgonna support me on this?
Well, the stitches arehealing nicely.
There's no signof infection.
Whoa.
Sorry.
Just need herfor a tiny moment.
Small favor.
Pills.
- Who's the wit?
- Doctor.
Don't worry.
I'll be firing him soon.
Wait in my office.
Incision looks just bigenough for a chest tube.
Collapsed lung?
Someone mistake youfor a pinata?
Delightful.Usually we just get
the elf jokes this time of year.
No on trauma.
Negative ppd.
What flavor dwarfsare you guys?
My daughter and I both havecartilage hair hypoplasia.
Think you can make a punout of that?
Yes, but I don't wantto be insensitive.
She's got a bit ofa short fuse, doesn't she?
It's a bleb.
Wait in my office.
Bleb's not a diagnosis.
It's an evasion.
We'll schedule an mrito make sure.
But a certain number ofese cases are idiopathic.
Let me translate thatinto tolkien for you guys.
Means dr. Cuddy'sgot no idea why your
daughter's lung suddenly popped like a balloon.
You think you do?
Give me her chart.
And my pills.
Santa needs us.
Did you get thatlooked at?
- I'm fine.
- Great.
I just admitted a cartilagehair hypoplasia dwarf.
- 15 years old--
- what are you gonna do?
I thought I'd getyour theories,mock them,
then embrace my own.The usual.
Wilson told us he ratted.
Your choice of verb,I take it.
It's appropriate.He betrayed you.
And you shouldtake the deal.
Unexplained lung collapseand anemia.
Cuddy thinksit's idiopathic.
"Cuddy" and "idiop" beingthe relevant partsof that sentence.
Well, I'd say tb, but cuddy'salready ruled it out.
Then you'd be just as bigan "idiop" as her.
Don't you peopleknow your dwarves?
There are over 200varieties of dwarfism,
each with differentmedical complications.
You can't expect us to beintimately
familiarwith all of them.
- The sick dwarvessure expect you to.
- Cartilage hairhypoplasia.
- They have compromisesimmune systems.
- Gold star for cameron.
For extra credit,explain to the special needssection the class
why our patient's negativetb test is irrelevant.
A pdd involves plantinga fragment of tb under the skin
to see if the immunesystem recognizes it.
Because of a compromisedimmune system,
our patient could have tbbut not recognize it.
The little peoplelove you.
Let's go see a dwarfabout a gallium scan.
Gallium isa radioactive isotope.
It travelsthrough your veinsallowing us to seeany bright spotsthat mightindicate infection.
I'm 4'1".
That's 1.5 canesin metric.
You don't look a dayover four feet.
- I saw in the file thather dad was normal-sized.
- It's average-sized.
Compared to you,I'm sure it was huge.
So did he have a fetish,or did he just
fall in lovewith your long-legged soul?
He grew up in the circus.
Said I reminded him of home.
Seems like you're the onewith the fetish.
I'm certainly curiousabout the logistics.
- Did you stand on a table?
- House.
- Pretty much he'd flatand spin me.
- Mom!
so, abigail,you want to hop upon the table for me?
- That's gonna be tough.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh, let me give youa boost.
stop treating herlike she's five.
Just bring over a stooland let her climb up herself.
Mom, it's okay.
I was just tryingto be helpful.
She also hates jews.
I've dealt with worse.Being different,
you getused to people's idiocy.
Still beats the hell outof actually being an idiot.
What?
Care to go for a spin?
What the hellwere you thinking?
You didn't thinkratting outthis hospital's
best doctor meritedchecking withyour boss first?
I didn't rat him out.
I got him a deal.
Which he'll never take.
- He will if we--
- how long have youknown house?
Did you think he'dsuddenly become reasonable?
I made the deal.
It's done.
You can either keepyelling at me,
or you can help meavoid a complete disaster.
It already is gonna bea complete disaster.
He's not gonna take the deal.
He's gonna go to jail.
Because he's a child.
He's too stubborn.
When a child misbehaves,what do you do?
You take awaysomething he loves.
We can't take awayhis vicodin.
Not only will he be in pain,
he'll start to detox.
We tell him the only wayto get
the pills backis to take the deal.
- He won't be ableto function.
- That's the point.
You gonna explain thatto his patient?
What choice do we have?
Gallium scan shows nobright spots of any kind.
Means it's not tbor any other infection.
There's no bright spotsbecause the whole thing'stoo bright.
Except for the liver.
The tech overexposedthe image a bit,but it's nothing.
- The liver looks fine.
- Could be lung cancer.
Tumor causesstructural damage.
Lung caves inon itself.Also explainsthe anemia.
Doesn't explain the liverproblem, though.
Her lung collapsed.
There is no liver problem.
You guys look at the liveron this thing?
- There's no liver problem.
- Seriously,look at the liver.
- There's nothing there.
- Why not?
Because there'snothing wrong.
Every organ in the scanis lit uplike a 100-watt bulb.
Except for her liver, whichis hovering around 60 watts.
And not one of them good60-watters,
but an energy--
you're saying her liver'sshutting down
because the lightingis off?
You just don't want a cancer diagnosis
because then you'd have to deal with wilson.
Lung cancer isa lame diagnosis.
Avoiding wilson isan added bonus.
House, we need to talk.
Not taking the deal.
Glad we talked.
Ultrasound her liver.
- Sit down.
- Stand up.
- Your turn.
- House, you're offthe case.
Your treatment privilegesare suspended
until you accepttritter's deal.
Well, I'm obviouslynot gonna take the deal
just so I can have the funof treating a dwarf.
So i assume there'smore to this threat.
- I'm also cutting offyour vicodin.
- That could work.
I'm taking over as attending.
Get an mri of her lungs.
This is not lung cancer.
We'll find out as soonas we mri her lungs.
You're gonna come begging meto save this girl
long before I comebegging your for pills.
I hope not.
For everyone's sake.
- this is wrong.
- Cutting house off?
Might not work,but it's not wrong.
Bone windows looks clean.
- Abigail, we need youto hold still, okay?
- can I come out?
Just hang in there two more minutes and we'll be done.
Okay.
Because it's effectivedoesn't make it right.
Cuddy's bending the rules to
get a patientto do the right thing.
- Who'd work for a doctorlike that?
- And the endsjustify the means?
If the ends involve uskeeping our jobs, sure.
Lung parenchyma is clean.
No masses.
It's not lung cancer.
Abigail, you okay?
House was right.
Her liver's failing.
Endoscopy confirmedthe vomiting
was cause byvariceal bleeding.
Bloodwork also confirmshouse's hypothesis--
I get it.House was right.
It's the liver.Let's move on.
What causes liver diseaseand a collapsed lung?
- Schistosomiasis,the parasite--
- there's no eosinophilia
- Cirrhosis could explain--
- could be a hepatoma.
She's 15.
It's not liver cancer.
It's not unheard of.
Cirrhosis fits better.
The question is,what caused it?
- Could be hepatitis,budd-chiari.
- Or drugs and alcohol.
If anyone has a reasonto dull the pain,
it's a teenage dwarf.
I'll do a liver biopsyto confirm.
I'll search the patient's homefor drugs and alcohol.
Cameron,you got a moment?
What exactly isyour problem with me?
Hepatoma isa weak diagnosis.
- So this isall about the case?
- What elsewould it be about?
I made this dealto help him.
And helped yourselfat the same time.
This is not my practice.
This is not about my car.
I gave both of them upto help house,
and I would've gone onwithout them
if hadn't almost maimedthat little girl
and if he hadn'tpunched out chase.
Was it an easy choice?
- Of course not,but it's right.
- Then why wasn't it easy?
Because he's my friend.
- It's obviously complicated.
- It's complicated?
When you decidedto talk to tritter,
your life gota million times better.
How do youseparate that out?
How do you pretendyour windfall
isn't relevantto this decision?
It was the right thingto do.
You pretendingyour motives are pureis why I have a problem.
- Where's cuddy?
- In this drawer.It's a rescue mission.
But I got it under control.
You can leave.
You were rightabout the liver failure.
Patient hadvariceal bleeding
which suggestedcirrhosis, but--
off the clock.
You predicted this.
You obviously saw something.
Obviously.
Liver biopsy was negativefor cirrhosis.
But it showssclerosing cholangitis.
Even weirder,there's no increasein alkaline phosphatase.
Medical mystery.
Sounds like the kindof thing I'd be good at.
Breaking and entering.
Sounds like the kindof thing you'd be good at.
I take it that's where cuddy'sbeen keeping your pills.
One theory, one drawer.
Really?I thought you'd be all
for this "torture house plan".
It works,therefore it's good.
On the other hand, I don'twant to talk you
outof this deal by pointing outyour hypocrisy,
so patient's life at stake,blah, blah, blah, blah.
Forget aboutthe specific nature
of the liver dysfunction.It's irrelevant.
The dwarf's problem is global.
That's why the gallium scanwas bright.
And it's gonna spread throughout
her entire bodyunless you stop it.
If that were true,more than lungs and liverwould be affected.
They will be.It'll spread though the
biliary treeand hit her pancreas next.
Strop retracing your steps.
Get ahead of it.
Forget the liver and focuson the pancreas.
'Cause after that--actually, after that
doesn't really matterwhat it hits
because pretty much all roadslead to a dead dwarf.
I get why you don'twant to go to rehab.
But only an idiot goes toprison for being stubborn.
Only an idiot stands between
ahab and his whale.Move.
Sorry.
Santa's got gifts.
Olive oilwasn't in the kitchen.
It was inthe medicine cabinet.
Home remedyfor ear infections.
Ear infectionsare fairly typicalamong chh dwarfs.
Or it's a symptom.
Certainly wouldn't indicatea pancreatic problem.
Or house is wrongand it's a symptom.
Laxatives.I don't thinkthey were used
to maintainher girlish figure.
- Again, intestinal problemsare common--
- again, it might bea symptom.
And glucosamine suggestschronic joint pain--
who ordered the alpha-1antitrypsin deficiency test?
I did.
You think the problem'sin her pancreas?
Well, I think it will be.
I think we need toforget about the liver.
We just forgotabout the lungs.
Now we need to forgetabout the liver?
We need to stopretracing our steps
and get aheadof this thing.
House, you've tanned.
You don't think I could'vecome up with this?
Did you?
You suspended housebecause it'd be dangerous
having him in charge,but getting his opinion--
I'm sure he gave youthat opinionsimply
because he wasworried about the patient.
Just because house wants his pills
doesn't meanhis theory is wrong.
No, the test resultsmean that.
Your test was negative.
And the biopsy indicated severe duct inflammation.
Do an ercp to check the liverfor bile duct cancer.
Just because it wasn'talpha-1 doesn't meanthe pancreas isn't next.
you needed an organ.
He needed a fix.
He'd have made upany story for a pill.
You didn't give himanything, did you?
No.
There's no bruise or nothing,
but it really hurts.
Unfortunately, that painand lack of bruising.
Is typical ofa zygomatic break.
- That sounds bad.
- Hmm, bones arealigned properly.
Which er did you go toafter the car accident?
Princeton plainsboro.
Here's my discharge slip.
Okay.Gonna get you someacetaminophen with codeine.
I tried that,and it makes me nauseous.
Uh, there's a drugcalled gabapentin
which is good for certainkinds of pains.
Great, 'cause I haven'tslept in days.
Gabapentin's not reallygonna help with the sleep.
Is there something elseyou can give me?
Uh, vicodin's your best betwith sleep issues.
Thanks so much.
Unfortunately,our policy forbids
prescribing opiates to new patients.
How can a clinic have a ruleagainst relieving pain?
Just with opiates.
We find that it helpsweed out drug seekers.
- You think I'm a drug seeker?
- I'm not saying that.
- Well, thengive me the vicodin.
- I can'T.
- Because you thinkI'm a drug seeker.
- I just said I didn'T.
No, you said that the policywas to stop drug seeking.
Then you said I'm nota drug seeker.
Policy doesn't apply.
I'm sorry.
That's the policy.
Gabapentin workson nerve damage.
You're prescribing itfor a broken face.
Might as wellhand out band-aidsfor a severed carotid.
You're a doctor.
Not by thisclinic's definitionsince I'm neither a moronnor a mindless drone.
- Security.
- Forget it.I'll throw myself out.
That tube is goingall the way down to my liver?
Don't worry.
You'll be sedated.
Sometimes doctorshave to do things
that make peopleuncomfortable to help them.
But we always want torespect the patient's wishes
and not shove thingsdown their throats.
Foreman.
- You haven't given herthe sedative.
- No.
Abigail!
She's unconscious.
Check her airway.
Airway's clear.
Her breath smells fruity.
Diabetic ketoacidosis.
Hang an insult drip at.1 migs per kig per hour.
Pancreas is failing.
You ready to callhouse yet?
You were right.
The patient's pancreasis failing.
Told you you'd comebegging me for help.
Her insulin production
is almost non-existent--
- give me my pillsor lose an arm.
- The girl is dying.
- So give me my pills.
- Take the deal and I will.
You'd rather kill this girlthan give me my pills.
I would rather loseone patient now
than the dozens we will losewhile you're in prison.
Well, have funexplaining that
to her itsy-bitsygrieving mother.
what if we sacrifice this girl
and house still goes to jail?
I'd feel bad.
Can we get on with this?
House correctlypredicted the spread.
Means we've gota global systemic illness
affecting lungs, liver,and pancreas so far.Ideas.
Langerhanscell histiocytosisattacks multipleorgan systems.
Histiocytosis usuallystarts in the brain,
then moves to the internal organs.
Abigail's brain is fine.
Cystic fibrosis.
Exocrine function is normaL.
Hodgkins lymphoma.
It's a systemic cancer which her dwarfismpredisposes her to.
Do you have any ideasthat aren't cancer?
- Cancer fits.
- Autoimmune fits better.
We should treat herwith prednisone for lupus.
That'll spike her blood sugar and put her back in a coma.
It's much safer just to runa double-stranded dna test.
Not if she dies beforewe get the results.
One of you is probably right.
Why don't we hold the snipinguntil we find out which?
Wilson, do an lpfor lymphoma.
You guys, run an antibody testfor lupus.
Because ofyour daughter's dwarfism,we've had to
picka higher entry pointfor the lumbar puncture,
- which increases the risk.
- So why not dothe lupus test first?
In the interest of time,we think it's bestto proceed on both fronts.
You have no idea what'swrong with my daughter.
- We have several theories.
- What does dr. House think?
He's--he had to go home sick.
My daughter may be dying,
and he's gone homewith the sniffles?
He's not--he was the only onewho seemed
to have any ideawhat was wrong with her.
He better bereally damn sick.
He is.
unless you got vicodin, go away.
House, it's me.
I, uh--
oh, god.
- I don't have--
- no pills, no egg nog.
What happened to your arm?
Cut myself.
Wilson was wrongabout lymphoma.
Kid's not losing any weight,no night sweats.
Cuddy send you?
No, she doesn't trust menot to give you pills.
Is she right?
House, these cutsare straight in a row.
You did this on purpose.
Cutting releasesendorphins.
Endorphins relieve pain.
You gonna get mesome pills?
- No.
- Then you can leave.
No constitutionalsymptoms means--
soons the kid gets cured,
cuddy's got no pressure to fold.
You really thinkshe's gonna fold?
Autoimmune fits betterthan cancer.
But lupus loves kidneys,
usually attacks them first.
- Kidneys are fine, right?
- Yeah.
House, take the deal.
You can survivewithout vicodin.
After you were shot,you stayed clean for months.
Yeah, I wonder if it had
something to dowith the absence of pain.
Leave that.I want to be able to
pour alcohol on itso I can distract myself.
Then you canrip off the bandage.
Kid been sick lately?
There's a historyof ear infections.
Say abigail's immune systemis like a shy guy in a bar.
And the ear infections,they come in and tryto coax him to--heh.
To hell with the metaphor.
You get the point, right?
Nerd gets drunk.
Trashes the bar.
One of the autoimmunestriggered by a minor infection.
Factor in her age,elevated sed-rate, anemia...
it's still's disease.
You start her on prednisone,
methotrexate, cyclosporin.
House.Stop this.Please.
- What'd he say?
- Still's disease.
- It's chronic, but manageable.
- A diagnosis that'svirtually unconfirmable.
And with a treatmentthat's more dangerous
than what we wereconsidering for lupus.
How bad is he?
Are you askingbecause you care,
or because you're wonderingwhether to trust his opinion?
Both.
He's detoxing.
In agony.
He startedcutting himself.
But he's still house.
I'll order the treatment.
Your plan isn't working.
Two days down,one to go.
Figured I'd show youhow much it isn't working.
Yeah, clearly the drugshave no hold on you.
We both know that my pridefar surpasses my instinctfor self-preservation.
You want to redeem yourself?
Give up now.
And you'll go to jail.
- I've done nothing wrong.
- And you'll go to jail.
Which makes thisyour last chanceto do me
a kindness beforeruining my life forever.
The nausea's bad this time.
You can write me a scrip for metoclopramide
so I can stop puking.
They'd give me thatin rehab.
Then you shouldgo to rehab.
I have a patient.
I'm so sorryfor your loss.
I know it's little solace,but he went without pain.
House.
Well, look onthe bright side.
At least you don't have to
go by mrs. Zebalusky anymore.
- That's gotta be a relief.
- You know this man?
I'm sorry.
He's sick--
did you hear my diagnosison the dwarf?Still's disease.
Did you even consider those ear infections,
or you just wrote it offas a dwarf thing?
You sure he's dead?
Dr. Wilson sometimesmisses things.
Trying to embarrass mein front of grieving widowcrosses lines--
right!I'm pathetic.
I'm strung out,I haven't slept,
puking every hour,and I still out-diagnosed you.
But I'm supposed to letyou decide what's best--
please!Please leave.
Sorry.
I'm done.
House.
You didn't come in herejust to embarrass me.
You could do that any time.
Stealing oxyfrom a dead man.
Yeah, you don'thave a problem.
- How's the girl?
- Much better.
- House was righT.
- It happens.
I thought we couldhandle this.
Still's diseasenever crossed my mind.
Don't beat yourself up.
I didn't get it either.
I feel likea mob informant.
You wanna go inside?
- Got a cafeteriain there, right?
- I can't testify.
Drug addicts hurt the people
around them with their habit.
House has hurt plentyof people, you included.
He saves lives.
People thatno one else can save.
And no matter how muchof an ass he is,
statistically houseis a positive forcein the universe.
The pills let him do that.
Vicodin does notmake house a genius.
Whatever he does on the pills,he can do off.
He's just notwilling to try.
I won't testifyagainst him.
Then we'll subpoena you.
And your previous statementwill be read into evidence.
And you will be chargedwith interfering
with an investigation.
And you will go to jail.
- Again, statistically,better me than him.
- Statistically...
the two of youwill be in jail.
dr. Cameron!Dr. Cameron,come quick.
There's something wrong with abby.
Couldn't be too severe.
Her cardiac alarmdidn't go off.
It's not her heart.
She's bleeding.
Picking up a scrip.
Under zebalusky.
This is, uh,dr. Wilson's patient.
Yeah.
Wilson's busy right now.
What with mr. Zebaluskydying in agony
on account of hismetastic lung cancer
and not having the pillsto relieve that agony
because of somemoron pharmacist.
Sign the book.
Bleeding wasn't a rupturedeardrum,
ear infection,or bleeding disorder.
Her heart rate's climbing.Blood pressure's dropping.
She's on the vergeof a multi-system failure.
Head ct was clean.
Means it's nota neurological problem.
- Basically we have nothing.
- Cancer is stillon the table.
Spinal fluid wasnegative for lymphoma.
- What other--
- leukemia.We need to doa bone marrow biopsy.
None of the blood testssuggest leukemia.
Cancer doesn't explainthe collapsed lung.
Unless a small clot lead to a pulmonary infarct.
It's a long shot.
Autoimmune is way more likely.
Autoimmune diseasesrespond to steroids,
which we've given her.
And she got betterfor a while.
We stoed the treatmenttoo soon.
Because she crashed.
All we're doing is bouncingback and forthbetween cancerand autoimmune.
We're going in circles.
Give me half an hour.
Can I have a french fry?
- Get your own.
- You took the last ones.
- What's wrong with you?
- I got spinalmuscular atrophy.
Guess it not contagious.
Nice bear.
- It's a dog.
- house.It's not still'S.
Steroids helpeduntil the patient
started bleedingfrom the ears and mouth.
- That's a bear.
- His name is bill.He's a dog.
You win.
You can have vicodin.
Words have set meaningsfor a reason.
If you seean animal like billand you tryto play fetch,
bill's gonna eat youbecause bill's a bear.
Are you on something?
You got your handson pain meds.
Bill has fur,four legs, and a collar.
He's a dog.
It's between cancerand autoimmune.
See, that's what we calla faulty syllogism.
Just because you call bill a dog
doesn't mean that he is...a dog.
We gotta x-rayour patient's leg.
- Her leg looks fine.
- Weird, huh?
- Why aren't you detoxing?
- Will power.
What--what--
normal's not normalif you're not normal.
- Did you just take a pill?
- No.
So how does a dwarfhave completely
normal growth plates?
It's impossible.
We must bemissing something.
How many pillshave you taken?
Not nearly as manyas I'm gonna take.
Forgotten how deliciousthey werE.
I didn't give themto him.
Can we forget my vices,get back to my virtues?
We were missing the fact that just because
we called her a dwarfdoesn't mean she is a dwarf.
Everyone assumed she wasbecause of her mother.
There's not testfor chh dwarfism.
So she lost an identity,but we gained a symptom.
If she doesn't haveskeletal dwarfism,
then her short staturemust be caused
by growth hormone deficiency.
And something's wrong with her pituitary gland.
And based on her size,it's been wrong for a while.
So what connects a long-termpituitary issue
with problems in the lungs, liver, and pancreas?
Oh, you guysand your bickering.
Cancer versus autoimmune.
- Obviously you thinkit's something else.
- Nope.I think it's both.
Langerhans cellhistiocytosis.
Also known as,"you got your cancerin my autoimmune" disease.
The immune component respondedto the still's treatment.
Lead to the short-termimprovement.The cancer portion didn'T.
We dismissed this earlier
because there wereno neurological symptoms.
Yeah.It's not your fault.
The only neurological symptomwas her height.
Who could've noticed?
This isyour pituitary gland.
And this is the granulomathat's been crushing it.
No pituitary equalsno growth hormoneequals about that much.
She's not a dwarf?
Just hormonally challenged.
- What about my mom?
- Your mom'sthe real deal.
But you're justa tiny little poser.
Your recent ear infections caused your bodyto release
a cascade of the same cellsthat made the granuloma.
They attacked your lungs,moved down to your liver,
then hitched a rideover to your pancreas.
We can nuke themwith a mild course of chemo
and then removethe granuloma.
And then what?
What will happen to her then?
Let me seeif I can make this clear.
This pill represents...a pill.
And my mouth representsyour daughter's mouth.
We deposit the pillin the month.
You may never be tall enoughto play in the wnba,
but you'll be ableto post up your mom no problem.
What if I don'ttake the pills?
What if you remove the thing in my headand give me the chemo,but not the pills?
Would I stillget better?
Your body needsgrowth hormonefrom lots of things.
Like...to grow.
I like who i am now.
- Nobody your agelikes who they are now.
- I do.
You like needing helpwhen you want somethingoff a high shelf?
Not being able to pressan elevator buttonabove the eighth floor?
Having to smell assevery time you stand in line?
You don't need growth hormone.
It's just your ticketout of the freak show.
Can't you delivera diagnosiswithout
making her feel thather life isn't worth living?
I'm trying to help her.
You're tryingto make her taller.
Not too tall.
Just tall enoughto wipe her own butt.
- Are you high?
- Higher than you.
If my daughterdoesn't want to choosethe easy path,I won't force her to.
Then you're a lousy mom.
You want your daughterto be a freak.
- We're not freaks.
- You want herto overcome adversity.
- Yes.
- Then why stop at height?
Poke a stick in her eye.
Imagine how interestingshe'll be then.
Being little is notthe same as--
you and I have found out that
being normal sucks'cause we're freaks.
The advantage of being a freakis it makes your stronger.
Now, how strong do you reallywant her to have to be?
Tell her what youhave to tell her.
Tell her you lied.
Even if you didn'T.
This is who you weresupposed to be.
You hate normal.
It's not that simple.
If I grow, I'll fadeinto the background.
I'll be boring.
We'll get you a funny hat.
You could never be boring.
You want me to belike everybody else?
I want you to havewhat I can'T.
Abigail agreed--abigail agreed to takegrowth hormone.
- Who's abigail?
- your non-dwarfdwarf patient.
Oh, good.
Then the growth hormonemakes sense.
- Christmas eve.
- Yeah, I know.
Deal expires tomorrow.
You have plansfor tonight?
You worried I'm gonna bepopping more pills?
Thought you might preferpeople over pills.
Hey, mom.I guess you guys are
already up at aunt sarah'S.
I'm sure dad'sin the egg nogand you're probably
suffering throughanother dried out turkey.
Just wanted to saymerry christmas.
house?Are you okay?
I tried calling three times.
Larry Zebalusky. Dr. James Wilson.
Take as needed.not to exceed 4 per day.OXYCODONE
I'm ready to takethe deal.
Well, that's off the table.
The clock doesn'texpire until--
got new evidence.
We don't needwilson anymore.
The thing about addictsis, uh...
no matterhow smart they are,
they are dumbwhen it comes to drugs.
So, uh, I've been keepingan eye on the pharmacy log.
Seems some patient of wilson's named zebalusky
managed to pick uphis oxy prescriptionafter he died.
Jesus walks, huh?
*So have yourself a merry little christmas now*
merry christmas.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-colleen3684
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
House
Season 3 Episode 10