Yo, yo!
Turn that back on.
What the hell, Garcia?
Put it back on!
Don't look at me,
'cause you know I didn't do it.
All right?
Don't look at me.
Hey, you better have put
fresh batteries
in that thing,
like I told you.
I did, Sarge, right when you--
when you gave it to me, I-I did.
I put 'em in.
Well, then, hit it
or something.
Otherwise, y'all are gonna
have to listen to me sing!
Here.
All right, don't panic.
Don't shoot us,
and don't die.
You got it, G?
Up and at 'em.
You're supposed to be
in clinic duty.
Yeah, like I can
sleep down there
with all the crying
and coughing.
Here.
Ex-Marine.
Thinks he has
Gulf War Syndrome.
There's no such thing.
So he's been told.
It hasn't stopped
the unexplained fatigue, rashes,
and joint pain.
And just so you know,
he's the nephew
of a benefactor
I owe a favor,
so you're gonna take this case
whether you like it or not.
Why wouldn't I want
to take the case?
The guy's tired and sore.
It's gonna be chapter one
in my--
Don't panic.
Don't shoot us,
and don't die.
You know him?
Never met him before
in my life.
Okay, well,
you're about to.
He's on his way here.
Get your ass up
and get your team together.
You have work to do.
www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@MAOREN Sync:FRM@??·?
That's amazing.
No, it's not.
It's not?
I can play the harmonica
with my nose,
make a penny come out
of a child's ear--
or any other orifice,
for that matter--
and, given the right
circumstances,
can bring two women
to simultaneous ecstasy.
The right circumstances be
their agreement to bill youyoon the
And what I absolutely
cannot do
is dream about someone
I've never seen before.
Well, just because
you don't understand it
doesn't mean
it can't happen.
True...
it can't happen
because it can't happen!
Well, maybe you didn't
dream about this guy
specifically.
Right, just some other guy
who looks exactly like him.
No, you imagined
some generic Marine,
then you placed his face
in the dream
after you saw the picture.
Sort of a coincidence
mixed with a little d?j?vu.
There's no record of him
ever coming into the clinic.
So I must have seen him before
somewhere else.
Fine, you've known him
since Cub Scouts.
A more interesting question
isn't what you dreamed, but why?
I'm guessing
you're longing for either
a renewed relationship
with your dad...
or a new relationship
with one of the Village Peop
He wasthe Navy,
not the Marines.
I thought your dad
was in the Marines.
The guy
in the Village People.
Actually, he's only in the Navy
when they sing In the Navy.
The rest of the time,
he's just in generic fatigues.
What?
You brought it up.
You didn't flush.
I didn't pee.
Male. 34.
Just got out of the Marines
after two years in Iraq.
Admitted complaining
of chronic fatigue,
joint pains,
intermittent rashes,
and sore throats.
Thinks he has
Gulf War Syndrome.
Why is he here
instead of the VA?
Because he has a rich uncle
Cuddy's
trying to avoid fellating
who doesn't buy
the VA's diagnosis
of "nothing's wrongatosis."
The VA's right.
There's no such thing
as Gulf War Syndrome,
especially in veterans who've
never served in the Gulf War.
Different war, same place.
Whatever was tern 1990
is still there.
What's there can
send you home in a pine box,
but it can't get you sick three
months after you've gotten home.
What, so thousands of soldiers
are lying about their symptoms?
You send 700,000 people
on vacation to Hawaii,
some are gonna come back sick.
Doesn't mean it was
caused by snorkeling.
He's right.
The studies all show
the same pattern of symptoms
in veterans who were sent to
the Gulf and those who weren't.
That's it?
You believe her but not me?
Stick to your guns, Chase.
Just 'cause there isn't
a sing unifying symptom
doesn't mean there isn't
something going on.
It could just affect
everyone differently.
You think this guy has
Gulf War Syndrome?
'Course not.
He's depressed, and he's looking
for a disability check.
Most likely because
he's just realized
that knowing how to
barter for sex in six languages
and open a beer bottle
with your eye socket
are not the most
marketable skills.
Why'd you take this case?
Because a good scientistTA
continually questions
his own theories
and assumptionsu
Cuddy's making him.
Now I'm making you.
Do a full physical.
Recheck his blood
for HIV, Hep C, malaria,
schistosomiasis,
and "T strain" A. baumannii
just to make sure
the VA's dotted their Is.
And find out every hospital
and clinic he's ever visited,
every city
he's ever lived in, and...
whether he's ever been
on TV.
TV?
Problem
could be neurological.
Everyone knows
TV rots your brain.
It's usually the worst
on my palms
and the bottoms of my feet.
I get these
black dots all over.
I don't see anything.
It comes and goes.
You sure it's not
just scrapes and bruises?
I know the difference
between a rash and a bruise.
Sometimes it's harder
than you realize
to distinguish
between the two.
You obviously exercise.
My problems aren't caused
by my workouts.
But you do work out,
and by the look of you,
pretty strenuously.
That's not usually
the case with patients
whose principal complaint is
chronic fatigue and joint pain.
I was in the Marines
for 12 years.
I'm used to doing PT
every day.
Just because I can push
through the pain
doesn't mean it's not there.
Listen, we're not saying
we don't believe you.
The hell you aren't.
We just need to be specific
about what exactly
the problems are.
I sleep ten hours a night,
but I feel tired all the time.
I constantly get coughs,
rashes, sore throats.
My knees and hips feel like
someone poured sand
in my joints.
I get these weird tingling
sensations in my legs.
Sometimes, they're cold.
Other times,
feels like my blood is boiling.
Specific enough?
Look, I don't care
what you guys call it--
Gulf War Syndrome,
Iraq Fever,
or jusorCrappy Sickness X.
I just want someone
to figure out what it is
so they can cure it.
Except for the supposed
pain in his joints,
none of the other symptoms
he's complaining about
are currently evident.
Besides low potassium
probably caused
by him over hydrating
after working out,
his blood work's
all normal.
Low potassium could also
probably be caused
by the experiments
or vaccines
in anti-chemical
warfare pills
he was given before
he deployed to Iraq.
Not to mention the fact
that whole country's littered
with hundreds of tons
of radioactive shrapnel
from depleted
uranium munitions.
Did you go to medical school
in France?
There's no trace of uranium
in his urine.
And he was given the vaccines
and meds two years ago
without any allergic
or adverse reaction.
Has he ever done
any modeling?
We forgot to ask.
We should send his urine
to the University of Leicester.
There's a professor there
who's developed
a more advanced screening
technique for uranium.
If the levels are too low
for us to detect,
they're way too low
to cause any damage.
Where you goin'?
This way.
Did you find out about
any television
or other media exposure?
Do you really care?
Or are you just trying
to waste hospital resources
to get back at Cuddy
for making you take the case?
Of course I care.
What a horrible thing
to say.
Do a LexisNexis search.
Get a copy of his credit report.
Before or after
we tell him to eat a banana
and discharge him
with a psych referral?
I say before.
And I say in-between,
give him a polysomnogram.
Sleep apnea can cause
chronic fatigue and paranoia.
Find out where he went
to summer camp.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's just
a little too much coffee
this morning.
Were we...
walking you to the bathroom?
I wish.
Wilson was just in there.
These guys know
what I'm talking about.
That's his third REM cycle,
and his breathing's
completely normal.
There's obviously nothing
wrong with his sleep pattern.
If it's not uranium,
it's gotta be some other
sort of toxin.
Or nothing at all.
You really think
there's something wrong,
or do you just want
Foreman to be wrong?
Bo.
Well, it's not
his sleep pattern.
If you really think
it's a toxin,
you can do a liver biopsy
in the morning.
We can't leave.
If we don't monitor
the whole test,
House won't accept
thresults.
He'll just make us
do it over.
It doesn't take two doctors
to monitor
what's clearly gonna be
a normal polysomnogram.
Oh, so you want me
to stay?
You're the one who thought
there was something wrong.
I never said it was
a sleep disorder.
You wanna flip for it?
Just go.
Oh, come on.
Don't be a baby.
Fine.
I'll stay.
You know what we could do.
Here?
Why not?
We're surrounded by
empty rooms with beds in them.
Yeah, and video cameras
too.
So we turn 'em off.
That's all I need is House
or Foreman walking in on us.
We have the keys.
No.
What if he wakes up?
All right.
Suit yourself.
Damn it!
Hello?
Is anybody out there?
I think there's
a problem in here!
What's wrong?
u mean, what's wrong?
You don't smell that?
Nothing smells, John.
Are you kidding me?
It's disgusting.
How long have you thought--
Wait.
Open your mouth.
Smell's not in the room.
It's in your mouth.
What's going on?
What?
You were wrong about
the "nothing's wrongatosis."
You can fake fatigue
and joint paint,
but you can't fake bacterial
vaginosis in your mouth.
Where's his mouth been?
Says he hasn't performed
oral sex on anyone
in over a year.
Selfish bastard.
Because he hasn't been
with anyone
since his last girlfriend
dumped him
and after he deployed
to Iraq the second time.
Selfish bitch!
We've ruled out HIV,
diabetes,
and any other
endocrine abnormality.
Could be autoimmune; Sjoegren's
decreases salivary flow,
creates a hospitable home
for bacteria.
No, his eyes
and tear ducts are fine.
Who was his last
girlfriend?
Yeah, we'll...
get right on that.
Chronic fatigue,
joint pain,
and opportunistic infection
spells cancer.
Probably lymphoma.
We should biopsy his tonsillar
and submandibular lymph nodes.
Right about cancer.
Wrong about lymphoma.
Unless you're simply
hiding the fact
that his lymph nodes
are swollen.
Get Wilson to biopsy
his salivary glands.
He's got parotid cancer.
And see if you can
get to the truth
about who he's been dating.
No way a Marine goes aear
without getting some blood
on his bayonet.
It's not an STD.
You just said--
Just do it.
The antibiotics
should at least
relieve the infection,
also reduce the odor
and taste in your mouth.
Not soon enough.
All right.
You're gonna feel
a little burn.
You know,
I never even dipped.
Chewing tobacco.
Practically everyone
in my unit did but me.
I was so paranoid
about cancer.
Well, if it's parotid
cancer,
it's very treatable
if diagnosed early.
My mom had cancer.
Which is why I know
that diagnosing cancer early
means before there's
any serious symptoms.
Certainly tastes like a pretty
serious symptom, you know?
We'll know more
after the test.
If he was just trying
to mess with Cuddy
for wasting his time,
,this would have stopped
as soon as the patient started
exhibiting actual symptoms.
So the question is,
why is he wasting our time?
Or is he wasting
our time?
You think
he's got a medical reason
for asking for the guy's
credit report?
I don't.
Where were you two
when the guy woke up?
Uh, we just--
stepped out for a second.
To do what?
To...get a coffee.
We'd been up
most of the night.
He's just pushing to make sure
we have a complete history.
Obviously,
we're missing something,
or we'd have the answer.
You didn't have any coffee
when you came back.
All right, already.
We confess cu caught us.
We snuck into one of the
sleep lab rooms to have sex.
We shouldn't have done it while
we were supposed to be working,
and we're sorry.
Now can we move on?
House'll do Wilson
before you do Chase.
No, you would do House
and Wilson
before I do Chase.
Now can we get back
to work?
She did me once.
She was stoned!
Biopsy's inconclusive.
I'm gonna do a sialogram
27ile we wait
for the results
from the additional blood work.
No hurry.
Probably nothing
we can do at this point anyway.
As long as the cancer
hasn't spread.
He's spitting stink.
You should focus
on the living.
I need a prescription.
I just wrote you
a prescription.
For Vicodin.
I need alfuzosin.
No, you don't.
Have you figured out
where you met your Marine?
What?
Oh, that.
Haven't really
thought about it.
I can't pee.
You can't remember him,
can you?
I can't pee.
So stop taking the Vicodin.
I wanna pee and
not be in pain.
Why don't you go to sleep?
I don't pee
when I'm asleep.
Maybe you'll dream
about him again.
Maybe he'll give you
an address.
I haven't peed
in three days.
I read that REM sleep
is the brain's way
of working out problems.
Very useful.
Did you hear what I just said?
Yeah, you lied
because you want to avoid
talking about your obsession.
I'm not obsessing.
Why don't you
just ask him?
I haven't peed
in three days!
You'd be dead.
I'm not counting
intermittent drips.
You'd be in agony.
I passed agony yesterday
around 4:00.
His mother, brother,
uncle, and best friend
all confirm he hasn't
had a date in over a year.
Which means
it not an STD.
If you come up with something
medically relevant, page me.
What did you want me
to tell him, the truth?
No. You didn't have
to be so convincing.
Don't worry.
I'll make it up to you.
This is getting
out of control.
Don't pout.
Our patient woke up
with an infection
while we were getting
our ros off.
Do you want to stop?
No.
But, uh, I don't want
to get caught either.
You think I do?
You certainly
didn't go out of your way
to keep the volume down
when we were in the sleep lab.
I couldn't help that.
Why would I
wanna get caught?
Maybe you wanna give House
a reason to be jealous.
I'm over House.
All this is
is uncomplicated sex.
Don't try to make it
more than that.
I'm not doing it
at work anymore.
Fine.
Wanna go grab some lunch?
I think the in
is the way to go.
We haven't had a condom
break t, thank God,
but it's bound to happen.
Especially the way
we've been doing it.
On a bed of nails?
No. He's not kinky.
He's just...
insatiable.
I can barely make it to any
of my morning classes.
You smoke?
No way.
Stop it!
Sorry.
Any history of hypertension,
blood clots, strokes?
Nope. Besides my OCD,
I'm fit as a fiddle.
You have OCD?
Duh. Can't you tell?
Any other compulsions
besides drinking
massive amounts of water?
No, that's it,
thank God.
My therapist says
it could be a lot worse.
You get up in the middle
of the night to drink?
Yeah, every couple
of hours.
Well, then your therapist
is an idiot.
Unconscious people
don't have OCD.
They can, however,
have diabetes insipidus.
That's impossible.
I eat candy all the time.
Different kind
of diabetes.
This kind is caused
by a banged-up pituitary.
You're obviously more
of a lover than a fighter.
I'm guessing either
a car accident
or...you cracked your skull
on the bal tce beam.
How'd you know?
Easy.
Nice ass, no boo,
You got palms
like a longshoreman.
Wait here.
You need a CAT scan.
Oh, my God.
Don't worry,
just means you'll be taking
two hormone supplements
d of one.
Okay, this time you're
gonna feel a little pressure.
We're injecting
the contrast material.
Could you turn up
the music?
Sure.
Looks pretty good
so far.
Still can't hear it
that well.
Can you hear it now?
John?
John!
John, can you hear me?
Still no...relief?
I got relief.
Just got no pee.
If the pills didn't work,
you may need a catheter.
You didn't come here
to talk to me about my pee.
What's going on?
He's got cancer,
all right.
But it's not
in his salivary glands.
It's in his brain.
And it's bad.
At least six tumors,
maybe more.
He lost his hearing.
His sight's
probably next.
Death is probably next.
No way he could have
grown all these in a week.
They can't be older.
The VA couldn't
have missed all these.
Maybe they didn't miss them,
just mixed 'em up.
Switched his films with
another patient's by mistake.
Maybe.
But it means some poor sap's
getting his melon sliced
at the VA for no reason.
And this poor sergeant's
gonna be dead
by the end of the week.
Where have you two been?
Lunch.
Why, what happened?
Wilson's found
some fast-growing,
elusive, or magic
brain tumors.
What'd you find?
Nothing.
He's telling the truth.
About what?
About everything.
Where he's lived,
who he's dated.
Besides forgetting to mention
his dad's shin splits,
his granddad's nose bleeds
and to return
a few rented DVDs,
everything he's told us
has checked out.
You have them
researching your dream?
No. I have them
researching my patient.
You had a dream
about a patient?
This poor guy's brain
is riddled with tumors,
and you're checking
his credit report?
Come on.
I need you guys.
Where are you going?
To do my job.
He's not your patient.
He is now.
Go home and go to sleep.
Maybe you'll dream the cure
to late-stage brain cancer.
How is he?
He's dead.
Oh...God.
At least, he will be
in a few days.
The question is why?
The only explanation is that
the VA hospital screwed up.
There was definitely
no mix-up.
I hathem recheck.
Yes.
Why would
a government agency
lie to cover up a mistake
that might have ht hed
the death of a guy
they'd been trying to kill
for the last two years anyway?
They didn't lie.
Did you just take
two Vicodin?
No. It was an antidepressant.
I was told to take two
every time
you walked into the room.
The VA scan
of his brain.
No tumors.
Yes, this is proof positive
that someone
didn't have tumors
in their brain.
You see that bright spot
below his left orbit?
That is a titanium pin
your patient had inserted
20 years ago.
Unless you think the VA
happened to
mix up his scans with someone
who had the exact same pin,
they didn't screw up.
You paged us?
Why didn't you send his urine
to Leicester like I told you?
Because
you told me not to.
Why did you choose that moment
to listen to me?
You think depleted uranium
might have something to do
with his tumors?
Radiation's the only thing
GIat would make
tumors grow that fast.
High doses of radiation.
Even if he ate depleted uranium
bullets for breakfast,
he still would have been
exposed to less radiation
than we've given him
in the last two days.
Do it anyway.
And you,
call his uncle back.
Find out if he ever
brought his nephew
to any hospital parties
or fundraisers.
No. Not until
you give me a reason.
Because...I'm your boss.
A rational reason.
Or at least admit
that you don't have one.
I've got a full bladder,
and I'm not afraid to use it.
But you are, apparently,
afraid of discoverinscthing
you can't rationally
explain.
Shut up!
Do what you're told.
Cuddy and Wilson may not have
to listen to me, but you do.
What the hell
was that all about?
I don't care.
Which is why I didn't
feel the need
to ask him
eight personal questions.
I'm over him.
Just making
an observation.
All right, ready
whenever you are.
I'm ready.
Wait a minute.
Zoom in.
I don't see it.
You sure you got
the right coordinates?
Yeah, she's in
the right place.
Go 10 millimeters above
the AC-PC line on the Z access.
Ten mil above AC-PC on Z.
It's not there anymore.
Are you sure you got
the gantry angle right?
Yeah, I'm sure.
It's not there.
It disappeared.
Six tumors
don't just disappear.
Unless they were never
there to begin with.
The VA didn't screw up.
Maybe someone else did.
Maybe it was
Dr. Self-Righteous.
I saw the tumors.
There was no mix-up.
Maybe there's
something wrong
with the portable imager
in the O.R.
Something that would cause it
to show brain tissue
in perfect detail
but completely miss
neoplastic tissue?
Then they were never tumors
to begin with.
I told you, I saw--
I know, you saw something
that looked like tumors.
We all did.
We were all wrong.
Well, maybe
he doesn't have cancer.
Maybe he has a brain infection
that's causing
multiple abscesses.
That miraculously healed.
No, they were healed by the
antibiotics we're giving him
for the vaginosis
in his mouth.
If it's an infection, why didn't
it show up in his blood work?
I don't know. Yet.
Dr. Wilson,
we have a problem.
What did you do?!
I can't feel my legs!
I can't feel
my legs!
What'd you guys do?
John.
John, calm down.
We didn't even operate.
Could it be a residual
effect of--
I can't move my legs!
It's not the anesthesia.
John, John, we're gonna figure
out what's wrong with you.
First we need to know
one thing--
Have you ever appeared
in any pornos?
Chronic fatigue.
Sore throats.
Rashes.
Putrid discharge in the mouth.
Multiple abscesses
in the brain.
Hearing loss.
And last, but not least,
lower limb paralysis.
He's certainly given us
plenty of clues.
It's gotta be
some sort of infection.
That's miraculously
improving in his brain
but getting worse
in his ears and legs?
Could be an infection
and cancer.
Neoplastic Syndrome
could depress his immune system
and cause the other symptoms.
Mm-hmm.
You're basing this theory
on the negative biopsy,
the lymph nodes
that aren't swollen,
or the tumors that were
never there to begin with?
And what are you
gonna base your theory on--
his favorite restaurants?
I was right.
He's excreting depleted
uranium in his urine.
We should start him
on an IV infusion
of isotonic sodium
bicarbonate.
It's not depleted uranium.
You're the one--
Who asked for the test
when we were thinking cancer.
We no longer are.
Depleted uranium doesn't
just cause cells to mutate.
It can cause cell death
as well.
Not spinal cord cells.
At least, not until the dose
is high enough
to kill all his other
cells first.
So you're sayinghe radioactive
uranium in his urine
is irrelevant.
The sun's radioactive.
The earth
is radioactive.
This hospital is filled
with radiation.
The issue is not
where it is
but how much there is
and what damage
that amount could cause
in someone's spinal cord.
And as I already
stated quite clearly--
Got it.
We're all idiots.
What's your theory?
Gimme your keys.
Why?
You ever tried
riding a motorcycle
with a distended bladder?
Keep him on
antibiotics.
Check his hearing
and paralysis every hour.
So you basically
want us to do nothing.
No, I basically
wanna do nothing.
I want you to keep him
on antibiotics
and check his hearing
and paralysis every hour.
Wait, you can't
go home now.
Actually,
I have to go home now.
It's two days
past my bedtime.
House, he needs your help.
And I need sleep.
Hey, it's the brain's way
of working out problems
that the conscious mind can't
solve during the day, remember?
No. Nothing.
I'm gonna die, aren't I?
No, we're not.
We should start treatment
for the uranium toxicity
like you said.
But House--
Isn't here.
If House wanted to be
involved in the case--
If he wanted us to start
this treatment,
he would have told us to do it
the last time you brought it up.
You have a better idea?
No.
Then we're going
with Chase's.
Tell him not to get
the lines tangled.
The infusion is slow.
We can't have
any kinks in the line.
I went to medical school too.
Keep your arms on your body,
above your heart.
I can't feel mt stomach!
I don't feel that.
I don't feel anything!
Paralysis is ascending.
If it keeps going, we're gonna
need a respirator.
What?
What are you saying?
Can you breathe?
No.
Not yet.
--accident on the Garden
State Parkway southbound
at exit 91...
So, where were we?
You have
a nice night?
No.
The paralysis
is ascending.
The last check, it was
nearly to his diaphragm.
Tells us something.
Means it's getting worse.
Worse is something.
Also tells us
it's not the uranium.
Did we think it was?
We started him
on sodium bicarb
to try to flush the uranium
out of his system.
Great. Now the fact that he's
getting worse tells us nothing.
Never thought it was
uranium.
For all we know, the uranium
treatment is what's making him--
A sodium bicarb infusion
wouldn't have any effect on--
On what?
Kind of hard to say what
it wouldn't have an effect on
if you've no idea
what's there to affect.
We had to do
something.
Well, next time...
go with something
that has a chance of working.
Like what?
You come up with
some brilliant idea
while you're warm and cozy
in your bed at home?
We need more information.
How much more information
could you possibly want?
We have a medical history
going all the way back
to his great-grandparents.
A non-medical history going--
It's not enough.
It's all
we're gonna get.
Wanna bet?
Who approved
a sodium bicarb infusion?
Don't look at me.
I was home in bed.
What's wrong?
He's unconscious.
His skin has lost
all color,
and his BP and hematocrit
are plunging.
He was only on
the sodium bicarb--
He's bleeding out.
He can't be bleeding out.
There's no blood
in the bed.
Fine, he's bleeding in.
There's no sign of bruising
or internal hemorrhaging.
Paralysis must have
reached his diaphragm.
He's not able
to oxygenate his blood.
He's not able to oxygenate
his blood
because he doesn't
have any left.
There's no evidence--
It's the only thing
that would explain--
There's no reason
for blood loss.
There has to be a reason.
He needs a transfusion.
Get me 4 units of O negative.
Stat!
Let's elevate his feet.
He doesn't need
a transfusion.
Nobody asked you.
In fact,
why are you even here?
Because, obviously,
you need my help.
Get out.
House, his blood
obviously didn't
just vanish into--
What the hell is this?
Somebody must have spilled
something.
Somebody else should be
getting me 4 units...
What the hell is that?
It's a urine catheter
collection bag
with a rip in it--
what the hell does it look like?
What?
It's just urine.
It's sterile.
No one's getting me blood.
Why isn't anybody
getting me blood?
You're bleeding.
House, are you all right?
Why are you even here?
I'm always here.
No, you're not.
There's a reason.
There has to be.
--incident on
the Garden State Parkway...
So.
Where were we?
You have a nice night?
Yes, I did, thank you.
I'm guessing
better than our tient,
probably due to his BP
and hematocrit plunging.
How'd you know?
The answer was staring
right at us the whole time,
as plain as the nose
on our faces.
Or the nose
on his face.
What's going on?
What'd he say?
No hairs,
and cauterization scars.
Which means?
He had it cauterized.
How could you know that?
Just makes sense.
Undoubtedly done to stop
the same childhood
nosebleeds
that plagued
his grandfather.
Undoubtedly, because
they were both born
with Hereditary Hemorrhagic
Telangiectasia.
What's he saying?
I'm saying you've got
a genetic disease
that's destroying
your capillaries.
That no one in his family's
ever been diagnosed
with before?
Not surprising, since the most
common initial symptoms--
skin rashes and nose bleeds--
are often written off
as the result
or minor trauma
or dry weather.
But they can also be
the result
of his arteries and veins
merging together.
He obviously has AVMs.
AVM near the spine
caused the paralysis.
AVM in his lungs prevented
his blood from being filtered.
Dirty blood
caused the joint pain,
fatigue, and the infections
in his mouth and brain.
Nothing that a few surgeries
won't clear up.
Get MR angiograms
of the aforementioned.
The Marines
weren't hiding anything.g.
He was.
Or at least
he forgot to mention
his bloody tissue issue.
What's going on?
What'd he say?
Oh, looks like
solving the case
solved your other problem.
There is no medicine
like happiness.
Except maybe laughter.
Or rubber tubes
shoved up your urethra.
You cathed yourself?
It's actually not that bad
after the first, I don't know,
nine or ten inches.
Cath relieved the spasm.
I'm as good as new.
Of course.
Just a minor spasm
in a muscle you've been using
multiple times a day
without any problem
for the past 45 years.
Not a major side effect
caused by the over-use
of a particular narcotic
pain killer.
Yeah, that was
my thought too.
So...
no reason to think about
cutting back on your use
of that particular pill.
Thank God.
Actually, it was a triple
dose of the good stuff
that allowed me
to finally get some sleep
and solve the case.
Pills made all my dreams
come true.
You really got the answer
in your sleep?
Got one in my sleep.
The other one
I got in the shower.
I've been thinking
about you.
You lied.
I didn't lie.
I simply chose not to share
completely irrelevant facts.
Like the fact
that you lied.
No wonder I couldn't
place his face.
You were practically swallowing
it on the dance floor.
I was not.
Talk about the cool uncle.
He donates the money, and
the nephew gets the write-off.
And, of course,
by write-off,
I mean he gets to put
your ankles--
This is exactly
why I didn't mention
our one date
over two years ago.
Because of my T-shirt.
Because you are
an obnoxious ass.
Because you would have
spent the whole time--
That's very smart.
'Cause this way,
I spent my whole time
completely focused
on the patient.
How did you even
remember him?
We were only at that party
for, like, ten minutes.
Is this some new
health plan?
You service
the Dean of Medicine,
and you get free health care
for a year?
Why are you smiling?
You remembered him
because he made out with me.
I'm good with faces.
So, this plan,
is it open to anyone?
Is there a co-pay?
You're lousy with faces.
Don't make this
about me.
This is your humiliation.
So how much for
private room coverage?
Get over me.
Gimme a break.
You hired me--
'Cause you're a good doctor
who couldn't get himself hired
at a blood bank,
so I got you cheap.
You gave me everything
I asked for,
because one night I gave you
everything you--
Stop staring at my ass
when you think I'm not looking,
showing up at restaurants
where I happen to be on a date,
and fantasizing about me
in the shower.
That ship sailed
long ago, House.
Get over it.
If you're still
referring to your ass,
I think
"that super-tanker sailed"
would be the more
precise metaphor.
Sorry.
I was looking
for an extra-large trash can.
Since when does he
clean anything up?
welcome to www.1000fr.com