Ladies and gentlemen,
step around, gather around.
Let me show you a way to make a little
easy money. Understand what I'm sayin'?
These are the blacks, don't follow them.
Follow the Queen... know why?
'Cause she's red, and that
means she is hot! Find the Queen.
The first of the day is free to play.
Who wants to play?
You look interested, my man.
You want to step on up?
Come on, now, who wants to play?
What about you, sweetie?
You're cute, come on up.
Cute girls win money all day.
You look lucky, now.
Follow the Queen, here we go.
Follow the Queen, follow the Queen.
She ain't no Helen Mirren,
but this Queen is for you.
Which one is it?
- It's right there.
- Right there?
Beginner's luck.
I'll tell you what, takes a woman
to know a woman, takes a lady
to find a Queen.
There you go...
Want to double up?
We gonna chance it, we gonna chance it.
All right, here we go.
All you gotta do is find your Queen.
You will not win again.
All right, here we go...
find your Queen.
Find your Queen.
Where is she?
Boom...
can you find her?
- Right there.
- This one?
Oh, my gosh, she is killin' me.
She is taking all my rent.
Anybody else want to get behind
the good-luck girl?
I can do it.
You can do it?
You're next.
Give me a chance to get my money back
or I'm gonna be out
here sleeping on the street.
Ready? This is the last time.
I'm not messin' no more.
You're taking all my money, girl.
Here we go.
This is your last chance.
Follow the Queen, follow the Queen.
Where's she at?
I'll show you one time.
There she is, boom, boom, boom.
Pick a card.
Uh, I can't decide.
What do you mean?
Just pick a card, just make a decision.
I can't decide.
Any card will do.
Left, right, center?
I don't... I don't know.
- Do you want the right?!
- I don't know.
The left?
The center?
I don't know. I...
Move out the way,
let somebody else play then.
I can't decide.
I... I can't.
- You want to flip a coin for it?
- What's wrong with me?
Transcript: swsub.com
Sync: jh26
Scariest 30 seconds of my life.
I couldn't do anything.
It's like I couldn't
move inside my head.
It's called abulia, the inability
to make a decision or exercise will.
Is it gonna happen again?
It's part of a T. I.A....
a Transient Ischemic Attack.
Blood was cut off to a
section of your frontal lobe.
Is that like a stroke or something?
A little.
What drugs have you taken recently?
No drugs.
Toxins are another possibility.
You might have been exposed
to something at work, for instance.
No real job right now.
Exposure can build up over
time and lie dormant for a while.
What was your last job?
Pet store.
Exotic pets?
Tropical fish.
And before that?
Unemployment.
And before that I sold
subscriptions on the phone.
And before that, unemployment.
Before that I worked at Jeans Gone Wild.
Before that, unemployment.
Before that, I walked dogs.
And before that...
Loss of free will.
I like it.
Maybe we can get Thomas
Aquinas in for a consult.
What caused the T.I.A.?
Arteries are clear.
No sign of a clot.
Could've dissolved.
Most likely came from her heart.
We should do a bubble study.
Clots are unlikely in a
29-year-old who's not on the pill.
It's probably a vaso-spasm
caused by drugs.
I don't think so.
She goes from job to job.
Maybe there's come kind of A. D. here.
Help us pinpoint where
the neurological...
She goes from job to job
because she's a scam artist.
She works just long enough
to qualify for unemployment,
then gets fired and gets high.
I still don't think it's drugs.
Did you check for infection?
LP showed nothing.
No fever, white blood count is normal.
Could be toxic exposure.
You're the one always
saying it must be drugs.
You figure he's a minority,
she must be stoned?
- You know that's not what I...
- She seems like a nice girl.
You haven't met her!
She was pregnant at 15, dropped out of
high school. She's a real overachiever.
Come on, cut her some slack...
her baby died of SIDS.
This isn't some romantic story
about a nice girl scarred by tragedy.
She's a drug-using scam
artist scarred by tragedy.
On the other hand,
her tox-screen just came back.
She's clean.
You're wasting my time.
He's waste...
Second ex-Mrs. Wilson want money?
I am no longer paying alimony.
She wanted her independence,
so she got her Realtor's license.
Market's doing badly, she wants money.
The market's doing badly,
she's moving into a condo.
She wants...
She wants me to take Hector.
Pool boy?
Dog.
No longer interested.
We got him on our honeymoon.
So I'm, like, the other parent.
But I can't take him.
My hotel doesn't allow dogs.
Besides, I'm always here.
I asked Cuddy to a play Thursday.
Oh, you... okay.
She said she was busy.
And you didn't believe her, so
you bribed a janitor,
broke into her computer,
checked her appointments...
- I asked her as a test.
What would you have
learned if she'd said yes?
A lot about bondage.
She's busy for me, but not for you.
She's not interested in the playquaplay,
she's interested in you.
No, I'm not getting sucked
into the vortex of your insanity again.
Don't pass me notes in class,
don't tell me to ask her to the prom.
You cannot see her socially.
You're leading her on.
I'll consider that,
after I take her to the Hockney exhibit.
On Thursday.
See, she is busy.
It's not a date.
She enjoyed the play.
I enjoyed her enjoying the play.
The woman works hard.
It's nice to see her relax.
So all this enjoying
is an act of charity?
I'm keeping the receipts
for tax purposes.
What's life without the
ability to make stupid choices?
She needs her free will.
Find out why her brain froze before she
can't decide to take her next breath.
You find the toxins,
you run the bubble study.
You won't find anything,
but I'll get the office to myself.
There's a lot of porn
piling up on the internet.
Doesn't download itself.
Eric... Eric!
Hello, Mr. Foreman.
Dr. Chase, how are you?
Good.
You're lucky you caught us...
I'll meet you outside.
Hey, Dad.
Uh, I've gotta go.
Why are you here?
Everything okay?
Good as ever.
We're staying at
a hotel down the street.
You didn't bring Mom with you?
It's gonna be her 60th
birthday in a few days.
I know...
we talked about it on the phone.
You said you couldn't come home.
You didn't have to come.
You haven't been home in eight years.
She should see you...
while she still knows who you are.
Dad, I've talked to her on the phone.
She only knows who I am... sometimes.
Sometimes...
is important.
So what's up with your dad?
Didn't know he was gonna be in town?
No.
A building this old,
there could be toxic exposure anywhere.
Asbestos, mold, the coloring
agents in the old wallpaper.
Or it could be drugs.
I thought we ruled out...
Clean tox-screen means
drugs didn't cause the T.I.A.
Drugs can be laced
with toxic substances.
Arsenic, rat poison.
The drugs wash out of her system,
the toxins stick around.
Exposure could come
about any number of ways.
There's no reason to assume
it was through drug use.
Absolutely, except for the crack pipe.
I'll test her blood
for arsenic and rat poison.
Yeah, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
Your dad asked you out for dinner?
I'll do the tests.
You're stuck with your family.
You like Hockney?
You heard about that.
The pop stuff or
the Venezuelan pictures?
That's a trick question.
Yes, but you have
no idea how it's a trick.
I like art.
I'm open to new things.
What's the problem?
You're going to a gallery to see
Venezuelan pictures that don't exist,
but you won't go to a play with me.
Why?
House, why is my social
life suddenly red hot?
One minute I'm mushing
along with the huskies, as usual,
and suddenly it's global warming.
You think you saw somebody
else pick up a toy from the sandbox,
and suddenly you want it.
Is that why you said no?
Maybe I just want a friend,
and I thought Wilson was a safe choice.
I'm not safe?
Cool.
James Wilson is never the safe choice.
We're going to a gallery,
we're not getting married.
Sure, you say that now.
He always marries 'em in the end.
Is that Eric?
Eric!
Oho ho ho.
Oh, baby, baby.
I wanted to find that picture
I took at your high school graduation.
I had it re-framed.
It's in one of these suitcases,
but I don't know...
You could show it to me later.
Your father wants to
know if you've been praying.
You don't have to just
come out with it like that.
But I only want to know if you're happy.
Sure, I'm okay.
You like it here, you have friends?
Yeah, everything's great, Mom.
That's why I brought
the picture for you.
I remember when you were little,
you liked to look in the back
of the math book because you knew
even though it made no sense then,
by the end of the year,
you'd understand it all.
That's why you brought the picture?
You wanted to look ahead
to see how far you'd go.
Now you're a grown man,
I thought you might like to look back
to see how far you've come.
It all makes sense now, doesn't it?
That isn't mine.
It was in your closet.
It belongs to this guy
who used to live with me.
You might want to let him
know he's got arsenic poisoning.
We should get a sample of
his hair so we can see the extent...
But I don't do...
I don't do drugs.
Get a crash cart in here!
Respiratory arrest!
Are you sure it isn't from the arsenic?
Dr. Foreman said I was poisoned.
Your hair showed only a trace amount.
Not enough to damage
your lungs like this.
We need you to stay still now.
Six-millimeter cuts
starting at the apices.
Also, I just wanted to let you know,
should you change your mind,
I'll be available.
Aren't you getting
tired of hearing me say it?
I have no intention of going
out with you, of having sex with you...
of doing anything with you except work.
We don't have to make
a big deal about it.
I just thought I'd let you know.
I've decided Tuesdays
would be a good day to do that.
You did not suddenly
fall in love with me.
You were looking for something,
and I happened to be...
It's fine.
No need to go on about it.
I'm dancing through the lung bases.
- We need to put this behind this.
- Understood.
But you keep bringing it up.
You're the one who's still talking.
Look, I'm not demanding
anything from you.
I'm not following you home.
I've got no expectations.
A gentle, polite reminder
once a week is hardly stalking.
There's a mass...
just outside the lingular.
Biopsy shows there are white blood
cells in the walls of the blood vessels.
They're not supposed
to get past the bouncers.
It's gotta be autoimmune...
something lymphocytic.
The white blood cells
are attacking her own body.
Only question is
what kind of autoimmune?
It doesn't matter what kind.
It always matters what kind.
Treatment's always steroids.
Treatment is always boring.
Diagnosis...
Okay, it's affecting
the larger blood vessels.
It's gotta be Giant Cell arteritis.
I'll start her on steroids.
It's affecting the
smaller blood vessels.
Gotta be lupus vasculitis.
I'll start her on steroids.
It's affecting...
Yeah, got it.
Start her on steroids.
Good idea.
Told you it was boring.
I gotta go out.
Why?
Wilson's got a date.
It's got 15-foot ceilings,
it's an open floor plan.
You know, I can't believe you called me.
Hey, I need a condo.
Didn't you and Wilson have
your first date around here?
Wow, you rember where
our first date was?
I didn't think you
were paying attention.
Really?
He's my best friend.
Our first date was in Boston.
Oh.
Not quite as close
to here as I rembered.
But we're not here to talk about him.
Absolutely not.
Wait'll you see the kitchen.
All-granite countertops.
Since I wasn't paying attention
back then, what was it like dating him?
So this is Hockney?
No.
I don't know what happened.
I'm sure you don't.
I never knew your
tastes were so eclectic.
Oh, the Hockney exhibit
finished on April 20th.
I thought it was May 20th.
Okay, my bad.
This is not somewhere
I'd bring someone on a date.
N- not that this is a date, obviously.
I was just thinking...
he's doing landscapes
on multiple canvases now, and
they're kinda peaceful.
And you're always so busy.
I don't think I've ever
seen you embarrassed before.
Oh, it was never adate.
I was coming off a bad relationship,
and he said we could go out as friends.
You know,
just go see plays, go to a museum.
I didn't think you liked Trenton.
Love it.
So he'd say it's not a date,
but then he'd jump you.
Oh, no, he meant it.
James Wilson, carefully calibrating
his level of protectiveness for your
individual needs.
Did you just compare Wilson to a tampon?
No.
It was very endearing.
He really just wanted to be a friend.
So I jumped him.
The bedroom's through here.
That's such a bad idea.
There is no way that won't
cause damage to the large intestine.
Are you keeping us here to torture me?
Is that a bicycle pump?
That's what I'm saying.
It's like walking into a sticky trap.
Once you're the focus of
all that attention, it's addictive.
This unit's kitchen
has got a chef's oven.
I cook a lot.
Go on.
It's the emotional stuff
that really sucks you in.
He's just so "knight
in shining armor," you know?
Always there to support you,
until one day he's not.
But by then, you're hooked.
Hey, do you think that you
could talk to him about taking the dog?
He's the only one that
Hector really gets along with.
Hey, we're here to talk real estate,
not Wilson.
So you're saying if you'd actually had
sex before you connected emotionally,
you'd have gotten over him.
- Oh, yeah. It seems weird, right?
'Cause sex with James was fantastic.
Nobody works harder to
give a woman what she wants.
It's got six burners.
The chef's oven.
Right.
How you feeling?
That wasn't my crack pipe.
You told me.
Are you tired?
I just took a hit off it a couple times.
What's wrong with having a little fun?
Your personal life
is none of my business.
You don't like me, though, do you?
That's your imagination.
I've seen every kind of drug abuse.
No offense, but you don't
even stand out in the pack.
I'm betting you got money
the same place you got attitude.
You know, people who quit drinking,
and people who lose weight,
they think they're better
than the people that couldn't.
And because you got out of the projects,
you think that anybody
who didn't is weak and stupid.
I'm not judging you.
Take a breath.
The only difference between me and
you is that I made some bad decisions,
and you made some good ones.
You make bad decisions
every day of your life.
Stop doing drugs, stop having fun.
Go back to school and get your GED.
Yeah, where's the money coming from?
The system's not set
up for people like me.
What are you staring at?
Your eyes.
There's yellow in the sclera.
Her liver's failing.
Without a transplant,
she'll be dead in the next 48 hours.
We should increase
her immunosuppressants,
and target more specifically,
add methotrexate.
Let's do more of what's not working.
This is not an autoimmune disease.
Her white blood cells are attacking
her body. That's autoimmune.
First brain, then lungs, now liver.
All getting worse and all in two days.
It's moving too fast.
It's gotta be cancer.
Lymphomatoid granulomatosis.
It's rare even by our standards,
but it fits her symptoms.
Explains why the
steroids aren't working.
- Poor fingernail growth.
- A lot of people have bad fingernails.
A lot of people don't have
three organ systems shutting down.
Her blood vessels are
taking this thing everywhere.
She needs total body radiation.
We can't do anything
until we can confirm...
Running those immuno-chemistries could
take a week. She'll be dead by the time.
That doesn't make radiation any safer.
Okay, suppose Chase
and Cameron are right.
Suppose it's an autoimmune disease.
What's the biggest danger
of total body radiation?
It suppresses the immune system,
which is what we're trying
to do with the steroids anyway.
I don't usually put out on
my first date, but I've gotta say
that is a rad move.
Get her consent.
Start the radiation.
The patient is not too thrilled with me.
I'll get her consent.
Foreman's got a personality issue,
soyou'regonna step in?
A patient doesn't like Foreman.
I'm interested.
Fatigue, hair loss, possibility
of damage to the lungs, infertility.
All possible side effects of radiation.
Why don't you like Dr. Foreman?
He thinks he's better than he is.
How good is he?
I don't know.
Can we get back to what's wrong with me?
There's a small possibility
of leukemia sometime in the future.
Hardly worth mentioning.
You can't say that he
thinks he's better than he is
if you don't know how good he is.
No one's as good as he thinks he is.
I am.
You might also get cataracts.
Sign here.
I don't know.
You're telling me how dangerous this is.
We're saving your life.
We're that good.
Sign there.
I can't decide.
Would you rather a pencil or a pen?
Who's the better James Bond,
Sean Connery or Daniel Craig?
Now, see, that's not even a decision.
It's happening again.
I can't...
I... can't...
Up her blood thinners
and get her down to radiology.
The attack will be over in 20 minutes.
Then she'll want to sign this.
Bonnie called last night
to talk about the dog.
Your name came up.
Good Lord, how do you still have teeth?
She's the worst Realtor in New Jersey.
What is this, escalation?
I go out with Cuddy,
you hook up with my ex?
I don't even know what
that's designed to do.
You're an addict.
I'm saving you from yourself.
By condo shopping?
Thank you.
If I can figure out
where you keep going wrong,
then I can nip this
Cuddy thing in the bud
before she becomes
the fourth ex-Mrs. Wilson.
Yes, I was worried there
was no way to stop that train.
You have to have sex with Cuddy.
Wait... to stop the train?
Bonnie said I'm bad in bed?
Huh?
Yeah, she also said that if she'd
slept with you before she liked you,
then it would have made it easier
to handle when you turned into the sorry
bastard who left her alone.
I told her you were wasting her time,
by the way.
You think that's gonna stop her?
The woman's the worst
Realtor in New Jersey.
How do you feel?
Weak.
Sleeping a lot.
That's normal after radiation.
Deep breath.
A little queasy too.
When I feel sick to my stomach,
I always want vanilla ice cream.
It's soothing.
It's best to stick with liquids for now.
Shh.
I'm getting a murmur.
Oh, my arm.
It's hurting me!
Take it off!
Oh, my God, oh, my...
Pain is the issue.
Just the pressure of the BP
cuff was enough to start her screaming.
That's not cancer.
It sounds like...
Sounds like she's septic.
A lot of things can cause pain.
How much pain?
Too much.
It's not cancer.
It's not autoimmune.
It's an infection and
we fried her immune system.
But she had no fever, LP was clear.
Do an echo to confirm it's in the heart.
And then I'll tell our
patient that we just killed her.
I'll tell her.
You haven't been
returning my phone calls.
- I'm busy.
- Well...
But if you have half an hour
a little later this afternoon,
I just found this unit
ten minutes from here.
- It hasn't been on the market yet.
- I'm off the market for condos.
James was right?
I never had the teeniest
chance of selling you anything.
Of course he was right.
Wilson doesn't stop giving good
advice just 'cause you're divorced.
He's compulsive about remaing
on good terms with his exes.
Do you want to know
why I named that dog Hector?
No, let's keep it a mystery.
Because even when he was a puppy, he was
the worst-tempered dog we'd ever seen.
He was supposed to be house trained.
He'd pee on the carpet every morning.
When we had people over,
he had to nip at their ankles.
"Hector does go rug" is
an anagram for Dr. Greg House.
That's how early in
the marriage I resented you.
Wow.
Did I ever waste money
on that place setting.
James at least had the decency
to feel guilty when he hurt me.
Whereas I didn't hurt you.
I didn't even marry you, cleverly
hoping to avoid moments like this one.
You always needed him,
and he was always there for you!
If you keep yelling,
I think you'll owe me sex.
You knew he had a wife waiting
at home... you didn't care.
I'm not saying you broke up
the marriage, but you didn't help.
First, "Hector does
go rug" is a lame anagram.
You want a better one for Gregory House?
"Huge ego, sorry."
Second, find a new career.
You're never gonna sell anybody
if you let them control the agenda.
Third, I don't owe you anything...
I'm not Wilson.
I'm not gonna buy a condo
just to make you feel better.
You okay?
Yeah.
Tell me how to do this.
House says people thank you after...
It's not typical.
I already killed this woman.
All I can do now is
not make any more mistakes.
First of all,
stop thinking you can minimize the hurt.
A lot of people are
afraid of the word "dying."
If you pussyfoot around it,
she is not gonna read your mind.
Okay.
No, it's not.
When you look in her face, you're
gonna feel the instinct to temporize.
Crush it.
Yeah.
Then wait.
Give her time to process the news.
Let her know you'll be
with her through all of it.
Wait till she's done thinking,
till she meets your eyes again.
Then, if you feel it's appropriate,
you can touch her.
Maybe put your hand
on her arm like this.
Let her know she's still
connected to another human being.
You've got this down to a science.
You're freaking out.
I told you...
Give her what she needs.
What she doesn't need is
a doctor who's not there with her
because he made the wrong call.
You are freaking out.
You should be freaking out.
I won't let her see it.
Let her see it.
Hey.
How come no mask?
We think...
you have an infection.
Didn't the radiation work?
It didn't do what it was supposed to do.
You're dying.
What...
you mean, like,
things are bad, and someday I'm gonna...
How much time?
We can't know exactly.
A year?
Less than a year?
Less than 24 hours.
I don't understand.
Why are you saying this to me?
You trying to scare me?
Why would you do that?
I'm sorry, it's true.
How bad is this cancer?
Yesterday you thought I had a chance.
You don't have cancer.
You came in with an infection.
We didn't catch it.
What kind of infection?
Doesn't matter.
The radiation was the
worst thing we could've done.
We destroyed the part of
your body that was fighting it off.
It spread to your heart.
Then give me drugs.
They have drugs for infections.
Antibiotics work with the immune system.
But your immune system is
nonexistent because of the radiation.
If it's my heart,
you can get me a new heart.
People have heart
transplants all the time.
It wouldn't help.
The infection is everywhere.
There's nothing anybody can do.
I'm so sorry.
We've called your grandparents.
Get the hell away from me!
Get out!
I think it's broken.
Nothing like a melodramatic
gesture to solve everything.
We were wrong too.
Steroids wouldn't have helped her.
I didn't not help her.
I actually pulled the trigger.
There's nothing left for you to do.
- One of us could go home with...
- You're trying to make me feel better.
Yeah.
I killed a woman.
Don't you think it's appropriate
that I feel like crap
for at least a little while?
It won't help her.
Where is he?
He went to the ICU.
What are you doing?
Prepping for an aspiration.
We still don't know what infection...
- It's not gonna help her.
- It's not gonna hurt her.
- Well, it is, but it's not gonna...
- No.
It's just gonna take a few minutes.
Grab a piece of an abscess, some pus.
You really don't care.
You really don't care
why she's gonna be dead.
She's gonna be dead because...
What?!
What did we screw up, what did we miss?
I need to know.
You'll have to wait.
We're moving her back to her room.
Patients who've had total
body radiation have to stay in ICU.
ICU isn't gonna help her.
Let's give her some privacy.
What do you want?
Want to see if I'm dying on schedule?
Or do you want me to
tell you it's all right...
I'm okay with it?
I'd like your forgiveness.
I don't expect it.
Good, 'cause this isn't like you ran
your cart into mine at the supermarket.
No.
Your grandparents haven't arrived yet.
If they don't make it on time, is there
anything you would like me to tell them?
I never really knew them.
You got any friends you want me to call?
It's the middle of the night.
They're not the kind of friends
you ask to help you move, never mind
watch you die.
I never did much.
No kid to leave behind.
When I go,
the world's not gonna be any different.
Kind of a relief for you, huh?
You were right...
about me.
Yeah, which time?
I, uh...
I had a problem with you.
But you were wrong too.
I've made some bad decisions.
Stole cars, robbed houses.
Killed a woman.
But then I got another chance.
I left home, went to college,
entered a whole other world.
But some part of me I can't get rid of
always thinks
if I'm not the smartest,
if I'm not the first, everywhere I go,
they'll figure out I'm
not supposed to be here.
They'll send me back.
You know that's not gonna happen.
You're out.
I'll never be out of there.
When I came home that last
Christmas I was in college,
it was like
the rooms
felt so small.
I was suffocating.
But when I was standing
on the stoop saying good-bye,
my mom put her arms around me.
That was...
that was the last
time I ever felt at home.
I only put distance...
between you and me because
I know there isn't any.
You were right about me too.
That stuff about the system
being against people like me.
I know it's crap.
I mean, it's true, but it's also crap.
I just wasn't ready to try again.
But I always thought I was young,
I had time.
Aren't you ever gonna leave?
No.
Yeah?
Time of death 3:35.
Do whatever you want.
You wanna go get drunk?
No, thanks.
I've got paperwork.
Listen, I don't...
I don't know what I believe,
but sometimes I need to think there's
something out there paying attention.
So when I can't talk to anybody, I talk
to God and pretend somebody's listening.
We were all wrong, you know?
Even House was wrong.
I know.
I got your consent.
Her bra hook.
What?
She scratched herself with her bra hook.
That's how the infection got in.
Staph aureus.
She died from a simple staph infection?
That and some bad decisions.
I'll be outside.
Go home,
have a few drinks,
go to sleep, get up tomorrow,
and do it all over,
only better.
If you need absolution,
go to a priest or give alms to the poor.
Whatever ritual comforts you.
I killed her.
Yeah, me too.
This wasn't, "Oh, I should
have thought of that idea sooner.
"This wasn't messing up a dosage.
We see a disease rushing
down on someone like a train,
we can't always get them out of the way.
This wasn't that.
No.
And you'll do it again.
For a lot of doctors, this
would be a once in a lifetime mistake.
But we're not a lot of doctors.
We must've saved more patients
than the guy down the street.
A few of the ones that he'd save
by doing what everyone else does,
we will lose.
So you're giving me numbers.
'Cause they don't lie.
I can't forgive you, Foreman...
because there's nothing to forgive.
What did you tell him?
That guilt is irrelevant.
You want to get something to eat?
Can't.
Got a dog waiting at home.
What's wrong?
I did something bad, Mom.
I hurt somebody.
It wasn't your fault.
It was.
Then I forgive you.
I forgive you.
I can see from your face...
you'd never hurt anybody on purpose.
Do you know who I am, Mom?
It's Eric.
Of course.
My little boy's name is Eric.