Host: www.CsSubs.org - Thanks Guys
You okay?
Yeah, I just got clipped with a beam.
What the hell do you two think you were doing?
We thought we heard someone in there.
You never go in without authorization.
Captain, this is all me.Amy just followed me in.
So torching your ass last year wasn't enough, huh?
You need to stop trying to prove how
tough you are before you get yourself killed.
Yes, sir.
Go have the paramedics look you over.
Come on, derek, let's get this
ladder to the second story.
Let's go.
Derek!
What's happening?
I'M...freezing.
House Season 3 Episode 11
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-Vicky8800-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
I'm fine.
Er docs don't think so.
Your temperature's been going up
and down like a roller coaster.
How old are these skin grafts?
Last one was about six months ago.
Gonna run some tests,and we'll get
a consult with dr. House.
I'll be fine.
You'll be doing what the doctors say.
Got it?
I'll check in later.
Hey.
The way you covered for me last night.
He's my brother.
I know how to eat it from him.
I'm gonna stop after my shift, okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
So where is this dr. House?
Speaking engagement.
Not guilty.
And on the charge of gaining control of
said medication by fraud, how do you plead?
Not guilty.
Very well.
Preliminary hearing is set for
the 19th at 10:00 am,
at which time I'll determine whether
there's enough evidence to proceed to trial.
Next case on the calendar,people V. Williams
charged assault for second degree
You're gonna go talk to him?
I was just gonna ask him where he gets his hair cut.
They have your signature in a prescription log,
a security camera video,
and a pharmacist's sworn statement saying
you stole the dead guy's pills.
You're already looking at ten years.
You want to add witness intimidating charge?
Go ahead.
Ask him about his hair.
He suffered third degree burns over
54% of his body a year ago
and arrived in the er last night
disoriented and shivering.
For 12 hours his temperature was
bouncing between 96 and 102.
Why don't you contest the search
of the pharmacy records?
Yeah, you could argue it violated
doctor-patient confidentiality.
Except he wasn't the patient or the doctor.
He was the guy who stole from
the patient and the doctor.
This was the third time he had been
disoriented in the last two weeks.
Running into smoke-filled burning buildings
can be a bit disorienting.
Fortunately, I have the cure.
Stop doing it.
He's not in a burning building anymore,
and he's still shivering.
A hypothalamic tumor could cause
a vacillating temperature.
So could er nurses who are too busy to notice
that a patient likes both hot coffee and cold sodas.
He tested negative for hep c,tb, hiv,
lyme,and his tox screen's clean.
In case you hadn't noticed,
not exactly in the mood to dance.
I'm not asking you to dance.
I asking you to do your job.
Ekg showed arrhythmia.
Probably just a mild heart attack.
No chest pain.
And smoke inhalation already
explains the arrhythmia.
The guy was in the burn unit for six months
and had multiple surgeries.
Could be a hospital-acquired infection.
Maybe mrsa
Works for me.
Draw blood cultures.Start him on antibiotics.
Vancomycin plus broad gram negative coverage.
If you called to see the design
for my prison tats,they're still in r&D.
You need to talk to tritter.
Not according to my lawyer.
Your lawyer isn't gonna be able to get the da
to the drop the case.Tritter caN.
Yeah, you know what else tritter can do?
You are not impressing anyone.
You may call yourself principled,
but what you really are is stubborn,adolescent idiot.
- This isn't his fault.
- I'm not the one--
you used the rectal thermometer on him.
You insulted him instead of apologizing.
You flaunted your drug use in his face.
And you refused to accept a deal--
I accepted the deaL.
Not until after you stole a dead guy's pills.
Allegedly.
Tritter has been opening doors
for you every step of the way,
and you keep slamming them shut.
There are no more openings to give, house.
If you want to stay out of prison,
you gotta make one for yourself.
It's vicodin.
You function better on it.
Talk to him.
Mrsa's a bacteria that often
infects hospital patients.
The burns on your chest and arm exposed
raw flesh that made youa wide open target.
But the antibiotics will take care of it, right?
Depends on what strainit is.
We'll know more once weget the results
back from these cultures.
So this...
mrsa thing...
would it make everything look blue?
He's seeing blue.
Who'd you get the scrip from?
Cuddy.
You want to know what I gave her?
Mrsa wouldn't change his ocular palette.
Heavy metal poisoning could cause
vision changes,particularly thallium.
If it was thallium,he'd be losing his hair.
So maybe it's menopause.
He's 28 years old.
Yes, his age is the reason it's weird
that a man has menopause.
Male menopause.
High estrogen,low testosterone.
Explains the temperature swings,disorientation.
Endocrinologically similar to female menopause
but without the vaginas and mah-jongg tiles.
Male menopause doesn't explain the blue vision.
The blue vision isn't a symptom,
it's a side effect of viagra.
It's right there on the label.
Which I have no reason to have read
except that I'm a doctor.
He's not taking viagra.
You mean he didn't tell you he was taking viagra.
I don't care how sick he is, trust me.
He still thinks he's got a shot.
Menopause causes temperature swings, limpness.
Limpness causes pills,pills cause the blues.
He's presenting no other signs of premature aging.
Aging's not the only cause.
You said that's he got burns on 54% of his body.
Sure it's not 55%?
Burns to his genitals could cause testicular trauma.
Which in turn could cause?
Run a hormone panel.
Comes back positive,pump him full
of testosterone and send him home.
And stop following me.
Thank god my parents are dead.
If the old man had heard I had menopause
I'd never live it down.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Once these testosterone pellets dissolve
your system will be back to normal.
Yeah, but till then I'm an old lady.
Okay to come in?
It's not mrsa.
He's not being isolated anymore.
Anyone not in a white coat is welcome.
You're looking better.
How you feeling?
I'm good.
Turns out I got some hormone thing.
They're fixing it right now.
You okay?
Yeah, I think so.I just--uhh!
Derek, you in pain?
You need to get these out.
- Hold on.What's wrong?
- Get these out.
- What's going on?
- Looks like an allergic reaction.
Derek, hold on,
we're gonna get you something to stop it.
- No, just take 'em out!
- You gotta calm down.
Get 'em out!Derek!
Derek, let her go!
I need two milligrams iv lorazepam stat!
Get 'em out!
Complaint department's across the hall.
I'm busy.
Can I just assume that you told me
how unfair I'm being and--
I'm sorry.
You could throw a dart at all
the adjectives between arrogant
and unhinged and I'm sure
you'd hit one that describes me.
There's a reason I operate that way.
I live in pain.
Pain that on good days is merely intolerable,
but on bad ones will suck
the life force right out of you.
Doesn't mean that I've handled this right.
Actually...means I was wrong.
Thank you.
I know that couldn't have been...
easy for you to say.
Even if you don't mean a word of it.
I'm sorry.
You can hook me up to a damn polygraph.
And I'm sure you'd pass.
The thing is, I've never been interested
in what you have to say.
All I care about is what you do.
I'll see you at the hearing.
it wasn't the medicine.
Contamination and allergy tests
both came back negative.
There was nothing to suggest a pulmonary embolism.
And his ekg showed the expected tachycardia
from the exertion of the attack.
And I'm fine by the way,thanks for asking.
aggression comes on that fast
it's gotta have a neurologic basis.
We should do a ctfor a frontal lobe tumor
and an lp for meningitis.
Great.
Have at it.
That's it?
No challenging our theory?
No tearing us down?
No need.
You've got it under control.
Where are you going?
Upstairs this time.
To do what?
Check myself into rehab.
did tritter offer you another deal?
Nope.This is all me.
So, no slaps on the back,encouraging words?
We're just trying to understand what this is.
I hope it's me detoxing.
Otherwise I soiled a perfectly good pair
of underwear last night for nothing.
So this is for real?
It's not just a show for tritter?
Absolutely it's a show for tritter.
And the judge.
Unfortunately,unless it's real,
there is no show.
Hey, if it doesn't help my case,then at least
I can go to prison with heightened senses.
All the better to enjoy my strolls around the yard.
Time's up.Group's starting.
Gonna need to check that stuff.
When I lead the big patient rebellion,
voldemort here is first to go.
Ct was normal.No frontal lobe tumor.
Lp was negativefor meningitis.
We're back to square one.
What about something vascular?
Polyarterit is nodosa?
Brain lesions would've shown up on the ct
legionnaire's explains the chills and temperature.
Altered mental status causes the aggression.
We would've seen respiratory problems.
We're throwing darts.
We need to go to house.
We need to deal with this ourselves.
He can make the time.
Derek's still his patient.
The man's life as he knows it could be over.
I think you of all people would
want to cut him some slack.
We're treating a man who runs into
burning buildings for perfect strangers.
He didn't ask for what's happening to him.
House did everything to himself.
He's been cut more than enough slack.
Right now, house has more important
things to deal with.
It was the first time I'd seen him in months.
I guess I was hoping he'd put his arms
around me and tell me he understood.
But he said he wasn't ready to forgive me.
he may never be ready.
You're doing the only thing you can do.
You're trying.
How about you, greg?
You thought about how to fix things
with people in your life?
No need.
People in my life have no expectations of me.
Makes all our lives easier.
Apparently not.
- The first step in recovery--
- is admitting I have a problem.
I've obviously done that,or I wouldn't be here.
I've even embraced step two.
I've accepted that there is a higher power.
Maybe not a god perse,
but that andre the giant guyw as powerful.
Where I start to butt up
against it is step three
surrendering my will to this higher power.
I'm sure andre's ghost has my back
and all,but my free will?
I never leave home without it.
Kind of like your pills.
If you could do this on your own,
I assume you wouldn't be here.
True.
Everybody lies.
His tox screen.
It's been clean every time.
Exactly.
It shouldn't bE.He's had extensive skin grafts
which hurt like hell.
Not everybody's house.People can handle
pain without medication.
But they do have pain.
This guy's worried about losing his job
so he's hiding the pain.
We find out where the pain is
maybe we find out where the problem is.
Or he doesn't feel pain.
Either way,it's something.
When?
Two minutes ago.Pulse is 137.
Respiration 42.
He was fine.He was just telling me a joke.
Get her out of here.
No fluid in his lungs.
O2 set's 85.He's hypoxic.
We're gonna have to intubate.
It's not his lungs.
He's got marked s-t elevation.
He's having a heart attack.
Pick a color.
Medication time.
You are a ray of sunshine on a cloudy day.
He's stable.
Won't stay that way.
His blood tests show troponins and ckmb up.
Chase was right.He was hiding chest pain.
He's been having a whole series of heart attacks.
Heart attacks can't cause you to
reach out and choke someone.
Lack of oxygen to the brain causes disorientation.
Increased adrenaline causes rage.
More important question is,
what caused the attacks?
Where you going?
To see house.
We have a 28-year-old with clean arteries,
no valvular abnormalities having multiple attacks.
I'm not gonna wait for chase to
give us another breakthrough.
Maybe we should go.
We don't have an answer yet.
I'm fine by the way,thanks for asking.
Whoever came up with buprenorphine to
wean off vicodin should be shot.
Then stabbed in the eye.
Think someone needs to adjust my meds!
The heart shows no signs of inflammation or
the cause of the heart attacks isn't internal.
It must be external,something environmental.
None of the attacks happened in the same place.
Still must be something in common.
First one happenedin an apartment building fire.
Fire, water, smoke,oxygen masks.
And the second and third ones happened here.
There's no fire,no water, no smoke.
His clothes are all different.
He'd been cleaned.
That's the what'S.How about the who's?
His partner amy was at all three attacks,
but--anyone else?
People don't cause heart attacks.
Well, you should be worried about proving me wrong.
amy?
Would you come with me, please?
Anything new on my brother?
We're not quite sure yet.
Could you come with me?
Yeah.
What's this all about?
I don't know.
They wanted to talk to us together.
Derek!
House was right.
I don't get it.
How can I be causing his heart attacks?
You may be carrying an agent that triggered them.
It could be anything.
Mold spores,poisonous plant residue,
something you picked up at a fire site.
Until we identy the agent,
we can't allow you near derek.
I can't believe that I'm doing this to him.
You can't blame yourself for this.
You know how he got those skin grafts?
He was trapped in a fire.
We were clearing rooms in an office building fire,
and the ceiling collapsed.
And it cut me off from the rest of the group.
And I kept yelling that I was fine,
but derek refused to wait for
the team to clear the debris,
so he took off looking for another access point.
He got caught in a back draft.
He almost died because of me once.
And now it's happening again.
You're not my mom.
You don't have to keep checking up on me.
How you doing?
Not bad.
Considering I've just learned
I'm completely powerless
see this big fancy wing?
It was built because this program works.
Faulty logic.
This big fancy wing exists because
some people with money think that it works.
They want to believe they can buy a better world.
This is nothing short of idealized despair.
Let other people wallow in it.
I don't even know what that means.
None of this means anything.
It's just nonsensicals logans and platitudes.
Meaning takes time.It takes work.
What do you think I've been doing?
You've been here for two days.
Talk about wallowing in it.
We all get it.
We know how much pain you have.
You're here to deal with that
and get on with your life.
Right.
I should have an affair with a dying patient
and move into a hotel.
You're a coward, house.
You find fault in everybody,because
you're afraid to look at yourself.
Thanks.
I was running short on platitudes.
You can leave now.
We tested amy for about a dozen different agents,
but they all came back negative.
So she's not causing the attacks.
Derek...are you in love with her?
What does that have to do with anything?
Amy told me how you got those skin grafts.
And the way you're always watching out for her.
And I see the way you look at her.
Have you told her how you feel?
She has a six-year-old daughter.
Women with daughters can still fall in love.
I know.
Because she did.With my brother.
They're engaged.
broken heart syndrome.
He's in love,and it's killing him.
Thought that only happened to 80-year-old widows.
Thanks to his menopause and estrogen level
he basically is an old woman.
Bhs is an acute physical response
to an emotional experience.
Stress triggers a flood of catecholamines
that's a plain old stress cardiomyopathy
not a heart attack.
But if you're too worried about losing your job
to get it treated,they can devolve
into full-on heart attacks.
You think it's a coincidence this
started when amy got engaged?
No, I don'T.
But now that you know the why
what are you gonna do to stop the how?
We already put him on beta blockers
and nitroglycerine,no effect.
We need to put him on anti-depressants.
Not if you're right.
Anti-depressants would inhibit
his autonomic nervous system
which would only speed up the heart attacks.
We could trypropyl thiouracil.
Slow down his metabolic rate.
Thyroid effect would only weaken the heart.
The only other optionis blood thinners.
This is not a fat guy with plaque-filled
arteries and a swollen heart.
He's a guy whose brain is trying to his heart.
So buy him a girlfriend.Make him happy.
That might make you happy.
The only thing that'll make him happy is amy.
So keep him away from her.
He has a myocardial infarction every time
she walks in the room.
What do you think will happen to his heart
when we tell him he can never see her again?
he needs a shrink.
Chase's idea is as good as any.
Because short of fryingh is brain
and wiping amy out,
he's screwed.
We need cuddy.
Why?
So you can tell her why you need to
fry a guy's brain.
The guy's heart isn't working
and you want to shock his brain.
Electroshock therapy is the only way
to erase his memories of amy
and stop the brain's chemical attack on the heart.
This is 1940.The problem can be
controlled with anti-depressants.
Cameron?
Anti-depressants would inhibit his
autonomic nervous system,speed up the attacks.
Lmno, ptu, blood thinners,none of
them will solve this problem.
The man's got a real-life harlequin romance in his head.
We're gonna pull out the 1940 playbook.
Bilateral electrodes,
high stimulus sine-wave intensity,
turning that dial all the way to 11.
It's basic brain chemistry.
We interrupt protein synthesis,
altering the neuro transmitter system.
End results: No memories,no amy,no problem.
Go ahead.
You heard the lady.Go plug him in.
Am I really that pathetic?
What are you talking about?
If I had pitche delectroshock therapy
as a cure for broken heart syndrome any other time,
you'd have dug in and maybe try
a hundred other useless things first.
So either you're actually beginning to trust me,
or you just feel sorry for me.
You presented a reasonable argument.
You were clear-headed and non-impulsive about it.
Never once used the word "moron."
The rehab's working, house.
you'll still be able to perform routine
functions like walking, talking,tying your shoes.
The treatment targets the anterior cingulate cortex.
It should only affect your experiential memories.
So my parents?My childhood?
If this works,you won't remember them.
Or your fire fighting training.
And amy.
Are you okay with that?
I wouldn't miss her,right?
Tell amy how you feel
because if she loves you
no.I won't do that to her.
Or to my brother.
You're effectively killing
who you are just to keep this secret.
She doesn't love me.
Caterpillar?
Lower intestine  with ulcerative colitis.
You crash art therapy classes
just for the adrenaline rush?
Cuddy wouldn't get off the phone
until I promised I'd come and see for myself.
I gotta admit,this move I did not expect.
Well, don't tell anyone,but the photos of
smiling people in the brochure
is just marketing.
Well, you're obviously making an effort.
So i suppose the next step is for me to...
talk to the da.
Which you have no intention of doing.
No.
So words mean nothing,actions mean nothing.
What the hell is left?
You son of a bitch!
What about your words?Your actions?
"Gotta get house cleaned up.
Gotta get him to show some humility."
But when it comes to actually doing something,
you've proved that all you care about
is bitch-slapping a guy
who refused to kiss your ass.
You ever trust an addict?
You ever give one the benefit of the doubt?
How many times did it work out for you
yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it.
So you were screwed over by your wife,
your mother, your partner.
But you keep sending them christmas cards
while you take it out on everyone else.
No more christmas cards.
No, I learned...
people like you...
even your actions lie.
I'm scared.
I know.
I'm gonna give you a muscle relaxant
so your body doesn't convulse.
Count backwards from ten.
10...
9...
8...
7...
go.
what's your name?
Derek.
Heart sounds good.
Do you know what city we're in?
No.
Would you be okay with a couple of visitors?
Derek, it's--it's me.Brock.
I'm your brother,and when you get out of here
you'll be staying with me.
I'm amy.
I'm your friend.
I'm sorry.
But I don't remember either of you.
we've give him four rounds of electroshock.
The charge made his voice a little higher,
but the ekg and bpare good.
Good.
We're gonna give him his last round in the morning,
then be in court for your hearing.
Thanks.
I'm gonna stay here.
Monitor derek.
Thanks for the update.
My next condolence callis arriving.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I got you something.
Nice.
I figured it might help make a
good impression on the judge.
It's not that nice.
I had no business blaming you for any of this.
I know you were just trying to help me.
Protect me.That's what friends do.
Is this an apology?
Part of the program.
You don't like it,I can stop.
Not at all.
It's just so...unfamiliar.
Please, keep going.
He looks lost.
It's gonna take him a while.
Brock's pulling a double shift.
He can't stand to see him this way.
Derek's gonna need him, amy.
I know the timing isn't great
with a wedding coming up.
What wedding?
Yours.You and brock.
We're not getting married.
We don't even date.
Why would you think we're getting married?
When you first offered dr. House the chance
to check into drug rehab,how did he respond?
He told me to get ou tof his office.
I warned him that...
he could end up in prison and
lose his medical license.
If he was concerned,he didn't show it.
so you continued your investigation.
Yes, which is what lead me to the hospital pharmacy.
Turn it off.
I thought I told you never to call me
when I'm on trial.
The memories were false.
We fried his brain for nothing.
Whatever was killing him before is still there.
We did an mri.
There's a slight hypoperfusion
in the anterior cortex.
What did you find when you checked the pharmacy log?
Hold on, mr. Vickers.
Thanks, your honor.Hard to hear.
Did you test for clotting time and lv function?
I believe this is a medical emergency,your honor.
His blood's normal,and his heart's
pumping it up to the brain.
But it's not all getting there.
Something's obstructing the blood flow.
Dr. House, you were given adequate notice
to make arrangements for your patients.
There's no hyper intensity to suggest
a foreign body near the region.
And no signs of infection
or vascular malformation.
- It's lower down.
- Dr. House, hang up.
- The cytology on the lp doesn't suggest a tumor.
- Now!
Hang on a second.
Does your voice always get that high
and annoying when you're angry?
Do you want to go to jail?
No thank you.
Set him up for a selective vertebral angiography.
I'm on my way.
Dr. House--
house, sit down!
Why?I'm bored.
There's nothing I can say or do that's
gonna make a difference here.
If you leave this room,
I will find you in contempt.
Get a recess.
Are you out of your mind?
They said they wanted me there,
but I don't think they liked me.
His voice isn't high because of the electrical charges.
It's another symptom of menopause.
His system keeps getting hit by women's issues.
So let's follow the pattern.
What might obstruct the blood flow
that's more common in women than men?
Is the catheter in?
go back to court.
We'll let you know the results.
Shut up and wire him.
Center the image on the interpeduncular cistern.
Keep it moving at 30 frames per second.
If you think the arteries are narrowing,
we're gonna need still shots,
which we can do without you.
The problem is not how wide the road is.
There's a guy with a squeegee on the sidewalk
flagging cars, that's what's causing the slow down.
We find him,we find the problem.
He's wired.
- Go.
- Injecting the dye.
Blood's in the capillaries.
There.
Mr. Squeegee.
Spinal meningioma pushing on the
nerves to the vocal chords.
Creates the voice change.
And that nerve just happens to live right near
the meningeal branch of the vertebral artery.
Obstructs the blood flow to the brain.
Brain malfunctions,creating false memories.
Memories cause love.
Love kills.
And we didn't completely screw up.
Cleaning the slate bought us time
to find the real problem.
On the other hand,if we'd been better,
we wouldn't have needed the time.
Schedule him for surgery.
Dig that thing out.
He can start enjoying real misery
instead of the fake stuff.
House.
I just heard that you apologized to wilson.
Detoxing.
I didn't know what I was saying.
Excuse me.
I have to go to jail.
What is your position at princeton-plains boro?
Chief administrator and dean of medicine.
and you're responsible for oversight of the pharmacy?
Yes.
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt.
I hope you don't mind that
we continued on without you.
I said I was sorry.
There's no need to be sarcastic.
What is this?
That's our prescription sign-out log
from december 24.
Does that appear to be dr. House's signature?
- Yes.
- What has he signed for?
a prescription for oxycodone in
the name of patient larry zebalusky.
- And did those pills ever reach that patient?
- No.
- Why?
- He was already dead.
And dr. House knew this.
Yes.
so...
dr. House had no legal or medical basis
for acquiring that oxycodone?
Dr. Cuddy?
He never got the pills.
It's his signature.
The log is strictly controlled.
Dr. House did pick up a prescription,
but it wasn't for oxycodone.
It says oxycodone.
- You testified it was--
- I know.But it wasn't oxycodone.
Dr. Wilson informed me that dr.House already tried
to steal the pain medication of this patient,
which made clear to me that dr. House was in
a particularly vulnerable and desperate state.
So I went to the pharmacy and I swapped bottles.
Dr. House only got a bottle with placebos.
I understand your impulse to
protect a valued colleague.
I have it right here on the inventory report
your honor, she's lyinG.
She's obviously forged that report.
In light of this evidence...
if this is real, why didn't she mention it earlier?
I move to dismiss this case.
There is other evidence,your honor.
Everyone shut up and sit down.
Dr. Cuddy, why are you only now
coming forward with this?
I guess I never expected it to go this far.
The witness is excused.
Your honor, you can't serisly believe--
dr. House, please stand.
My suspicion is your boss--
my suspicion is you have better friends
than you deserve.
Rules and laws apply to everyone.
You are not as special as you think.
But detective tritter chose to make you so.
Detective,I don't know exactly what's going on here,
but I am sure that this man is
not flooding the streets with cocaine.
I'm also certain that,knowing dr. House,
he must've done something to set you off.
But you're gonna have to live with it.
Given dr. Cuddy's testimony,I'm not going to
allow this to proceed to jury.
Case dismissed.
Court is adjourned.
Dr house, you're still guilty of
contempt for that little walkout earlier.
You'll be spending the night in jail,
and after that, you're going right back to your rehab.
Bailiff, take dr. House into custody.
Dr. House.
So should I be looking for you in the shadows?
Flinch every time a car backfires?
Good luck.
I hope i'm wrong about you.
we got the meningioma.
Your brain should start generating
real memories again.
What do I do when I get out?
You have people who love you.
They'll take care of you.
You start over.
surprised to see you're not spooning
your way through the walls.
So, what do you say?
How about a conjugal visit to celebrate?
There's nothing to celebrate, house.
You made me perjure myself.
Fabricate evidence.
You make everyone around you worse for being there.
The only bright spot is that
now I own your ass.
When you get out of rehab
you're gonna be pulling double clinic duty,
giving lectures to students helping me find donors,
and pretty much anything else I ask.
You got it?
Your buprenorphine.
You get these from the pharmacy of from voldemort?
Voldemort.Why, what difference does it--
That's vicodin.
He's been slipping you vicodin?
No!
He'd be risking his minimum wage job to do that.
The whole time?
My higher power said it was okay.
Nothing's changed?
Nothing's changed.
The apology.
You didn't need to do that to make this work.
Believe what you want.
Good night, house.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night, wilson.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-Vicky8800-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
House Season 3 Episode 11