Fran?
I'm robi
Please,come in.
cute home.
Two bedroom,one bath?
Yeah.
A guy I know collects those.
He says they're worth
a fortune on the internet.
Yeah.
You've never used our agency before,
have you?
Is it that obvious?
As you can see,
we offer a full range of services.
"Round the world"?
Our deluxe package offers
all the services of a,b,and C.
How much?
$1,000.
And satisfaction's guaranteed.
Twice.
I'll get the money.
I'll get ready.
Harrington?
Harrington.
What are you doing up there?
All right,now.
Don't take this personally,
but you're gonna have to go??
Fran?
Is this okay?
Are you all right?
Oh,god.
Fran?
Yeah,I--
I need an ambulance at 500 north sycamore.
I don't know.
My...friend collapsed.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-HCµ°?? addychristen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
House
Season 03 Episode 18
and what were you doing when you fainted?
We were just--
looking for her cat.
And have you banged your head recently?
No.
Is this a motion sickness patch?
I must've forgotten to take it off.
I just got back from a trip.
Oops.
Scopolamine can cause
dizziness and blurred vision.
You probably hit your head
when you fell
and that caused the blackout.
I thought those patches were supposed
to prevent you from getting sick.
Every drug has a side effect.
But it might be a good idea
to keep your eye on her
for the next few hours
to make sure she's okay.
Oh,actually I--
she has to get back to work.
Is it important?
We just don't like people to be alone
after they leave here.
I'm fine.
Really,I'm-- I'm--
Fran?
Fr-Fran?
I got a seizure. Code cart!
What's wrong with her?
I have no idea.
Where's house?
Antique vintner's cane.
It cost me $900.
It had a corkscrew in it.
Ah,that would explain
the "vintner's" reference.
Could be used as a weapon
against the pilot.
Only if you stuck it
in a bottle of zinfandel.
You'll get it back when we land.
I want my blankie!
Give her 20 milligrams of antihistamine.
It could save her life.
Cause if she doesn't shut up,
I'll kill her.
delivering good
will to yet another continent.
You only forced me to deliver a speech,
not good will.
You gave a three-minute speech.
You know how much
WHO accreditation means to the hospital?
May have been short,
but it had girth.
And the room service thing
was just spiteful.
I was hungry.
- $300 for a bottle of wine.
- Was thirstY.
$120 on video services.
I was lonely.
That's $500 in expenses
I can't justify.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Right.
Here you are,sir.
Welcome aboard.
Mr. House,you're right here in 2a.
Ms. Cuddy,you're in the next cabin
and to the left,9c.
No,I booked two first-class tickets.
This must be a mistake.
No mistake.
Just arranged for a $500 fare reduction.
Expense problem solved.
Where did you travel?
Duluth.
To visity sister.
Really?
Is this her artwork?
fire...butt?
I was a little drunk.
Where were you a little drunk?
I turned 58 last march.
Same age my mother was
when she died.
Next week I packed a bag.
I went to jfk.
Looked at the big board.
Took the first plane
that went to a warm place.
Caracas.
Oh,my god.
Did you drink the water?
Eat salads? Any raw foods?
Yup.
And?
I also did mescal shooters,
and snorted cocaine from
a homosexual man's stomach.
Did you have sex?
No.
Not with him.
I had sex with el gordo.
He was a large man.
Oh,my god.
I never do things like that.
I should have gone to visit my sister.
It was stupid.
That's why I'm sick,isn't it?
Uh...
it's...possible.
Here you are.
Rib eye,medium rare.
Thank you.
Some more pinot grigio?
Uh,no.
I think I will switch to the syrah.
Sir,are you all right?
He's drunk.
See?
[korean]***
Does anyone speak korean?
Is anyone a doctor?
Yes.
I'll go get her.
What do you want?
Did you really think I was gonna leave you
stuck back here for 18 hours?
Go on. Enjoy.
The vicodin and the wine.
I could sleep anywhere.
Thank you.
we should put her back
on the scopolamine patch.
She can't wear motion sickness patches
for the rest of her life.
no,but if it does relieve her symptoms,
it'll narrow down our search.
Ugh,anything else
you two guys want to agree on?
You have a problem with us agreeing?
no,I have a problem with
the other thing you're doing
which makes me question
your motive for agreeing.
I'll put her backon the patch.
What else?
It's got to be something neurological.
We should do a ct and
look for a brain tumor.
It can also be an allergy or
something environmental.
We should check her home.
Bit more likely she got sick in caracas
than in new jersey.
Right,
I forgot there are no toxins in the U.S.
I think I'm starting to feel sorry for house.
Get a tox screen,chem 20,std panel,
blood cultures,
then you run a ct,
and you check her house.
Please.
Not funny.
Wasn't supposed to be funny "ha ha."
Fever,headache,severe abdominal pain,
and a rash
all over his lower back.
It's serious.
It may be contagious.
We just attended a symposium
on pandemics
and you run right into one
on the flight home.
Talk about a small world.
If it's meningococcus,
half the passengers on this plane
could get infected
and die before we reach new york.
Is someone sick?
No.
Someone has a hangover.
He had a snoot-load of bloody
marys before dinner.
Watch the movie.
That booze did not give him the rash.
It is textbook meningococcus.
It's also textbook allergic reaction
to pollen,peanuts,
semen-stained polyester blanket
he's lying on.
Mr. Peng's throwing up again.
We have to turn around.
What?
- Why do we have to turn ar--?
- We don'T.
You misunderstood.
Dr. Cuddy just meant that
he might feel less nauseous
if he was facing in
a different direction.
She didn't mean to
panica plane load of people.
We're about to head over the north pole.
We don't turn back now,
the next er's 15 hours away.
He'll be fine.
I'm a doctor too.
You haven't examined him.
Korean male, mid-thirties, 5'9, 160, bald,
scar on the rightside of his jaw,
medic alert bracelet on his left wrist
indicating that he is allergic to at least,
penicillin.
Without any way to do an lp,
or rule out meningococcus,
our only choice is to assume the worst.
Good point.
On the other hand,
I ama board certified specialist
in infectious disease.
She assigns parking spaces.
Please let me know if he gets any worse.
Think we should feed the cat?
Bowl's full.
If he wants it,he can get it.
Cadmium yellow?
Heavy metal poisoning would explain
the ataxia and the seizures.
Not unless she was painting with her tongue.
Is Foreman right?
Did you agree with me
because of our relationship?
Relationship?
You know what I mean.
You mean because of
our lack of a relationship?
I mean because we're having sex.
Yes,Foreman's right.
I thought you were completely wrong
about the medicine,
but agreed with you anyway,
because I figured then you'd do
mein some old lady's home.
Then well played.
Come on,we're supposed
to be looking for toxins.
We agreed it was a brain tumor.
What?
He's watching.
Haven't you had any body watch before?
Is that guy really sick?
No,he's all better.
I don't believe you.
Look that way.
Why?
Cae you're gonna throw up
and I don't want it on me.
I'll get some towels.
Give her a banana.
Monkey see, monkey barf.
You smell vomit--
okay.
I wasn't expecting that.
I need help.
Who doesn't?
I need someone to talk to.
Can you say...
"crikey, mate"?
Crikey, mate.
Perfect.
No matter what I say,
you agree with me,okay?
O-kay.
Nicely done.
You disagree with everything I say.
Sorry.
Not understanding.
That's close enough.
And you...
get morally outraged at everything I say.
That's permanent marker,you know?
You guys are good.
We are looking for the simplest way
to explain these symptoms.
Organophosphate poisoning.
Some international flights spray pesticides.
Uh, could be.
Sorry, english not so nice.
Is this a joke?
Just passed the halfway mark.
Can't turn around.
- Nice call. - No worries.
We think it's pesticide poisoning.
We don't spray these flights.
Dramamine overdose.
wouldn't explain the fever.
jet lag.
Wouldn't explain the abdominal pain.
Deep vein thrombosis.
wouldn't explain the nausea.
Food poisoning.
What was on the menu?
Steak and sea bass in first class.
Fettuccini and seafood kebabs in economy.
Since when does food poisoning cause a rash?
Sea bass,seafood kebabs?
He had the sea bass.
Please tell me she had the kebabs.
I think so.
Ciguatera poisoning.
It's an instant onset toxin.
Symptoms include'e' all of the above.
It's only found in certain kinds of
tropical gamefish such as...
sea bass?
Make sure you get a resume from him.
Hello.
Excuse me.
ladies and gentlemen,
I have a brief announcement
concerning your meals.
If you ate the sea bass
or the seafood kebabs,
you have ingested a dangerous toxin.
However,if you proceed to the restrooms,
both on your left and right and in the rear of
the plane and vomit as soon as possible,
the toxic effect should be minimal.
Thank you and havea pleasant flight.
Meningococcus makes just as much sense.
I know.
What'd you find?
Nothing in her house.
Big waste of time.
Medically.
Ct was a complete waste.
She was negative for tumors,
her blood was negative for drugs,
heavy metals,
tropical diseases,food poisoning,and stds.
Also no signof lead poisoning or sepsis.
Apparently, venezuelan tattoo parlors
have standards after all.
Good to know.
We sure she's even sick?
Two more seizures in the last two hours.
Which is slower than she was having them
before you put the patch back on.
I'm an idiot.
She's exposed herself to so much crap,
I just assumed it was a zebra.
It's breast cancer.
since when is breast cancer treatable
by motion sickness meds?
It's not.
But the inflammation caused
by the paraneoplastic syndrome
caused by the cancer can be reduced
by anticholinergics.
Hey,here you go.
Is he gonna die?
We're doing all we can.
We don't know what's wrong with him yet.
Am I gonna die?
No.
Here,chew on these.
Good news is
all the pilots are red meat men.
Although I was kind of looking forward
to landing this puppy myself.
Peng's getting worse.
That makes sense.
First class ate before coach.
He digested more
of his food before he threw up.
Or you're wrong and we're gonna start
seeing neurological symptoms soon.
Seizures, paralysis, ataxia.
We're not gonna see ataxia.
You're so sure you're right.
No,it's just hard to show clumsiness
when you're lying moaning in the fetal position.
Hey!
Sss-- stand up!
Nobody speak korean on this flight?
I assumed you did.
I know how to ask him
if his sister's over 18.
I don't think that's gonna help.
Hey!
Stand up!
Stand up.
Don't play the cripple card with me.
*******
Oh,hi.
I'm leaving.
Work.
Oh,okay.
Important client.
Sure.
Um,listen...
are you close?
Why?
She needs a mammogram.
Oh,god.
I know I'm throwing a lot at you.
She just has no family in town.
And I really think
she could use a friend right now.
Okay,put your hand here.
You don't have to stay.
No,it'S...
no problem.
But why?
You don't even know me.
You gotta be scared.
I almost hope it's breast cancer.
No.
Then it wouldn't be my fault.
Whatever it is, it's not your fault.
That's not true.
You can control things.
Not everything.
But you don't have to take stupid risks.
I was being an idiot.
You were having fun.
You have regrets?
Yeah.
robin.
Hold still.
Good.
Okay, we're gonna get just one more.
Sorry, I know it hurts.
It's not that.
It's my eye.
My right eye, I--
I can't see.
it's definitely ataxia.
It's definitely a rash.
You want to look at itfor five more minutes
before concluding it's also definitely a leg.
Thin leg.
It's been in a cast.
So?
So it could be radiation poisoning.
From a broken leg?
From the x-rays they took of it.
He could break every bone in his body
and still not have enough x-rays
to cause radiation sickness.
Unless those x-rays
were performed in "wankoff",
north korea by a third-grade
dropout with a 50-year-old imager.
Which accounts for the absence of fur.
Radiation poisoning accounts for
all the symptoms.
I have hair.
I haven't had an x-ray
since I got my teeth whitened.
You're pregnant.
I'm what?
Explains the nausea, abdominal pains, fever.
And why you're stuffing your 36cs into a 34b bra.
- and her rash?
- Pupps.
A common pregnancy rash.
I can't be pregnant.
You a virgin?
- No,but--
- you're pregnant.
Mazel tov.
Let's get him into the chair.
Two different diagnose
I thought  you didn't believe
in coincidences.
I believe in statistics.
200 passengers on the plane.
10 should be gay,
two should be with child,
and one should be incredibly annoying
with an extra ass chromosome.
House.
Get him some iodized salt to protect his thyroid.
- I'm going back--
- house.
You're wrong.
I said we should've turned back.
You should have listened to me.
Now we're eight miles over the arctic??
I'm trying to listen to you now,
so shut up.
Heart's fine.
Breasts are firm.
is it contagious?
A lot of the passengers are scared.
Tell them there's nothing to worry about.
Is there something to worry about?
Yeah.
Tell them there's nothingto worry about.
Get me a flash light.
Cover your left eye with this.
Mm-- photophobia!
Symptom of meningitis.
We need antibiotics.
I'll call down to the pharmacy.
You're creeping me out.
Then get me a lab.
Pseudomonas smell yeasty.
Staph smells musty.
Some liver diseases smellof ammonia.
House,I'm not in heat.
Citrusy on the nose,
with a blush of toasted coconut.
I need to get a better look at your rash.
Use your imagination.
Fine,shall I gowith lifeguard cuddy
or mother superior cuddy?
Three more passengers are sick.
If we don't get drugs,
we're gonna have a lot of dead passengers.
Blindness in her right eye
indicates it's not breast cancer.
It's likely neurological.
I just met her today.
You should go.
She needs someone here.
That's not your job.
Please let me know that she's okay.
It's just sex.
There's no such thing.
Other eye.
are you saying women can't separate
the physicalfrom the emotional?
No one does it well.
Women do it worse.
You just want us to stop,
because you thinkit's affecting--
me.
Yeah.
Polyspikes over 01 and 02.
That's her left eye.
Burst suppression on every lead.
Fran?
She's comatose.
nothing...
Nothing...
Come on,nody has no meds.
Excuse me.
Open your mouth.
Where is the acyclovir?
I'm not on any meds.
Well,you'd better get some.
You've got herpes.
Oh,what do you know?
He's got some.
This must be your lucky day.
This is for real!
People are sick.
Some of us will be deplaning in body
bags unless you cough up.
Thank you...
thank you.
Thank you.
God bless you.
her brain is shutting down
because of intercranial pressure.
Or her nerves are dying.
Because of the increased pressure.
She has a bleed in her brain.
- You said the ct showed--
- no tumors.
But if she has an avm
leading to a cerebral hemorrhage,
we could have missed it.
She needs a burr holeto relieve??
you want to drill in her brain because of
an invisible bleed the ct couldn't see?
We should do an lp to confirm
the presence of red blood cells.
And her brain herniates and
then she dies.
Right, better to kill herin the or.
Chase,what do you think?
Here's a cliffhanger.
I think it'd help to know what she has
before we start digging into her brain.
Might be betterto play it safe to start.
Do an lp.
Sex better be damn good.
Lotta apples, not many candy bars.
Any antibiotics?
Three caps of augmentin.
There are six patients.
Give them to peng.
He's allergic to penicillin.
The first aid kit has two epi pens.
if he has a severe reaction,
ten epi pens won't save him,
you take the pills.
He's worse.
He's a guy who doesn't speak english.
Give him the meds.
If it's not meningitis,
we're risking his life
and flushing meds down the toilet.
Then do an lp on him.
If it's clear,you win.
If it's cloudy,
he gets the augmentin and
we risk a reaction.
Sounds like a plan.
Oh,except for the part
where we don't have an lp needle.
Oh,and the shaking of the plane means
I'll probably pierce his spinal cord
and cripple him for life,
but,i mean,
it totally sounds like a plan.
You're right.
Let him die.Give me the meds.
Got it.
Damn.
- What is it?
- Shut up.
Don't get hysterical.
Just tell me what the hell it is.
House!
We should have turned back.
We should have turned back!
House!
Hold this.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a passenger with a confirmed
case of bacterial meningitis.
And even if we land as soon as possible,
the passenger will not survive.
It's very likely that some of you
have been infected as well.
As soon as you start feeling symptoms,
we need to isolate you
in the first class cabin.
Fever, rash, nausea,
and in the late stages...
tremor in the left hand.
I have that.
Oh, god.
No!
What do we do?
Break out the bubbly.
Yo! Listen up!
Bad news is you have an illness.
The good news is,it's not meningitis.
It's not fatal.
It's just embarrassing.
It's conversion disorder.
Or commonly known as mass hysteria.
It happens often in high anxiety
situations,especially to women.
I know it sounds sexist,
but science says you're weak and soft,
what can I do?
house, you're wrong.
Look at my hand.
Yeah,look at her hand.Shaking left hand.
What is that a symptom of?
Not meningitis.
It's basically a symptom of nothing.
put the idea into their heads
and watched it happen.
Same thing that peng cruelly did
with the puking and the rash.
The rash is in my head?
Your mind controls your body.
It thinks you're sick,
it makes you sick.
If--if you'll all just calm down,
your symptoms will soon go away.
And to facilitate this process,
your flight crew will move through the cabin
with a complimentary bar service.
Thank you and, as always,
have a pleasant flight.
- Still feel like puking?
- No.
How did you know?
Lp was negative.
I came up with an alternate theory
and I tested it.
Couldn't have done it without you.
Rage is a symptom of mass hysteria.
Just one more thing to clean up.
Peng set off the mass hysteria.
What set off peng?
He really is dying.
Yeah. And I haven't the faintest idea why.
What's extension pastoring?
It's when you're molested
by a priest's cousin.
Do we really need these three?
Worried they'll make you look bad?
Could be symptomatic of head trauma.
Cerebral infarction or
intercranial hemorrhage.Thoughts?
How long till we land?
Too long to wait.
His head's as smooth as a baby's bottom.
No bumps,so I think we
can rule out head trauma.
So you gotta choose between what's left.
Clog or a leak?
you're talking of toilet?
House.
Is this actually helpful?
Not so far.
What about syphilis?
First of all,he apparently speaks
a language that no one else speaks.
Which makes talking up the
ladies a little rough.
We're flying out of singapore.
If he has a credit card and a condom,
he can get anything he wants.
What?
Condoms.
He has focal limb paralysis.
His legs got paralyzed by a condom?
No, by cocaine
that was inside the condom,
and is now spreading
through his digestive tract.
You think he's a mule.
I think he's a jackass.
We're gonna have to operate.
Cool.
They're gonna kill her.
We were wrong.
Which means Foreman was right.
Maybe Foreman's right about us too.
Maybe we should just stop all this.
I mean, if it's affecting our jobs.
It's not affecting our jobs.
We had sex in a patient's bedroom.
A bedroom we were examining for toxins.
Yeah, our judgment's right on the mark.
All right, no more sex at patient's homes.
No more sex with cats watching.
Anywhere else you want
to cross off the list?
- The bowl.
- What?
Has she eaten since she's been here?
She's been sick since she's been here.
What if it's a symptom?
- Why would you think--
- the bowl was full.
you're gonna need to hold him down.
He's not gonna like this.
Do you really think he's a mule?
It fits the symptoms.
You sure he's not contagious?
Pretty much.
Can't be"pretty much" sure.
It means you're not sure.
Oh, aren't you clever?
Well,I know you're
"pretty much" unconscious,
but as it's been pointed out to me,
"pretty much" doesn't mean squat.
Okay, hold him tight.
The faster we do this,
the less likely he is to die of shock.
Tighter.
- Sorry.
- Do that again.
Ease off, then press down.
Pressure on his joints
relieves his pain.
Okay.
Wrong again.
Where's his wallet?
DANGER:PREMISES HAVE BEEN FUMIGATED WITH
METHYL BROMIDE NO ADMITTANCE FOR 72 HOURS
Scuba certification card.
- Big deal.I have one of these.
- Yeah.
Do you alsohave a receipt from
tekong's scubarental dated yesterday?
Tell the captain to drop as
low as he can under 5,000 feet.
- We're at 38,000.We can't--
- peng's got the bends.
He went diving yesterday,
and like an idiot,
he surfaced too quickly.
And like a bigger idiot,
he boarded a flight which is pressurized
to 8,000 feet above sea level.
Low pressure is killing him.
Tell the pilot to dive until we can
club baby seals out of the window.
And get him some oxygen.
Fifty years ago,it was one estate.
The two homes shared an electrical system.
Unfortunately the exterminator
didn't know that,
so when they fumigated next door,
the poison gas flowed through
the old pipe and into your house.
the scopolamine patch was
masking the effects of the poison.
You'll have to stay here
for a few more days,
but after that you should be fine.
I'm sorry about your cat.
And your hair.
For 12 years,
harrington never left the property.
I thought I was being
punished for going away,but
really...
I was being punished for coming home.
Thank you.
I saved your life.You owe me.
I wasn't sick.
But you didn't know that.
You owe me.
I know it now.
Your mind convinced your body to
get a rash,photophobia,and vomit.
How do you know it wouldn't have
shut down your cold,cold heart next?
I don't owe you.
You're mean.
That's how I compensate for being weak...
and soft.
I just wanted to say thank you.
you're extremely welcome.
And I'm in new york every monday.
Are you handicap accessible?
*Stitch in your knitted brow*
*and you don't know how*
hi, robin?
This is, um, uh,
dr. Wilson, f-Fran's doctor.
James.
It was a toxin.
We caught it on time
and she's gonna be fine.
Yeah, it is.
listen, I was just wondering if
you were coming back in again to visit.
- Nice catch.
- Thanks.
Think even house would be impressed.
I don't know about that.
Any idea how you want to celebrate?
What?
I want more.
I thought you were getting a
little worn out, but--
that's not what I meant.
I know.
I was just hoping you'd take the hint
and pretend you never said that.
I want this to be more than it is.
I thought we were clear.
In the beginning,
but you can't tell me you--
yes, i can.
And I don'T.
It was.Fun.That's it.
And now it's over.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-HCµ°?? addychristen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
House
Season 03 Episode 18