Hey, you guys ready to order?
Uh, sure.
Okay, Priya?
Uh, I'll have
the shepherd's pie.
You want to split
that with me?
Oh, no, no, no,
he doesn't.
Why not?
Well, you have milk in
the taters,
milk in the gravy,
parmesan crust.
Your lactose-intolerant
boyfriend will turn
into a gas-filled
Macy's Day balloon.
Not quite accurate. The Macy's
balloons are filled with helium,
whereas Leonard produces copious
amounts of methane.
So, no, on the shepherd's pie.
Can we move on?
Yeah, a little tip:
he says he can eat frozen yogurt.
Do not believe it.
Sea bass!
I'll have the sea bass!
You gotta like this,
the girlfriend and the
ex-girlfriend bonding
over your rooty-tooty
stinky booty.
Kill me.
It wouldn't help.
The human body is capable
of being flatulent for hours
after death.
Guys, sorry I'm late.
I have amazing news.
Bernadette, before you
change the subject,
does anyone have any
final comments on
Leonard's faulty
digestive system?
So, what's your news,
Bernadette?
The thesis committee accepted
my doctoral dissertation.
I'm getting my PhD!
Wow!
Oh, congratulations.
Wow, so that means you're a
doctor, you're a doctor,
you're a doctor,
and Howard,
you know a lot of doctors.
Congratulations, honey.
Thank you.
So, Howard, tell us,
how's it feel knowing
that when you two get married,
you'll be referred to
as Mr. and Dr. Wolowitz?
Unless he takes Bernadette's
last name.
And considering
her advanced status,
that could open
some doors for him.
Please, this isn't about me.
I'm proud of you.
Well, you'll be
really be proud of this.
I was headhunted by a big
pharmaceutical company.
They're gonna pay me
a buttload of money!
What?
Bernadette, that's great.
Howard, do you make a buttload?
Better than what you've
got a buttload of.
Hey, if I roll down the windows
in the car, everything's peachy.
If you do it,
you're still not a doctor.
Yeah, just a heads-up
on the car window deal.
It helps, but everything is
not "peachy."
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 4x24 ?
The Roommate Transmogrification
Original Air Date on May 19, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
? Oh, if there was a problem,
you can't solve it ?
? Check out the hook
while my DJ revolves it ?
? Ice, Ice, baby ?
Oh, God, I feel
ridiculous in this dress.
You look beautiful,
Lieutenant Uhura.
Now prepare for... inspection.
Shh, my brother's
going to hear you.
Relax, he's got
headphones on.
And we're ten miles above
Earth in a starship.
Really, ten miles?
You're orbiting inside
the atmosphere?
Moron.
I can't believe
I'm wearing
my brother's Halloween costume.
I can't believe you think
he only wears it on Halloween.
Open the landing bay doors,
shuttle craft approaching.
Okay, gotta go.
Hey, what's up?
Is that my future
daughter-in-law, the doctor?!
No, Ma! It's Raj!
He's a doctor
too, right?!
Yes!
Like Leonard and
the skinny weirdo!
Sheldon, yes!
Everybody's a doctor but me!
Well, whose fault
is that?!
What's up?
Leonard's putting disgusting
memories in
my memory foam mattress.
Can I stay here tonight?
Sure, but I'm going out
with Bernadette.
It'll just be you and my mother.
I guess that's okay.
Ma, can Rajesh sleep over?!
Of course, he and I
can play doctor!
She's kidding, right?
I don't know, she's pretty
feisty since
they put her on
hormone-replacement therapy.
Paging Dr.
Cutie Pie!
I must say, Amy,
I was very impressed
to see that Bernadette got
her PhD.
It's indeed admirable.
Although, it is...
microbiology.
Your doctorate is in
neurobiology.
I fail to see the distinction.
I'll make it simple for you.
I study the brain,
the organ responsible for
Beethoven's Fifth Symphony.
Bernadette studies yeast,
the organism responsible
for Michelob Lite.
Is there something wrong
with your neck?
It's a little stiff.
What a remarkably fragile
structure
to support
such a valuable payload.
Not unlike balancing a Faberge
egg on a Pixie Stick.
Have you considered massage?
I'd like to respond
to that sarcastically:
Yes, I relish the thought
of a stranger covering my body
with oil and rubbing it.
I was proposing you massage your
muscles with your own hands.
Still sounds like a lot
of unnecessary touching.
Trust me. With your right hand,
locate the spot
where the scapula meets
the acromion process.
All right.
Now push your third finger along
the ridge of the shoulder blade,
making a small rotation
as you do so.
Rotating.
You should feel
a small node-like object
rolling back and forth along
the bone.
You mean the myofascial point?
Obviously.
Now bear down on it like
the seventh grade noogies
we all know too well.
Oh, dear Lord, yes, yes,
oh, yes!
Amy, I've never been touched
like this before!
Oh! My hands are magic!
Don't flatter yourself.
Your hands are blunt tools
guided by my knowledge
of the nervous system.
I could just as easily have
paralyzed you.
There's someone at my door.
That doesn't interest me.
Good-bye.
- Can I sleep here tonight?
- Why?
Leonard's having
astronomically inaccurate
Star Trek sex with my sister.
I can see how that would be
upsetting. Come in.
I'll get the sheets
and blankets for the couch.
Oh, don't bother.
I'll just sleep in Leonard's room.
No, I can't authorize that.
Well, he's in my bed.
Why can't I be in his?
The Hammurabic Code is
"an eye for an eye,"
not "a bed for a bed."
Come on, dude, I'm exhausted,
and Tyra Banks says
the most important item in your
makeup bag is
a good night's sleep.
All right.
This is a form
indemnifying me
from your use of
"Leonard's bedroom."
Sign here, indicating
that I tried to stop you
and did so using
a stern facial expression.
Good night, Sheldon.
Wait. Not yet.
We still have to go over
safety procedures.
Now, the apartment has three
emergency exits located
here, here, and here.
In the event of a power outage,
luminous paint will guide you
to the nearest exit.
You're kidding.
-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-
I never kid about safety.
What are you doing here?
I was sleeping.
In my bed?
Well, I would've slept
in my own bed,
but it was being used
to bring shame to my family.
And the memory
of Gene Roddenberry.
Oh, you heard?
"Scotty, I need more power."
Sorry. Does Sheldon know
you're sleeping in here?
Are you kidding?
He made me sign a waiver,
participate in
an emergency fire drill
and take a refresher course
in CPR.
Thank God he had a dummy.
Oh, yeah.
Mouth-to-Mouth Mona.
You know,
she used to date Howard?
Oh, my God, she's that Mona?
Why can't you and my sister
spend your nights here?
We tried. She doesn't get along
with Sheldon.
Sheldon doesn't get along
It's still no reason
for me to have to listen to you
arm your
photon torpedoes every night.
Okay, well, how about this:
until Priya gets her own place,
you stay here and I'll stay at
your apartment.
Can I bring girls here?
You?
Sure. Bring as many as you want.
Okay, deal.
Just not against their will.
You really think you should be
eating that cake?
Why?
If you're gonna be
a trophy husband
for a rich wife,
you might want
to watch your waistline.
He's right.
A minute on the lips,
a lifetime on the hips.
Yeah, ha-ha.
First of all, I'm not threatened
by my fianc?e's success.
I'm proud of her.
And secondly,
I have my own career.
Until you have kids.
Good news, Raj.
I got the blood work
back from the lab.
You're okay to stay for a while.
When did you take my blood?
Not important.
Your sugar was a little high.
I'd follow up
with your regular physician.
In the meantime, I have some
paperwork here
for you to go over.
What the hell is this?
Boilerplate stuff.
A modified roommate agreement
for a temporary house guest.
And a living will and durable
power of attorney.
This says you can make
nd o of li" decisions for me.
As your friend, let's hope it
doesn't come to that.
Please sign.
Did you sign this?
There's a reciprocity
clause.
You get to pull
the plug on him, too.
Well, that seems fair.
Congratulations and welcome
temporarily aboard.
Here's your I.D. card,
your key and your lapel pin.
Which Leonard was
too cool to wear.
FYI, part of your
responsibilities
as roommate pro tem
will be to drive me
to and from work, the comic book
store, the barbershop
and the park for one hour every
other Sunday for fresh air.
Bring a ball or a Frisbee,
you know, something
he can chase.
Also, you're tasked
with bringing home
all takeout dinners.
Tonight is Thai food.
You'll find the standard order
in appendix B
or downloadable
from my FTP server.
If you have
any questions,
here's the FAQ sheet,
or if you prefer
the human touch,
I do a live web chat called
"Apartment Talk"
on Tuesday nights.
No backsies.
Sheldon, dinner!
What is this?
This is the difference
between
eating and dining.
Remarkable.
I'm just realizing how much
Leonard's been skating by
all these years.
It's not a big thing.
Just think of me as
a brown Martha Stewart.
Hey, Sheldon,
did you change
your Wi-Fi password again?
Yes, it's "Penny, get your
own Wi-Fi." No spaces.
Thanks.
Wow! What's with
the fancy spread?
My new roommate
is bending over backwards
to ingratiate himself to me.
Uh, nice touch,
by the way.
What do you mean "new roommate"?
What happened to Leonard?
The same thing that happened
to Homo erectus.
He was replaced
by a superior species.
I'm the new Homo in town.
That came out wrong.
All right, let me try this
again. Where's Leonard?
He's living at my place,
so I'm living here.
You're living here
provisionally.
But I must say
it's looking good.
Oh Leonard and Priya
are living together?
That's big.
No. Origami napkin swans...
that's the headline.
It's a good thing.
So do you know what kind
of research you'll be doing
at this pharmaceutical
company?
Well, there are a couple of
opportunities available,
but I volunteered for the
premature ejaculation project.
I mean, it's not like either
one of us has heart disease.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I got you a little present.
Oh, Bernie, no.
You didn't have to.
I wanted to.
Come on, open it.
You bought me a Rolex?
How much did this cost?
Oh, you let me worry
about the money.
I just want my baby
to have pretty things.
More wine?
Oh, no, no, no. I've had
way too much already.
Here's an interesting
fact about alcohol...
Hit me.
Man is not the only species
that ferments fruit
in order to become intoxicated.
Can you guess what the other is?
sometimes they pack
the alcohol
in their trunks.
Monkeys.
When does a monkey
have a trunk?
When a suitcase just won't do.
Mmm, all right.
It would appear as if alcohol
is playing keep-away
with your intelligence.
Good night.
Please note,
it is now past 10:00 p.m.
Per our roommate agreement,
kindly refrain
from raucous laughter,
clinking of glasses,
and celebratory gunfire.
Okay...
explain something to me.
You watch Leonard put up with
that guy for years and years.
What has to break inside
your brain for you to think,
"Oh, Krishna, I've got to
get me some of that"?
Well, it's a lot better than
having to wear noise-cancelling
headphones in my own apartment.
What? Oh, God, yeah. Yeah.
Leonard's a noisy little dude
in the sack.
Every night.
Really?
Even during allergy season,
when he has to alternate
between kissing and breathing?
It's my sister. Can we not
talk about this anymore?
Yeah. Sorry, sorry.
Can I tell you a secret?
Yeah.
I screwed up.
Leonard's a great guy.
Never should have
broken up with him.
Well, uh, to paraphrase
"It's better to have
loved and lost
"than to stay home every night
and download
increasingly shameful
pornography."
Ohh... you poor baby.
What's wrong with me, Penny?
Nothing, nothing.
You know, if we weren't friends,
and you hadn't brought up
that creepy pornography story,
I'd be on you like
the speed of light squared
on matter to make energy.
Hey, you totally got that right!
"E=mc2."
I listen.
I have no idea what it means,
but I listen.
To friendship.
Would you booze hounds
please stop that infernal clinking?!
And the answer
was elephant!
Mmm.
Leonard, sweetheart, we're
kissing, not eating hot soup.
Sorry.
That's my parents
on video chat.
Go hide
in the bedroom.
Oh, come on!
Why don't we just tell
them that we're dating?
Oh, we've been through this.
It's not the time.
When is the time?
I've got five brothers
and sisters.
One of them is bound
to screw up real big,
and then I'll tell my parents
about you. Now, shoo.
Fine.
Hello, Mummy. Hello, Daddy.
We heard there was a tornado
in Kansas City.
Is that close to you?
No.
Where is your brother?
Out with friends.
I don't like it, a young girl
alone in an apartment.
I'll sleep so much better when
you move back here next month.
You're moving
back to India?!
Who's that?
Oh, my God! There's someone
in your apartment.
Call the police in America!
When were you going
to tell me about this?
Oh, hello, Leonard.
What a pleasant surprise!
Mummy, Daddy, you remember
Rajesh's friend Leonard.
I thought you said Rajesh
was out with his friends.
He has many friends.
Rajesh has many friends?
Why are you lying to us?
She's lying because she doesn't
want you to know we're dating.
Leonard!
Well, what difference
does it make? If you're
moving back to India,
we're obviously breaking up.
You know what?
I don't want to deal
with this right now.
So...
Hot in India?
Of course it is.
It always is. It's India.
Now, what do you have
to say for yourself?
Uh...
That is a beautiful tapestry.
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
Oh.
Okay, look.
This never happened.
Do you understand me?
Really?! Still
can't talk to me?
What are you
doing here?
What?
I said, what are you doing here?
I live here.
I have paperwork
that says differently.
Priya's going back to India.
Irrelevant.
Rajesh and I have
a good thing going
and you're not going to ruin it.
What are you doing here?
I've been up all night.
- I had a fight with Bernadette.
- Why?
She gave me
a beautiful watch.
Leonard, do you
understand this?
Yes.
Talk to him.
Damn.
What's going on?
Oh...
It's-it's not what
it looks like.
What does it look like?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org