Ma, Ma, calm down.
Listen to me.
I know it says click
with the mouse,
but on a laptop,
the trackpad is the mouse.
Now, put your finger on it.
Doesn't matter which finger.
Good choice.
Now move it down
to your e-mail icon.
Yeah, the little envelope.
What do you mean,
"What does it look like?"
It looks like an envelope!
Fine, you don't like
the computer,
don't use it!
Sure, we can exchange it
for a salad spinner. Good-bye!
That's a Hanukkah present
you're regretting, huh?
I won't say that
all senior citizens
who can't master technology
should be publicly flogged,
but if we made an
example of one or two,
it might give the others
incentive to try harder.
I had a great idea.
You know how
we're always having
to stop and solve
differential equations,
like when you're doing
Fourier analysis,
or using the
Schrodinger equation?
Howard doesn't.
He's only an engineer.
I was thinking,
we could write a little app
that would use
handwriting recognition,
and then run it through a
symbolic evaluation engine.
You just use your smartphone,
take a picture
of the equation and bam!
You know what's a great app?
The one that makes fart noises.
You know, Leonard,
that's actually
a valid idea.
Very good.
Can you say that and not
make it sound like I'm a cat
who learned
how to use the toilet?
No.
The two achievements
are equally surprising
and equally admirable,
though if pressed,
I'd have to give
a slight edge to the cat.
I'll save you the pain
and nervousness
of waiting for the answer.
I agree to be part of
your project. Congratulations.
Oh, yay for me.
What about you guys?
I can't promise anything,
but people do make money
off stuff like this.
A few extra bucks
would be nice.
I could finally move out
of my mother's house.
Where would you go?
I always dreamed about building
a little place of my own
over the garage.
You know, if I made more money,
I could take time off from work
and give pretty girls
submarine rides.
What's that?
Some weird sex thing?
No.
You take pretty girls underwater
in your private submarine,
and you show them fish.
Why does everything
have to be dirty with you?
I was thinking we could work
on this at night,
and then maybe
in a couple of weeks,
we'll have ourselves an app
to sell.
Sounds like
we're in business.
I think we should take a picture
to capture this moment.
Yeah.
Oh!
Was that the best 99 cents
I ever spent, or what?
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 4x12 ?
The Justice League Recombination
Original Air Date on January 6, 2011
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
I checked the
App Store.
No one is doing
handwriting-recognition
differential equation solving.
Oh, dear Lord, shush.
What?
You have so few good ideas,
Leonard.
And you're just going
to spill the beans
in front of an outsider?
Who, me?
Sheldon, I don't think
Penny cares
about handwriting-recognition
based differential...
? The stars at night
are big and bright ?
? Deep in the heart
of Texas... ?
She's not going
to steal our idea.
What idea?
We're gonna write an application...
? The prairie sky
is wide and high ?
? Deep in the heart... ?
Okay, stop, stop!
? Of Texas. ?
Whatever your secret is,
I'm sure it's boring,
so I'm not interested.
It's not boring at all.
You see,
in higher order mathematics,
there are certain sets
of equations that...
Bored.
Satisfied?
Hardly.
Consider this unlikely
but very plausible scenario.
A young woman alone
in the big city.
Her ridiculous dream
of becoming an actress
lies shattered about her.
Hey, wait a minute.
Well, hang on. Let's
see where he's going.
Then it hits her.
How is she going to survive?
I mean, she has no prospects,
no marketable skills.
And then one day,
she meets a group of geniuses
and their friend Howard.
Hey, I...
Hang on.
Let's see where he's going.
She befriends them,
and then lies in wait
until they reveal
a marketable idea,
which she steals
and sells to the highest bidder.
- That is ridiculous.
- Oh, is it?
Let's see you come up
with an explanation
as to why this woman hangs out
with us all the time.
Oh, great. You know what?
I've already mooched
dinner off you guys.
I don't need to listen to this.
There's your answer--
free food.
All right,
I've taken the liberty
of drafting
these workflow charts
which outline our various duties
and the path we will follow
as we develop
our ground-breaking new app.
Hey, why am I in charge
of phone support?
Seems a bit racist.
A customer service
representative
with an Indian accent
will create the impression
we're a vast enterprise that
uses overseas call centers.
Oh.
Very clever.
But still racist.
Duly noted, Steve
from Wichita.
Why am I listed as your
executive assistant?
Because the word "secretary"
has fallen into disrepute.
FYI, my mother's
birthday is coming up.
I'm going to need you
to pick up a present.
Okay, we need
to stop for a minute.
Leonard, please,
we can talk during our break.
We have one coming up
at midnight.
We'll need snacks.
Sheldon, you're not in charge.
It's my idea.
I'm in charge.
Oh, of course you are.
Look at the organizational
chart.
You're clearly listed
as founder.
Well, yes, and you're listed
as Chief Executive Officer,
Chief Financial Officer
and Chief Operating Officer.
You missed
Chief Science Officer,
Chairman of the Board, and Head
of the Secret Santa Committee.
Okay.
You need to get clear
on this right now.
I am in charge of this project.
Ooh. Leonard's going all
alpha nerd on Sheldon's ass...
All right. All right,
I'm not going to argue with you.
Sheldon Cooper is nothing
if not a team player.
Dr. Hofstadter,
you have the conn.
Thank you.
I thought we might start
by talking
about the user interface.
Oh, dear Lord, we're doomed.
So this button here
will allow you
to scan a new equation,
but over here,
you can press this,
and just substitute new values
for the coefficients.
Good one, boss.
What?
This diagram.
I assume
you were opening with a joke.
It certainly buoyed up
this employee's esprit de corps.
It's not a joke.
It's the real design.
In that case, may I offer
27 little tweaks
to make it
slightly less embarrassing?
Sheldon, I think
this will work.
Let's just try it my way.
Oh, I'm-I'm sorry.
I assumed that you wanted
candid truth-telling
from your employees,
but I realize now,
you want the mindless nattering
of complacent
yes-men.
Are you done?
If you say so, boss.
So right now,
this button-press event
is just triggering
a dummy procedure call...
How about this
for the app name?
The Surprisingly
Helpful Equation-Linked
Differential
Optimized Numerator.
So it spells "Sheldon."
Does it?
A happy accident.
We're not doing
names now. Howard?
Like I was saying, right now
it's just a dummy procedure,
but eventually,
it will drop us into...
All right, fine.
If we're not going
to give it a name,
can we at least give it
a secret code designation?
- No.
- Hear me out.
The atomic bomb
was The Manhattan Project.
Windows 95 was originally
Project Chicago.
For our app, I would humbly
suggest Project Nodlehs.
That's just
"Sheldon" backwards.
Another happy accident.
We're not wasting time
with names right now.
I see.
Is that decision open
for discussion?
No.
Is the decision to not
discuss it open for discussion?
No.
Again,
right now it's just
a dummy procedure,
but eventually,
it will drop us into...
I call for a vote
of no confidence
and an immediate change
in leadership.
Sheldon, stop it.
When in the course of human
events, it becomes necessary
to dissolve the bonds
that tie three competent
scientists together...
That's enough, Sheldon.
All right, let's get right to the vote.
Show of hands--
all those opposed
to Leonard
and his reign of tyranny.
Okay, that's it, you're fired.
Really?
Why?
Because you're impossible
to work with.
I see.
And is that open
for discussion?
What are you doing?
Oh. Good morning, shoemaker.
I think you'll be pleased
with what the elves were up to
last night.
I fired you.
Oh, I know. I'm now
an independent contractor.
No, you are
now nothing.
You have no connection
to this project whatsoever.
But I made it better.
I don't want it better.
I want it my way.
Well, that speaks volumes,
doesn't it?
All right, I suppose
I'll go put on my bus pants.
What the hell are bus pants?
They are pants one wears
over one's regular pants
when one sits on bus seats
that other people
have previously sat on.
But perhaps
from your lofty heights
atop the corporate ladder,
you've lost touch
with the struggles
of the common man.
Look, I'm still happy
to drive you to work.
Nothing's changed
in that regard.
We're still roommates,
we're still friends.
Except you identified me,
your best friend,
as a gangrenous limb
that needed to be severed
from the organism
and tossed away.
The desperate act
of a little man
with a big Napoleon complex.
You know what?
Go put on your bus pants.
Mm. Last night,
I had a dream
we got so rich from the app,
you and I bought matching
side-by-side mansions.
But...
there was a secret tunnel
connecting your front yard
to my back yard.
What do you think that means?
It means after we play handball,
I'm showering at home.
Good morning, Friend Howard.
Friend Raj.
I see you gentlemen
are enjoying beverages.
Perhaps they would taste better
out of these.
"World's Greatest
Astrophysicist"?
Don't thank me. You earned it.
"Howard Wolowitz."
Why not
"World's Greatest Engineer"?
I'm sorry.
I typed that
into the label maker,
but I just couldn't press enter.
Now down to business.
What would it take for you
to abandon Leonard
and join me in a rival company?
Unless, of course,
the mugs are sufficient,
in which case, welcome aboard.
We're not quitting on Leonard.
I understand.
Your loyalty is admirable.
But what if I were
to up the ante?
What are you talking about?
Monogrammed key chains
with a built-in laser pointer.
No?
How about can cozies
emblazoned
with our university mascot?
Go, Beavers.
I'll be back.
Okay, let's try this one.
"Spherical Hankel function."
Hold on.
That's it!
Eureka!
Hey, we agreed when
it was "Eureka" time,
we were all gonna
say it together.
Fine.
Let's say it together.
No. The moment
has passed.
Greetings, gentlemen.
How goes your
little project?
You mean,
"Project Lenwoloppali"?
Ah, a combination
of all your names.
Very clever.
I assume "Koothranardowitz"
was taken?
We're actually
scanning equations
and getting good results.
Oh, well then,
by all means, carry on.
I wouldn't want
to impede your progress.
Howard, did you solve
the install time problem yet?
No. It's a little tricky.
I'm gonna try having it pick up
the libraries dyn...
What are you doing?!
Playing the theremin.
No. I mean, what are you
doing with a theremin?
Playing it.
I've loved the theremin
from the first moment
I heard the original
Star Trek theme.
And it's been killing me
that it just sits in my closet,
gathering dust.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Sheldon!
We're working here!
That's all right.
I can barely hear you
over my theremin.
Well, that was a
little uncalled for.
No, that was
completely called for.
We need quiet.
So, your project is more
important than mine?
Well, seeing as your project
is to sabotage my project, yes.
Don't beat around the bush,
Leonard.
If you don't want me here,
just say the word,
and I'll leave.
Could have beaten
around the bush a little.
? Nobody knows ?
? The trouble I've seen ?
? Nobody knows my sorrow ?
? Oh, oh, oh. ?
What you doing?
Trying to contact
your home planet?
I'm practicing my theremin.
Oh.
? Nobody knows ?
? The trouble I've seen ?
? Glory, hallelujah. ?
Something got you down,
there, Sheldon?
Leonard kicked me out
of my own apartment.
And his app team.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
He wouldn't drive me
to work today.
I had to wear
my bus pants.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
And they're
still sticky.
Aw...
Probably going to have
to throw them away.
Hey, you don't need
Leonard and his app.
You can make one with me.
With you?
Seriously,
I have a great idea for one.
Is it better than your idea
to move to Los Angeles
and become a famous actress?
Okay, look...
when you see someone
wearing shoes you like,
you just snap a picture of them,
and the app goes on the Internet
to find out
where you can buy them.
That's your app idea?
Well, you don't like it?
I didn't say that.
But no, I don't.
Why not?
Oh, Penny,
where do I begin?
The simple-mindedness
of your idea
is exceeded only by its
crass consumerism and banality.
And Leonard didn't want
to work with you?
Imagine that.
I know, it's baffling.
? Nobody knows ?
? The trouble I've seen... ?
Sheldon, I'm gonna
make some cocoa.
Do you want some?
Do you make it
with milk or water?
- Milk.
- Real cocoa?
That's what it says
on the packet.
Do you have
those little marshmallows?
No, sorry.
Well, I suppose
it's appropriate.
What does that mean?
A disappointing drink
for a disappointing day.
Hey, look at this.
20 people from the university
have already signed up
for our private beta.
I'm telling you,
the Lenwoloppali
Differential Equation Scanner
meets a real need.
We've got a hit.
What do you think we
should sell it for?
Well, based on the fact
that our potential market
is about 70 or 80 guys,
and you want a submarine,
I'd say about a
million dollars a pop.
Well, what if we put out a lite
version for half a million?
You know,
get the word of mouth going.
Hi. I'm sorry
to bother you guys,
but you've got to come
take your Sheldon back.
What's he doing
in your apartment?
Well, he was moping down in the
lobby, so I invited him over.
Now I regret it.
Why do you regret...
Uh, never mind, stupid question.
Look, can't you just let him
play with you until bedtime?
We're not playing.
This is real work.
We're going to
be hundred-aires.
Okay. What if I got him
to apologize
and promise to behave?
Then I guess we would
let him back on the app team,
and while we're doing that,
you could take an aerial tour
of L.A. on your flying pig.
Okay. Wait right here.
I'll tell you one thing.
If I get rich enough,
that's the kind of girl I want
to take on a submarine ride.
And yes, that time,
I meant it to be dirty.
Really?
Leonard wants me back?
Oh, yes. He says they
are lost without you.
Well, we sure saw that coming.
That's right.
You know what
I'm going to do?
I am going to sit here
and just let them stew.
No, no, no. You know,
they have
suffered enough.
Everybody's
The thing is, you're going
to have to offer him
a face-saving
way out of this.
How?
Say you're sorry.
Oh, no.
Mrs. Mary Cooper
didn't raise her no liars.
Okay. Um...
How about this? You know
how you're always trying
to learn about sarcasm?
No.
No?
I was being sarcastic.
Oh. Good for you.
So all you have to do here
is say you're sorry to Leonard,
but say it
sarcastically.
Of course.
He will hear it as an attempt
to mend fences,
as opposed
to the withering condemnation
you and I will know it to be.
Yeah. Yeah, that
was my plan.
All right.
Come on. Let's go.
Oh, by the way,
thank you
for the delicious cocoa.
Oh, you're welcome.
Boy, I'm getting
good at this.
Okay, now that you're
back on the team,
let's get you caught up.
Before you begin,
let me say again
how deeply sorry I am
for my earlier behavior
and how much I respect
and admire your leadership.
Thank you.
So as you can see,
not only can you store
your favorite equations,
but you can forward them
to your friends
or post them on Facebook
right from the app.
Well, I must say,
I am impressed.
Thanks.
You all have clearly put
in a lot of hard work.
We have.
As a result,
you have taken
the most important step
on the road to success:
learning what not to do.
Now, let's start fresh.
Howard, we're going
to need some tea.
Okay, these are Uggs.
These are Crocs.
These are knockoff
Manolo Blahniks.
Bored.
Look, you said it yourself,
we have to create a database
before you can write
an alga-thingy.
Algorithm.
You see, Penny, Alan Turing
defined an algorithm...
Bored.
Okay.
These are Steve Maddens.
These are Nine West.
These are Target. Oh, but don't
they look like Chanel?
These are
Michael Kors...
? Nobody knows... ?
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org