All right, I'm ready
for my next question.
In a world where rhinoceroses
are domesticated pets,
who wins the Second World War?
Uganda.
Defend.
Kenya rises to power
on the export of rhinoceroses.
A Central African
power block is formed,
colonizing North Africa and Europe.
When war breaks out, no one can
afford the luxury of a rhino.
Kenya withers, Uganda triumphs.
Correct.
My turn.
In a world where a piano is a weapon,
not a musical instrument,
on what does Scott Joplin
play "The Maple Leaf Rag"?
Tuned bayonets.
Defend.
Isn't it obvious?
You're right. My apologies.
What the hell are you guys playing?
It's a game we invented.
It's called Counterfactuals.
We postulate an alternate
world that differs from ours
in one key aspect and then
pose questions to each other.
It's fun for ages eight to 80.
Join us.
All right.
I like a good brainteaser.
Give it a whirl.
You're in luck;
this is an easy one.
In a world where mankind is ruled
by a giant intelligent beaver,
what food is no longer consumed?
Uh... a BLT where the
"B" stands for beaver?
I don't know.
Leonard, be serious.
We're playing a game here.
I can figure this out.
Let's see.
Um, well, beavers eat tree bark.
The only tree bark I know that
humans consume is cinnamon.
So, I'll say cinnamon.
Incorrect.
Obviously, the answer
is cheese Danish.
What?
In a world ruled by a giant beaver,
mankind builds many dams to
please the beaver overlord.
The low-lying city of
Copenhagen is flooded.
Thousands die.
Devastated, the Danes never
invent their namesake pastry.
How does one miss that?
This is ridiculous.
You're just making stuff up.
Is he always like
this when he loses?
Oh, yes.
You should've been here for the
great Jenga tantrum of 2008.
You bumped the table
and you know it.
Perhaps it would be
kinder to play a game
more suited to his abilities.
We'll close our eyes and
count to ten while you hide.
I'm going to my room.
Very good, Leonard.
But next time, don't tell
us where you're hiding.
? Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ? ? We
built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 4x03 ?
The Zazzy Substitution
Original Air Date on October 7, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Did you guys see the paper
in The American Physics
Journal on supersolids?
It's pretty interesting.
This guy's working from
a hypothesis where...
Spoiler alert! Spoiler alert.
What? Don't ruin it for me, man.
I printed out a PDF
to read on the potty.
On the potty?
What are you, five?
It's a potty. What do you call it?
Toilet.
That's a little vulgar for
the dinner table, don't you think?
Oh, and "potty" is okay?
"Potty" is innocent.
"Potty" is adorable.
What do you do in the potty,
wee-wee?
If I don't have to boom-boom.
Greetings.
You all remember Amy Farrah Fowler.
Nice to see you. Hello.
Sorry we're late.
I must take responsibility.
I had to stop for
feminine hygiene supplies.
Aha. Okay.
I believe she's
experiencing her menses.
Actually, I'm not.
In order to avoid surprises,
I wear them all the time.
Aha. Okay.
"Toilet's" sounding
pretty good now, huh?
Hey, look, it's Shamy.
Shamy?
A juvenile amalgamation
of our names.
Sheldon, Amy-- Shamy.
Oh.
I don't like that.
Don't do that.
All righty. What's new?
Well, just recently, I learned
that you refer to us as Shamy,
and I don't like that.
I got it.
But what I was going for was,
you know, how's your life?
Like everybody else's.
Subject to entropy,
decay and eventual death.
Thank you for asking.
Why is she not taking our order?
I should've warned you,
one has to navigate a
labyrinth of social nonsense
before one can be fed here.
Really?
I assumed an establishment called
the Cheesecake Factory would
function more efficiently.
It's how they lure you in.
I believe it's called "
bait and switch."
Okay, I'm just gonna walk away,
'cause... I don't want to be here.
So, this is nice.
First time we've all
gotten together to eat.
You're right, he's a
festival of humdrum chitchat.
Okay, that's all I got.
Howard, you're up.
Um... tell us about your work, Amy.
I doubt you'd understand.
Sheldon tells me you only
have a master's degree.
Raj, do you have any
questions for Amy?
I'm curious as to why
we're not eating alone.
They can't function without me.
I'm the social glue that holds
this little group together.
You're welcome.
Listen, can I talk to you
about your girlfriend?
She's not my girlfriend.
She's a girl and she's my friend,
but there's no touching or
unsanitary exchange of saliva.
Got it.
Although, for the record,
on one occasion,
she licked her thumb to
remove raspberry jelly
from the corner of my mouth.
It's an action we both
regret to this day.
Uh-huh.
Anyway, I'm not sure
she's the best fit
for our little-- how should
we call it-- rebel alliance.
Oh, I never identified
with the rebel alliance.
Despite their tendency
to build Death Stars,
I've always been more
of an empire man.
Yeah, not my point.
I know what your point is.
You're intimidated
by Amy's intellect.
To that I say, buck up.
Okay, let me just
get right to it.
Amy is judgmental,
sanctimonious and frankly...
just obnoxious.
So?
So we already have
you for all that.
Are you suggesting I terminate
my relationship with Amy?
No, no, of course not.
Just have your relationship
someplace else.
May I point out that
for eight long months,
I suffered in silence
as your female companion
filled our apartment with her
off-key country music caterwauling,
the unappetizing spectacle
of her grinding a pumice stone
against her calloused feet
in our living room,
and night after night of
uninformative TV documentaries
about the Jersey Shore.
Suffered in silence?
Yes.
And I'd thank you to do the same.
Reall-- Silence?!
Ah.
Nothing makes beer
taste better than
cool clear Rocky
Mountain spring water.
Where are the Rocky
Mountains, anyway?
Philadelphia.
Really?
I thought they were
out West someplace.
Think about it, Raj.
Where did the movie
Rocky take place?
Philadelphia.
Okay, now I get it.
So this is the plan?
From now on, we're just
gonna hide out in here
to avoid the Shamy?
I'm very comfortable here.
Penny, dear, why don't you shoot
another silver bullet my way?
Get one yourself.
Ooh, somebody's been
taking bitchy pills.
God, he's an ass when he drinks.
Oh, he's an ass when he doesn't.
You just don't hear it.
Think we need to start
entertaining the possibility
that the Shamy could
go on for years.
Well, if that's the case,
Penny will have to get satellite TV
and maybe once a week run a
vacuum through this place.
I thought you were going
to talk to Sheldon.
I did. Well, what'd he say?
Well, he pointed out that
he kinda sorta had to...
put up with you.
Kinda sorta had to?
I didn't agree with him.
Well, you defended me, right?
I tried, but...
...he made a fairly
well-reasoned argument.
You're not doing that right.
What?
Gimme.
No. Trust me.
No! I do this for
my mom all the time.
See?
With the grain.
Wow, that is better.
And someday, when you
have varicose veins,
I'll show you how to massage them.
Oh, God, never again.
I assume by "never again,
" you mean never again will you drink
all of Penny's beer,
then run down to the gas station
for a couple of 40s,
a box of Slim Jims
and the latest issue of
Bombay Badonkadonks.
I was homesick.
The highlight of the evening
was when you showed us
your Bollywood break
dancing skills.
That's very offensive.
Yeah, we all thought so.
Oh, no.
What?
It's John and Yoko.
More like Yoko and Yoko.
Greetings. Hey.
I brought Amy here
to show her some of
the work I'm doing.
It's very impressive,
for theoretical work.
Do I detect a hint
of condescension?
I'm sorry, was I being too subtle?
I meant compared to the
real-world applications
of neurobiology,
theoretical physics is--
what's the word I'm looking for?--
hmm, cute.
Are you suggesting the
work of a neurobiologist
like Babinski could ever
rise to the significance
of a physicist like
Clarke-Maxwell or Dirac?
I'm stating it outright.
Babinski eats Dirac for breakfast
and defecates Clarke-Maxwell.
You take that back.
Absolutely not.
My colleagues and I are mapping
the neurological
substrates that subserve
global information processing,
which is required for
all cognitive reasoning,
including scientific inquiry,
making my research ipso facto
prior in the ordo cognoscendi.
That means it's better
than his research,
and by extension, of course, yours.
I'm sorry, I'm-I'm still trying
to work on the defecating
Clark Maxwell, so...
Excuse me, but a
grand unified theory,
insofar as it explains everything,
will ipso facto
explain neurobiology.
Yes, but if I'm successful,
I will be able to map and
reproduce your thought processes
in deriving a grand unified theory,
and therefore, subsume your
conclusions under my paradigm.
That's the rankest psychologism,
and was conclusively
revealed as hogwash
by Gottlob Frege in the 1890s!
We appear to have
reached an impasse.
I agree.
I move our relationship
terminate immediately.
Seconded.
There being no objections...
Uh-uh.
...the motion carries.
Good day, Amy Farrah Fowler.
Good day, Sheldon Cooper.
Women, huh?
Can't live with them,
can't successfully
refute their hypotheses.
Amen to that.
Hey, Sheldon.
Hello.
I hear you broke up with Amy.
A breakup would imply
she was my girlfriend.
She was a girl who was my friend
who is now a girl who
is not my friend.
Wow. That's like the
worst country song ever.
So, how are you doing?
Regarding what?
Amy.
I don't follow.
Well, breakups-- or whatever the
hell this is-- can be tough.
Penny, I assure you, I'm fine.
My relationship with Amy
was purely intellectual,
There were no emotional bonds,
the severing of which would
cause me any discomfort.
The relationship simply
outlived its utility,
and I'm continuing on
with my life as before.
Okay. Good.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm off to buy a pussycat.
I gotta tell you guys,
I'm a little worried about Sheldon.
We're all a little
worried about Sheldon.
No, I mean since the
Shamy hit a reef.
Oh, I thought you were just
making a generalization:
"You know,
I'm worried about Sheldon
"someday setting off a
low-yield nuclear device
because the cafeteria
ran out of lime Jell-O."
What does "hit a reef" mean?
Uh, went splitsville.
Pardon?
Turned to boom-boom.
Ah.
I think Sheldon really misses Amy.
You should lend him your copy of
Bombay Badonkadonks.
He got a cat to keep him company.
You're kidding.
He takes it everywhere:
to bed, to the bathroom.
He takes the kitty to the potty?
I thought we discussed the P-word.
Don't try to change me, dude.
I am what I am.
Oh, gentlemen.
Hey. Aren't you going
to introduce us
to your little friend?
My apologies.
Raj, Howard, I'd like you to meet Dr.
Robert Oppenheimer.
Hello. Hi.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
the father of the atomic
bomb wants a saucer of milk.
Okay, I get it.
We're worried about Sheldon.
Yeah.
Hey.
Oh, no.
Robert Oppenheimer was lonely.
So you decided to get the
whole Manhattan Project?
but he's so zazzy.
Okay, we need to talk.
About what?
Cats, Sheldon.
You're clearly upset
about Amy being gone,
and you're trying to replace
her with a bunch of cats.
Clowder. What?
A group of cats is a clowder.
Or a glaring.
Okay, yeah, fine.
It's the kind of thing you ought
to know now that we have one.
Terrific. My point is,
you need to face up
to what you're feeling
with this breakup.
It wasn't a breakup.
A breakup would imply that
Amy was my girlfriend.
Okay, I got it, I got it;
she's not your girlfriend.
Now listen to me.
I know about loneliness.
I know about trying to replace
someone with other stuff.
When I broke up with Penny,
I got back into my cello,
I built a bunch of model rockets,
I got those weightlifting gloves
and that five-pound dumbbell.
You didn't break up,
she dumped you.
She didn't dump me.
It was mutual!
I was there. She dumped you.
Okay, fine.
Live with cats.
Be like my Aunt Nancy.
She had dozens of them.
And do you know what happened
after she died? They ate her.
You don't have to sell
me on cats, Leonard.
I'm already a fan.
All right, fellas,
who's in the mood for Fancy Feast?
Well, that's not fancy at all.
Hi, Mrs. Cooper. Thanks for coming.
Where is he?
He's in his bedroom.
Now, when you said on the phone
he broke up with a girl,
you meant an actual girl,
not something you kids
whipped up in a lab?
No, she's real.
Did they sin?
No, no, it's not like that.
It's, uh...
I don't know what it's like.
But there is something I
should prepare you for.
Oh, relax, Leonard,
I have raised that boy.
I've seen him at his best,
I've seen him at his worst.
There's nothing he can
do that'll surprise me.
Hold on to that thought.
Come in.
Surprise.
Mom, what an unexpected pleasure.
My, my, that's a powerful smell.
I'd like you to meet Oppenheimer,
Frisch, Panofsky,
Feynman, Weisskopf...
Yeah, I get it.
You got a lot of cats
and you gave 'em cute Jewish names.
What are you doing here?
Leonard called.
And he said that you were
pining for a young lady.
Oh, that's preposterous.
I'm not pining over anyone.
Oh, lambchop, we can
quibble what to call it,
but I think we can
both agree it's creepy.
I do not agree.
Cats make wonderful companions.
They don't argue or question
my intellectual authority,
and this little guy here,
I think you'll find
to be quite zazzy.
You should have called sooner.
Shelly! Dinner's ready!
Coming!
No cats!
Aw...
What is she doing here?
I called her.
Your mother thinks
you might be losing
your mind over me.
As a neurobiologist, I was curious.
Well, rest assured, I am in
full possession of my faculties.
25 cats!
Oh, God bless you, dear.
Sheldon, sit down. Let's talk.
All right, but you're
not fooling me.
Whenever you say we have to talk,
it means you want me to listen.
Then stop talking.
Yes, ma'am.
Now, the reason I
called Amy over was
to find out what type
of person she is.
And after chatting a bit,
I have to say that while she is a
perfectly unique young woman,
you two are definitely not
suited for each other.
That's a peculiar conclusion.
By any standard,
Amy is more similar to me
than anyone I've ever met.
Oh, I'm sorry, Shelly,
I can't see it.
Well, whether you see
it or not is irrelevant.
I can't see subatomic particles,
but nevertheless, they're there.
Excellent point.
A physics point.
Touch?.
Well, putting aside the pig Latin,
it's a good thing that
you two decided to
end the relationship
so I didn't have to end it for you.
Amy, after consideration,
I believe we may have acted rashly.
I propose we resume
our relationship
and attempt to resolve
our differences.
I'll agree to that only
if you'll stipulate
that 80% of our difficulties
were caused by you.
I'll go as high as 40. Sixty-five.
Done.
You understand that moving forward,
we deal with the fact that my
mother does not approve of you?
I do. I find being cast
in the role of bad
girl oddly titillating.
Would you like to see my cats?
I would. I love cats.
They're the epitome
of indifference.
Ah, then you may find
Zazzles a little cloying.
I saw what you did there.
He thinks he's such a smarty pants.
He's no different from any man.
You tell 'em not to do
something, that's all
they want to do.
If I hadn't told my brother Stumpy
not to clear out the
wood chipper by hand,
we'd still be calling him Edward.
Now, don't you move.
I'll bring over all the food.
No, no, no, I can do it.
Well, isn't that sweet?
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Thank you, Amy.
Here's your cat.
And here's your $20.
Next!
Thank you, Amy.
Here's your cat.
And here's your $20.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --