Previously on
The Big Bang Theory:
Guess who I found at LAX.
My baby sister Priya.
It's really nice
to see you again, Leonard.
Yeah, it's good
to see you, too.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You slept with
my sister?!
Yeah.
This is a terrible
betrayal of my trust!
Would it help
if I told you
that I offered
her my heart,
and she kinda
stomped on it?!
How hard did she stomp?
Very hard.
Okay, I'm good.
What's so funny?
Nothing. Just thinking
about the noises people
make during sex.
I do sometimes get a bit
carried away, don't I?
It's cute.
You sound a little
like a drunken monkey.
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh!
You know it's meant
as a compliment.
That's how I take it.
This is perfect.
I hope this moment
never ends.
Me, too.
Well, gotta go.
Oh!
Already?
Why don't you stay over?
I'd love to, but you know
my mother needs me in
the morning.
I think the woman can manage
to put a wig on by herself.
It's not just the wig.
It's pinning her hair up,
drawing on her eyebrows.
It's a two-person job.
It's just, when you leave right
after we make love,
it makes me feel...
cheap.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
What can I do?
Stay.
Okay.
Like, what, another five,
ten minutes?
Go home.
Your call.
Howard...
have you ever considered us
living together?
Boy, I don't know.
You, me, Ma living
under the same roof?
No, I mean just you and me.
You can move in here,
or we can find a place.
I've got a better solution.
What?
We wait for my mom's heart
to explode
from all the salt she eats.
Then we just stick her in
the ground, flip her mattress
and move into the big bedroom.
Great.
Look at us planning
a future together!
Who's there?!
Are you a
sex criminal?!
Sex criminals
don't have keys, Ma!
Where were you
so late?!
I was out with Bernadette!
I know what
that means!
I watch Dr. Phil!
I hope to God
you used a condom!
I'm not having this conversation
with you, Ma!
God forbid you get one of
those new fancy sex diseases!
Nobody has a disease!
I hope not!
I share a toilet
with you!
Is that what
you want?!
To give your
mother herbies?!
That's it!
I don't have to take this!
Good luck with your eyebrows in
the morning!
Who's there?!
Are you a
sex criminal?!
I'm still leaving!
I just forgot my Claritin!
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 4x16 ?
The Cohabitation Formulation
Original Air Date on February 17, 2011
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Hey, what's up?
I need a place to crash.
Uh, sure.
Why?
Big fight with my mother.
Still arguing over
which CSI is the best?
No, we agreed they all have
their merits.
This was about Bernadette.
What's going on?
Howard's gonna sleep here
tonight.
He had a fight with his mother.
Did you offer him
a hot beverage?
No.
Leonard, social protocol states
when a friend is upset,
you offer them a hot beverage,
such as tea.
Tea does sound nice.
You heard the man, Leonard.
And while you're at it,
I'm upset
that we have an unannounced
houseguest, so make me cocoa.
Point of inquiry,
given that Leonard is
your secondary friend
and Koothrappali is
your primary friend,
why didn't you seek refuge
under his roof?
There's no room.
His sister is staying with him.
Wait, wait. What?
Cocoa, Leonard.
Focus.
I'm down in
the dumps here.
Priya's in town?
Yeah, some work thing.
Anyway, my mother seems
to think that Bernadette...
Hold on.
When did Priya get here?
I don't know.
A couple of days ago.
The thing is, Bernadette doesn't
like that I have to take care
of my mother, and my mother
doesn't trust Bernadette...
Yeah, that's a real pickle.
Bye.
Don't worry.
As your tertiary friend,
I am prepared to step in
and comfort you.
That's not really necessary.
No, no. I'll finish
making the tea,
while you narcissistically
ramble on
about whatever's troubling you.
Thanks.
That's what
tertiary friends are for.
Who is it?
It's Leonard.
You can't come in.
I just want to talk to her.
I forbid it.
Open the door,
Rajesh.
You heard me.
I forbidded it.
"Forbidded" it?
"Forbaded" it?
Get out of the way.
What are you doing here?
I have business in Los Angeles.
Why didn't you call?
Clearly, she was
sending you a message
to take a hike, Mike.
I'm sorry.
I thought about calling,
?but I just wasn't sure if
seeing you was such a good idea.
I know. Last time
I came on too strong.
Can we talk in private?
No!
Sure.
It's completely inappropriate
for a single woman
to entertain a man in private.
If you insist on talking,
you must do it on the couch!
All right, you may talk in
the bedroom,
but I want this door
to remain open!
All right, just this once
you may close the door.
But keep in mind
I'll be right out here
monitoring the situation!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Oh, damn it.
Leonard, when you get this
message, call me.
Priya, this is your brother.
When you get this, tell Leonard
to check his voicemail.
Would you be sleeping over
again this evening?
Because you're welcome to.
That's very nice of you,
but I made other plans.
Well, just keep in mind that
should you ever need
a slightly apathetic tertiary
friend, I stand at the ready.
Hi, Howard.
Hi, Sheldon.
Hello.
Hey.
Why are you
holding hands?
I forbid you to hold hands.
Rajesh, you know Leonard and I
spent the night together.
Yeah, but you were just
sleeping,
because I forboded you
to have sex.
The word is "forbade""
You sure?
That doesn't sound right.
Listen, Rajesh, Leonard and I
have decided
to see each other again,
and you don't get
to tell me
who I can and can't have
a relationship with.
Actually, he can.
The Hindu Code of Manu is
very clear in these matters.
If a woman's father is
not around,
the duty of controlling her base
desires falls
to the closest male member of
her family, in this case, Raj.
The code also states
that if she disobeys,
she will be reborn
"in the womb of a jackal
and tormented by diseases."
If true,
that seems
like an awfully large gamble
given that the prize is Leonard.
There it is, Priya.
We're Indian.
We believe this stuff.
I think it also says that
if you eat beef,
you need to live with cows
for three months
and drink their urine.
Some of it makes sense,
some of it's crazy.
My point is, you can't go out
with Leonard.
Who can't go out with Leonard?
My sister.
Penny, this is
Raj's sister, Priya.
It's very nice to meet you.
Oh, yeah, you, too.
Priya, if you're experiencing
any tension or awkwardness,
it may stem from the fact that
Leonard and Penny used to--
if I may quote Howard--
"do the dance with no pants."
Sheldon!
Really?
Hey, Bernadette, can I
talk to you for a second?
Sure.
Penny, you became disenchanted
with Leonard
as a lover.
Would you please tell
my sister why?
Listen, my mom's
going to Palm Springs
to visit her sister.
That's two whole nights
in a row I can sleep over
with you
all the way to morning.
Unless the desert air
dries out her sinuses,
in which case I'll have
to schlep out there
with the big humidifier.
That's it?
That's your big solution
to all of our problems?
If your mom's nose holds up,
we get two nights together?
Isn't that great?
No, it's not great.
You need to make a choice.
Me or your mother.
Uh...
Wrong answer.
No, wait.
You didn't let me finish.
I'm listening.
Uh...
I came as quickly as I could.
Okay.
Why?
To comfort you, of course.
Sheldon told me about Leonard
dating Rajesh's sister.
So I high-tailed it over here
to pick up the pieces
of your broken heart.
Amy, I'm fine.
You don't have to
be strong for me.
Now let's talk about Priya,
that man-stealing bitch.
What?
In situations like this,
best girlfriends are often
catty about the other woman.
Really, I am not upset
about Leonard and Priya.
Oh. Then perhaps you don't
understand what's going on.
Your former boyfriend
has replaced you
with what appears to be
a very suitable mate.
Arguably much
more suitable than you.
Oh. Well, good for him.
Hey, what do you mean,
"more suitable"?
Well, granted, Penny, your
secondary sexual characteristics
are reasonably bodacious.
But Priya is highly educated,
she's an accomplished
professional,
and she comes from the culture
that literally wrote the book
on neat ways to have sex.
Whereas you, on the other hand,
are a community college dropout
who comes from the culture that
wrote the book on tipping cows.
Yeah. Okay, I got it.
I got it.
So... what is
all that stuff?
This is a portable
electroencephalogram.
I'm doing research
on emotions and brain activity.
So when you start crying,
I can see which region
of the brain is activated.
Then I'm going to stimulate
the analogous area
in the brain of a rhesus monkey
and see if he cries.
Cool, huh?
I choose you.
Really?
Yep. I moved out
of my mother's house.
Cord is cut.
I'm all yours.
What did she say
when you told her?
I don't know. She hasn't
responded to my email yet.
This is so great.
I love you, Howard.
I love you, too.
So what's for dinner?
Well, I don't really have much
of anything in the house.
That's fine.
Why don't we go fool
around in our bedroom?
And then you
can go shopping.
I thought maybe after we eat,
we could see an early movie.
I'd love that.
I love the way you say,
"I'd love that."
She says it the same way I do.
Everybody in India
says it that way.
It's not a big deal.
Rajesh, don't be a child.
I'm not being a child.
Leonard, I swear to God,
if your sister
ever comes to town,
I shall have my way with her.
My sister's 38 and married.
All the more shame
that will fall
upon the house of Hofstadter.
Ooh, I thought I smelled pizza.
That's remarkable.
If pepperoni
were an explosive substance,
you could replace
German shepherds
at our nation's airports.
Hi. Penny, right?
Oh, yes. H-Hi. I'm sorry.
I didn't know you had company.
I don't want to impose.
No, no. It's not
an imposition.
At this point, in our ecosystem,
you are akin to the plover,
a small scavenging bird
that eats extra food
from between
the teeth of crocodiles.
Please, fly into our open maw,
and have at it.
If I had more than a box of
baking soda in my refrigerator,
I wouldn't have to take that.
Hi, bestie.
Hi.
So, um, Priya,
you're a lawyer, right?
I know. Pretty boring, huh?
Oh, come on.
It's not boring at all.
She's currently helping set up
a secondary derivative market
which would allow
overseas car firms
to hedge their investments
against potential advancements
in battery technology.
Hmm?
Thank you, Leonard.
That doesn't make it
sound boring at all.
So, how you holding up?
I'm fine.
Oh, who are you kidding?
She's breathtaking.
So, Penny,
Leonard tells me
you're an actress.
That must be
pretty exciting.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's real great.
Today I drove to Van Nuys
for an audition
I thought was going to be
for a cat food commercial.
Turned out to be porn.
Did you get the part?
I didn't do the audition.
Given the state of your career,
can you really afford
to be picky?
I took acting classes
when I was at Cambridge.
I loved it.
We did Taming
of the Shrew.
Oh, wow. I love
Taming of the Shrew.
I did a paper
on it in high school.
"Who knows not where
a wasp does wear his sting?
In his tail."
"In his tongue""
"Whose tongue?"
"Yours, if you
talk of tails,
and so farewell."
"What, with my tongue
in your tail?"
I'm regretting
my earlier cattiness.
She is an
absolute delight.
Wow.
Wow, indeed.
I can't believe we're
finally living together.
Yeah.
You know what would make
this moment perfect?
What?
A little snack.
You got any string cheese?
No.
I-I might have some cheddar.
Not as good.
You can't make strings with it.
Remind me to put it
on your shopping list.
Okay.
You have
hypo-allergenic detergent?
No.
Better put it on the list.
If you wash my underwear
with regular soap,
I get little red bumps
on my tuchus.
Wait a second.
I'm doing your laundry?
Well, honey,
it's not gonna do itself.
Oh, before I forget,
tomorrow morning, you're
driving me to the dentist.
I have to take you?
You don't have to take me.
You get to take me.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me
your mother usually takes you
to the dentist?
It's not weird.
There's lots of kids there
with their moms.
I can't believe this.
What? It's fun.
If I have no cavities,
afterwards,
we go out for a treat.
All right, Howard, let's get
something straight right now.
I'm not going
to be your mother.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where did that come from?
Who's that?!
Is it a
sex criminal?!
Nobody wants to do
that to you, Ma!
Where were you?!
Didn't you read my email?!
You know I can't turn on
that ferkakta computer!
I left you some brisket
on the kitchen counter!
Thank you!
Remember
to floss after.
We have the dentist
in the morning!
Oh, hey.
What's up?
I just wanted to
check in on you.
Why?
It seems like the
appropriate thing to do
when one's best friend
finds herself replaced
by a smart, beautiful woman
with the smoldering sexuality
of a crouched Bengal tiger.
I already told you,
I'm okay with it.
I mean, if anything,
I'm quite pleased
that Leonard
has found someone
that makes him so happy.
It's okay, it's okay.
Thank you.
Now, let's get these
electrodes attached
and see what's going on in that
pretty little noggin of yours.
Okay.
I smell Chinese food.
It's actually Thai.
You're slipping.
Are Leonard and Priya here?
They went to Catalina
for the weekend.
Oh. Where's Raj?
At home, forbidding it.
How about Howard?
I'm given to understand
his mother grounded him
for running away.
Oh, okay.
Well, I guess it's just
the two of us, huh?
Actually, it's
the three of us.
AMY
What up, bestie?
Good news.
Thanks to you, I was able
to make a rhesus monkey cry
like a disgraced televangelist.
Great.
So, you feeling better?
Not really.
Sheldon, you have
a guest who's upset.
Right. I'll make tea.
- Sweetie, it's okay. I don't want tea.
- I'm sorry. It's not optional.
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org