I'm telling you, if xenon emits
ultraviolet light,
then those dark matter
discoveries must be wrong.
Yes, well, if we lived
in a world
where slow-moving xenon
produced light,
then you'd be correct.
Also, pigs would fly,
my derriere would produce
cotton candy,
and The Phantom Menace
would be a timeless classic.
Oh, you're so arrogant.
If you were a superhero,
your name would be
Captain Arrogant.
And you know
what your superpower would be?
Arrogance.
You're wrong again.
If my superpower were arrogance,
my name would be Dr. Arroganto.
I love watching Raj and Sheldon
try to work together.
Yeah, it's like
if Alien and Predator decided
to go partners
in a Jamba Juice.
Has it occurred to you
you're missing the big picture?
If you look at neutron
scattering data...
Oh, Penny?
Penny?
What's up?
Nothing. I just wanted
to make Raj stop talking.
No, no, no.
He won. Suck it up.
Well, I'd ask you guys
if you want dessert,
but I know Sheldon doesn't
eat dessert on Tuesdays.
And even if Raj wanted
something, he couldn't tell me.
Howard won't order anything,
but he will come up
with some sort of skeevy comment
involving the words pie
or cheesecake.
And Leonard's
lactose intolerant,
so he can't eat anything here
without his intestines
blowing up
like a balloon animal.
Hang on a second.
I could have the fruit platter.
You want the fruit platter?
Does it have melon
on it?
Yeah.
No, I can't eat melon.
Oh, Howard,
heads up.
Your ex-girlfriend just
came in for her shift.
When was the last time
you saw her?
Oh, not since we broke up.
Wow. How am I going
to play this?
Sophisticated and relaxed?
Friendly, noncommittal?
Cold and distant?
Hi, guys.
Hey.
Hello.
I see you decided to go
with pathetic and frightened.
It's one of his best moves.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 4x04 ?
The Hot Troll Deviation
Original Air Date on October 14, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
So, my dear, we meet again.
Hello, Howard.
I've missed you.
I've missed you,
Katee Sackhoff.
One question.
Anything.
Why am I wearing my
Battlestar Galactica
flight suit in bed?
Why are you in bed with me?
If we start to question this,
it all falls apart.
Sorry.
Oh, ravish
me, Howard.
My loins
ache for you.
Okay, if you insist.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, have you seen
my girdle?!
No, Ma!
I can't find it, and I'm late
for my Weight Watchers meeting!
Maybe it committed suicide!
Leave me alone!
Now, where were we?
I believe you
were about
to rip off my uniform
with your teeth.
Bernadette?!
What are you doing here?
Well, if I had to
guess, I'd say I'm here
because you saw me
earlier this evening,
and you're still
hung up on me.
No, I'm not.
Clearly you are.
Otherwise, based
on past experience,
we'd be done by now.
Okay,
I'm a little confused here.
GEORGE TAKEI:
Oh, my.
Can I help?
Not that kind of confused.
What's George
Takei doing here?
Howard, do you have
latent homosexual tendencies?
No, of course not.
So you say.
Yet, here I am.
George, let me
ask you something.
How did you deal
with being typecast
as a science fiction icon?
It's difficult.
You try and stretch
as an actor--
do Strindberg, O'Neill,
but all they want is,
"Course laid in, Captain."
Tell me about it.
It's frackin'
frustrating.
Wait. Katee,
why are you leaving?
She's leaving because you
really want to be with me.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, I found my girdle!
It was in the dryer!
Great, Ma!
I think it shrunk!
I'm spilling out like
the Pillsbury Doughboy here!
And with that mental picture,
I think we're done
for the evening.
You know, you never
told me what happened
between you
and Bernadette.
I did a stupid thing.
Yeah, I guessed that.
It was the kind of thing
that makes it kind of hard
to face her now.
That covers anything
from farting in bed
to killing a homeless guy.
Oh, my God.
You ran over a hobo.
No. Stop asking.
All right, fine. So you want to
get back together with her,
but you're too
ashamed to face her
because of whatever
it is you did.
In a nutshell.
Okay.
Well, how about this?
Kidnap Bernadette from the opera
wearing a creepy mask so
she doesn't know it's you.
Now, you see, I don't know
if you're kidding or not.
You're being
unreasonable.
Why can't
I have a desk?!
Our collaboration is a work
of the mind.
We don't need desks.
You have a desk.
Correct.
But I can't have one.
You're two for two.
Why can't he have a desk,
Sheldon?
Oh, Lord, will
this day never end?
As I've explained repeatedly
to Dr. Koothrappali,
whose ability to comprehend
the American idiom fails him
when it's convenient,
there's absolutely
no money
in my budget for
additional office furniture.
Oh, but there's money
for a drawer full of Red Vines,
a marshmallow shooting rifle,
and a super executive ant farm
with glow-in-the-dark sand?
Yes.
Okay, what if he
buys his own desk?
Yeah, what
if I buy my own desk?
That's ridiculous.
Why?
Because...
Yes?
It's my office.
Sheldon.
All right, all right.
He can buy his own desk.
And I can put it in your office?
Well, you really want
to dot the I's and cross
the T's, don't you?
Why would you want
a glow-in-the-dark ant farm?
They do some
of their best work at night.
Ah, it's okay.
Penny?
Would you have opened the door
if you knew it was me?
Not since I found out
the teddy bear you gave me
had a webcam in it.
I just have a question.
Does Bernadette
ever talk about me?
Oh, absolutely.
She does?
Yeah, sure.
Just yesterday, she asked,
"Why is Howard hiding
under the table?"
She saw that, huh?
Oh, no, not at first.
Right after I pointed it out.
Let me ask you something else.
Is she seeing anybody?
Oh, not that I know of.
Hey, while
we're on the subject,
why did you guys break up
anyway?
Oh, I'd rather not say.
Howard, if you want my help,
I've got to know what happened.
But it's embarrassing...
Yeah, that's what
I'm counting on. Spill.
Okay. Well, you know
World of Warcraft?
Um, the online game? Sure.
Well, did you know
that the characters in the game
can have sex with each other?
Oh, God. I think
I see where this is going.
Her name was
Glissinda the Troll.
Bernadette walked in on me
while we were doing
the cyber-nasty
under the Bridge of Souls.
Oh, you're right.
That is so embarrassing.
Would you talk to her?
Bernadette or the troll?
Bernadette. She
was so mad at me,
she wouldn't even listen
to my side of the story.
Well, what was your side?
Well, for all we know,
Glissinda the Troll
wasn't even a real woman.
I mean, she could've been
a 50-year-old truck driver
in New Jersey.
Really? And that didn't
make her feel better?
Will you talk to her, see
if there's any chance at all
we could get back together?
Oh, gee, Howard,
I really don't want
to get in the middle of this.
No. Why would you?
I'm just another lonely
nerd, living with his mother,
trying to find any scrap
of happiness he can.
You know, maybe to make up
for the fact that his dad
left him when
he was 11.
Okay, I will think about it.
You know, I've always
blamed myself
for him leaving.
I always thought it was because
I wasn't the son he wanted.
Yeah, I said I'd
think about it.
I wasn't athletic,
yeah, I was kind of sickly...
Okay, fine. Look, look,
I'm calling her now! See?!
Thank you.
So anyway,
Howard asked Penny
to talk to Bernadette,
and she did,
and Bernadette agreed to meet
him for a cup of coffee.
One question.
Yeah?
Why on earth
are you telling me all this?
I don't know.
Sometimes your movements
are so lifelike,
I forget you're
not a real boy.
You said I could
buy a desk.
This isn't a desk.
This is a...
Brobdingnagian
monstrosity.
Is that the American idiom
for "giant, big-ass desk"?
It's actually British.
Can you say it again for me?
Brobdingnagian.
One more time?
Now three times fast?
Brobdingnagian, Brobdingna...
How did you even
get it in here?
That's for me, Ramon, Julio,
Jesus and Rodrigo to know
and you to find out.
All right, you've
made your point.
A fine prank, very amusing.
Now get it out.
No.
Yes.
Yes!
I have three brothers
and two sisters, Sheldon--
I can do this all day.
All right, if you're
not going to remove it,
I'll remove it for you.
Knock yourself out.
Help me move my desk.
No.
Yes.
No. It's too Brobdingnagian.
Why do you even want this here?
Its size is completely
disproportionate
to its purpose.
Well, seeing as its purpose
was to piss you off,
I'd say it's spot-on.
All right, I see
what's going on.
This is the opening
salvo in what will be
an escalating series of
juvenile tit-for-tat exchanges.
Well titted.
Thank you.
Stand by for my upcoming tat.
Hey, Sheldon?
Yes?
No.
See what I did there?
I turned it around.
Sorry,
I had to clock out.
Oh, no, that's okay.
How have you been?
Okay. You know,
busy, schoolwork. You?
Same. I took a scuba-diving
course over the summer,
but it turns out I'm
terrified of the ocean.
Too bad.
You wouldn't know anybody
who wants to buy a wet
suit, boy's large?
Yeah, forget it.
Not important.
So, are you
seeing anyone?
Well, to be honest, I...
Hey, how are we
doing over here? Can I
get you something to drink?
Not for me, thanks.
I'm okay.
Are you gonna want
to order food?
Maybe later.
Okay.
So, are you seeing anybody?
No.
That's what I told him
when he asked me.
I hope that's not out of line.
No, it's fine.
Penny, can we have
a little privacy?
Oh. I'm sorry.
What about you,
have you been seeing anybody?
Well, you know
how it is with guys.
I mean, we have needs and...
So you've been seeing
other girls?
Well, not real girls.
Does that mean slutty trolls?
You know, you look thirsty.
I brought you some iced tea.
Thank you.
It's passion fruit,
new on the menu.
I know. I work here.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, you're right. Doy.
So, Howard,
yay or nay?
Isn't there somewhere else
you can be?
Not where I can hear you guys.
Okay, fine.
I'll admit, there are dark,
sordid little corners
of the Internet
where the name Wolowizard
is whispered in hushed tones.
The only reason I go there,
the only reason
I've ever gone there
is because I don't have
a real woman in my life.
You happy?
Yeah, that'll hold me
for a while.
Howard, you did have
a real woman.
I was right there
in the next room
while you were clicking
that troll's brains out.
Yeah, but we
weren't...
I-I mean, you
and I never...
Had sex?
Yeah.
Well, whose fault was that?
Complimentary nachos!
You enjoy.
Never had sex? Wow.
What do you mean,
whose fault was that?
Well, we could've
been having sex,
but you never made the move.
I didn't think you wanted me
to make the move.
Howard, a girl doesn't go out
with a man like you,
with your looks,
your fancy patter
and your tight hoochie pants
if she's not expecting him
to eventually make the move.
Really?
Really.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, this is a little awkward,
but my manager says
I can't actually
give nachos away.
So... just take that
when you're ready.
Yeah, we had
a really great talk,
and we're gonna start
seeing each other again.
Oh, congratulations.
Have you broken it
to the troll yet?
Did Penny tell you about that?
No. Steve Patterson told me.
The greasy old fat guy
in Facilities Management?
Yeah.
How'd he know about it?
He's Glissinda the troll.
Sorry, dude,
the thermostat's
on my side of the room,
so it stays Mumbai hot
in here until you turn off
that stupid Indian music!
I'll turn off the music
when you get rid of that
salmonella-ridden parakeet!
Oh, too bad! Sheldon's
pathologically
afraid of birds!
Hey, look, Sheldon!
Birdie, birdie, birdie!
That's it! Prepare
for marshmallow death!
Eat flaming Nerf!
So anyway...
That's great news
about you and Bernadette.
Yeah. I think I'm gonna take
her to miniature golf.
Ah. Well, I guess
for you guys that's
like regular golf.
Short jokes? Really?
You're, like,
a quarter of an inch
taller than me.
Yeah, and don't
you forget it.
I had a good time.
Me, too.
Kiss her good night.
All right, now a little tongue.
GEORGE TAKEI:
Hold on there.
We've only just rekindled
the romance.
Let's not sully the moment
with the exchange of saliva.
Don't listen to him.
She wants it.
Tongue.
La, la, la, la, la.
See?
Now make the move.
Mm-mmm.
Too soon.
Trust me, she's ready.
Make the move.
No, no, no.
A lady wants to be wooed,
courted slowly.
How would you know?
I read.
Listen to me, Howard, it's time.
Make the move, now.
Mm! What are you doing?
You said... well,
the "move," remember?
Oh, not now.
We're starting a
new relationship.
I need to get to
know you again.
No, you don't.
It's me.
The lusty charmer
with the fancy patter
and the hoochie pants.
Be patient;
we'll get there.
Told you.
Oh, God, what's that smell?
Oh-ho-hoo!
Yes?
What are you
doing in there?
I'm making
hydrogen sulfide
and ammonia gas.
Just a little experiment
in pest control.
It's not gonna work, dude;
I grew up in India--
an entire subcontinent
where cows walk in the street,
and nobody has ever had
a solid bowel movement.
Well, we'll just see
how long you can hold out.
Well, we'll just see how
your noxious gas fares
against my cinnamon-
apple-scented
aroma therapy candles.
Didn't you say you're
making hydrogen sulfide gas?
Yes.
Isn't that flammable?
Highly.
Oh, dear.
This is not over.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org