Here's what I wonder
about zombies.
What happens if they can't get
any human flesh to eat?
They can't starve to death--
they're already dead.
You take this one.
I spent an hour last night on
"How do vampires shave
when they can't see
themselves in the mirror"?
Well-groomed vampires
meet in pairs
and shave each other--
case closed.
Yeah, okay, so, zombies.
I guess it depends
on the zombies, Raj.
Are we talking slow zombies,
fast zombies?
Like, in 28 Days,
if those zombies didn't eat,
they starved.
You're thinking
of 28 Days Later.
28 Days is where
Sandra Bullock goes to rehab
and puts the audience
into an undead state
Hey, don't bag
on Sandra Bullock!
You think it makes you
look cultured,
but you just
come off as bitter.
Oh, Dr. Siebert,
twelve o'clock.
Why's the president
of the university
slumming in the cafeteria?
Perhaps he's emulating
Shakespeare's Henry V,
who dressed as a commoner
and mingled among them,
to find out how he was being
perceived by his subjects.
Of course, if he'd
have read any
of the 1,300 e-mails
I've sent him on the subject
of his administration,
he could have saved himself
the trouble.
Or maybe he heard it's
Tator Tot Tuesday.
That's why I'm here.
Hey, there's
my favorite geniuses!
How are we doing today?
That depends--
how much longer
do you plan on
fondling my shoulder?
Sorry, Dr. Cooper, I forgot
you have a touch phobia.
It's not a touch phobia,
it's a germ phobia.
If you'd like to go put on
a pair of latex gloves,
I'll let you check me
for a hernia.
Yeah.
So, listen, fellas, who's up
for a little party this Saturday night?
Open bar, good eats, might
even be a few pretty girls.
Sounds great!
I'm in!
Hold on.
Just because the nice man
is offering you candy,
doesn't mean you should jump
into his windowless van.
What's the occasion?
Just a little fund-raiser
for the university.
Aha! The tear-stained air
mattress in the back of the van.
I understand
your reticence, Dr. Cooper,
and I sympathize,
but the hard facts are,
occasionally,
we have to shake a few hands
and kiss a few butts
to raise money for our research.
I don't care;
it's demeaning.
And I refuse to be
trotted out and shown off
like a prize hog
at the Texas State Fair.
Which, by the way, is something
you don't want to attend
wearing a Star Trek
ensign's uniform.
All right,
let me put it this way.
You're gonna put on a suit,
you're gonna come to this party,
and you're gonna
explain your research
to a bunch of old people,
or I swear to God,
I'll blind you with a hot spoon,
like they did  to that little boy
in Slumdog Millionaire.
Oh, you don't want that.
So, Saturday night!
It's gonna be
off the hook.
Ugh!
Get over it.
Oh, boy!
Tator tots and
a party invitation?
What a great day!
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang-- Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 4x15 ?
The Benefactor Factor
Original Air Date on February 10, 2011
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
There you go.
Are you sure
this is right?
Yeah, just tuck that
part in your pants;  you'll be fine.
Okay, let's go smooch some
rich, wrinkled tochis.
Oh, Howard, I can't believe
Bernadette let you go
to a fancy party
wearing a dickey.
Excuse me, my girlfriend
doesn't pick out my clothes.
My mother does.
Oh. We should
get going.
What about Sheldon?
Sheldon is not going.
Really? What do we tell Siebert?
Tell him Dr. Cooper feels
that the best use of his time
is to employ his rare
and precious mental faculties
to tear the mask off nature
and stare at the face of God.
Sheldon, it's Saturday night,
you'll be doing laundry.
Don't tell him that,
tell him the mask thing.
Hey, put your tie
back in your pants.
Nice place.
Reminds me of my parents'
house back in New Delhi.
- You're kidding.
- No. We are very wealthy.
But the only difference is,
we have more servants.
- More than this?
- More than we can use.
You see, in India,
we don't make the mistake
of letting our poor people
have dreams.
Ah. There's my band
of brainiacs.
Where's Dr. Cooper?
He's tearing the mask off nature
to look at the face of God.
The board of directors insists
he has a beautiful mind.
I think he's just bananas.
Come on, let me introduce you
to one of the university's
leading donors.
I think we were misled
about the cute girls.
Mrs. Latham, I'd like
you to meet three
of our outstanding
young researchers.
This is Dr. Leonard
Hofstadter,
Dr. Rajesh Koothrappali
and Howard Wolowitz.
Well, what happened
to you, Wolowitz,
couldn't stick with it
long enough to get your PhD?
I'm an engineer.
Most engineers
don't bother with a PhD.
But you may be
interested to know
I designed the zero-gravity
waste-disposal system for NASA.
Got it--
you're a space plumber.
I'm gonna go hit the bar.
Tell me about
these two.
- Do him first.
- Dr. Hofstadter
is representing our
experimental physics
program tonight.
I think you'll
really enjoy
hearing about his
fascinating work.
Right.
Fascinate me.
They're cute when they're about
to wet themselves, aren't they?
I'll make it
easy for you.
When you arrive at the lab
in the morning,
what sort of machine
do you turn on?
Coffee maker?
All right, Dr. Kooth--
uh, whatever it is-- you're up.
It's Koothrappal
I have to tinkle.
And so, instead
of bowing to pressure,
and going to that
pointless soiree,
I stayed right here
and did a load of whites.
Well, normally I respect
your macho rebellious attitude
toward "The Man,"
but, in this case, I think
you've made a foolish mistake.
Unlikely.
But make your case.
Keeping in mind that
your critical attitude
is ruining our
Saturday night together,
and I'm not above
minimizing your window.
Sheldon, like it or not,
until you manage
to upload your intelligence
into a self-sustaining
orbiting satellite,
equipped with high-speed
Internet and a cloaking device,
you will be dependent on other
members of the human race.
That's it.
Prepare to be minimized.
I'm not finished.
All scientists have
to fund-raise, Sheldon.
How do you think
I paid for my lab?
I went to Saudi Arabia
and met with a prince
who had an interest
in neurobiology.
Your lab is funded by some
Middle-Eastern dilettante?
Technically,
Faisal is my fianc?.
But I do have a state-of-the-art
two-photon microscope
and a place to stay in Riyadh
for the winter.
Well, that explains those
puzzling camel race photos
on your Facebook page.
And consider this:
without you to make the case
for the physics department,
the task will fall to people
like Leonard and Rajesh.
Are you trying to scare me?
'Cause you're succeeding.
Well, then prepare
to be terrified.
If your friends
are unconvincing,
this year's donations
might go to,
say, the geology department.
Oh, dear, the dirt people!
Or worse-- it could go to...
the liberal arts.
No!
Millions of dollars
being showered on poets,
literary theorists
and students of gender studies.
Oh, the humanities!
On the bright side, I don't
think President Siebert
will be making us go
to any more fund-raisers.
It was so much easier
at my bar mitzvah.
The old people just came up
to you, pinched your cheek
and handed you a savings bond.
Oh, don't be such gloomy Gusses.
Look at the size
of these shrimp!
At what point do we start
calling them lobsters?
Face it, Raj,
we crashed and burned tonight.
Oh, you didn't
do that badly.
Mrs. Latham, the first machine
I turn on in the morning
is the helium-neon laser,
'cause it needs to warm up.
I no longer care, dear.
But don't worry,
I really enjoyed
meeting you this evening.
u're kidding.
That was good for you?
'Cause I was sweating
through my T-shirt.
Excellent! There's
nothing I like better
than making smart people
feel ill at ease.
Why?
Oh, I don't know,
it's one of the fun things
you get to do when
you have lots of money.
Watch.
Hey! Who said you
could eat that shrimp?
See? Fun.
No, no, no, I'm just here
for your money.
I don't want to shake
anyone's germy hands.
Explain it to
them, Siebert.
I must confess
I don't understand you,
President Siebert.
First you say you want me
to appear at your fund-raisers,
but now you say
you never want me to go
anywhere near your fund-raisers.
Forgive me, but that sounds
like a mixed message.
Here we go again.
If there's simply
no talking to me,
why did you call?
I'm sorry, someone's
on the other line.
Why don't you see if you
can organize your thoughts,
and we'll try again later.
Cooper-Hofstadter residence.
Go for Cooper.
Good morning, Mrs. Latham.
Well, yes, of course
I remember you.
A woman well past her prime
seeking to augment
her social status
by doling out her late husband's
ill-gotten gains.
So, how much money
are you going to give me?
I'm not crazy--
my mother had me tested.
Well, if you're not
going to give me money,
then why are you calling?
She wants to talk to you.
Who's crazy now?
Hello, Mrs. Latham.
Yes, I live with him.
I don't...
I-I really don't know why.
Tonight? Sure,
that'd be great.
Okay, I'll see you then.
Bye.
She wants to have dinner
and talk about my research.
An entire dinner
to talk about your research?
Where you going, the drive-thru
at Jack in the Box?
Well, wherever
we're going,
she's sending a car
to pick me up.
Okay,
- I see what's happening.
- What?
My stature intimidates her,
so she's using you to get to me.
Crafty old gal.
Excuse me, but you are not the
only distinguished scientist
in this apartment.
I've been published in
peer-reviewed journals,
I received a Dissertation
of the Year award
for experimental
particle physics.
No, that can't be it.
And since you seem
to have forgotten,
the reason we live together
is we're best friends.
And I got your back, Jack.
That was a great meal.
I'm glad you
enjoyed it.
The only time I eat this well
is when my mom's in town
- and she takes me out to dinner.
- Is that so?
You kind of
remind me of her.
She enjoys making people
uncomfortable, too.
Well, you remind me of
a boy I dated in college.
- No kidding.
- Sweet boy.
Very smart.
If only he'd had money.
Yeah, um...
so, hey,
speaking of money,
how are you feeling about
helping the physics department
get a cryogenic centrifugal
pump and molecular sieve?
Well, I must say, you make a
very persuasive case for it.
Oh, good, good.
And I'm seriously
considering taking it
to the next level.
Terrific. Great.
What level is that?
Okay, now you don't
remind me of my mom.
I'm sorry, so, eventually,
zombies are going to attack
the rehab facility
where Sandra Bullock is?
Yes, Sheldon. Keep watching.
You know, it's a shame, all that
work she's doing to get sober,
only to be torn apart
and eaten alive.
Hey. How was dinner?
Swell. I need a drink.
Do we have any alcohol?
No. But we have potatoes--
I could make you vodka.
It'll take two weeks.
Leonard, are you okay?
Um, I'm not sure.
What's going on?
Well, Mrs. Latham said
she was seriously considering
donating money so we could get
a cryogenic centrifugal pump...
Yes!
Oh, wow!
...then she stuck
her tongue down my throat.
Why?
Okay, we can't keep
explaining everything.
Read that book
we got you.
She hit on me.
Wait-wait-wait.
Are you telling us
that old lady wanted
to have sex with you
in exchange for giving your
department millions of dollars?
I think so.
You lucky duck.
You're really
a broken toy, aren't you?
I was able to get out of there
before anything else happened,
but she wants to see me again
tomorrow night.
Excellent!
What are you planning to wear?
What?
Penny, you're an expert on trading
sexual favors for material gain--
walk him through this.
Well, n-no, hold on a second,
I'm not going to sleep with her.
But we need a cryogenic
centrifugal pump.
Well, forget it!
It's not gonna happen.
Well, come now, Leonard,
this may be your only chance
to make a real contribution
to science!
I repeat: Not gonna happen.
What was all that
about me trading sexual favors
for material gain?
It was a compliment.
I believe in giving credit
where credit is due.
Okay, fine. I'll tell him.
Leonard, Mrs. Latham's car
is here for you.
I won't be too late;
I'm just gonna make
a final pitch for the funding
and then say good night.
Hold on,
I have something for you.
What's this?
Just a few things you
may need tonight.
Baby oil, condoms
and, uh...
a little something I procured from the
school of pharmacology.
They say it is to Viagra as
Viagra is to a green M&M.
I am not going
to have sex with her.
Maybe this will overcome
your reluctance.
I went on the Internet
and found a photograph
of a 25-year-old Mrs. Latham
to get your libido humming.
Check out those saddle shoes.
Are you insane?
I'm not going
to prostitute myself
just so we can get
some new equipment.
Oh, come on! Why not?
Good night,
Sheldon.
Given how much time
you spend engaging
in pointless self-abuse,
you might consider,
just this once,
using your genitalia to
actually accomplish something!
He still won't shag
the old lady, huh?
No. But thank you for asking.
Hey. Hi.
Hello, Leonard.
I hope you're hungry.
I'm very hungry.
For food, right?
Oh, I made you uncomfortable
last night.
I'm so sorry.
No, that's okay.
No, it most
certainly is not.
Leonard, I'm making the
donation to your department
regardless of what
happens between us.
- Really?
- Well, of course.
There's no quid
pro quo here.
You and your colleagues are
doing remarkable research,
and you deserve the money.
Oh.
Then what was
last night about?
I took a shot; sue me.
Oh.
You're a very
handsome man, Leonard.
Thank you.
It was foolish of me to
think someone your age
might ever be interested
in someone like me.
Oh, don't say that.
- You're a very attractive woman.
- Oh, please.
- No, it's true.
- Well, aren't you sweet.
Just for the record...
you'd remember a night with me
for the rest of your life.
I'm sure I would.
But why-why, exactly?
You're a very smart man.
How do you think I landed
such a rich husband?
I hadn't really
given it much thought.
Well, think about it.
Do you mean...?
Yep. I'm that good.
Oh, what the hell.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Good morning, slut.
What?
Oh, please, I recognize
the walk of shame
when I see it.
All you're missing is
a little smeared mascara
and a purse with panties
wadded up in it.
What's
going on?
Oh, nothing's going on.
Excuse me.
- Are you just getting home?
- Yeah.
That's a good sign, right?
Oh, yeah.
I'm so proud of you!
You sold yourself out
like a common streetwalker!
No, I didn't do it
for the money.
She stiffed you?
I believe that's what
your roommate did to her.
What?!
Again, read the
book we gave you.
No, I mean,
I-I got the money first.
Smart. Get paid up front.
Yeah, I think you have a real
knack for gigolo work, Leonard.
Uh...
I'm gonna go lie down.
That's a good idea;
get your rest.
There are a lot more
rich old ladies out there,
and Daddy needs
a new linear accelerator.
And I thought he didn't learn anything
from his relationship with you.
Hey!
Another compliment!
Learn to recognize them.
Ah, there he is!
The man of the hour!
He took one for the team!
I didn't do it
for the money!
Keep telling yourself that--
it makes it easier.
Trust me, I know.
Cool, buddy!
That's awesome!
Yeah!
How was she?
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org