Monsters!
Those guys
hunt monsters.
That is so cool.
Come on!
Mom doesn't want
to leave these people,
so let's take them
with us.
I hate this place
right now.
Those Hunters, t-that's on me.
I brought them here.
Everywhere I look,
I see them.
I see Maggie.
Sam!
You know, I think
I just need some time.
And what about that kid
with the dumb
Bambi-look on his face
all the time?
Hello.
I am a Winchester!
You killed Michael.
You consumed his grace.
Do you have
your powers back?
I'm me again.
And your soul?
You want to know how much
of my soul I had to burn off
to kill Michael.
Yes.
I don't know.
So, what's the verdict?
I'd keep an eye on him,
but I think...
if he seems okay,
he probably is.
I feel...
different now.
What was that?
It was nothing.
Just the wind.
Okay, that --
that wasn't the wind.
I'll check it out.
- What are you guys doing?
- Dad?
Barbara.
Hi, Sheriff.
Do your parents know
where you are right now?
Why do you care?
You're supposed
to be studying.
At Mom's.
This is not your weekend.
Besides, she's --
Out of town. With Todd.
I know.
She called you.
You weren't home.
She called me.
She's worried.
Well, you found me.
Good for you.
- Hey. Watch it.
- Or what?
Hey, where you going?
Um...bathroom.
You guys need some space.
Ugh.
Oh, God.
Tom, you shouldn't
be out here.
But I didn't mean
to embarrass you.
Yeah, you never do.
- Barbara?!
- Stay here.
Barbara!
Barbara?
Hey!
Thomas! Thomas!
No! No!
No...
? Supernatural 14x16 ?
Don't Go in the Woods
Original Air Date on March 21, 2019
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Morning, sunshine.
Hey.
What you looking at?
Porn? Sex tapes?
Nip slips?
The Internet is more
than just naked people.
You do know that, right?
Not my Internet.
All right.
Check this out.
So, this girl --
her body was found
just outside
Big Creek State Park in Iowa.
Uh, covered in bite marks.
The police are saying
it's an animal attack.
But...?
But I did some digging,
and I found that
there weren't a lot of bodies,
but a lot of people
do go missing in that park.
Look at this.
Park ranger back in '06.
A poacher in '98.
And on and on and on.
I mean, I've only
gone back to 1943,
and I've already found
54 missing people.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Sounds like
our kind of thing.
You sure you're up for it?
I mean, I know you wanted
to take some time.
No, I-I'm -- I'm good.
Honestly, I-I'm good.
All right.
Well, let's hit it.
You got it.
I'll grab Cass.
Mm. He actually left.
What?
Early this morning.
Why?
I don't know.
Something about
being cooped up
in the bunker
for a few weeks.
We all need to stretch
our legs. I get it.
All right.
Uh, then, Jack.
Uh...
I don't want Jack on this.
I thought you said Donatello
gave him the all clear?
Yeah, he did.
And I'm --
I'm sure he's good.
But...
Jack's got his mojo back.
His powers have gotten us
in trouble in the past --
the security guard.
So I just want to make sure
that, you know,
he's right before we put him
back out there.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Hey, uh...good reading?
- Yes.
Did you know Article 246
of the Haitian criminal code
officially makes it
against the law
to turn a human
into a zombie?
Good.
Jack, listen. Dean and I are
heading out on a case.
And...you don't
want me to come?
Look, truth is --
We don't want to leave
the bunker empty.
In case, uh, Mom or...
some of the other Hunters call
and need help, so...
And this place is long overdue
for a restock.
So, uh, your mission,
should you choose to accept --
made you a list.
My mission is shopping?
Beer, TP, eggs...
beer again.
- Twice?
- Yeah.
I'll do it.
Great!
We'll be in touch.
I'm sorry.
I just don't really see
how this is an FBI thing.
Wildlife preserve
is government property.
We're the government.
Yeah, well, it is
a large piece of land --
coyotes, rough terrain.
We try to limit hikers
to the trails,
but some of them
don't listen.
Okay, but the girl who died,
she wasn't a hiker.
Do you know what
happened to her?
Like I said, coyotes.
You know, do you mind
if we take a look at the body?
Do I have a choice?
Not really.
Whoa! Mo--
Seriously?
How long you been
doing this?
Well, got catlike reflexes,
okay? What can I say?
Said a coyote did this?
Not even close.
Mnh-mnh.
Look at the skin
around the bite.
It looks...burnt.
So, what the hell
can do that?
? We face them all, ghost! ?
? Ghostfacers! ?
? We face the faceless,
we face the dead! ?
Eliot, stop.
What? The Ghostfacers
are cool.
No.
They're really not.
Pure power at hand...
Uh...
Is that
what's his name?
Bambi?
Hey!
Hello.
Are you lost?
Um...
no.
Shoot that ghost right
in the face! Boo-yah!
Winchesters still
suck ass, though.
Affirmative.
You live with
Sam and Dean, right?
They're not here
right now.
Are they
fighting ghosts?!
What's a ghost?
I should go.
Hey, it's...cool.
We know.
About their whole
Hunter thing.
Oh. Good.
I don't like to lie.
It makes my stomach hurt.
Like when you have to burp,
but you can't burp.
Yeah.
So, you need
something?
I do,
but the store's closed.
Not anymore.
Hey!
Come in.
You okay?
No.
I think I should
talk to them.
Who?
Barbara's parents.
Tom, that's not
a good idea.
I've already spoken to them.
They're grieving.
Dad.
This was my fault.
- That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
Tom, they just need
a little time.
We all do.
I feel...
bad for him.
Same.
I mean, living with
a bunch of dudes.
Their whole place must smell
like beer, Kleenex,
and
Old Spice.
I've been watching these guys
called the Ghostfacers.
You heard of 'em?
No.
They're awesome!
They know all about ghosts,
and I'm reading books.
Oh, I like books, too.
I'm reading about zombies.
Zombies are real?
Well, no.
Not really.
It's kind of
disappointing.
- But there are other monsters.
- Like what?
Oh, vampires, werewolves,
shapeshifters --
I've seen one of those --
djinn, rugaru --
That's a funny name. Yeah.
Wraiths, sirens, demons, ghouls.
All sorts of things.
And you know
about all of them?
Well...yes.
Jack, will you be
my best friend?
Dude, stop stalking him.
Sorry.
Ever since he found out
about this stuff,
he's been obsessed.
It's fine.
Do you ever,
like, hang out?
Well, we have movie nights
on Tuesdays.
Dean usually picks.
I've seen "Lost Boys"
like 36 times.
I mean with kids
your own age.
Well, I'm two.
...enty.
I'm twenty.
Two.
I'm twenty two.
Okay.
Well, we're going
to the Stoke place tomorrow,
if you wanna chill.
It's this old farmhouse
outside of town.
No one goes there.
So we can talk
about monsters.
And other
non-freak things.
I...
I think I'd like that.
It's $37.08.
But for the beer,
I need to see some ID.
ID?
Kohonta.
Gesundheit.
No, not --
Kohonta.
It's a -- It's a local
Native American legend.
I can't find much about it,
but they're sort of...
twisted monsters
that roam the woods
"driven to consume
sweet mortal flesh."
- You think this is our Hot Lips?
- Could be.
I mean, according
to the lore,
Kohonta get so starving,
they spit up stomach acid.
Mm. Gross.
Yeah.
If that is our monster,
it's old...
and...
hungry.
How much longer?
Keep up, old man.
What was that?
Nothing.
It's just the wind.
We should head back.
Sara?
Hey!
Who the hell are you?!
I'm talking to you, freak!
I --
Sara, run!
Hey, did you know when some
animals get a taste of people,
that's all
they'll want to hunt?
I mean, I'm reading on here
that tigers, even bears --
Tom, you've got to stop.
You won't let me talk
to Barbara's parents.
I have to do something.
You said it was
a coyote, right?
Barbara!
Yeah. It was.
Sheriff, there's a...
situation at Big Creek.
It got somebody else,
didn't it?
But did --
did they find him?
No, not yet.
Sara, what did you
see out there?
There was this guy.
I think...it was a guy.
He looked like he was
covered in something.
And...
he was whistling.
I ran, but Fitz, he...
Can you tell us
exactly where you were
when this thing
attacked you?
I think...
a few miles past
the old Parker cabin.
Parker?
Okay, wrap it up!
Sheriff, we've got
a search party out there.
Not anymore. You're bringing
everybody in. Now.
What's going on?
What does it look like?
We're done here.
I'm not wasting time and money
hunting for a rabid coyote.
Okay, Sheriff, this wasn't
an animal attack.
Then what was it?
Look, if you want to pull your
men out of there, that's fine.
But we still need
to get in there.
It's not happening.
Look, I don't care
if you guys are the FBI.
Nobody goes in those woods
without my say-so.
Understood?
Mm-hmm.
- Hm.
- Good.
He wants us to call off...
Well, we should probably
do what he says.
Oh, yeah.
Definitely.
We're done.
? It was love ?
? It was real ?
I'm gonna fail.
I'm gonna fail
the SATs.
No way.
I mean, you get 400 points just
for spelling your name right.
Mmm.
So, I mean...
you'll at least get that.
Probably.
- Maybe.
- Shut up!
It's not my fault you're so cute
when you're angry.
? It was love ?
? It was real ?
If you two are going to kiss,
can you go to the other room?
- Myeh!
- Hmm...
I'm trying
to work here.
Okay. Chill.
Come in.
Jack. You came.
Yeah.
You invited me.
Yeah. We know.
- Are these --
- Books.
On monsters.
Awesome.
? ...again ?
? Can you teach me
how to love again? ?
What's that?
Music?
- I like The Who.
- Who?
Oh, my aunt
listens to them.
They're...old.
Well, Dean says any music
made after 1979 "sucks ass."
That's because Dean
is also old.
Sit down.
? But it was love ?
? It was real ?
What's the sat?
The...SAT's?
You were
homeschooled, huh?
Uh...yes.
Whoa.
Do demons really
look like this?
Uh...
No.
They don't have horns.
They actually
look like smoke,
unless they've
possessed a human.
Then, they can look
like me or you...
or anybody.
Really?
And you've
seen one before?
I've killed one.
Yeah?
How?
This is an angel blade.
So...it's made
out of angels?
Uh, no, it kills
angels and demons.
- Cool.
- Hey! Unh-unh!
You're not going to go swinging
some giant knife around.
- I was just gonna --
- Remember that time
you almost killed yourself
with a Slinky?
I didn't.
He tried to eat it.
I was 3.
So, how do you use it?
Well, there are standard
hand-to-hand combat moves.
Like a lightsaber.
Or you can throw it,
like...this.
Nice.
That sheriff was definitely
hiding something.
Yeah, either that
or he's scared.
Oh, by the way, uh,
"Kohonta" means "whistler."
All right.
How do we kill it?
Well, here's the thing.
The lore doesn't really specify.
Great. Well, my vote?
Shotgun, head, done.
Drop your weapons!
You boys don't listen,
do you?
Told you.
Stay out of these woods!
I don't care
if you're FBI.
All right. Sheriff.
We're not FBI.
Does the word "Kohonta"
mean anything to you?
No.
- You're lyin'.
- I'm not.
You're coming in with me.
Move.
Now!
Sorry, Sheriff.
Getting closer.
I-I'm just
a little rusty.
Mm-hmm.
It's cool if you
can't do it, dude.
I can do it, okay?
Just...watch.
- What...
- The... - Hell?
Dude!
Are you like...
a Jedi or something?
Kinda.
Watch this.
Holy...
This is so cool.
Max?
Uh...
Okay, Jack.
Cut it out.
Don't worry. You're safe.
Look.
Whoa. Jack.
I can control it.
I don't care!
Just stop!
Jack?
What?
Seriously, Jack!
Stop!
Stacy!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Stacy!
- Oh, God! Oh, God!
It's okay, it's okay.
E-Eliot, go call 911.
It's okay.
You stay with me, okay?
Please.
I was in control.
E-Everything was fine.
She moved.
Get away from her!
911.
What's your emergency?
Stacy. It's okay.
I'm here. Okay? Okay?
Stacy. Please.
I can fix this.
What are you doing?!
Trust me. Okay.
Sir? Sir? Hello?
Are you still there?
Stace?
How?
I-I fixed you.
Don't.
But she's okay.
Everything's fine. Right?
No!
Okay?
Just...get away.
Eliot?
I don't know...
what you are.
But stay away.
We hunt things.
Fight things and kill things
people don't understand.
So...
Kohonta.
Talk.
Uh...
I-I...
I didn't think
it was real.
The Kohonta was a tribal legend,
an old story.
I haven't heard about it
since I was a kid.
But then I s-saw it
the night
Barbara was killed.
Wait a second.
So that's why you've been
trying to keep people
out of the woods?
So what the hell
is this thing?
It's not what. Who.
The Parker family,
they were some
of the first white settlers
around here.
They set a homestead up
in these woods -- the cabin.
And then?
Things went bad.
There was a hard winter.
Their oldest son, Henry,
survived...
but he did things.
What kind of things?
Like Donner Party?
Pretty much.
They say that boy
not only ate his family,
they said he went...
mad with hunger.
He went after my people,
and then when my tribe
caught him, they...
Killing him
would have been too easy.
They wanted that boy to suffer.
For his crimes
against our people,
crimes against nature.
They cursed him.
He's doomed
to roam the woods...
...always starving.
And if he didn't feed...
...his body would eat itself.
The Kohonta aren't born.
They're made.
So they just let some
flesh-eating freak loose?
They bound him
to this forest.
They marked the trees
to keep folks away.
But that was
a long time ago.
Yeah, people forget.
- Even me.
- Well, it's a good thing.
Like I said,
we hunt these things.
- What do you mean?
- Kohonta, werewolves, demons.
Those are real?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And we kill 'em.
You --
Just the two of you?
- We know what we're doing.
- Do you?
Look, if those monsters
are out there,
why don't you tell people?
Give them -- well, us --
a chance to fight back?
Because telling people
about this stuff --
they don't always believe.
Your people tried to warn you
about this whistling freak.
Nobody bought it.
Not even you.
So?
Just record them,
put it on YouTube.
Knowing about monsters
and fighting 'em
are two different things.
So you make that choice
for everybody?
Imagine telling them.
Imagine the lives
you could save.
No. No.
It doesn't work
like that.
People die.
Even when they know
how to fight,
people still die.
Tom.
- I can't do this anymore.
- Where are you?
Just listen.
Whatever's out there...
I just want you to know
I'm going to find it...
and kill it.
Tom!
No! To--
He's alone out there.
We gotta find him.
- Okay, slow down.
- Look, I-I lied to him.
I told him
it was a coyote.
Listen. We're gonna help you
protect your son, okay?
We're not entirely sure
how to kill this thing.
I am. Look.
The story says a silver blade
through the heart.
Silver blade. Can do.
Thomas!
Hey!
Aaah!
Go! Go!
Whoa.
You don't like that, huh?
Come on!
Yeah.
Come on, come on.
Aaah!
Whoa.
That was like
full-on "Raiders."
Tom.
He's alive.
- Easy.
- D-Dad?
Thomas.
Did we get it?
The coyote?
- Okay...ready?
- Yeah.
You want an ambulance
for you?
I didn't know
what to tell him.
How about the truth?
He's your son.
He deserves the truth.
So, telling the kid --
you think that's the best idea?
What? You don't?
It doesn't make his life
any better, you know?
Do what we always do.
When in doubt, lie.
Yeah, right.
Like we did with Jack?
I took care of it, okay?
We took care of it.
No, no, Dean.
We did not take care of it.
You did.
And do you think you really
took care of it the right way?
Jack said he was fine.
Yeah. He's a kid.
And when we were kids,
how many times did we tell Dad
that we were fine
just to make him happy?
Hey, kid.
We're back.
You still at it?
Almost there.
How was the Hunt?
Oh.
Uh...disgusting.
Oh. Well, I got
the supplies.
Except for the beer.
I didn't have ID.
- You have tons of IDs.
- They're fake.
Jack...listen.
Dean and I, we --
we want to talk to you
about your powers.
W-What about them?
This Hunt, we, uh...
we didn't want you coming along
because we didn't
want you using them.
Not yet.
Not for now.
You know, you just
got 'em back, Jack.
We want to make sure you're
comfortable with them again
before you...
Before you go
all X-Men.
It was crappy of us
not to tell you.
You know, we were
trying to be nice.
'Cause we care
about you.
But because we care about you,
you deserve the truth.
You understand that?
Jack?
I understand.
I won't use my powers
without permission.
Promise.
Great.
And I guess I'll go
get some beer.
What about everything else?
You good?
I mean, anything happen
while we were gone?
No.
Nothin'.
Good.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man