What just happened?
This is the end...
of everything.
We had a deal!
Michael.
Thanks for the suit.
I'm useless.
Charlie?
She wasn't cursed.
This was.
You have
the mind of a Hunter.
I don't remember most
of what Michael did.
No! Ugh!
And now
he's hurting people.
It's all on me.
It's my fault.
Good morning!
Whoa, whoa, Harper,
it's me.
Winston, God.
I'm sorry, I just, uh --
just wanted to make sure
that we're still on for,
you know, dinner tonight.
Um...
yeah, sure.
Harper.
Are you okay?
I heard a scream.
Is this guy
causing trouble?
"This guy"? Miles, we went
to high school together.
Miles, we talked about you minding
your own business, didn't we?
Put the stapler down.
I heard a scream.
Guy's always
been creepy.
He's just overreacting because
nothing ever happens here.
Nobody comes
to the library anymore,
not even
for story time.
Isn't that sad?
Well,
I'm here.
I'll see you tonight.
- For our date.
- For dinner.
Which I'm sure will be
a very nice time.
Yes!
? Well, you can tell
by the way I use my walk ?
? I'm a woman's man ?
? No time to talk ?
? Music loud and women warm ?
? I've been kicked around
since I was born ?
? And now it's all right,
it's okay ?
? And you may look
the other way ?
? We can try -- ?
? Supernatural 14x06 ?
Optimism
Original Air Date on November 15, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Geez.
What's up
with the sugar?
Well, without my powers,
everything tastes different.
So, I can't get this
how I like it.
Seen Sam?
He went to meet up
with Charlie.
You were on an overnight run
to Mary and Bobby's place.
He said
it couldn't wait.
They're probably doing something
really exciting.
So, this is where
all those people went missing?
Yep.
Right.
So, he just
left you here, huh?
Yep.
Sam wanted someone around
when you came back.
He's worried about you.
Yeah,
sounds like him.
Dean, what happened
with Michael --
no one blames you.
Cool.
Well, I blame me,
so...
Still with that cough,
huh?
Yeah, maybe I'm allergic
to sitting around doing nothing.
All right.
What do you want
to do?
Hunt.
Sam says
I can't go alone,
but Cass and I,
we've been working cases.
And he says you've been
doing good on those.
No offense --
Cass is an insurance policy
on those hunts.
Sam's just trying
to keep you safe, okay?
He's a smart guy.
Hmm.
Look.
Winston Mathers.
Dead,
with what appears to be
human bite marks
taken out of the corpse.
"Human" bite marks?
And other people
have gone missing, too.
Well, Sam's not
gonna like it.
Sam's not here.
Okay, you know what?
You did good work. Okay?
- I'll go check it out.
- No.
We're supposed to have a partner
for all hunts now, right?
We can be
hunting buddies.
Okay. Uh...
"A" --
don't call it that.
And "B" --
you're gonna back me up?
Dean,
I need to do something.
You don't understand.
I could have
killed Michael.
Here,
when I was strong enough,
I could have.
But there was
so much going on,
and then
everything else happened
because I was distracted
and stupid and --
Hey.
You didn't
do anything wrong.
And neither did you.
But that doesn't make it
any easier, does it?
So, I can't just sit here
in the bunker
thinking about it
all day.
What I could have
done differently,
how I can't do
anything about it now.
But I can do this.
I can hunt.
Give me a chance.
Are you sure?
Just you guys?
I mean, we can probably send
some other hunters out there.
It's so close and --
Yeah.
Be careful.
Dean's going out on a hunt
with Jack.
Good for them.
Are you sure
this is the right place?
Well, it's where
those four people disappeared,
and when
I was scouting around,
I found this.
- What, goo?
- Goo.
So, yeah, I'd say
this is the right place.
Now I'm just trying
to figure out
what we're dealing with.
Thus, books.
? Ever since
she came to town... ?
This was Winston's
favorite spot?
His obituary said
he loved having breakfast here
every morning,
which is sort of
oddly specific.
Yeah,
when a young guy dies,
they never know
what to put in those things.
Hi, there.
- Help you?
- Yeah.
Uh, Agent Berry,
FBI.
This is my partner,
Agent Charles.
Wondering if you can give
us some details
on a regular of yours,
Winston Mathers?
Sure, hon.
Um,
detail number one --
Winston's dead.
Detail number two --
huh,
that's all the details.
Winston dead.
No details.
Uh, you know,
you're gonna want to be
a little more helpful
than that.
Listen,
Deep State.
Flashing a badge
might work on people
who don't have a working
knowledge of the Constitution...
...but that ain't me.
Now I got to go
earn some money.
Or you could stay here
and earn some money.
He, uh, came in every day
like clockwork.
But you really want to ask about
Harper Sayles.
Winston just started
courting her.
What's "courting?"
It's what you do
before you start dating.
Oh, and that's the thing you do
before the sex.
Sometimes you just
have the sex.
Okay, that's...
Who is Harper Sayles?
Harper's
a really sweet woman.
Everybody in town knows her.
It's been a sad life.
Prom queen in high school.
Very popular.
And her boyfriend
ran off on her.
She did not take it well.
- Ever since then, well...
- Everything just seems to go wrong.
She's lost people --
Not people. Men.
- Men.
- A lawyer.
- A florist.
- A gym coach.
- Now Winston.
It just honestly seems like all
she cares about are her books.
Romance novels,
mostly.
Heroes and damsels.
- Ask me?
- She's bad luck.
- Real shame.
He'll be fine.
Your brother,
I mean.
He's got
other friends, right?
Funny.
Um, he used to have
a pretty damn good wing man.
So, call that guy
to check on him.
That "guy" was you.
No,
it wasn't.
Right. I -- Sorry.
I didn't mean to...
I'm just saying,
I'm not surprised
you survived the apocalypse.
Yeah.
Well, I am.
Sam,
before all this,
I was just a programmer
at Richard Roman Enterprises.
I lived with
the love of my life, and we --
Wait, you -- you did?
Yeah.
So, your Charlie,
she --
I guess
she never met Kara.
Kara.
Uh...
she owned a bakery
outside of Chicago.
Cupcakes.
It was like something
out of a storybook.
She always
smelled like peaches,
and her smile
was just...
Michael and Lucifer,
when they started their war,
first thing,
a giant EMP or something like it
went off
over North America.
Fried every bit
of technology.
Cellphones,
power plants.
For the first few days,
we banded together.
Thought,
"Hey, someone'll save us".
No one ever did.
When the food ran out,
people got mean.
Mobs started forming,
stealing whatever they could
get their hands on.
A lot of people died.
Kara died.
People are always the same
when things go wrong --
they lose it.
One day,
the water gets shut off,
the next day,
people are on fire.
It's a fact
about society --
it all falls apart.
Not here.
Not yet.
Well, congrats, Mighty Mouse.
I think
you found us a case.
Thanks.
What's Mighty Mouse?
Eat up.
Pie's important.
Okay, uh,
can I ask you about
what Wanda said
about courting?
I mean,
I've seen romantic movies,
but I've never
experienced it.
Unless what you said about
Rowena and Gabriel counts.
No,
definitely doesn't count.
Look, I promise
when we get back home,
I'll give you
the talk, okay?
The talk?
Mm-hmm.
Right now what we got to find
is Harper Sayles.
I mean, that's just too much
bad luck for one person.
Maybe --
Maybe she's not human.
Well, that's what
we're gonna find out.
How?
You ever read
a romance novel?
Harper Sayles?
Hi!
Um, how can I help you?
Uh, FBI.
Got some questions
about Winston Mathers.
Oh, I already spoke
to the police.
Well,
I'm not the police.
I don't -- I don't want
to talk about this anymore.
Well, I'm gonna need you
to talk about it.
Hello.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm looking for the best book
on the area's history.
Excuse me.
I was talking with her.
Really?
Because it doesn't look like
she wants to talk to you.
- Listen, I'm, uh --
- FBI.
Yeah,
I heard.
But, see,
I haven't done anything wrong,
so you can't
do anything to me.
And if she doesn't want
to talk to you,
you can't make her.
Not without
arresting her.
But you're FBI,
so you probably
knew that already.
Okay.
Why don't you back off,
kid?
No,
you back off...
old man.
Uh --
Old man?
Yeah.
That's right.
Okay.
All right.
This isn't over.
That was
so chivalrous.
Yeah.
What's his problem?
He was just asking --
Y-You know what?
It's fine, I'm fine.
Thank you
for stepping in.
You didn't
have to do that.
I'm Jack,
by the way.
Jack Smith.
Harper.
I have
the perfect book for you.
That would be great.
Old man, my ass.
Harper.
Are you leaving?
Miles,
this is Jack.
He's visiting, and I'm getting
him my favorite book about town.
It's just
down at my apartment,
but, um, I'll come back
and lock up.
You're taking him
to your apartment?
You don't even
know this guy.
Miles, stop it.
Let's go.
All right,
where are we headed?
How many books
are you reading?
All of them.
I hate hunting.
Really?
'Cause I got to say,
you're kind of awesome
at it.
Yeah, well, when it's that
or die by angel kill squad...
Right.
I mean,
no offense,
but who wants
to be a hunter?
This job, it's just
a lot of tears and death.
Funny.
You, uh -- You said
something like that to me once
long ago about hunting.
Not you.
Uh, sorry.
Our Charlie.
Well,
she was right.
So glad
this is my last case.
What?
I told myself I'd help you out
for awhile,
at least until everyone
got really settled,
and then...
- I'm out.
- To do what? To go where?
- Away.
From monsters,
from people, from...
I'll go live on a mountaintop
or something.
As long
as there's good Wi-Fi.
Come in.
Okay,
I'm just realizing
it's weird
I brought you to my place.
That's weird.
I'm weird.
It's fine.
I think.
You need to get
that book, right?
I just don't want you
to think I'm --
I'm not putting
the moves on you.
- The moves?
- I'll go get the book.
Hey, uh,
do you mind --
Is it okay
to ask you about the guy
who was hassling you
at the library?
Oh, recently,
a boy I knew --
or was starting to know --
passed away.
It was terrible.
The authorities have been asking
a lot of questions,
but I don't
know anything,
and I'm a pretty private person,
so...
It's been
a little difficult.
- That's awful about your friend.
- Thanks.
Is this yours?
Oh, sorry.
I must've dropped that.
Your hand is wet.
Christo.
Did you say something?
Uh, no.
Uh...
I'm just nervous.
Come here.
Got something.
What?
Have you ever
heard of a Musca?
Yeah, like a hybrid
between a man and a fly.
A lot of stories
about them,
but no one's ever seen one
in real life.
If they do exist,
they keep to themselves.
Look at you.
Oh, I have read
all the books.
Nerd.
But check this.
Every few hundred years,
there's a "bad egg".
When a male
fails to find a mate,
he abandons
his community
and starts using people's bodies
to nest,
binding them together
with a viscous goo.
- And when the goo fits...
- Oh, great.
Our perp might just be a giant
fly with low self-esteem.
- Sam.
- Yeah?
What is that?
So,
where are you from?
I'm from a little town in Kansas
called Lebanon.
It's actually smaller
than this one.
Wow.
Yeah, my family's been here
for generations.
I'm the last one.
Are you okay?
Is this --
Is this your boyfriend?
I'm single.
Perpetually.
But Vance
was my boyfriend.
After high school,
he wanted to leave town.
I told him
we didn't need to.
We could see the world
in books.
Which I know
sounds way too sappy.
And...
he left anyway.
Without you?
I don't blame him.
But that, well...
that was the beginning
of my bad luck.
Just so many things
that I --
I try
to stay optimistic.
Me, too.
I've had some...
not-so-great stuff
happen in my past.
Trying to be positive...
it can be hard.
Jack?
Do you believe
in love at first sight?
Do you...
...mind if I use
the bathroom?
Jack.
Uh, Dean?
Um,
I'm at Harper's place.
The silver and the holy water
didn't do anything,
so she's not
a demon.
Where are you?
Because Harper is not
a monster,
and I'm 99% sure
she's in love with me.
That's not
how it works, kid.
Okay, but she was looking at me
with these googly eyes,
and then
she asked me --
Look, I promise you
that Harper Sayles
is not in love with you, okay?
Would you calm down?
Okay.
But if she is, I need to know
everything about sex. Go.
Jack,
listen to me.
The guy that she works with
is dead,
and I mean
fresh dead.
Something bit out
his throat.
So, we got bigger things
to worry about right now.
Okay,
what should I do?
Well, something's definitely
stalking Harper,
or at least the people
around her.
She said that she had bad luck.
Maybe she's cursed.
Well, seems like
the guys around her are cursed.
Okay,
guys like me?
Yeah.
Look, just keep her there --
Dean?
- Are you upset?
- What?
Ugh, I freaked you out,
didn't I?
I'm sorry. Sometimes I can
come off as intense.
No, you're fine.
I'm fine.
So...
do you want to go get coffee,
or...?
I don't know.
You don't know?
No, no, no, it's okay. It's okay.
We're here to help you.
I'm Dean,
okay?
I work with Jack.
We're not FBI.
We're here to save lives --
maybe even yours.
Save me?
From what?
That.
- Who's out there?
- It's not a "who".
At first,
I thought it was a ghost,
but then it punched me in the face.
- A ghost?
No, he's saying
it's not a ghost.
Yeah, now I'm thinking,
uh --
- Who is this?
- That's my old boyfriend Vance.
- How did he die?
- Die? I think he lives in Connecticut.
- Not anymore.
- Harper!
Vance?!
- Vance?
Vance.
All right, so we're dealing with
some sort of undead,
risen dead --
something in that wheelhouse.
Harper!
Silver. Silver.
Risen dead?
- Yeah.
- Harper!
Looks like you
finally get your zombie, kid.
- Zombie?!
- Oh, he means --
Silver can hurt it,
maybe slow it down,
but there is only one way
to stop these things.
- Jack, get her out of here.
- I-I can't just leave.
Go, now!
Archie! Hey!
Let's dance.
Charlie,
you can't just quit
and go live on
a mountain somewhere.
- People need people.
- Why?
'Cause they're the luckiest
people in the world?
No, come on.
We just do.
We're social animals.
- Emphasis on "animals".
- Yeah, but you're also a hunter.
The things
that we've seen,
it's not so easy
to just walk away from it all.
Believe me, I've tried.
Our Charlie tried.
Yeah, well, again,
she ain't me.
It's my life,
Sam.
Not hers
and not yours.
He's back.
That's got to be
our guy, right?
- I say we rush him.
- No, no, no.
Wait for it.
We don't want to run up
and tackle some regular guy
just 'cause he's into
weird fashion.
Mm, don't we?
Come on.
Damn it!
Go, go, go, go!
Wait!
W-What is happening?
No, look -- Look, we have to
keep moving.
Hyah!
What the hell?
You were gonna come back
and lock up, remember?
No. Apparently,
my dead high-school boyfriend
attacked us,
and I forgot.
Where'd they go?
Not a lot of options.
Look at this.
I cased
this block earlier.
That was
definitely locked...
and, you know,
not covered in goo.
You said there was something
in the book about, uh, uh,
a brass nail dipped
in sugar water can kill it?
In theory, since no one's
actually seen one.
And we have exactly zero
of those items handy, so...
So,
we get creative.
Ugh.
Oh, God.
That is, uh...
Yeah, smells like pine cleaner
and rotting meat.
Sam?
Yeah, he was chloroformed,
all right.
I found him.
He's still alive.
We should
get him out of here.
- Charlie?
- Sam!
Charlie!
Hey, hey, Charlie.
So...
we got creative.
Cool.
Don't worry.
I locked it.
Did you flip the switch
under the lock?
What -- What switch?
I'll get it.
Harper, don't!
Don't!
Harper?
Aww, sweet.
No, no.
What are you doing?
What?
He's my boyfriend.
He just gets
a little jealous sometimes.
But he's dead.
And stalking you.
No,
he's stalking you.
It's a little game
we play.
Some people
pretend to be naughty nurses,
some people get tied up.
We do this.
Oh, and he has to eat flesh
to maintain his body.
Stupid magic.
But it all
works out.
Except...
not for you.
I'm sorry about all this,
Jack.
I actually think I liked you.
But you're obviously a hunter,
and I come from a long line
of necromancers.
I mean, I can mostly
only raise the dead,
but that comes in handy.
And I can't let you
or your friend
get in the way
of the love Vance and I share.
It's first love, Jack.
The best kind.
Without baggage or compromise.
I mean, I did have to kill him
to keep him here after college,
but...every relationship
has its stuff, right?
And all the other guys --
none of them are like Vance.
Strong and courageous and --
So, they all had to die.
Especially Miles,
who just -- ugh.
So, I had Vance
crush his throat.
I wish I could have watched.
And now
we're going to kill you.
Shh.
Okay.
Not a lot works
on these things.
Uh, headshot?
No, no, no.
Creeps like this, you got to
get 'em back in their grave.
Drive a silver stake through
their heart to keep 'em there.
Okay, so...?
So, we got to convince this guy
to get six feet under.
And you're gonna convince him
with your shotgun?
Not exactly.
Harper?
Why are you
doing this?
I-I thought we fell in love
at first sight.
What?
I'm not weak
like those other guys.
I'm not afraid
to really love you.
What would it be like to be
with someone alive?
Who could walk you
down the aisle
in front
of the whole town?
And start
a family with.
With me.
But I tried
to kill you.
Every relationship
has its stuff, right?
We can stay
in the town you love
a-and never leave.
She's mine!
Hey!
No!
Hey, okay, look, I'm sure
you were in love, okay?
But this isn't love,
not anymore.
I love her.
Yes, sure, sure,
but now it's like
some sort of a sick game,
you know?
I mean, you have to eat people
to stay together?
I mean,
is that romantic?
Huh?
You enjoy that?
Okay,
all right.
Look, let's just think
about this for a second.
Vance!
Baby, kill him!
You okay?
Yeah.
Just grab the girl.
Oh,
son of a bitch.
You know, I think that guy
from the bus stop --
I think
he'll be all right.
I bet they'll take good care
of him at the hospital.
He's also gonna wake up
with a serious headache.
Better than
being killed.
Hmm.
Got to say, I do feel
kind of bad for the Musca.
I-I mean,
he could have been happy
if it stayed
with his people.
Didn't have to go off on its own
just because --
Okay,
I get it.
I am
just like the bug,
and I shouldn't
go out on my own.
But your nifty metaphor
has holes.
I wasn't looking
for love.
I found it,
and I lost it.
And I didn't kill people
and literally nest
in their body parts, so...
Okay,
I know, I know.
How about this?
Don't leave.
Hear me out.
Sure, some people
can do bad things
when they're desperate
or scared,
but I mean,
the guy we just saved,
he has a wife,
children.
I'm not saying all people
are good people
or even that most people are,
but...
if we help people,
then maybe they'll help people
and all that.
And that's worth it.
Even with all the tears
and death --
it's worth it.
Just to be
super clear,
I am not like
the fly monster.
But...
I'll think
about staying.
? We're traveling down
two different roads ?
? In worlds so far apart ?
? You want me,
yet there's something else ?
? Before me in your heart ?
Harper: "Jack.
I'm already writing --
isn't that crazy?
I'm not crazy.
But our love is so vivid.
I can't wait to find you.
You're the first man to ever
get me to leave McCook.
Now I'm in the world.
I'm sorry I have to kill you
for what you did to Vance,
but then I can bring you back
so that we can be together
again.
It's gonna be...perfect.
See you soon.
Love, Harper".
? If we can't live together,
then it's best we live apart ?
? You'll go your way
and I'll go mine ?
? We'll both make
a brand-new start ?
So, now that Vance
is in the grave,
he can't hurt anyone?
Yeah.
Silver stake
through the heart --
that ought
to do the trick.
And...that's love?
Eh.
Actually, love can get
crazier than that.
And it might
get crazier,
with Harper still out there,
but, uh...
You did good,
kid.
And?
And what?
I was right,
and you should be letting me
go out on hunts.
Okay.
All right.
Look, it's not about
being right, okay?
You're gonna make mistakes.
Hell, I make them
all the time.
But it's how
you handle yourself
once you've made
those mistakes.
And you learn
from them.
And...
how to not beat yourself up
over them?
You know, Jack,
you're pretty smart sometimes.
I tell you what --
when Sam gets back,
I'll talk to him about
getting you out on more hunts.
Okay?
In the meantime, we'll get you
a crate of cough drops.
I'm fine.
It's all part
of being human, right?
Mm.
You sure you're okay?
I don't know.
Jack! Jack.
Jack!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man