Impossible odds.
Walking right into
a trap.
Feels like home.
Michael conned me.
Kept me trapped and drowning
inside my own body.
I own you.
And he's out there
hurting people.
His name. Gadreel.
I have Sam locked away
in a dream.
Say "Poughkeepsie."
It's our go word. It means
"drop everything and run."
Get...out!
I know this must be
so hard without your grace.
Jack!
Please don't be sad.
Maybe this is how
things are supposed to be.
He's gone.
Here's to you, Jack.
My magic draws power
from the human soul.
It could save him.
If Jack is in Heaven,
I might be able to pull
his soul into his body.
With the spear
still in play,
could be a shot at actually
killing the son of a bitch.
No.
When I gave up Dean,
you didn't think to question?
This time, he is buried.
And now...
I have a whole army
out there,
ready for my command.
? I rode into town today ?
? In my mind, I said,
"Lord, I'd love to stay" ?
? Something in me said,
"Boy, move on" ?
That weather.
? Don't know what it is ?
? The good Lord bred it in my bones ?
Not even playing around.
? And I'm searchin'
for a rainbow ?
Everybody's shopping at the
store like it's the End Days.
The milk and bread aisles
were a war zone.
But I battled through it all
for your stupid bag of limes.
? You'll be waiting at the end,
and I know ?
Hey, I'm not makin' the house
special without the limes.
What are we -- savages?
Well...
? I'd see the hill
with that pot of gold ?
Tequila shot and a beer.
Best damn house special ever.
? This old mount I'm ridin',
she's gettin' kinda tired ?
No complaints here.
? But in my heart, she knows
there's this one desire ?
Whoo! Mmm.
? She's gonna take me to the end of our road ?
Is there any word from Sam?
Still working that ghoul thing
in Wichita with Cass.
They should be back tonight.
? Then she'll lay down and die ?
? And I'll say, "God rest her soul" ?
? And I'm searchin'
for a rainbow ?
Wet one out there, eh?
Yes.
And you are...?
Pamela Barnes.
Waitress, hostess,
Ouija board enthusiast.
- We met the last time you stopped by --
- Oh! Mr. Winchester.
And the time before that.
I brought the papers
I mentioned.
I know you said
you weren't interested,
but it's just a few signatures
and you could --
Can I get you a drink?
I'm in a bit of a rush.
Well, sorry you wasted
your trip out here,
but, um...Rocky's
still isn't for sale.
Rocky's
looks pretty dead.
It's a very generous offer.
Well, all the same,
this bar?
I've never had
anything this nice.
So that sale
that you want so bad,
well, it's just not
gonna happen.
Need to borrow an umbrella?
? And I'm searchin'
for a rainbow ?
Mm-hmm.
You just gonna leave
the drunk guy
out there
with all the booze?
What, you mean
that unconscious drunk guy?
Yeah, I am.
Do a shot with me.
I'm heading out
for a hot date.
How come you always
have a boyfriend?
How come you only want
what you can't have?
Whoa.
Besides, you don't want me.
You just like to flirt.
I'm a psychic,
so I kinda know.
All right.
So, still not ready
to sell the bar, huh?
It's a lot of money.
Sell? This bar?
This is my dream.
Yeah.
Dean?
You wanna come out here?
? I rode into town today ?
What's up?
? In my mind, I said,
"Lord, I'd love to stay" ?
Trouble.
What kind of trouble?
? Something in me said,
"Boy, move on" ?
That kind.
Dean Winchester?
Yeah?
I got a score
to settle with you.
You and your brother
killed my entire nest
back in Sudler.
Is that right?
Nice.
- Whoo.
- Oh.
What you got?
Worst part of working here is
having to clean up the blood
after some pissed-off monster
busts in to kill you.
? And I'm searchin' for a rainbow ?
Well, what can I say?
I'm famous.
? Supernatural 14x10 ?
Nihilism
Original Air Date on January 17, 2019
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Now, this...
just feels right.
Hope is an amazing thing, isn't it?
You had no chance
of winning this.
None.
But you had hope --
hope that I wouldn't
see you coming,
but I saw everything.
It'll be the end of him.
Ketch says
he'll set up a meeting.
Jack! - Jack!
And now I have
my perfect vessel.
I've just destroyed
the one weapon
that could really hurt me.
Thanks for bringing that,
by the way.
Don't interrupt me.
You think these
can hold me?
Yes, we do.
Dean.
Come on, Dean.
Are you in there?
Dean's not home
right now.
Please leave a message.
Oh, right. That.
Did you forget?
My monsters are out there,
building an army.
Maggie? Hey.
What's happening out there?
I brought every hunter
I could find, like you said,
and we're trying to track down
the monsters,
but, uh,
there's so many of them.
We're getting reports
of attacks all over the city.
No kills, just bites
or scratches.
It's like they're
trying to infect --
- Yeah, I know.
- Sam, where are you?
Top of Hitomi Plaza,
10th and Main.
- We've got Michael.
- Do you?
Okay, we'll get there
as soon as we can.
No, no, no, just save
as many people as you can.
Don't worry about us.
We'll figure it out.
- Thanks.
- Okay, what's the plan?
With the angel cuffs on,
Michael's under control.
Keep telling yourself
that.
Get him downstairs, dump him
in the trunk of the Impala,
and take him
back to the bunker.
But Garth is in the trunk.
It's a big trunk.
Monsters!
More like the Calvary.
I called them.
It's a party.
Sam, I don't know how long
I can hold them.
Yeah, well, we have to
get Dean out of here.
Yeah, well,
we can't go this way.
It's not like
any of us can fly.
- Well, one of us can.
- Shut up!
Sam, are we gonna
die here?
Jessica?
You said you're
always here, right?
Sam, what are you doing?
Billie -- uh, uh,
Death assigned a reaper
to keep an eye
on Dean and me.
Her name is Jessica,
and she is always --
Hello.
Where's Jessica?
Well, my name's Violet.
It's my shift.
We have shifts now,
because you mess up so,
so many things.
Sturdy door.
Okay, all right. Well, Violet,
we have to get out of here.
And I want you
to know that
you have
my full emotional support.
W-We don't want
your emotional support.
We -- We want your actual,
physical help.
Sam, who are you talking to?
You can't see her?
I can.
You know, in my world,
we locked Death away
and enslave the reapers.
Lovely. Well,
just look at you now.
Okay, look, sorry,
but we're stuck, okay?
And Death owes us one
after we fixed
that whole Rowena thing.
You know about that, right?
Oh, yes, the Rowena thing
you started.
We're gonna die here.
- And my brother --
- Reapers can't intervene -- and rules.
Don't give me that whole
clean hands --
Even if I did
feel inclined, uh,
we don't have access
to that kind of --
- Yeah, well, uh --
- Shh, shh.
Sam, what is she saying?
She's not saying
anything.
Okay.
What?
How did you do that?
I, uh, didn't.
Have fun.
Now what?
Shouldn't we put him in
the dungeon or something?
Jack's right --
we don't know
how long those cuffs
are gonna hold.
I mean, Bobby improved them,
but --
If those cuffs won't hold him,
neither will the dungeon.
I can hear you.
Really?
Okay, so, what?
Okay, listen.
Back when Gadreel possessed me,
he -- he created,
uh, I don't know,
like a -- like a fake world
inside my head.
But Crowley was able
to force his way in,
he showed me
how to take control,
and I drove the angel out.
The problem is...
Crowley's dead.
Yeah.
Okay, so...
Sorry. It's Maggie.
Hey.
Sam, we're almost
at Hitomi Plaza.
A-All right, uh,
yeah, we're, uh --
we're actually
back at the bunker.
What?!
Yeah, long story.
I'll explain later.
Uh, Maggie, we, uh --
we left Garth in the trunk
of the Impala
back at Hitomi Plaza.
Can you make sure
he's okay?
Okay, but, Sam,
the monsters --
they've stopped
attacking people.
- What?
- Looks like they're leaving the city.
They're heading west.
Remind me, Castiel --
we're west
of Kansas City now?
You're bringing
them here?
You think?
Jack,
let's lock it down.
Yes, uh, put a chair against the door.
That'll help.
Nothing's changed.
Either my monsters get here
or I break these chains.
But tonight...
everybody dies.
And, Sam?
The last thing you'll see
is this pretty smile...
...as I rip you apart.
What is that?
It's the, uh,
messed up
British Men of Letters thing
they used to get
inside people's heads.
I figure if I can get in,
maybe I can wake Dean up,
get him to fight, you know,
to force Michael out.
If he can.
Yeah.
Cass, this is
all we got.
Any word from Sam?
Still working that ghoul thing
in Wichita with Cass.
They should be back tonight.
Ohh!
Ha!
- Whoo!
- Ha! Oh!
- More shots!
Oh! Mr. Winchester.
? I rode into town today ?
I brought those papers
I mentioned.
I know you said
you weren't interested,
but it's just a few signatures
and you could --
Can I get you a drink?
I'm in a bit of a rush,
so if you could...?
Any word from Sam?
Still working that ghoul thing
in Wichita with Cass.
They should be back tonight.
Nice.
Any word from Sam?
Still working that ghoul thing
in Wichita with Cass.
They should be back tonight.
Huh.
? I rode into town today ?
What's up?
Just had some serious
d?j? vu.
? In my mind, I said,
"Lord, I'd --" ?
So, they left you
to keep an eye on me?
Gotta say,
little insulting.
I mean, what are you?
You're nothing.
That's not what
you said before.
Ah. Yes.
A moment of
familial weakness.
- It won't happen again.
- It doesn't matter.
Sam and Dean --
they're gonna
beat you.
Oh, please.
Sam's in so far over his head,
he's drowning.
And Dean?
Well, I've got Dean
under control.
No.
Dean --
he's strong.
He's a gnat.
I'm a god.
Who would you bet on?
You don't know anything
about Dean.
I'm in his head...
literally.
I know everything.
Like, I know how sad he was
when you died...
on the outside.
On the inside, well,
it's not that
he was happy --
he just didn't care.
'Cause you're not Sam.
You're not Cass.
You're a new burden
that he was handed.
You're a weak,
helpless thing.
You think that
they care about you,
love you?
You're a job,
a job none of them
wanted.
- And you --
- Jack?
Go help Sam.
Wait.
Don't believe
anything he says.
He's lying.
No, I'm not.
And I can still
hear you.
Maggie? Maggie?
You there?
Yeah?
A group of them
got out in front of us,
headed your way
in a black van.
Right. We'll be ready.
Okay. We've, uh, got some heavy
hitters coming through soon.
And...
And Sam needs our help.
You all know what the
Winchesters have done for us.
- They gave us all a second chance.
- Maggie?
Whatever happens,
we can't let the monsters
get back to the bunker.
Look at you.
Playing nursemaid
to an nephilim.
Nothing like
the Castiel I knew.
He would've never been
so...anemic.
You're confusing loyalty
and compassion with weakness.
Tell me.
Why do you love this world
enough to risk your own life?
Tell me.
Why do you hate this world
enough to burn it to the ground?
Because I can.
Because...
Me and my brother --
my Lucifer --
when we fought
in my world,
we thought that God
would come back,
give us answers --
why He'd gone,
what we'd done --
but, instead,
do you know what happened?
Nothing.
No God.
And now...
now that I'm in here --
now I know why.
God -- Chuck --
is a writer,
and like all writers,
He churns out
draft after draft.
My world? This world?
Nothing
but failed drafts.
And when He realizes
that they're flawed,
He moves on
and tries again.
No, that's not how...
Why would He do that?
Because He doesn't care!
About you, me --
anything.
Now, at first, I thought
I'd do it better.
Show Him.
Be more God than God.
But now...
I just want to burn
every one of His little worlds
until I catch up
to the old man.
And then what?
Even God can die.
Hey, you in there!
We've got you surrounded!
- "We have you surrounded"?
- Shut up!
Smithy, what do you see?
No movement.
Tiger, how about you?
They're gone.
There's some tracks here.
Don't go in there alone!
They're on foot.
They went around us.
They're probably heading
for the bunker.
This...
is it going to work?
I don't know.
Well, if it doesn't, maybe
there's something I can do.
The magic that's
keeping me alive,
what if I can do more?
And burn off your soul?
Not all of it.
Jack.
Dean wouldn't want to be saved,
not that way.
You don't know what
you're walking into.
Last time Dean
was possessed,
he said it felt like
he was drowning.
This time...
What?
It'll probably
be worse.
Cool science project.
I give it a solid B-minus.
Okay, in theory, I should be
connected to Dean's mind.
Cass, you should be able to
hitch a ride with me.
Oh, Cass...
I believe in you.
What should I do?
Pray.
And make sure
no one kills us.
Well, I like this plan.
See, out here,
I'm all chained up.
But in there...
you're all mine.
So...what are
we waiting for?
Cass...
where are we?
In Dean's mind.
Then where's he?
Excellent question.
We had a deal!
Wait. Hold on, okay?
We're coming.
You can't escape me, Dean.
You're gonna die.
And this -- this is what
you're gonna become!
Somebody help me!
No!
There's so much.
Your own father didn't care
whether you lived or died.
It's about
who's the bigger badass.
So much trauma
in Dean's mind.
So many scars.
Well, yeah.
Dean's been through a lot,
but he's strong.
Sam...
you've both
been through a lot,
and Dean
is more than strong.
What I meant was,
if I knew...
if I knew
what I was looking for,
I could just --
I could simply go to it.
But because Michael has Dean
trapped away, drowning,
I have to wade through
all of Dean's
most terrible memories.
Cass, wait a second.
Would Michael bury Dean
in trauma?
What do you mean?
I mean,
Michael said it himself.
The reason he left Dean
in the first place
was because Dean was
fighting back so hard.
So if Michael wanted
to keep Dean placated...
Dean thrives on trauma.
I mean, he's had to
his whole life, right?
It keeps him alert,
keeps him ready,
but if I wanted to
distract Dean, I-I...
I'd give him something
he's never had before.
- Contentment.
- Exactly.
So maybe, instead of looking
through his bad memories,
maybe let's, uh...
maybe let's look through
his good memories.
I think I'm adorable.
You seem pretty cheery.
Strippers, Sammy,
strippers.
We're on an actual case
involving strippers.
Finally. I'll stay here,
hook up with the posse.
'Cause you know me --
I'm a posse magnet.
Hey, see if they got
any pie.
This bar -- This bar --
This bar --
I've never had anything
this nice.
Rocky's
still isn't for sale.
Wait a second.
Still working that ghoul thing
in Wichita with Cass.
They should be back tonight.
So that sale
that you want so bad,
well, it's just not gonna happen.
Yes. Definitely...
You just gonna leave
the drunk guy out there
with all the booze?
Cass.
This has never happened.
There.
Let's go there.
Hey! There they are.
? I rode into town today ?
Kill a ghoul, get a beer.
? In my mind, I said -- ?
Dean?
Got this great IPA
from Austin -- Cosmic Cowboy.
You're gonna love it.
Hey, Dean,
what's going on here?
What are you
talking about?
Cass? Sam?
I'm glad
you're back safe.
I was starting to worry.
Don't tell Dean.
He'll use it against me.
? You'd be waiting at the end,
and I know ?
Uh, Pamela Barnes was blinded
when she saw my true form.
Yeah. She was also
killed by a demon, so...
Hey, what are you guys
waiting for?
Drink up.
None of --
None of this is real, okay?
T-This -- This bar,
uh, uh, Pamela...
Excuse me?
You've never met anyone
more real than me,
Sam Winchester.
You're just a complex
manifestation of Dean's memories
designed to distract him.
You really know how to
talk to a lady, don't ya?
Okay, listen to me.
You have to remember
what's going on
out -- out
in the real world.
I know it's raining.
What else do I need to know?
No, I'm not talking
about the rain --
I'm talking about
Michael!
Where'd they go?
Ohh!
Is that...?
- Ohh.
- I think I can hear them.
So, you guys gonna tell us
about the hunt or what?
Okay. W-What?
You were just...
What the hell
is going on here?
Okay. All right.
Now you're starting
to worry me.
What is going on?
Ohhh.
? I rode into town today ?
You guys got real messy
on that ghoul hunt, huh?
No, we didn't get messy
on a hunt.
We got messy just now,
in this bar,
in a vampire fight.
? I rode into town today ?
Maybe we should
rethink the beers.
Yeah.
Okay, Dean, listen to me.
I think you're --
you're stuck in a loop
in -- in your mind.
Michael is possessing you.
You -- You have to
remember that.
Michael?
Yes.
Michael's in the Cage.
Come on, guys. What is this --
some kind of a joke?
No, Dean, it's not a joke.
Okay. Okay.
If we're
all in Dean's head,
then he should be able
to control things,
like a lucid dream?
? And if the wind
ever shows me where to go ?
Yeah. I-I don't know.
Maybe. I...
? You'd be waiting at the end,
and I know ?
Get me a shot.
With your brain.
Okay. Dean, listen to me.
This bar is not real.
Pamela isn't real.
Man, we were there together
when she was blinded.
? This old mount I'm ridin',
she's gettin' kinda tired ?
? She's gonna take me to the end of our road ?
You're blind?
Yeah, I've been blind
for a while.
Thank Feathers here
for that one.
That was --
Dean, that was an accident.
? And I'm searchin'
for a rainbow ?
Dean, she's not just blind.
She's dead.
Pamela died helping us.
What happened?
Pamela?
No. No, no, no, no.
Guys, this is --
this is my life.
This --
This is the dream.
No, no, it's not.
It's just a dream, Dean.
That's all it is.
Please, you have to --
you have to
try to remember,
because the people
in your life --
in your real life,
out there --
we need you to come back.
Poughkeepsie.
What'd you say?
I remember.
I remember everything.
Hey, fellas.
Well, this is fun.
Get out of my head.
You don't mean that, Dean,
not really.
You may lie to them,
but, deep down,
I know you.
I am you.
You only tolerate the angel
because you think you owe him,
because he "gripped you tight
and raised you from Perdition."
Or whatever.
But since then,
what has he done?
Only made mistakes,
one after the other.
And, Sam --
oh, Sam...
You know, Dean was his happiest
when you quit hunting,
leaving him with your dad,
just the two of them.
See, deep down, he knows that
you will always abandon him,
again and again.
Shut up!
You don't need them.
You don't even like them.
They're not your family --
they're your responsibilities.
They're a weight
around your neck.
And deep down,
you wanted --
you were desperate
to get away from them.
And that is why
you said yes.
I said
shut your damn mouth!
Wait.
Something's wrong.
You're stalling.
Am I?
Monsters! We're barely
ahead of them.
Where's Sam?
We need --
Never heard about them.
What's going on?
They're trying to
help Dean.
Tiger, lock down
the front door.
The rest of you guys,
get ready
if they make it through.
- Yes.
You ready?
Okay.
He's buying time
so his monsters can get to us
and rescue him.
You think I need them
to save me?
Please.
Fine. You're so tough,
why don't you snap your fingers
and nuke us all?
Is that what you want?
Yeah, I do.
He can't.
Because, in here, we're all
just mental projections,
so in here,
we're all the same.
So, in here,
you're all talk.
You think I need
my powers?
I destroy worlds,
and I'd crush you
with my bare hands.
Prove it.
- Is that...?
- It's them.
Okay, they can't.
They won't be able
to get through the door.
- They won't have to.
-Tiger?
Tiger shouldn't have gone
in the woods alone.
You should've locked the door.
Whoa! Ow!
No!
You fellas didn't think
this out, did you?
Even if you could
force me out,
what do you think
I'd leave behind, hm?
You'd be nothing
but blood and bone.
Then we don't
kick him out.
We keep him in.
Aah!
It'll hold.
My mind, my rules.
I got him.
I'm the Cage.
We'll get the rest
of this cleaned up.
Yeah.
What about the rest
of Michael's monsters?
We're getting in reports.
After you guys woke up,
they all just went
their separate ways.
I guess Michael
can't control them now.
Huh.
Maggie...
Thank you.
For everything.
It wasn't me.
Jack, he...
I didn't know he could
still do that angel stuff.
Yeah. Yeah.
I didn't, either.
That magic
burns off your soul.
It was an accident.
Yeah, but you can't afford
that kind of accident.
You need your soul
to stay alive, to --
They would've killed you.
I know.
Look, I'm not mad at you.
I...
I've just seen firsthand what
the absence of a soul does.
And it's not just about
you staying alive, Jack.
It's about you staying you.
You understand?
It won't happen again.
Okay.
It's just you.
It's just...you.
Let me out! Come on!
It's all you.
Dean.
So...not all good news.
I did say
I'd see you again soon.
You could've knocked.
Figured all that banging on the
door in your head was enough.
Michael's all locked up.
Seems that way.
Sam said that
one of your reapers
really came through
with the assist.
I'm thinking
that was probably you.
Don't tell anyone.
You broke the rules.
I took a calculated risk.
I warned you
about the dangers of jumping
from world to world.
But you ignored me,
didn't you?
Rescuing Mom and Jack,
helping out
those other folks --
I'd say it was worth it.
And just look at you now.
Do you remember visiting
my reading room?
The shelves and shelves
of notebooks
describing the ways
you might die?
Yeah.
Upbeat classics.
Well, it's
the funniest thing,
but they've all
been rewritten.
They all end
the same way now --
with the archangel Michael
escaping your mind
and using you as his vessel
to burn down this world.
All of them?
All of them.
Except one.
What am I supposed to do
with this?
That's up to you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man