Who are you?
We're the guys that
save that world.
- What are you doing?
- What I have to.
He's brain dead.
Machines keeping him
breathing.
It's like you said, Dean.
Whatever it takes.
Huh?
Nick said when he left
he was just gonna go home.
I-I didn't know
he was...
Killing people?
My whole family
was slaughtered.
The best thing
I could hope for
is that I catch the monster
who did it.
There's this guy.
He said his name
was "Abraxas."
No way.
Nick?
Aah!
You couldn't fix me 'cause
I don't want to be fixed.
I can feel him
in my head.
Michael gets out,
that's it for this world.
Billie said that there's only
one way that this ends right.
A Ma'lak box.
Secured and warded.
Once inside...nothing gets out,
not even an archangel.
Plan is to charter a boat
to take me out to the Pacific.
Splash.
You and Michael,
trapped together --
for eternity?
It's the only sane play
I've got.
No. No!
Sam!
No, no, no, no!
What?
Sam?
Sammy?
Sammy!
? Supernatural 14x12 ?
Prophet and Loss
Original Air Date on January 31, 2019
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh, hey.
Didn't mean to wake you.
Sorry.
No, it's just a...
bad dream.
Sammy?
It's fine.
You want
to talk about it?
No, I'm --
No, I'm okay.
What are you doing?
Why don't you get some sleep?
You know, Dean,
you don't
have to act like
what you're planning to do
is just business as usual.
I-I know you're scared.
Never said
I wasn't scared.
- But it doesn't matter.
-Doesn't matter?
Dean, we know we could die,
uh, doing what we do.
It's always a possibility.
But what you're talking about
is far worse
than death.
Michael's an archangel.
He could
literally keep you
buried in a coffin,
alive, forever.
Okay.
I get it.
But what's
the other option, huh?
Michael gets outta my head
and ends the world?
'Cause it's all right there
in Billie's book.
Yeah, but that's only
if don't find another way
to take Michael off the board,
and there has to be another way.
And what
is that other way?
Exactly.
Aah!
Help, please! Please!
No!
Please! No!
Okay, sunshine.
Soup's on.
And bad
as the food is here?
Gourmet compared to what
you'll be gettin' in jail,
so...enjoy.
When am I
getting out of here?
I'm not sure.
At least four jurisdictions
want to prosecute.
You were a busy bee.
Yeah, what went down...
none of that
was my fault.
Right.
'Cause you were "possessed."
By "Satan."
And that's real.
That's a real thing,
okay?
And he left me, but...
...it changed me.
Listen,
you piece of crap.
You want to say the Devil
made you do it,
well,
you stick with that.
'Cause either way,
you're gonna be locked up
for the rest
of your life.
You're done.
You're buried.
Hey.
Man, I-I just want
to make sure that
you're still with me
on this thing.
You're gonna see it
through to the end.
Well, I gave you my word,
didn't I?
Okay, all right.
Just, you know,
after what you said last night,
I-I-I don't need you and Mom
coming up with
some way to stop me.
You know,
Mom hates this.
I hate this.
I know.
And Cass and Jack,
you haven't even told them.
Okay, well, yeah,
that's because I'm not good
with the whole big goodbyes,
all right?
I-I-I don't need
to get shaky on this thing.
Wouldn't be
the worst thing.
You know what
Michael wants to do,
you know that
this will stop it,
and you know that
there's no other way.
So just put the end of this trip
out of your head, okay?
Sam.
Cass.
Were you able
to talk him out of it?
No. So I'm counting
on you.
Um, any luck?
I-I did as you asked.
I've -- I've looked for
any possible way
to forcibly extract Michael
and destroy him.
- But so far, nothing.
- And what about Rowena?
She went through the entire
Book of the Damned
and found nothing.
And I told her to do it again,
see if she missed
something, and, uh...
well, the woman has a remarkable
command of profanity.
All right, thanks.
Uh, keep going.
Sam. Maybe if
I spoke with Dean...
It wouldn't matter.
Believe me,
I-I've never seen him
like this.
He won't listen to me.
H-He just --
No.
If we don't
find some way...
...Dean's gone.
"For I will
strike down the firstborn
in the land of Egypt..."
What are you doing?
"And against
all the gods of Egypt
I will execute judgment."
You don't have to do this.
No. Please, no!
"I am the Lord."
You ever think about
when we were kids?
Maybe. Yeah, sure.
Sometimes. W-Why?
I know I wasn't always
the greatest brother to you.
Dean,
you were the one
who was always
there for me.
The only one.
I mean, you practically
raised me.
I know things
got dicey...
you know, with Dad...
the way he was.
And I just...
I didn't always look out for you
the way that I should've.
I mean, I had
my own stuff, you know.
In order
to keep the peace,
probably looked like
I took his side quite a bit.
Sometimes, when I was...
when I was away,
you know it wasn't
'cause I just ran out, right?
Dad would...
He would send me away
when I really pissed him off.
I think
you knew that.
Man, I left that behind
a long time ago.
I had to.
And if we're gonna
get through this,
I-I have to do
like you said and...
try and keep my mind off
of where we're going.
So if we could not
have conversations
that sound like...
deathbed apologies,
I would
really appreciate it.
Right, yeah.
Answer me.
You owe me that.
I think God's
pretty done with you.
Why would you even
bother praying to him?
I wouldn't.
Could you do me a solid?
I have to use the can.
Oh, come on.
Seriously?
Come on, man,
give me a little bit of --
a little dignity.
I got, uh -- I got, uh, cuffs.
I got a bum leg.
What the heck am I gonna do?
Thank you.
You know the drill.
Hands behind your back.
Yeah.
Listen, I, uh -- I'm pretty sure
I found us a case.
A case?
Yeah.
You know this trip
isn't about finding a case.
I know, I know,
but -- but it's on the way --
uh, Fort Dodge, Iowa.
And if we can help,
then shouldn't we?
It's on the way.
Maybe.
Yeah. "One last case
for the Winchester boys."
Don't --
You had to go there.
Okay, j-just...
There have been
at least two murders.
Uh, one was just tonight,
and the police reports say,
a couple days ago,
a woman drowned in, uh,
bloody,
red saltwater.
Like seawater?
Yeah, except there's
no sea around here.
And then, tonight,
a guy had his throat slit.
Both bodies
were dumped in alleys.
The murders happened
somewhere else.
And both vics had
graffiti carved in them.
- "Graffiti"?
- That's what the cops said.
But, uh...
it wasn't "graffiti."
- Enochian.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Uh, sir, FBI.
We're here to talk to you
about your brother, Alan.
Oh. Well, definitely
brothers.
Uh, Alan was my twin.
I'm Eddie.
I can't believe
he's gone.
We were close.
Best friends.
Alan always said
he was my "big brother,"
'cause he was born first.
By, like, four minutes.
Losing him is like
losing a part of myself.
I never knew
it could be this bad.
Cops said your brother
was connected to, uh,
another victim.
Yeah, I-I know. Uh...
They both had that
graffiti carved in them.
What kind of
monster does that?
A-Actually,
it wasn't, um...
It wasn't graffiti.
It was, uh...
It was
an ancient language.
It meant, um,
"I am the Word."
What?
Was your brother
a very religious man?
No. Not really.
Did he know
anyone who was?
Well, I mean, most of
the people we know, uh,
they're
Church on Easter types...
except --
- Except what?
There's this guy,
Tony Alvarez.
Him and Alan
were friends.
He was always quoting stuff
that sounded like
it came from the Bible.
Can I see
that paper again?
Of course.
This is Tony...
before he got too weird.
There, on his arm.
It's Enochian.
It means "the Word."
A killer who reads
and writes Enochian?
M-Maybe some kind of
screwed-up angel?
I suppose Tony could have said
"yes" and gotten possessed,
but there aren't that many
angels around anymore.
Well, no, angels aren't the only
ones who know Enochian.
Dean! It's so good to hear from you.
Okay. Well. Good.
Uh
listen, Cass.
Uh, Sam and I are
working this case.
You're working a case?
That is so good to hear.
So I assume that means you're
not going through with it,
because I have to say, Dean,
this plan of yours,
it was born of -- of
desperation, not reason.
My "plan"?
I-I know that
I'm not supposed
to know
what I know, but...
Look, I'm fine
with my plan, okay?
We can talk
about my plan later.
Dean.
You are making
a terrible mistake.
Does the name "Tony Alvarez"
mean anything to you?
- Y-Yes.
- Say more.
Antonio Alvarez is --
is next in line to be prophet
when Donatello dies.
- Okay. Thanks, Cass.
- Wait, Dean, Dean.
We need to have
a conversation.
Look, I really got to handle
this right now, okay?
So thank you, and, uh...
it's good
to hear your voice.
Dean?
- Really?
- Dean, it's Cass.
I had to tell him.
Well, it turns out
that Alan's friend Tony
is a killer prophet.
How's that
even possible?
I guess anyone
can be a prophet, right?
Not like there's a-a background
check or anything.
Yeah, but before one
reveals itself,
the previous one
has to die.
So does that mean
Donatello's dead?
Dr. Rashad?
Hi. It's Dean Winchester.
Yes, yeah. We --
W-We've spoken before.
Uh, I'm Donatello Redfield's
nephew.
Yeah, how is --
how is Donatello?
He's, um...
He's still
alive, right?
Uh-huh.
Well, Uncle Donny's
a fighter.
You keep
me posted, okay?
He's still with us.
So, wait a second.
I-If Donatello is still
technically online,
then -- then why is
Tony Alvarez off the bench?
Let's ask him.
Tony Alvarez?
Wow.
Enochian 101.
Looks like a whole semester
of Prophet-speak.
Wow.
Hey, check this out.
Are these
future vics?
I don't know.
But these
look familiar.
Hmm.
Well,
he likes souvenirs.
Explains how our lady Vic
drowned.
Look at this.
It's all "word of God"
and
"divine retribution."
I-I mean, slaughter
of firstborn sons,
the -- the drowning of Egyptians
in the Red Sea...
Wait, wait, wait. So, Alan was
the oldest of the twin, right?
- Yeah.
- So firstborn.
- Of course.
- And then she died
in salty, bloody water.
The "red sea."
So then,
what's next up?
Hey, Dean.
"And there went out fire from
the Lord and devoured them."
Hey, Sam.
Check this out.
Hey. Y-You don't
have to do this.
You don't have
to do it.
Whatever you what,
I'll give you anything.
No!
Let me go, please!
"And the son of Aaron offered
strange fire to the Lord..."
I'll do anything you want!
- "...which he commanded them not."
- No!
"There went out fire from
the Lord and devoured him
and he died
before the Lord."
What are you doing?
Come back!
Please, come on!
Whatever you want,
I-I'll give you anything!
Please!
The pain
becomes salvation.
What are you doing?
No, no, no!
No!
Go on. Get out of here.
Go. Now.
Sam? Sam!
Tony Alvarez, right?
And who are you?
You can't --
You can't do this.
I'm doing God's work.
I'm carrying out his orders.
You think
God spoke to you?
I-I've been chosen.
I hear his voice in my head.
Yeah?
What's he saying now?
Nothing.
Yeah. 'Cause whatever
you heard,
it wasn't God.
Those people you killed
were innocent.
Please!
You're not chosen,
pal.
You're just a psycho.
No.
So, what if he is hearing
something, right?
I mean, what if, uh --
what if he's picking up
some sort of vibe
from Donatello, you know?
No, no...
- Donatello's out cold.
-No...
Yeah, so we think --
he's out cold.
No!
No, no, no.
Ohh!
He's got my gun!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
No, no, no. Wait.
Stop. Hey, stop.
Stop, stop, stop.
- No, no, no!
- Wait --
So, then, this might
not end with Tony Alvarez.
Because the next prophet's
gonna show up somewhere,
a-and -- and the crazy
could start all over again.
By the way, Cass...
I thought there could only be
one prophet at a time.
Yeah, there should,
but Donatello is between
life and death.
I mean, you know,
perhaps the next prophet
was activated
before his time?
- And went all Hannibal?
- The natural order's been upset.
Perhaps Donatello's state
has created a prophet
who's not only premature...
but malformed.
Okay. But if Tony was wired
wrong because of Donatello,
then the next prophet
will be wired wrong, as well,
and then the next and the next
and the -- the next and...
How do we end this?
You know how.
Nick?
Is that you?
Yes, Nick.
Lucifer?
Sarah.
Your wife.
Sarah?
As in the ghost
of Sarah?
- Yes.
- I don't understand.
What -- What are you
doing here?
I never left.
I'm held here
by unfinished business.
Oh, my God.
My unsolved murder,
and Teddy's.
Sarah, I...
I've missed you.
I never thought
I'd see you again.
I'm so sorry.
No, Nick.
You're not.
But I found who killed you,
Sarah.
A cop --
Frank Kellogg.
I mean, not a cop --
a demon.
It's not Frank --
it's, uh, Abraxas.
Uh, it's confusing,
but I found him.
I killed him.
It. Whatever.
I got you justice, Sarah.
You're free.
You could leave.
And what about
Lucifer?
What about him?
He's dead.
My unfinished
business
isn't just about
how I died, Nick.
It's you.
I was here that night.
I saw what
he did to you. I...
You chose Lucifer.
You wanted him.
You...
You still do.
He chose me, okay?
You didn't come here
to find peace.
You came here
to find him
in the place where you
became one with him.
No.
Then show me I'm wrong.
Reject Lucifer
right now.
If you do,
I can leave.
I can find peace.
Reject him, Nick.
Please.
Please!
I-I can't.
I'm sorry.
You can't.
Because you are him.
You doomed me
to stay in this place forever.
You've doomed yourself.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Where are you
going?
Wherever it's darkest.
Wherever he is.
Nick!
Dr. - You're making the right choice.
Your uncle's in a persistent
vegetative state,
being kept alive by machinery
and nothing else.
Sometimes letting go
is the right choice.
Tell me about it.
Just coincidental, you all
being here at the same time.
Dr. Novak,
meet, uh --
Yes, I know.
I know these gentlemen.
Mr. Winchester
and the other Mr. Winchester.
- Doctor.
So, Dr. Rashad,
you were saying
there's been no improvement
with our uncle?
That's right. There's no real
brain activity to speak of.
Um, nothing beyond
the occasional muscle spasm
or, uh,
babble of words.
Strictly reflexive.
W-What kind of
babbled word?
Follow me.
So, "Doctor," checking in
on old Uncle Donny, huh?
Hey, Dean.
What happened to him --
that was my fault.
It was necessary.
But doesn't mean
I don't regret it.
It doesn't mean that
I don't wish that
there could've been
another way.
I know the feeling.
Oh, no.
No, please
don't compare this
with your
suicidal plan.
- Just stop.
-Okay. All right.
Why don't we
talk about that later?
Because,
according to your plan,
there won't be a later.
Cass...if you were
a friend of mine,
then you will understand
that I have to do this
and you won't
try to stop me.
You think
this is easy on me?
It has to be done.
So, then,
this is goodbye?
Guys.
Check this out.
Okay, so, a couple days ago,
Donatello started making
some, uh,
random noises.
Uh, Dr. Rashad thought
he might be coming out of it,
so he shot this video.
Boh ray,
kah lah teh nee hoh.
Rah may lah ray kee doh.
That's Enochian.
He's saying,
"I will strike down
the firstborn
in the land of Egypt.
I-I will execute
judgment."
Well, that's
the same thing that
that screwed-up
new prophet was spouting.
Donatello's mind
is fighting to rebuild.
It's -- It's like he's trying
to organize his...
his memories,
the words of God.
So that's what Tony
was picking up on.
Well, then,
I-I can fix him.
Wait. How?
I thought he was too far gone.
Dean,
if there's a spark --
a hope --
then I have to try.
You taught me that.
Get out.
What?
You heard him.
You said you wanted
to discontinue treatments.
And now we've changed
our minds.
Look, if there's a chance
that Donatello
could fight through this,
then we're gonna take it.
He ain't leaving the party
if the music's still playing.
Clear?
You all right?
If Cass isn't right
about Donatello,
then where does
that leave him?
Trapped.
Trapped
in his own body
somewhere between
life and death.
It's just tough to think about
somebody going through that.
Then don't.
Thinking --
highly overrated.
Easy for you
to say.
No, it's not,
actually.
Whatever's gonna happen with
Donatello, we'll know soon.
Right.
And then what?
Nothing's changed, Sam.
Hey.
Anything?
Something.
Something uncertain.
Well, what exactly
are you looking for?
That.
Donatello?
We should turn off
these machines.
Whoa. Wait, wait.
He could die.
There's only one way
to find out.
Hey.
Welcome back, champ.
Dean?
Get him his glasses.
Now, look at that.
It's a miracle.
Um...
Would you like
more grape Jell-O?
Well, a-actually,
I'd prefer
a bucket of extra-crispy
buffalo wings
with a side
of Tex-Mex sauce.
Okay. Take it easy, cowboy.
You just got back.
He is back,
isn't he?
I mean, this isn't some kind
of evil, weird version?
No. This is the --
the regular him.
But, um...he --
he -- he doesn't
have a soul.
Hm.
Well,
nobody's perfect.
Guys, w-what happened?
Did I work too much?
Overload on Enochian?
Hm.
Cass will
catch you up.
Jell-O?
Where's the party?
It's right here.
I mean, we're celebrating,
right?
- Okay.
- Yeah, but not too much.
Tomorrow morning,
we're, uh, back on track.
No rest for
the self-destructive.
Well, I would
call this a win.
Kind of nice.
We're going out on a high.
"Going out" being
the operative phrase.
Sorry.
"Sorry."
How sorry are you?
Sorry that you fight
to keep Donatello alive,
but when it
comes to you,
you just
throw in the towel?
Or are you sorry that,
after all these years,
our entire lives,
a-after I've looked up to you,
after I've learned from you,
I-I-I've copied you,
I followed you
to Hell and back,
are you sorry
that all of that --
it -- it --
it means nothing now?
- Who's saying that?
-You are,
when you tell me
I have to kill you.
When you're telling me
that I have to just throw away
everything we stand for,
throw away faith,
throw away family.
We're the guys
who save the world.
We don't just
check out of it!
Sam, I have
tried everything.
Everything!
I got one card left to play,
and I have to play it.
You have
one card today!
But we'll find
another tomorrow.
But if you quit on us today,
there won't be no tomorrow!
You tell me, uh, you don't know
what else to do.
I don't either, Dean.
Not yet.
But what you're doing now,
i-it's -- it's wrong!
It's quitting!
I mean, l-look
what just happened.
Donatello never
quit fighting.
So we could help him
because he gave up.
I believe
in us, Dean.
I believe in us.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Why don't you
believe in us, too?
Okay, Sam.
Let's go home.
What?
Maybe
Billie's wrong.
Maybe.
But I do
believe in us.
I believe
in all of us.
And I'll keep believing
until I can't.
Until there's absolutely
no other way.
But when
that day comes --
if that day comes...
...Sam, you have to take it
for what it is --
the end.
And you have
to promise me
that you'll do then
what you can't do now,
and that's let me go.
And put me
in that box.
You, too.
Yeah, all right.
All right.
Now, you heard me.
Let's go home.
Just don't hit me
again, okay?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man