I know what it's like
to see monsters.
Time to slice and dice.
And I know that when
they're gone...
...they never really go away.
Me and my brother?
we're the guys that stop
the monsters.
We're the guys that
scare them.
Dean!
We had a deal!
Thanks for the suit.
No!
Do you propose we wage a war
on the humans?
There are ways
to enhance your...talents.
Silver bullets aren't working!
Sammy.
When Jack's grace
was taken from him,
his being fell into chaos.
The cells
are gobbling each other up.
Jack!
Before my life is over,
I want to live it.
And when it's all over...
die.
He's gone.
Maybe we should start
thinking about next steps.
Wake and a bonfire,
Hunter style.
Michael wants the spear
because he knows
it can hurt him.
Where is it?!
You're no different
than him.
I am nothing like him.
Get in the damn car!
You're the Empty.
I'm taking him.
Take me.
Deal.
When you finally give yourself
permission to be happy,
that's when I'll come.
? Ahhh-ahhh ?
? Ahhh-ah ?
? Rocking around
the Christmas tree ?
? At the Christmas party hop ?
? Mistletoe hung
where you can see ?
? Ev'ry couple tries to stop ?
? Rocking around
the Christmas tree ?
? Let the Christmas spirit
ring ?
? Later we'll have
some pumpkin pie ?
? And we'll do some caroling ?
? You will get a sentimental
feeling when you hear ?
? Voices singing, "Let's be jolly" ?
Oh, my God, no!
? "Deck the halls with boughs of holly" ?
Please, no!
? Rocking around
the Christmas tree ?
? Have a happy holiday ?
? Everyone's dancing
merrily ?
? In the new old-fashioned way ?
That was the last
of 'em.
Didn't feed, either.
Like you said,
about tomorrow?
Keeping my "appetite up."
Michael?
Why here?
This building, this floor,
cleaning it out
and killing everyone?
I like the view.
Melanie.
These are
the latest volunteers?
Yes, sir --
the last ones.
Two wolves.
This one's a bit scrawny
and a bit familiar.
I recognize you, Garth.
We've met?
'Cause I think
I'd remember that.
Oh, I've spent some time
in Dean Winchester's head --
his, um, memories.
You were his friend.
Still am.
Makes one of us.
But I've got
a family now.
And there's a war coming --
your war.
And whether I like it or not,
for my family --
for my little girl --
I gotta be
on the winning side.
- And we're prepared otherwise?
- We are.
Tomorrow night, Kansas City
won't know what hit it.
? Supernatural 14x09 ?
The Spear
Original Air Date on December 13, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Don't tell Sam.
Jack, it's the middle
of the night.
Ah, I know. I couldn't wait
till breakfast.
Sam says this stuff
will rot your teeth, but...
- I like it.
- Jack.
If you can't sleep,
that's understandable,
given recent events.
You mean dying
and coming back to life.
Yeah, we've all
been through it.
It's something of a rite
of passage around here.
That's not --
I've been thinking
about Heaven.
My mother.
You think she's safe?
Yeah, of course.
But how could
the Empty get in?
And I thought Heaven was
supposed to be perfect.
No. It's not.
Nothing's perfect, Jack.
But I know Naomi,
and she's complicated,
but there is nothing
that she won't do
to protect the souls
that are in her charge.
Try not to worry, okay?
- Okay.
Cass.
The deal you made...
why can't
Sam and Dean know?
They can. I...
I just don't...
I don't want them to.
They don't need
that burden.
- You don't need that burden.
- Of course I do.
You did that for me.
You know, the Empty said
that it wouldn't come for me
until I had finally given myself
permission to be happy,
but with everything
we have going on, with --
with Michael
still out there,
I don't see that happening
anytime soon.
This life may be a lot of
things, but it's rarely happy.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
At least we have
Krunch Cookie Crunch.
Yeah.
We do.
Did you take the decoder ring
out of the box?
Maybe.
The secret password
is...
"Cookietacular."
Shh.
Sam, that's not all.
They want me to "make the
change," become one of them.
-When?
-I don't know. Soon, I think.
Guess that's what she meant
by "volunteer."
Well, did they say
how it works?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, we're supposed to drink
blood mixed with
Michael's grace.
Garth,
y-you can't do that.
W-We don't know what
that stuff does, you know?
Look, Sam, I knew this
was a risky one.
Besides,
I'll just pull the old
fake-swallow-
and-spit-it-out-later
cough-syrup trick.
- What?
- Used to work on my mom.
- Garth --
- Well, most of the time.
This isn't your mom, Garth.
This is an archangel.
- Hey, dude!
- Oh, got to go.
Where'd you go?
No, Garth --
Garth?
Hey, buddy.
They're ready for us.
Balls.
Garth, huh?
He'll be okay.
He's fooled Michael
this far, right?
Dean, I pulled him
out of retirement
for an
undercover mission.
If something happens to him,
it's on me.
Okay. Hey, look.
Naomi gave us
Michael's location, okay?
We got a spy
on the inside --
for a change,
we're a step ahead.
And given everything
we've pulled off lately,
I like our odds.
It's Ketch.
Mm. Valko's compound
was a breeze,
as it turned out.
Jammed the security system
from the outside,
sedated the guard dogs --
Rottweilers, naturally...
- Ketch.
- Hey. You have it?
Sam, Dean.
What, no "hellos",
"how are yous"?
- No time.
- The egg, Ketch.
And as I was
just telling Jack,
I did, in fact, manage
to expropriate the egg
from a certain Hungarian
rare-weapons collector.
Yeah, uh, uh, Arpad Valko.
W-We got the messages, but so?
Unfortunately,
once I got back to Budapest,
where I was intending
to catch the red-eye
back to the good ole
U.S. of A.,
he unleashed a swarm
of mercenaries upon me.
I was cornered,
and so I was forced to,
I'm afraid,
drop the egg like...
well, to mix a metaphor,
like a hot potato.
- Oh.
- You dropped it?
Never you mind, boys.
I put it somewhere safe.
In fact, it should be arriving
in Lebanon, Kansas,
the day after tomorrow
between, mm...
2:00 and 6:00 p.m.
You put the only weapon
we have against Michael...
in the mail?
Ah, not just any mail.
I paid extra.
Certified Priority Express.
He paid extra.
Look, I improvised.
It's not
as if I have access
to the top-shelf clandestine
courier networks I did
during my
British Men of Letters days.
And really, so,
whose fault is that, hmm?
Okay, K-Ketch, we're --
we're not mad,
- W-We appreciate the effort.
- Do we?
It's just that big Michael stuff
is going down soon.
We -- We -- We kind of
needed the egg...now.
Oh. Well, um...
Sorry, chaps.
Buddy of mine,
he "made the change."
Says he's immune
to silver now.
- Pretty cool, right?
- Mm.
The only thing that can take him
down now is the Full Ichabod.
- Khhht!
- Oh.
Says he's never felt
so great.
Called archangel grace,
the ultimate powerup --
a real Chug Jug.
Dude, "Fortnite."
Oh, yeah.
Drink up.
You have nothing to fear.
Only about one in seven
volunteers explode
when they drink it.
Russian roulette odds.
I like it.
Well, sl?inte.
All gone?
All gone.
She's been seen
taking shelter
at an abandoned recycling
facility outside Omaha.
What would you like me
to do?
You feel that, buddy?
My pulse is up a bit,
and I'm a bit sweaty.
Send a team. Kill her
and destroy the spear.
I want it off the board
before tomorrow night.
Damn. I wish we could
sneak off to the gym.
I can feel them
drawing closer...
- Yeah, bro.
- ...each and every monster I've turned...
It's different than when I went wolf.
That was, like, white, hot energy, remember?
...taking their positions
throughout the city...
...waiting for my order.
- This? It's...
Oh, boy, I take it back.
- This is strong stuff.
- And your order...
what will it be?
- Well?
- It's not far.
It's being held at a hub
facility in Joplin, Missouri.
Apparently, it would've
made it to Lebanon
if it weren't closed
for the holiday.
Well, if they're closed...
Means we can get it.
How?
We break in.
Garth.
Hey.
Hey, Sam.
Michael's sending some guys
after...someone.
They're headed to an old
recycling plant north of Omaha.
Uh, says he wants them
to get a weapon.
A spear?
That mean anything to you?
Uh, yeah. I have an idea.
But what about you?
How are you?
Were you able
to fake 'em out?
Oh, yeah. All good.
Uh, but --
But what?
There's more.
I heard Michael's plan.
The whole damn town?
It's gonna be
a bloodbath.
All of Michael's monsters
activating all at once,
attacking, turning everyone
in Kansas City?
It's his army.
And all on a night
when nobody's guard's up --
all nogged up,
waiting for Santa.
- Merry freakin' Christmas.
- Yeah, well, Garth said
Michael was gonna give
the signal at midnight,
so if we can get to him
before he does...
Then we can stop this.
And with the spear
still in play,
that can hurt Michael.
Given as much trouble as he's
gone through to find it,
it might do worse.
Could be a shot at actually
killing the son of a bitch.
And we may be able
to trap him.
I mean, Bobby's been working
on those angel cuffs.
They might be able
to hold him.
Yeah, and --
and getting the egg?
I mean,
we have Rowena's spell.
We can put Michael
back in the Cage.
It's literally a trip
to the post office.
Okay, well, getting the spear
is literally a trip
to the Carter Lake
recycling facilities.
I say we get both.
Me and Cass -- we'll go deal
with Michael's monsters
and get the spear.
You and Jack --
you do your mail run
and get the egg.
We'll meet back at Hitomi Plaza
with both weapons,
and we'll hit him
from both sides.
You seem good lately.
Happy, even.
You --
We have
a broken tape deck,
we drove this whole way
without music,
and you did not complain once.
You know, I guess
I'm just fired up.
I mean, look. We got --
We got Jack back.
When was
the last time we had
a big, no-strings-attached
win like that?
But now we have Michael.
I know.
And, Dean...
we're taking a big risk
going after the spear
like this.
I know we are.
Listen to me.
Michael conned me.
Kept me trapped and drowning
inside my own body.
Now, when you and Sam
were possessed by Lucifer,
I -- I thought
I understood,
but I didn't,
not really.
So, yeah, if we get
a chance to trap him,
I'll take that,
but I won't be truly happy
until he is dead
and I kill him.
And now I have
a chance to do that,
so, yeah, I'm good.
Let's go.
All right.
That should take care
of the security system.
May I?
Oh. Sure.
I used to be able to do this
just by touching the handle.
Who taught you
how to pick a lock?
I did.
And the Internet.
I just...wanted
to stay useful.
Nice work.
I don't think she's here.
Well, she was.
The food's still warm,
so either she took a hike
or she's hiding.
Dean, where
are Michael's forces?
We're going off their Intel,
and they had a head start.
And a shorter drive.
Do you think
they already got her?
Well, there's no signs
of a struggle.
The Dark Kaia I know?
She wouldn't have gone out
without a fight.
It's lighter
than I expected.
Yeah, it'll do the job.
"Happy Holidays."
Sam!
Jack!
- Jack!
- I wouldn't.
Hey, Sam.
Michael.
Happy holidays.
How'd you find us?
What are you gonna do,
Sam, hmm?
You're gonna kill me,
anyways.
No.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Still no answer?
No.
I --
Sam?
It's Garth.
Hey, Garth.
Hey, Dean.
Uh, I tried to call Sam, but --
No answer. Yeah.
Us, too.
Yeah. Um, listen.
Michael left a few minutes ago.
I overheard him say he was going
to back up his forces.
Oh, do you mean
the "forces"
that are supposed to
be here at Omaha?
Because they
are definitely not.
What?
Dean, I swear.
Michael said --
It's okay. Just...call us
if you hear anything, okay?
Got it.
Garth.
Let's talk.
- So, what, was this a setup?
- I don't know.
Well, what do we do? Do we --
Do we go to Hitomi Plaza?
- Do we go t-to Joplin, Missouri?
- Dean!
- Why are you here?
- Hey.
What do you want?
Cass. Cass, no.
You know what we want.
You think you can
take this from me?
You've tried before.
Look, we didn't come
to fight you for it.
I came to ask.
You should know by now
I won't give it up.
Well, then,
you should just kill me.
There are people
that I care about --
my family --
and they're in danger.
Michael,
the one who tortured me,
the one
who tortured you --
he's gonna hurt them
and kill them.
And then, worse.
Thousands will die.
And the only thing in this world
that will stop him
is the spear
in your hands.
So if you're not gonna
give it to me,
kill me.
What'll you do for me?
What do you want?
I want to go back.
- To the Bad Place?
- I call it home.
But you came to this world
for a reason.
I came here to escape a life
of running from monsters.
But here, it's no different,
not for me.
Michael's monsters
haven't stopped hunting me.
At least over there,
I understood things --
the world, my place in it.
The magic
I used to get here,
magic from my home --
it doesn't work here.
To get back, I need help.
We'll do what we can.
The boy.
The special boy.
The one that used Kaia
to open up the door?
He can do it again,
for me.
Yes, he can.
And he will, if...
How do I know
you're telling the truth?
You don't.
Just like we don't know
you're telling the truth.
But we do know that
you are hiding something.
Like Dean said,
you came here for a reason,
but if you're so desperate
to return,
you're so driven
that you would consider
giving up your spear...
well, that means you have
a new reason,
something you're not
telling us.
You have people you feel
bound to protect,
to save.
So do I.
If you don't
bring this back to me,
I will find you
and kill you.
- How will we track you down?
- You've done it before.
Do it again.
Cass, hey.
Sam?
It was Michael.
He knew where we were.
He got the drop on us
and destroyed the egg,
and, uh...
Dean, he's got Jack.
- Sam?
- Hey. It was Michael.
He knew where we were.
He got the drop on us
and destroyed the egg,
and, uh...
Dean, he's got Jack.
How did you escape?
I didn't.
He knocked me out.
I...
I don't know why
he didn't kill me.
- So, what -- is he playing us?
- I don't know.
I mean, Garth's not answering
my phone calls.
Best guess --
Jack's in Kansas City
and that it's still game time
for Michael there.
I -- I'm gonna
head there now.
Okay. Hey,
we got the spear,
so we'll meet you there.
- Great.
-And, Sam...
-Yeah?
...don't you
go in there alone.
I know.
Drive fast.
Why am I here?
Why didn't you
just kill me?
In your present,
powerless condition?
Why would I bother?
Are you familiar
with Kansas City --
the people, the terrain?
Back in my world, I enlisted
a garrison to invade it.
We leveled it.
Death from above.
But there was
human resistance.
Things got messy.
I'm trying something
different this time --
an insurgency
from within.
My monster army turning
every last
man, woman, and child --
a wave
of transformation.
Vampires or werewolves --
it won't matter which.
Everyone they turn
will be mine.
No muss, no fuss.
Why would you think I want
to hear any of this?
I hate you.
Oh, but, Jack,
we're family.
You know, in fact,
we're the only kin each other
has left in this world.
My uncle's in the Cage.
And you --
you're not family.
Well, not literally, no.
Our connection,
our relation
is more a matter
of scale...
of power.
Haven't you learned yet?
In this reality, monsters,
humans, even angels --
they are insects,
atoms compared to us.
But you --
you're just a child,
a mere infant.
For you,
the past two years --
the entirety
of your existence --
feel like eons.
You don't even know
what time is.
But you will.
Real time, the time
that makes mountains,
that wipes out species.
You'll see it all...
with me.
No.
Year by year,
century by century,
and as your power
returns and grows,
we'll only become
more alike.
Oh, I know.
Your loyalty to Castiel,
the Winchesters,
the rest of humanity?
It will fade.
And so will the minor
differences --
angel armies
versus monster armies,
this Kansas City
or that Kansas City,
one world from another --
they'll fade, too.
Sam, Dean, and Castiel.
They'll come for me.
Mm.
You have
your coordinates?
Uh, yes, sir.
The Cathedral
on Oak Street --
embed myself
in the Christmas mass,
wait for Michael's signal.
All right.
You can go now.
- Jack.
- Sam?
Hey.
Where's Michael?
Ahh. I don't know.
Come on. Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Shh, shh.
- Garth.
- Hey.
- You're okay.
- Yeah.
Great.
Let's get out of here.
All right.
Dean and Cass
are almost here.
They got the spear.
As soon as they get here,
we regroup, go upstairs...
- Kick Michael's ass.
Yep.
Garth?
Jack!
Oh, Sam. He's in my head.
He won't stop.
He won't let me stop.
- Garth.
- I'm sorry.
Hey, don't do this.
You don't
have to do this.
Garth.
You can fight this.
You can fight this one.
Ohh!
Sorry, Garth.
I'm sorry.
Sleep tight, buddy.
Well, thanks for waiting
for us.
I didn't have a choice.
He drank
Michael's grace.
Why didn't he tell me?
I don't know.
When Garth turned, I think
it gave Michael a window.
I think that's how Michael
knew where we'd be,
how he got the jump
on us.
All right, well,
Garth's on ice now.
You know, maybe if we kill
Michael, it'll cure him.
Well, I-I called
the other Hunters.
They're on their way.
Take care of the city,
in case we don't win
up there.
I wouldn't bet against us,
you know?
Hyah. Hyah.
Ah! Whoa. Ah!
I got it. It's cool.
It's good.
How we looking
over there?
Good as new.
Jack.
He's up there,
waiting for us.
You know, Michael's monsters
are all over this city.
If he feared us
in the least,
he would've sent
some our way.
Yeah, well,
he could've killed me
back at
the shipping facility.
I think he wanted us to come here.
We have to remember --
Michael will sense
my approach.
So zero element
of surprise.
Walking right into
a trap.
Which is set
by a full-power archangel.
Impossible odds.
Feels like home.
Let's do it.
? Freude,
schoener Goetterfunken ?
? Tochter aus Elysium ?
? Wir betreten feuertrunken ?
? Himmlische, dein Heiligtum! ?
Come on, fellas.
You're gonna miss the show.
Mm.
There he is.
Castiel.
You do realize
I can feel you in here.
There's really no need
to be...
...coy.
Michael.
Tell me something, Cass.
Why'd you come alone?
Advance scout?
Strongest player first?
Not that strong.
But, hey, if they want to miss
all the festivities,
well, then that's...
...their...
loss.
But I got a schedule
to keep.
You got it.
I sure did.
I'm so glad
you could make it tonight.
I know you hate me, Dean,
but don't forget --
you let me in.
And now
you get to see it --
everything your mistake
will make possible --
all the bloodshed,
all the death --
all on you.
Dean!
Trust me.
That's gonna leave a scar.
Kill him!
Dean?
No.
Yeah.
When I gave up Dean,
you didn't think to question it,
to ask why?
Dean was...
resisting me.
He was
too attached to you,
to all of you.
He wouldn't
stop squirming --
to get out, to get back.
So I left...
but not without leaving
the door open...
just a crack.
Why wait?
To break him, to crush
and disappoint him so completely
that, this time, he'll be
nice and quiet for a change --
buried.
And he is.
He's gone.
And now...
I have a whole army
out there,
waiting,
ready for my command,
ready...for this.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man