You know my brother thinks
you can be saved.
You don't believe that.
No, I don't.
And it comes to
killing you,
I'll be the one to do it.
No.
Aah!
I just need your power.
I know this must be
so hard without your grace,
but you can get past this.
You did good, kid.
I was right.
You're pretty smart
sometimes.
Jack?!
I don't understand
how Lucifer could die
and I could live...
Aaah!
...how I would let
Lucifer possess me.
You were in a lot of pain.
I'm gonna find out
who killed my family.
I thought I saw something,
but I was wrong.
I don't know anything.
I think you do.
I know I've got issues.
It's not like I want
to do this, okay?
I need to.
I know I should stop.
It's just that...
these feelings afterward...
I hate.
I hate
that it feels so good.
Anyway, I know I've taken up
too much of your time.
If you say you can't tell me
what Arty told you during
confession, I accept that.
Of course, he was the only
witness to my family's murder,
but I understand you got
your vows to keep and all that,
but...
You really shoulda helped me.
Okay?
So you brought this
on yourself.
But, look, I will take
some of your advice.
Perhaps...
Perhaps the peace
I'm looking for
does lie in the power of prayer.
And I do agree with you, Padre.
There is a Devil,
and we should try to fight him.
Sometimes we just can't.
Hang in there.
? Supernatural 14x07 ?
Unhuman Nature
Original Air Date on November 29, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
- What's taking so long?
- I don't know.
Whatever's going on with Jack
is probably complicated.
Yeah, but, I mean, weird stuff
happens to kids all the time.
They get coughs,
bloody noses.
Is he okay?
I -- I did what I could,
but I don't --
I -- I don't know what's
wrong with him.
But you can figure it out,
right?
Jack?
Hey.
Jack!
I need a doctor!
Hey.
Look, could you just
get him inside?
Sir, I just need
some basic information.
That's the procedure.
I do the work-up,
then I take him back.
Okay, the basic information
is he's sick.
Do you see anyone here
who isn't?
His full name, please.
You do know his name,
right?
Jack.
Uh, uh, Kline.
Jack Kline.
K-l-i-n-e.
Date of birth?
Come on.
Is that important?
What did you say your
relationship is to the patient?
May 18th.
Date of birth --
2000 -- '99.
2000.
Uh-huh.
Family medical history?
Let's start with the father.
He's dead.
Cause of death?
He was stabbed through
the heart, and he exploded.
Okay, you know what?
We don't have time for this.
All right, he's sick.
His name is Jack Kline.
His father exploded.
There, you've got
all the basics.
Now what does he need
to do to see a doctor?
Jack!
Jack?!
It's all right, Jack.
Hang in there, buddy.
Jack, hey, we're
right here, buddy.
He's in good hands.
Don't worry.
So, there's -- there's been...
Uh, he's been coughing. There's been blood.
Okay, gentlemen, can you at
least wait outside, please?
It's been going on for a while.
What's happened?
Is he gonna be okay?
- The doctor will handle it.
- Okay.
Jack, we're right here!
Nick?
Hello. Diane Fargo.
Hey, yeah.
Yeah, you weren't easy
to track down.
I left Pike Creek
six years ago.
I'm working at the Tribune
here in Wilmington.
Oh.
-What can I get you?
-Coffee, please.
Well,
thanks for seeing me.
I didn't think you were
gonna remember who I am.
Of course I do.
I spoke to you the morning
after your family was...
Slaughtered.
And then you left town.
Yeah, just...
I couldn't stay, you know?
Too much baggage.
I had to rebuild.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
My ex-neighbor, Arty Nielsen,
was killed a few weeks ago.
- Really?
- Yeah, so...
just brought back all kinds
of bad memories, you know,
and, uh, I was just
looking for some answers.
To...?
My family.
The case was never solved.
The one witness was Arty,
and he said that he
saw someone leaving my house
the night of the murders,
and then he changed
his story.
It happens.
People say things
in the heat of the moment,
and then realize
they're not so sure.
Even you gave up
on the story.
There was almost no evidence
at the crime scene.
Mm-hmm.
The cops had zero
to say to me.
I even played with the idea
you did it, but you...
Well, I was getting hammered
at the Elks Lodge that night.
So...I moved on.
Yeah, well, I can't.
Nick?
No, I'm good.
Seriously.
As -- As soon as I figure out
what happened that night,
these demons will disappear.
Look, you were
a crime reporter, right?
So you've got to know all
the beat cops in Pike Creek.
Sure.
Okay, do you happen to
remember who was assigned
to my neighborhood
that night?
I think so.
All right.
I'm...pretty sure
it was Frank --
Frank Kellogg.
Last I heard,
he was doing private security
up in Montauk.
Frank Kellogg, Montauk.
This is crazy.
When Jack became human,
I was worried, you know,
given what we do, that -- that
something would happen to him,
but I thought it'd be
a vampire or a ghoul,
not a friggin' cough.
He's just a kid.
Hey, hey, hey.
Cass.
Doctor.
So, um...
What do we know?
Well, I can tell you
what we don't know.
I don't like
the sound of that.
Jack's test results
all came back negative.
That's great, right?
Well, Jack --
he's very ill.
We're just not sure
what we're up against.
You just said his tests
came back negative.
Well, those tests,
but we have to run more tests.
More tests?
Yes, until we can figure out
what's happening to him.
What is happening to him
right now?
Jack...
Jack's in total
systemic failure.
His body's in the process
of shutting down.
Lemme ask you a question.
How much longer
are we gonna give this?
How many more tests
are there gonna be?
My opinion?
I think we're done here.
Yeah, that was kinda
my opinion, too.
I mean, this place,
we tried,
but they've never seen
anything like Jack,
and we can't exactly
tell them what he is.
Then let's get
him out of here.
Let's bring him home.
Let's do what we do.
Let's find a way.
Hell, I was even thinkin'
maybe Rowena...
Already called her.
Uh, what --
What's going on?
What's it look like?
You can't expect him to hit
the street with nothing on
but a hospital gown,
his ass hanging out.
He's not going anywhere.
We're just getting
a second opinion.
Jack?
We're getting a second opinion.
If he leaves the hospital,
we are no longer responsible
for him.
You and he have to acknowledge
that you're leaving
against medical advice.
- Fine.
- We're leaving.
Yeah, there's just no talkin'
to him when he gets like this.
- Thanks for coming.
- I got here quick as I could.
How is he?
Well, uh...
I brought the
Book of the Damned.
Which, uh, you stole.
Which I borrowed amidst
the ruckus
of all those folks
arriving from the other world,
but we can talk
about that later.
Just how sick is Dean?
Yeah, about that, um...
What?
Is this a trick?
Samuel, I thought
we were beyond this.
Somebody is sick,
all right, but...
Listen, I-I don't know how
well you got to know
our -- our --
our friend Jack
with everything that was
going on when you were here,
but we've sort of been
taking care of him,
and, uh, he's, um...
Lucifer's son.
Goodbye.
No, no, no. Stop, stop.
He's a great kid.
His mother was
a fantastic human being,
a-a-and he wanted nothing
to do with Lucifer,
w-who is dead,
as you know.
I hope he's rotting.
Yes, but Lucifer
stole Jack's grace,
so he's powerless now,
and -- and something's
going on with him,
and he might die.
Oh, splendid!
The sooner the better!
From what I know
of the father,
the world will be better off
without the son.
You might be right.
We're all still
figuring that out.
I'm Jack.
And I know people have
a lot of strong feelings
about my father, but I'm --
I'm trying hard
not to be like him.
Sam and Dean, they -- they say
such nice things about you.
They do?
You saved all of us --
from Apocalypse World.
Well, that's true.
So, before you go,
I -- I just wanted to say...
thank you.
Jack.
Hey, buddy. Hey.
You're all right.
Bollocks.
Possim rei huius cognoscere
causas...
How am I?
And?
It's as I suspected.
A nephilim,
for all its power,
is an unnatural presence.
Part human, part angel...
It -- It doesn't quite fit.
It's delicate.
Its grace is what
holds it in balance,
and when Jack's grace
was taken from him,
his being fell into chaos.
The -- The cells
are gobbling each other up.
Well, if it's grace he needs,
he can have mine.
No, dear, it won't do.
Jack is part archangel.
He needs
a much stronger force
and probably
some kind of magic,
and he needs it quick.
- How quick?
- I don't...
I don't exactly know, but he's
enterin' a critical phase.
Sometimes he'll look
just fine,
but then his body
will give way and...
it'll be the end of him.
Hey.
Yeah, no.
Wasn't sure which one you
thought would be the best one.
Don't do it.
Evening.
Evening yourself.
You're out here alone?
That's sort of dangerous,
isn't it?
Weird!
That sounded weird.
I just meant be safe.
Just hadda use my phone.
I'm headed back in.
Copy that.
Have fun.
Did you wanna come in?
Meet my friends...?
That sounds awesome,
but it's a nice night,
and it's so loud in there.
I know.
That's the best part.
Come on.
It'll be fun.
Get away from me.
...what?
Get away from me!
Now!
Go!
Hey, pal.
I brought you some carbs.
You, uh...
You goin' somewhere?
Thought I'd go to Vegas.
Maybe Tahiti.
Okay.
Nice.
You think this is
the best time?
Pretty sure it is.
Listen, Jack --
Since I've been alive,
everyone assumed
I would be
this special "person"
who goes on forever.
Only now it looks like
forever
might be a couple
of weeks, so --
We don't know that.
What I do know is
I'm done being special.
Before my life is over,
I want to live it.
I-I just want
a chance to...
get a tan...
to see a hockey game...
get a parking ticket...
...get bored...
and when
it's all over...
die.
So that's your plan,
huh?
I don't want to
waste time arguing.
I know you disagree.
Did I say I disagree?
...and how likely
do you think that is?
Because no Hunter I've spoken to
has heard of anything.
...I know you're not
speakin' to me, Magda,
basically no one
is speakin' to me,
but I have a situation.
There's a wee nephilim
I know who's ailing...
Dean --
the bunker's vault has a number
of Enochian texts
on archangels, but nothing
on their half-human offspring.
And I've spoken to some of the
greatest minds in witchcraft,
and they all say there's
nothing that'll help Jack.
Well, then, they're not
the greatest minds, are they?
Well, I just got off
the phone with Ketch.
Um, he's got a line
on a shaman.
A shaman?
Yeah,
the British Men of Letters
used to use him --
as a consultant.
Whenever they needed to
"solve the unsolvable" --
he was their guy.
He's an expert in mysticism --
esoteric divinity.
I mean, Ketch says
the Brits swore by him.
Ketch "says."
Yeah.
His name is "Sergei,"
I-I got a location,
and Ketch says
he'll set up a meeting.
Okay, I'll go.
You and Dean need to
stay here with, uh...
Jack, hey.
W-What are you, uh --
We're -- We're headed out.
You're, uh...
Where?
We're takin' Baby
for some exercise.
You think that's
a good idea?
Yeah.
Come on.
Hey.
Why don't you drive?
...what?
Dean, I-I don't drive.
Now you do.
Okay, um...
Ah, ah, ah.
That "R" is not for "Race."
Put it in park.
- Okay.
- Start it.
Um...
Oh, boy.
There we go.
Okay.
D for "Drive."
Okay. All right.
Okay, uh...
Keep going.
That...
Okay, look.
You know what?
- I'm not very good at this.
- No, you're doing just fine.
Okay, try using one foot,
not two,
and, uh, just relax.
Take it smooth.
Don't overthink it.
Here we go.
Okay.
- See? Huh?
- Yeah.
Perfect.
Whoa, whoa. Let's keep it
in between the lines.
There we go. That's...
Okay, okay.
All right.
? Hard life ?
? Don't cry,
would you let it ride? ?
? You can see the mornin',
but I can see the light ?
? Try, try, try, let it ride ?
What do you think?
It's like I'm you.
No, it's not.
? While you've been out runnin' ?
? I've been waitin'
half the night ?
- Okay.
- Eyes on the road.
? Try, try, try, let it ride ?
Feels good, doesn't it?
? And would you cry
if I told you that I lied? ?
Yeah.
? And would you say goodbye,
or would you let it ride? ?
Oh, ho, ho.
All right.
? And would you cry
if I told you that I lied? ?
? And would you say goodbye,
or would you let it ride? ?
This is the best day ever!
? Try, try, try,
let it ride ?
? Would you let it ride? ?
You know what? There's nobody around.
Why don't you open it up
a little bit?
? Would you let it ride? ?
Yeah.
- Yeah!
- Huh?!
If this "Sergei" has anything
even remotely useful to offer,
I'll call.
Yo, Cass, wait.
Are you sure you wanna
handle this alone?
I, uh...
I feel the need
to do something.
And I think Dean's right.
We can't afford to overlook
any possibility.
He seems to be taking this
particularly hard.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he -- he, uh,
was pretty rough on Jack
at the beginning, and...
I don't think
he's forgotten.
And I know
he hasn't forgiven himself.
You know, he's lost people,
we've all lost people,
but, um...
This feels different.
Losing, um...
a son...
feels different.
I can drive.
Yeah, you can.
No, for real.
I'm a driver.
Yeah, born with
the wheel in your hand, right?
All right, so what do
you want to do next?
I know of a bar near here,
little low on class,
but high
on hook-up potential.
Personally, I've never
missed at this place. Hm?
Actually,
I've kind of got an idea.
Hey.
Yeah?
Frank Kellogg?
Do I know you?
Um, I just wanted to talk to you
for a couple of minutes
about the night
you came over to my house.
Pal,
I been to a lot of houses.
Yeah, but this was
in Pike Creek.
When you were a cop.
Nine years ago.
I don't remember you.
No, I wasn't there.
Um...
My wife and my son
were there.
Alone.
Until you showed up.
So let's talk.
Well, bait and beer.
You are a cheap date.
This certainly isn't Tahiti.
You once told me you and your
father did the exact same thing.
It was your happiest memory
of him.
I didn't say that.
It was how you said it.
I could tell.
I guess my point is that...
if I don't make it...
The stuff I'd miss -- it
wouldn't be things like Tahiti.
Or the Taj Mahal.
I'd miss more time
with you.
I'm getting that life isn't all
these big, amazing moments.
It's time together
that matters.
Like this.
Well, who'd have thought
hanging out with me
would make you
sentimental?
I've had a good life,
Dean.
Sergei?
Sergei?!
The angel Castiel?
And who else?
Do you see anyone else?
Is the Holy Fire
really necessary?
Self-preservation makes
many things necessary.
Please, sit.
As for
my curriculum vitae,
I'm passionately
peripatetic.
No roots.
I've re-crossed the globe
many, many times over.
Studying and observing
the skills of myriad witches,
and seers, holy men,
et cetera.
And what is it
exactly you do?
Answer
the unanswerable.
No.
Know the unknowable.
And I am first and foremost
a healer.
And you know Ketch?
We've never met
face-to-face,
but -- our reputations
are mutually stellar.
I wouldn't call Ketch
"stellar."
Then you have met him.
But -- back to this nephilim
you've been fostering...
Jack.
His name is Jack.
Well, "Jack" is in
a pretty pickle.
If what you're telling me is
right, his condition is dire.
Do you think
it's reversible?
Not as such, but...
it can be shocked out
of its progression
by a recharging agent.
Think of it like you're,
uh, rebooting a computer.
And where would one find
such a thing?
First and foremost,
a healer.
And...
Archangel grace?
Vintage. From Gabriel.
In trade for my home-brewed
cloaking spell.
He used it to hide away
in Monte Carlo.
With porn stars,
yes, I know the story.
But this alone
won't do the trick.
It must be administered
along with the precise
recitation of a spell.
And what is all this
going to cost?
Don't insult me.
I never take money.
My skills are exclusively
for barter.
Then what is it
that you want?
I don't know.
But...
tell the Winchesters
they owe me.
Well, Frank, how long
you gonna hold out, man?
Nick...
I don't even know what
you're talking about.
Really?
Okay, um, well,
let me just lay the scenario
out for you one more time.
My ex-neighbor, Arty,
said he saw someone
coming out of my house
the night of the murder,
right?
And then he changed his mind.
I didn't --
I didn't buy it...
...but, uh, he stuck
to story number two
till I came along.
Paid him a visit.
I was very,
very persuasive.
You saw somebody leave
my house, didn't you?
Didn't you?!
It was a cop.
So, Arty said when he
told the cops what he saw,
they threatened him.
They said, "Keep
your mouth shut or else."
It was like those, uh --
what do you call it --
cover up...
like they were protecting
one of their own.
What does any of this
have to do with me?
Glad you asked, buddy.
I got in contact
with the reporter,
and she gave me the name
of the beat cop
in our neighborhood,
yeah,
a guy she couldn't interview
'cause he left town
after the murders.
See where I'm going
with this?
I -- Look, I don't know
what happened that night,
I -- I --
Y-Your wife
called the precinct.
Thought she heard
a prowler.
And...?
I'm walking up
the front path,
no back-up,
and suddenly from outta nowhere,
there's this guy.
There's this "guy."
He said his name
was "Abraxas."
Abraxas.
The next thing I know,
I'm back in the patrol car,
and I'm --
I'm covered in blood.
My wife's blood.
And my baby's blood.
"Abraxas."
I know that name.
Lucifer knew that name.
Now, this -- this is crazy.
I was outta my head
that night!
I -- I wouldn't
kill anyone.
I know.
You were possessed.
What?
Yeah, this -- this --
all this, it's not your fault.
But this was the hand
that murdered my family.
And even if it
wasn't you --
it was still you.
I can't let that slide.
No.
No, please.
Please. No.
No.
Yeah.
Please.
I'm sorry, Frank.
No.
No!
This Sergei was legit.
I mean, he was definitely odd,
but he seemed honest.
So, we're still not certain
this is gonna work?
No, we're not certain,
but...
Gentlemen?
Are you ready, Jack?
Yes.
All right. Here you go.
Potione hac,
restitutus Eris.
Omnia erunt sicut erant!
Something.
Something good?
I think so.
Definite improvement.
- That's great.
- Mm.
Yeah.
Jack?
Did you say
the words right?
I did!
- Jack.
- Jack!
Say them again!
Of course we followed
the instructions,
and Rowena performed the spell
exactly as written,
but he is worse.
He's much worse.
You need to come at once.
I am a shaman. I realign
the harmonics of the universe.
I don't make house calls.
Jack isn't just
another sick kid.
This is the son of an archangel
of the Lord,
who is much more ill now
because of your "harmonics."
And?
Science is sometimes
trial and error.
Victory through
experimentation.
This was an experiment?
You never said that.
If Jack dies,
I will find you.
You can try.
All right...
I'm not very good
at this,
but the priest said
it would help, so, um...
I'm gonna try.
I say that I do
the terrible things I do
because I couldn't find
who killed Sarah and Teddy.
And that once I did,
I'd be free of this darkness
and this rage...
...but I lied.
Truth is...
...I like
doing these things,
and I don't want to stop.
I'm bonded to you
and what you are.
I mean, it's -- it's --
It's how you
first found me.
I don't know who I am
if I'm not you.
No consequences.
No pain. No sorrow.
I want that back.
I want it back.
I don't want to feel now
what I didn't feel then.
Where are you?
Help me.
I shouldn't have done it.
I shouldn't have taken him out.
It was what he wanted.
I mean, we knew he was gonna
get worse, regardless.
Yeah, but it was too risky.
Yeah, but, Dean, life,
all of it, is a risk.
Jack knew that.
Possim rei huius
cognoscere causas...
- And you made him happy.
- Mm.
You did more for him
than any of us.
So, what can we do?
Watch over him.
Stay by his side...
as he dies.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man