Then it's all true.
God, the Devil.
Now you live in a secret bunker
with an angel and Lucifer's kid.
Dad, none of this would have
happened without you.
Aah!
This isn't just Michael
we're talking about.
It's Dean.
I can feel him in my head.
Michael gets out,
that's it for this world.
Billie said that there's only
one way that this ends right.
- A Ma'lak box.
- You and Michael,
trapped... for eternity?
Okay, Sam. Let's go home.
Dad?
I don't think Jack is well, Dean.
Jack?
We found a way to bring you home.
We need to use magic
that will draw on your soul.
I am a Winchester!
You want to know how much of my soul
I had to burn off
to kill Michael.
Yes.
Nick. He's trying
to resurrect Lucifer.
I'm here.
No!
I'm trying to understand
Jack without a soul.
- Listen to me!
- Leave me alone!
I wish I could forget
about him! After what he did?
This is our only play.
Jack.
You lied to me.
You lied!
- No!
I don't understand.
The Ma'lak box can hold
an archangel.
Jack's not an archangel.
Yeah, apparently,
the kid leveled up.
So, what do we do?
We find him.
How?
I don't know, Cass.
You tell me.
Okay, the last time
we found Jack, it wa...
It was by praying to him, but
that's not gonna happen again.
Yeah, you think?
You should never have tried
to lock him away.
You know what?
You're right.
I never wanted to put him
in that damn box.
I wanted him dead.
Dean.
He's dangerous, Cass,
and you knew it!
You've known it for a long time!
But that's okay.
You know why?
Because me and Sam, we've killed
just about everything there is.
And this... Jack...
Oh, we'll find a way.
Because he's just
another monster.
You don't mean that.
The hell I don't.
All right. So, I guess
we got to find Jack.
Yeah. Then what?
I don't know.
Maybe we call Rowena,
see if she can put together
one of those, um,
"soul bombs."
The... thing you were gonna use
against the Darkness?
Yeah, might actually
put a dent in the kid.
Okay.
Sam, I know this isn't easy,
okay?
He... I know how much
he meant to you.
He meant a lot to me.
He was family.
But this?
This is not Jack anymore.
He's hurting,
he's killing people.
This isn't gonna be easy,
but we're gonna have to do
the hard thing.
We're gonna have to do
the ugly thing.
Ain't like it's the first time,
though, right?
No, honey, it's not like that.
She's just a friend from work.
You should've seen it.
I caught a steelhead this big.
I mean it.
We went up to the cabin...
Oh, my God.
She's such a bitch.
Baby, it's not you.
It's me.
No, I don't think he
took offense. You're awesome.
Just because Mommy and Daddy
aren't gonna be together,
we still love you.
I saw 'em
at Coachella last year!
- Nothing's gonna change.
- Greatest company to work for.
You won't be disappointed. Man
#6: I don't have any problem with those.
- You're my best friend.
- Your, um... profile said 6'1".
I am. Basically.
- You're finally getting a break.
- It's good to see you.
- Come on, baby.
- Why does everyone...
That's not porn.
I-I don't know what that was.
Stop lying!
Yeah, I know
it's a long shot, Rowena,
but just try, okay?
I mean, try.
She in?
She thinks
it's dangerous and insane.
But, yeah, she's in.
Well, she knows
what Jack's capable of.
Excuse me.
Coming through.
Nerds.
Takes one to know one.
What?
You. Come on, man.
You're always calling me a geek,
but you know every word
to every Led Zeppelin song...
Backwards and forwards...
You can discuss in detail
every major rock drummer
between '67 and '84,
and... you watch "Jeopardy!"
every night.
Okay.
All right, yeah.
But I'm nothing like these, uh,
you know, gaggle of Zuckerbergs.
Th-They're not...
Mirror Universe builds
facial-recognition software.
They've got contracts
with... with basically
every law-enforcement agency
on the planet. Okay. So?
So w-we need to track Jack,
but he flies,
so if we can't go ahead and
track his license plate,
maybe we can track his...
His face.
His face, exactly.
Okay.
Oh, I got this.
Can I help you?
Hi. I'm Dean Winchester, and
I'm looking for the devil's son.
- What?
Uh...
I meant I'm Dean Winchester,
and I'm looking
for the devil's son.
This badge is fake.
Excuse me.
Hey. I'm sleeping with
your wife.
- I know. Kind of into it.
- What?
Hey, let me ask you a question.
Tell me who
your favorite singer is.
What?
You...
Look, I know you say it's Elvis,
but we both know that's crap,
so tell me who
your favorite singer is.
Well, it's like you said.
It's Celine Dion.
Uh...
I mean Celine Dion.
It's Celi...
Dean, every time I try
and say "Elvis,"
it comes out...
The sad, horrible truth.
Yeah. You know why?
Because we can't lie.
All right!
Who ate my yogurt?!
Right here!
I knew it was you!
- That was the third... Son of a bitch!
- No!
Guess we're not the only ones.
Double?! You make double?
And that was my parking space!
I hate everyone!
I can't believe you taped it!
I thought it was hot!
Let's go.
In what was supposed to
be a speech on farming subsidies,
the President instead
spent more than two hours
disclosing his entire
tax history,
deep ties to Russia
and North Korea,
and a quote "demon deal"
he made
with someone named Crowley.
Dude. What the hell?
Over to you, Jack.
Did we just walk into a case?
Jack?
I love you.
I've always loved you.
Pundits on both sides
of the aisle...
Okay, Dean.
I think whatever
is happening here,
I-it's not just happening here.
Yeah, no, it's... it's
everywhere, but what...
Jack.
Son of a bitch.
- We have to find him.
- I hate everyone!
Like right now.
- I hate this!
- I am the stapler queen.
I am the stapler queen.
I am the stapler queen!
I need to go to hell.
You mean, like,
metaphorically or...
No. Literally.
And I understand
you can take me.
Really?
'Cause from what I remember,
you've been to hell...
More than once.
Well, this... it's different.
I need time to see the Cage
and study it.
Yeah, that's a no.
So you can go to hell...
Metaphorically.
No, don't.
Wow. Yeah.
You guys are screwed.
Hello.
Oh, hi.
I'm Jack.
I remember.
Well, good.
God.
Eh...
Chuck.
There you go.
Is it really...
How are You here?
You called me?
God...
I don't know where you are.
I don't know if you can hear me.
But please.
Sam, Dean... we need you.
My prayer?
That's why you're here.
Yeah.
Well, that and... him.
Jack.
He's a problem.
I don't mean to bother you,
but we talked before,
and I liked that talk,
and I thought we could just
maybe talk again...
maybe about your daughter.
No.
I don't understand.
You lied to us.
You said you worked with Kelly,
but after you left,
my husband and I,
we made some calls,
and no one knows who you are.
I...
I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Kelly's not away
on some "secret mission."
She...
They think she's dead.
What did you do to my daughter?!
What did you do?!
Stop!
When people can't lie,
the Internet gets real quiet.
Hmm.
Yeah, guess your life
isn't so perfect after all,
EightPackMommy.
- What?
- Yeah, she's got this blog.
Yeah, you know what?
Your kids aren't that cute.
And that gluten-free popover
looks like crap
because there's no gluten in it.
You know what I mean?
I'll stop talking.
Probably a good plan.
You're losing your mind
over one yogurt!
It was three yogurts!
I hate everyone!
- I just want to be loved.
- I hate everyone!
I hate everyone!
I just want a sweet life.
You see, this is why people need to lie.
I hate everyone!
It's good.
Keeps the peace, you know?
I hate everyone!
Seems like an odd stance for...
you. I hate everyone!
Is it?
I'm a writer.
Lying's kind of what we do.
- I just want to be loved!
- I hate everyone!
Sam!
I hate everyone!
Dean!
I hate every...
Cass?
Cass.
How'd you get here?
He brought me.
Hey, guys.
I know what you're thinking...
It's been awhile,
and I still look pretty good.
No, that's... that's not
what we were thinking.
Where the hell have you been?
Well, you know,
it's a funny story.
It reminds me of a song.
Answer the damn question!
Don't!
It's a little cramped in here,
don't you think?
There. That's better.
So... how's things?
Okay, look. I get it.
All right, I'm from
the deus from the machina,
and you have questions.
So, great. Go.
Yeah, like Dean said,
where have you been?
It's hard to explain.
Um... everywhere and nowhere,
to the edge of the universe
and beyond.
And I saw Springsteen
on Broadway. Man's a genius.
What about Amara?
She's been with me.
Yeah, it's been nice
reconnecting after the whole
"trying to murder me
and end all existence" thing.
- Where is she now?
- Reno.
Turns out she loves kino.
And you're here because...
Because of Jack.
Listen, you guys know me.
I'm hands-off.
I built the sandbox...
You play in it.
You want to fight Leviathans?
Cool. You got that.
You want to go up against...
What was it?
The "British Men of Letters"?
Okay.
Little weak, but okay.
But when things get really bad,
like the Apocalypse
or the Other Apocalypse,
that's when I have to step in.
So You're saying Jack
is Apocalyptic?
The kid said, "Stop lying,"
and I don't know if you noticed,
but the world kinda went insane.
...rioting in the streets
as the Dow drops
nearly 15,000 points.
And it's been confirmed...
The Queen of England is,
in fact, a lizard.
Inside...
See?
Can you fix it?
Fine.
Fixed.
- Really?
- I'm God, Sam.
Yeah, really.
Go ahead. Try it out.
Celine Dion rocks.
Yeah.
Yeah, we can lie again.
And the rioting?
Like it never happened.
Hey!
Who ate my yogurt?!
Dicks.
You're welcome.
Look, the point is
the kid did all that
with two words.
What's next? He sneezes and...
Whoops... there goes India?
I don't know. Maybe.
But this is bad...
Like Me Level Bad.
Can you stop him?
Not exactly.
But you can.
With that.
What is that?
I'm thinking of calling it...
the Equalizer!
Or...
the Hammurabi.
No?
All right, cool.
That's cool. Cool.
Wait, y-you're saying that
this thing could kill Jack?
That?
That'll kill anything.
So you've had this
the whole time and...
And we're just now getting it?
- Why?
- Because I haven't?
- Y...
- I just made that sucker.
Hasn't been fired yet.
So you don't even know
if it works.
If I say it'll work, it'll work.
There's no bullets.
Right, it doesn't exactly
use bullets.
See, existence is
all about balance, right?
Dark and light, good and evil,
chocolate and peanut butter.
Ugh, yeah, okay, Chuck.
- The point, please?
- Right.
So, this doesn't so much
fire bullets as it sends
a wave of multi-dimensional
energy
across a perfectly balanced
quantum link
between whoever's shooting it
and whoever they're shooting at.
What?
Uh, whatever happens to
the person you're aiming at
also happens to you.
So you kill him...
You die.
Right. Yeah.
Look, I know it's not perfect,
and I'd do it myself,
but, you know, if I bite it,
then... existence
also kind of bites it,
so one of you...
Sorry.
I don't understand why we're
talking about killing Jack.
Y-You can fix him.
You can...
You can restore his soul.
That's why I called you.
Yeah, not so much.
You're God.
Well, souls are complicated...
Even for me.
Besides, even if I could,
would you really want...
I mean, after what he did?
Then we bind him.
We throw him
in the Cage until...
Stop, Cass.
You heard him.
This is the only way.
And Billie said
the only way to defeat Michael
was to lock you in a box.
Ugh. Billie.
I liked the old Death better.
He was all about fried pickles
and tickle porn.
This new Death...
She's always sticking her scythe
where it doesn't belong.
There has to be another way.
Well, there's not.
Now, I know you don't like it,
and I don't really care.
'Cause you just heard it
from God Himself
that this is the only thing
that can kill Jack,
so either get on board,
or walk away.
What did you do to my daughter?!
What did you do?!
Stop!
Dean?
Yeah. Over here.
Hey.
Good, I'm glad you're here.
I actually needed to
talk to you about something.
Um...
Have a seat.
Yeah.
Uh... what's going on?
You know what I'm gonna say.
Let me guess.
This is where you tell me
you're gonna pull the trigger?
Yeah, it is.
We don't have a choice, Sam.
Of course we do.
Don't we always?
I mean, isn't that the point
of everything we've ever done,
that we always have a choice?
He killed our mom.
I get it. I was mad, too.
Or you know what?
Hell, I'm still mad.
And a part of me wants Jack
dead... it really does.
But, Dean, we haven't even
tried to save him.
S... Okay.
You heard him, right?
He actually blamed Mom
for what happened.
He doesn't have a soul.
And whose fault is that?
Mine.
I'm the one
who brought him back,
and I brought him back
because he's family.
Okay.
And then he came back,
and he burned his soul off
to save us...
You and me.
And now what? You...
Now you...
You want my permission?
You want me to say I'm cool
with losing him
and losing you all at once?
'Cause I can't do that.
I won't say that, 'cause I...
No.
I've already lost too much.
Jack.
I've been looking for you.
I haven't seen one of these
in forever.
Where'd you get it?
Another world.
Oh. Right.
So...
How many are there...
How many other worlds
or... or universes
or realities or whatever?
I don't know.
Kinda lost count.
Most of them are boring.
One's in reverse.
In one, there's no yellow.
One... One
of them's just all squirrels.
So, Michael said that
you create these worlds
and you just toss them away
like failed versions
of some book.
And you believe him?
Was he lying?
Is that what you're doing to us?
No. Sam...
you and your brother,
of all the Sams and Deans
in all the multiverse,
you're my favorite.
You're just so interesting.
I mean, like that thing
that happened at the office
earlier today...
That was crazy, right?
And I thought I could
make the world a better place
if people couldn't lie.
Well, it didn't.
It really didn't.
And I went to see
my grandparents.
The Klines.
Yeah, I thought they liked me.
Maybe they'd still like me.
And?
My grandmother said
I killed her... my mom.
And I did.
Just by being born.
Jack...
I used to hate myself for it.
But I don't
feel that way anymore.
I don't feel anything.
After she said that,
what did you do?
I just...
What did you do?!
Stop!
Just stop.
What?
What are you?!
I ran.
Do you watch us?
When you're not here,
are... are you...
watching us?
Yeah.
I mean, you're my favorite show.
Then why don't you do something?
If I had your power...
Sam.
We talked about this.
Not the way it works.
Wait a second.
Why, when the chips are down,
when the world is... is failing,
why does it always
have to be on us?!
Because you're my guys.
But right now,
we need to focus on Jack.
Ah, that kid.
Whew!
Wait a second.
You're scared of him.
Aren't you?
Do you know where he is?
I do.
Then what are you waiting for?
Oh. Nothing.
Dean's already gone.
Mary was a mistake.
But ever since then, I've tried
to do the right thing...
Except for Dumah.
She, um...
She led you astray.
And then I tried on my own,
but every time I try,
it... it never goes right.
It never...
All I ever wanted
was to be good.
But now I'm just...
empty.
Even this... I know you're here
because you love me,
and I want to love you back.
It's just...
...I can't.
You can't yet.
We just need time to fix this.
We need to go somewhere safe,
somewhere
where no one can find us.
Cass, step aside.
Dean.
Step aside!
Jack, go.
Run.
I can't.
You have to.
I won't run anymore.
You're not gonna lock me up
again, are you?
No.
Dean?
Dean!
I understand.
Dean, don't!
Dean?
Dean!
I know what I've done.
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, Dean!
Hey, hey, hey! Dean!
Stay back, Sam!
And you were right all along.
I am a monster.
Do something.
You're enjoying this.
Shh.
No.
Pick it up!
Pick it up.
The hell, Chuck? This isn't how
the story is supposed to end.
The story?
Lookit, the... the...
The gathering storm,
the gun, the... the father
killing his own son.
This is Abraham and Isaac.
This is epic!
Wait.
What are you saying?
He's saying
he's been playing us.
This whole time.
Come on.
Our entire lives.
Mom, Dad... everything.
This is all you
because you wrote it all, right?
Because... Because what?
Because we're
your favorite show?
Because we're part of
your story?
Okay, Dean, no offense, but your
brother is stupid and crazy.
And that kid is still dangerous.
So pick up the gun.
Pick it up...
pull the trigger...
and I'll bring her back.
Your mom.
No.
My mom was my hero.
And I miss her,
and I will miss her
every second of my life,
but she would not want this.
And it's not like you
even really care.
'Cause Sam's right.
The Apocalypse,
the first go-around,
with Lucifer and Michael...
You knew everything
that was going on,
so why the games, Chuck, huh?
Why don't You just snap
your fingers and end it?!
Look, I...
And every other bad thing
we've been killing,
- been dying over...
- where were you?
Just sitting back
and watching us suffer
so we can do this over and over
and over again...
Fighting, losing people we love?
When does it end?
Tell me.
- Dean, don't do this.
- No, we're done talking.
'Cause this...
This isn't just a story.
It's our lives!
So God or no God,
you go to hell.
Have it your way.
Jack.
Jack!
Stop it.
Stop it!
Jack.
Hey, Chuck!
Aah!
Fine!
That's the way you want it?
Story's over.
Welcome to The End.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
Wait. I thought Chuck said
that the gun
was the only thing that could...
He's a writer.
Writers lie.
What's happening?
Yeah, about that...
We should talk.
What the hell is happening?!
Souls.
They're souls from... from Hell.
Hi.
You, uh, need a ride?
I know, right?
Do you think it's...
Do you think it's expensive?
Honestly, it might be.
I think so.
Okay, let's look.
Oh, my gosh. Look at this one.
Stop.