I could have done this quick,
but I wanted to enjoy it.
[ Both grunt ]
? ?
You hurt my friends.
[ Groaning ]
You hurt my family!
[ Screams ]
You're not my father.
You're a monster.
I don't need you.
I just need your power.
[ Inhaling ]
? ?
Jack!
Sammy!
If we work together,
can we beat Lucifer?
We have a chance.
- We can't.
- Lucifer has Sam.
He has Jack.
Cass, I don't have a choice!
? ?
Bye, Dean.
Dean!
[ Gasps ]
[ Screams ]
? ?
[ Body thuds ]
- [ Groans ]
- Dean?
We had a deal!
? ?
Michael?
Thanks for the suit.
? ?
[ Thunder crashing ]
[ Breathing shakily ]
? ?
[ Liquid dripping ]
[ Thunder continues ]
? ?
[ Chains rattling ]
[ Footsteps approach ]
? ?
[ Groaning ]
Mm.
A little of this...
...a little of that.
? ?
And...
[ Grunting ]
Yes.
Good boy.
[ Retches ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Groans ]
[ Energy crackles ]
[ Screams ]
[ Thunder crashes ]
? ?
Hmm.
Too much "that."
How disappointing.
? ?
All right.
Who's next?
? Supernatural 14x02 ?
Stranger in a Strange Land
Original Air Date on
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Who goes to Duluth
in October?
You sure Michael didn't
touch down in Orlando?
[ Scoffs ]
Joe was
pretty specific --
Duluth.
Well, angels ain't known
for their veracity.
[ Clears throat ]
No offense.
None taken.
I tend to agree with you.
[ Pistol cocks ]
Here you go.
Thanks.
Hey, what's that?
So I've been searching through
police reports in Duluth.
Cops just turned up
a pile of corpses
that was dumped near
some train tracks
just north of town,
and their eyes
were burnt out.
So Michael?
We should go -- now.
This isn't just Michael
we're talking about.
It's Dean.
Yeah.
Cass, you know why you can't
come with us, right?
My angelic presence
would be sensed by Michael,
thereby nullifying your hopes
of a sneak attack.
Yeah. Sorry.
And...
you need me to stay here
and babysit Nick and Jack.
It's not babysitting,
Cass.
Only in the sense
that they're not infants,
but they both
have to be supervised.
Jack is...
lost without his grace,
and Nick is...
[ Scoffs ] I mean...
he's just a mess.
Well, i-it's not...
his fault.
Cass, Nick was housing.
You know, h-he deserves a shot
at rebuilding his life.
And yet every time
I look at him, all I can see
is the supreme agent
of evil.
You talking
about my dad again?
Look, I understand.
Being around Nick --
it's hard for me, too.
Uh, Jack, we're gonna need you
to sit this mission out.
Not a permanent thing.
I know the last time,
I sucked when it mattered,
and I need to improve.
So...
that's what I'm gonna do.
All right.
Okay.
[ Pistol cocks ]
Let's move.
? ?
[ Groans ]
[ Screams ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Knock on door ]
[ Groans ]
Hi.
I brought you
some nourishment.
Now that he's, uh...
gone, y-you must
remember to eat.
[ Sighs ]
Right.
[ Inhales ]
Thanks.
I'm not him, Castiel.
[ Sighs ]
I know.
But you still
can't look at me.
It's difficult.
You don't remember
all the things
that you did in his thrall,
but I do.
I know.
[ Sighs ]
I just don't --
I don't...get it.
I don't understand why I would
do something like that.
I don't...
I don't get how I would let
Lucifer possess me.
[ Sighs ]
? ?
You were in
a lot of pain.
And Lucifer saw vulnerability,
and he...
he exploited it.
Is that what you tell yourself
so you can be near me?
I guess so.
? ?
I just don't know
what kind of pain would
make me allow Lucifer
to possess me.
? ?
It was your family.
My family?
? ?
Sarah and Teddy?
[ Sighing ] No.
[ Baby crying ]
? ?
[ Gasps ]
[ Crying continues ]
[ Breathing shakily ]
? ?
[ Whimpering ]
[ Sobbing ]
Sarah: It's you, Nick.
You're special.
You're chosen.
Nick, I need you
to say "yes."
Then yes.
Oh, my God.
[ Voice breaking ]
Who could do that?
[ Breathing heavily ]
A man...
broke into your house...
and you weren't there.
That was no man.
That's not a man.
That's a monster.
[ Voice breaking ]
That's a monster, and then --
and then Lucifer found me
and made me a monster, too.
Oh, my God!
Ohh!
[ Sobbing ]
These are just
some of the victims.
More are in the hall,
a couple in a store room.
We don't usually see
this kind of action in Duluth.
The injuries
all pretty uniform?
Yep.
The boys upstairs think
maybe we're looking
at a spree killer.
If they were DOA,
you have an ETA on TOD?
Any sample DFA?
[ Clears throat ]
DNA?
Uh, frankly,
we don't even know
the precise cause
of death.
I mean, there were
the neck wounds, of course,
but there was also considerable
internal trauma, so --
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Excuse me.
Yeah. [ Clears throat ]
sure.
"DFA"?
I've been fighting a friggin'
apocalypse for 15 years.
My FBI might be
a little rusty.
All right.
Let's give them a quick
once-over, see what they missed.
? ?
Angel kills,
for sure.
And not grunts.
We're talking
five-star smitings.
Knife slits
in the throat.
And it doesn't appear
they bled out.
He kept these people alive
for a while.
? ?
Maybe these people
aren't...
people.
Looking at a vamp.
Same here.
Me too.
Why milk 'em
if he's just gonna smite 'em?
And why is an archangel
hunting vampires
in the first place?
? ?
[ Knock on door ]
Sorry. Excuse me.
Um, did anyone come to claim
or identify these bodies?
Oh, yeah --
a young lady.
Said he heard about the killings
on the morning news,
thought she might know
one of the victims.
And...?
She didn't.
Then she disappeared.
Never even gave us
her last name.
Huh.
Do you happen to have
surveillance cameras outside?
Looks like about...
two centuries of biblical lore.
Light reading.
I'm researching
how long it takes
archangel grace
to replenish.
Well...
archangels being
exceedingly rare,
the data on that
is woefully scant.
The books say it can take
from a month to...
A century.
Yeah.
Complicating factor
being your...
human component,
which slows the process.
Jack, um...
mourning
what you've lost...
it's wasteful.
Might be smarter to focus
on what you still have.
You don't understand
what I'm going through.
Yes, I do --
a little.
At the time
of the Great Fall,
when the angels were
banished from Heaven,
I lost what I thought
was everything.
I had no grace,
I had no...wings.
I felt hopeless
and useless.
What did you have left?
Well, uh...
Well, I had Sam and Dean.
[ Chuckles softly ]
But I had something else
that was extremely helpful.
I had myself.
Just the basic me,
as, uh...
as Dean would say, without
all the bells and whistles.
? ?
You know...
Sam and Dean, they weren't born
with their expertise.
They've been at it
since they were children.
Failing, winning,
developing over the years.
Patience...
persistence --
those are skills, too.
? ?
The past,
where you came from,
that's important,
but it is not as important
as the future
and where you're going.
? ?
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Get...out!
I don't think so.
You can't!
Oh, but I can.
Because, see...
? ?
I own you.
So hang on...
and enjoy the ride.
? ?
That doesn't make
any sense, Sam.
I've never heard
of an interaction
between an archangel
and a vampire --
certainly not
in this universe.
And...why would Michael
be killing them?
I mean, they're not
a threat to him.
Yeah, okay. Well, just let me
know what you find out.
[ Phone beeps ]
[ Sighs ]
Nick, are you, uh...
Nothing.
There's nothing.
There's no information.
There's no mention
of my wife and son
past the year
they were...
when they died.
There's -- There's nothing about
the case being solved. Nothing!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I-I didn't know that.
If I were around,
I would have been on those cops
every single day,
Castiel.
But I was out of my head
with grief.
I said yes to Lucifer.
I was a coward,
and now --
[ Snaps fingers ]
Don't.
? ?
Why did you do that?
Do what?
What went through your head
just now?
? ?
Um, I don't know.
Nothing?
What are you...
trying to get at?
Even though he's departed,
there may be...
some of his influence
still within you.
Just...
? ?
Lucifer may have inflicted
more damage on your psyche
than we suspected.
I don't have time
for this.
I'm not letting this go,
Castiel.
I'm gonna find out
who killed my family.
Nick!
? ?
And then what?
[ Sirens wailing ]
? ?
[ Pounding on door ]
Yeah?
Sam: Lydia Crawford,
this is FBI. Open up.
? ?
[ Pounding on door ]
Open up!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hey! Stop!
Get away from me!
Don't move.
We know who you are.
We know you went
to the morgue.
We saw your license plate
on the security cams
and pulled your address.
You should've ditched the car
when you first got turned.
Made this way too easy.
You're not FBI.
You're hunters.
That's right.
[ Gasps ]
I haven't done
anything wrong.
No,
vampires never do.
My nest --
w-we fed on animal blood.
We -- We lived quiet lives,
until...
until he came.
He?
He who?
I don't know his name,
but...
he was strong.
He tied all of us up
and...
[ Voice breaking ]
one by one, he'd take...
blood from us.
I couldn't see what he was
doing exactly, but...
every time, there would be
this explosion,
and my friends
would be dead.
And when he was
coming for me,
a couple of the others
tried to att--
tried to attack him.
I was able
to get away, but...
they didn't make it.
Why was he killing you?
Did he say?
I don't think
he meant to.
I-It's just that...
things seemed to go wrong.
He wasn't killing.
It was like...
It was like
he was experimenting.
Experimenting?
What for?
That --
That's all I know.
Okay.
Nice chattin' with you.
Wait, wait!
I-I don't know
what he wanted.
who he was.
But I-I do know
where he is.
If...
If you let me go.
? ?
[ Beeping ]
Thank you.
Ooh!
Very elegant.
But, then...
so are you.
[ Chuckles ]
Thanks for
showing me around.
I didn't realize there was
so much going on in...
Where are we, again?
Duluth.
Of course.
Nothing like
where I'm from.
What's it like
in your hometown?
Hmm.
Empty, wind-swept,
dead bodies laying around.
[ Chuckles ]
You're so funny.
What a nice surprise,
meeting you.
I bet you were wondering
what I was doing
all by myself
in that bar tonight.
I'm pretty sure I know
exactly what you were doing
in that bar tonight.
Oh, Michael.
[ Glass thuds lightly ]
I am so not that girl.
But you really are,
aren't you?
You're terrible.
You have no idea.
[ Giggles ]
[ Hisses ]
Did you honestly think
I didn't know what you are?
[ Grunting ]
You think you picked me?
I picked you.
[ Grunts ]
? ?
[ Grunting ]
Now...
summon your master.
Detective,
my wife and son were murdered
in Pike Creek, Delaware.
You're a police lieutenant
If you can't help me,
who can?
Hello?
[ Phone beeps ]
You gotta be k--
[ Sighs ]
[ Phone thuds ]
You know what a cold case is,
Castiel?
Uh...
It's a case too unimportant
for anybody to care about.
My wife and son are dead --
gone forever.
My life is gone with them,
and, uh...a-and nobody cares.
These cops don't care.
Well, I'm sorry.
That sounds...
very difficult.
Difficult?
[ Scoffs ]
Yeah, you know what's difficult?
There's no evidence.
There's no fingerprints.
There's no DNA.
I mean, how does that
even happen?
I mean, there was a witness
who came forward
and said they saw someone
coming out of the house,
and then they said
they didn't see anything at all,
and the case died.
Like everything else.
Nick.
You, on the other hand,
you've been given...
a second chance.
You're not dead.
You don't understand.
No, I do.
Oh, because
your body was stolen?
Because I am occupying
someone else's.
All angels have to
in order to walk the earth.
This...
This was Jimmy Novak.
"Occupy."
Sounds like a cleaned-up way
of saying "steal."
And, um, Jimmy --
Is that his name?
He all right with that?
Yes, he was.
"Was"?
[ Inhales deeply ]
Jimmy's dead.
Castiel...
you're just a stone-cold
body snatcher.
You're no different
than Lucifer.
I...
? ?
I need to look in
on Jack.
? ?
You know...
...in all
my thousands of years...
? ?
...what happened
to Jimmy Novak...
and his family...
? ?
...it's my greatest
regret.
? ?
[ Crow caws in distance ]
You first.
100-year-old cognac.
Strong notes of vanilla
and apricot.
And zero undertones
of silver.
I appreciate you
accepting my invitation.
Yes, well,
the ever-tactful Melanie
thought a refusal unwise.
She thinks you're a god.
[ Chuckles ]
An archangel.
But close.
And I'm the leader
of a werewolf pack.
Why on Earth would an archangel
care about us?
About me?
I admire you.
Eating on the run,
surviving,
despite being stalked
by those venal humans, who...
think of you
as nothing but vermin.
My pack has survived
and prospered for centuries,
despite the humans.
Yes.
Well, I'm new to town.
And from my perspective,
the real monsters
of this world --
the ones that cheat, covet,
lay waste to this planet --
are the humans.
Who made them top dog?
Pardon the pun.
God, I suppose.
God who?
? ?
Between us, Philippe,
God's on
permanent vacation.
Gone fishin'.
Demons and angels don't seem
to be much of a factor here,
so...
I'm in charge.
And what do you
want from me?
You and your kind,
you...
are who you are.
You kill,
but not for sport
or trophies --
to live.
There's a purity in that.
Isn't it time
you had your due?
Our due?
There are ways
to enhance your...
let's call them
talents.
And these ways are...
Fully tested.
There were some misfires early.
I will admit to that.
But I have
cracked the code.
And now what?
Do you propose we wage a war
on the humans,
keeping only
as many of them alive
as we need for slave labor
and a steady food supply?
Because I love
that world.
But, believe me,
it's an absurd dream.
Is it?
Why be the hunted...
when you can be
the hunter?
Hmm?
[ Knock on door ]
Can I help you?
Mrs. Kline?
Yes.
I'm...
a...friend of
your daughter, Kelly.
Oh.
My name is Jack.
So is mine.
I know.
W-Well, please, come in.
[ Chuckles ]
I was in the area
and wanted to say hello.
[ Ice cubes rattle ]
Thank you.
Kelly always had such nice
things to say about her family.
[ Chuckles ]
So, how did you know
our Kelly?
Through work?
She...
basically gave me
my start.
So you were like her intern.
[ Chuckles ]
Took you under her wing.
That's just like her.
[ Chuckles ]
We haven't heard from her
in a long time.
Well, she went traveling,
but she couldn't tell us where.
She really couldn't.
So it was part of her...
government work --
classified and all that?
[ Dog barks in distance ]
Oh, please.
[ Chuckles ]
Is that her?
Sixth grade.
She won the spelling bee.
"Chrysanthemum" was
the winning word. [ Chuckles ]
Lucky. We grew them
in the yard.
[ All chuckle ]
Forgive me.
But, um, Kelly told us
she was pregnant.
We didn't push
for details.
We felt she'd tell us more
when she was ready.
Uh, she...
she had the baby.
[ Laughs ]
A boy.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Voice breaking ]
We have a grandson.
You do.
And in the time
I spent with her,
she was
an amazing mother.
? ?
Her son loves her
very much.
Oh, I can just imagine.
She would sing and talk to him
even before he was born.
She made him feel...
safe and...
wanted.
I heard her tell him
that it isn't fate
or her or his dad
who sets his path.
It's himself.
Who he chooses to be.
I know it's nutty,
but...
Jack here --
he kind of looks like her.
[ Chuckles ]
See?
? ?
I don't know.
But...
I hope some day to have
a little of her courage and...
purpose.
? ?
I didn't mean
to intrude.
Oh, no, not at all.
Hey, no.
I had to meet you.
If you see Kelly...
tell her we miss her.
I will.
? ?
I miss her, too.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Chuckles ]
? ?
[ Sirens wailing in distance ]
Lydia.
I...
I didn't...
Of course you did.
The hunters.
[ Inhales shakily ]
Why do you think I dumped
your brothers and sisters
in plain sight?
? ?
Why do you think
I let you escape?
You let me escape?
Rule number 1 --
you can't have a trap
without bait.
That brings us
to rule number 2,
which says...
once the trap
has been sprung,
you don't need the bait
anymore.
[ Screams ]
? ?
Jack, what were you thinking,
taking that kind of a risk?
No, it wasn't a risk.
But t-to go out there
alone?
Jack, you have
been on the radar
of every angel and demon
and power broker in creation
since the day you were born,
and I'm sorry,
but you're not exactly
yourself.
Weak and defenseless,
you mean.
I mean that
the possibility of capture
is real, yes.
I heard what you were
saying, Cass,
about me finding out
where I came from.
Well, I never knew
my mother.
I thought the next best thing
might be for me
to meet the only real family
that I have left.
That is not --
[ Exhales sharply ]
Well, did it help?
And you didn't tell them
who you were, did you?
Of course not.
I wanted to.
I wanted to tell them
I was their grandson.
They thought I actually
kind of looked like her.
I...
I couldn't tell them
that she died.
They just...
love her so much.
? ?
I know I should have.
What you did,
you did...
from a place
of kindness.
I suppose there are
worse ways to be human
than to be kind.
? ?
Have you heard
from Sam?
Did they find Michael?
Yeah, they think so.
So they're gonna try
and kill him?
Uh...no.
No, the -- the plan
is to subdue him
using angel cuffs
and spell work.
They have to get Michael
out of Dean.
And if he doesn't leave?
Then they'll try
to drive him out.
- And if that doesn't work?
- Jack --
Cass, Michael
has to be stopped.
I know, and he will be,
after Dean is --
No, Dean doesn't matter.
You're all so focused
on trying to save Dean.
And I get it, I understand,
but if he can't be saved,
if it comes down
to him or Michael...
Michael
has to be stopped.
Caged or killed --
And if that means
that Dean dies, too?
Then Dean dies.
I know this Michael.
I've seen what he's done
to an entire world,
and so have you.
If stopping that
from happening here
means that Dean
has to die, then...
? ?
Do you think he'd want it
any other way?
? ?
[ Dog barks in distance ]
Well, it is so good to see you
after all these years.
I mean...
after that night,
you just disappeared,
and I never knew
what happened.
Yeah, after I lost my family,
I couldn't stand
being in that house
one more minute.
Nick,
I completely understand.
Do you?
I just hope these years
have been healing
and restful for you.
My whole family
was slaughtered, Arty.
There's no...restful
for me anymore.
The best thing
I could hope for
is that I catch the monster
who did it.
Well, sure, Nick.
We all -- We all want that.
Do you, though, Arty?
'Cause you said
you got a good look
at the man
who left my house,
and then
you changed your story.
? ?
Well, I had to, Nick,
because there was no man.
I mean, I...
In the heat
of the moment,
I guess I thought
I saw something.
I wanted so much
to help.
But I was wrong.
Hmm.
Is that the window
you were looking out of?
Uh...
[ Chuckles nervously ]
? ?
What made you
look out, Arty?
You hear
someone scream?
[ Chuckles nervously ]
Uh, I-I don't really remember.
? ?
The man you saw,
was he --
was he rushing out,
or was he casual?
Nick,
I told you that --
What, did he have
a hammer?
? ?
'Cause that's how the cops said
he murdered my family.
[ Voice breaking ]
He smashed their skulls...
over and over
with a hammer.
? ?
Nick, there --
there was no man.
[ Sighing ]
Oh, Arty.
Who got to you?
W-W-What?
Somebody get to you?
No.
They pay you off?
I mean -- N-No.
Or were you just scared?
[ Gasps ]
Huh? Huh?
[ Strained ] I just remembered wrong.
That's all there is to it.
My family deserves justice.
Do you understand me?
I deserve justice!
I'm gonna get justice!
Do you understand me,
Arty?!
[ Sobbing ]
I don't know anything!
Oh, I think you do,
Arty.
I think you do.
[ Door closes ]
[ Footsteps approach ]
[ Mice squeak ]
? ?
You think
vamp girl was lying
about Michael
hiding out here?
Not sure
why she would.
I mean, she has every reason
to want him dead.
She wasn't lying about
the slaughter happening here.
Whole lot of dried blood
on the floor.
Why was he
killing them?
And what did she mean
by "experimenting"?
[ Bag thuds ]
Don't look like
he's here.
[ Snarling ]
Werewolves!
[ Pistol cocks ]
? ?
Silver bullets
aren't working!
[ Groans ]
Nothing's working!
? ?
[ Snarling ]
Well, that works.
? ?
[ Snarls ]
[ Knife clatters ]
? ?
[ Snarls ]
[ Blade slices ]
? ?
[ Body thuds ]
Is everybody okay?
Anyone get bit?
No.
I'm okay.
[ Exhales deeply ]
What the hell kinda werewolves
were those?
Silver didn't touch 'em.
[ Door opens ]
? ?
[ Breathing shakily ]
Sammy.
It's me.
[ Exhales deeply ]
? ?
[ Grunts ]
Dean.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Is it really you?
Yeah, it's really me.
A-Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay!
But you got Michael
to leave.
No, I -- I don't...
I didn't.
What?
He just --
He just left.
Why?
I don't know.
? ?
[ Hammer thuds ]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man