I say that I do
the terrible things I do
because I couldn't find
who killed Sarah and Teddy.
But I lied.
Truth is...
I like
doing these things,
and I don't want to stop.
Even if you could
force me out,
what do you think
I'd leave behind?
You'd be nothing
but blood and bone.
Then we don't
kick him out. We keep him in.
It's just you.
- Michael's all locked up.
- Seems that way.
Do you remember visiting
my reading room?
The shelves and shelves
of notebooks
describing the ways
you might die?
They all end
the same way now --
except one.
What am I supposed to do
with this?
That's up to you.
Never been caught
by a human before.
You some kind of Hunter?
No.
No, I know a couple.
Picked up some tricks.
And a few other things.
Well, if you're not a Hunter,
let's make a deal.
Mnh-mnh.
No deals.
What do you want?
Abraxas.
Yeah,
the last demon I killed
said you and Abraxas
made quite the team
until he was captured
by a Hunter.
You left your pal
in the lurch,
but you know
who got him.
If I was there.
The Hunter who caught him,
who almost got me --
why would I
protect them?
Hell, I can even tell you
where to find 'em.
So...no need
for any of this.
Oh,
I don't know.
Where's the fun
in that?
Hibbing!
She's in
Hibbing, Minnesota.
? Supernatural 14x11 ?
Damaged Goods
Original Air Date on January 24, 2019
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
- Hey.
How you feeling?
What you reading?
Uh, going back through
the Book of Jubilees.
You know, the way
they classify angels is -- is --
it's really interesting.
Find anything
on Michael?
Not yet, but I -- but I --
but I just started.
We'll find a way.
Man, I-I-I...
I appreciate it,
you know, you...trying.
Well, yeah.
Of course.
I mean, always.
You want to hop in,
help out?
I got plenty
to go through.
Actually, I-I -- I thought
I'd go for a --
a drive, you know?
Just me and Baby,
long stretch of road.
And figured
I'd make it a twofer --
I'd go see Mom
at, uh, Donna's cabin.
Yeah.
Yeah,
Th-that sounds great.
Be good
to see 'em.
Just let me, uh,
find a stopping point
and get packed up.
Uh, actually, I was, uh...
was kind of hoping for
some one-on-one time
with Mom,
if that's cool.
Ye-- uh...Sure, yeah.
Whatever you need.
Okay.
Take care, Sammy.
Yeah,
he called last night.
Said it was just
a supply run,
but I'll take any excuse
for a visit.
Cabin's been
a little quiet lately.
Quiet?
Yeah, uh,
Bobby took off for a few days.
It's fine.
Just after everything
that happened with his son,
we needed
a little space.
Yeah.
Sam?
Sorry, I'm just --
I'm worried, you know?
Ever since
we locked Michael up,
Dean's been
acting strange,
and he just packed up
and left,
and then, uh...
And what?
He hugged me.
That's sweet.
Mom,
we don't hug.
I mean, w-we do,
but only if it's literally
the end of the world, you know?
Sam,
he'll be here soon.
I'll look after him.
- I'll get to the bottom of this.
- Yeah, all right.
M-Maybe it's like you said,
you know?
Maybe he just need some space,
like Bobby.
Yeah.
Well, and until
we know for sure,
we have to
respect that.
Yeah, you're right.
Uh, I -- I...
Yeah, uh...
talk soon.
Mmm. Oh, my God.
What?
You thought I was joking?
Best burger
in Minnesota.
Best burger ever.
- Glad it satisfied.
- Oh.
So good.
So, Dean.
Have you seen
Jody lately, hm?
The girls?
Oh, yeah.
You know,
I split my time as much I can,
help Jody
with their training.
Last month,
we took down a Vetala nest.
Mm-hmm.
Alex, little miss
"I don't want to Hunt"?
She killed two
all by herself.
Get out of town.
Good for her.
Anyhoo...
Now, what about you?
How's sheriffing going?
I know it was a little tough
last time, what with, uh...
- Doug, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you know,
the split was rough.
Doug's working
private security now,
up in Duluth.
Okay.
Any more questions?
Huh?
Just wondering
if you've run out of ways
to ask me how I'm doing,
so as to avoid me
repaying the favor.
I know you were
just possessed, again.
Sam.
He had us all out
looking for you.
And I know
you got an archangel
hitching a ride
up there in your noggin.
Also Sam.
What, does he got
a freakin' newsletter?
I'm just saying,
all that,
it can't be easy,
you know?
Well...
I'll make it through,
okay?
That's all we can do,
right?
Right.
Couldn't come through town
without seeing my D-train,
so thanks
for meeting me.
Oh, yeah.
Come here.
Oh.
Ohh.
You betcha.
I'll see ya,
Donna.
Hey, Mom.
You're here.
Yeah. Thought I'd stick around
for a couple days, if that's cool.
Of course.
Uh,
Bobby's gone.
We have a big couch
and a pull-out.
- Perfect.
- Awesome.
You know, if you wanted
to make it a full reunion,
we could
call Sam over.
Yeah, you know,
I was thinking
I'd actually be a little greedy
with my Mom time,
if that's cool.
Well, I just thought, you know,
if you're staying a few nights...
I don't want Sam here.
- Everything all right?
- Yeah, no.
You know what? I just --
I'm -- I'm hangry, okay?
Long drive,
haven't eaten,
and, uh, I'm starving,
actually.
Well, uh,
the delivery options
are a little limited
this far out,
and we both know
I'm not much of a cook.
Well, there's one thing
you can cook
better than anybody
on the planet.
Winchester Surprise?
Yeah.
I can't believe
you remember that.
I can't believe I ever fed that
to you and John.
It was so greasy,
like...
Heart attack
on a plate.
A delicious heart attack
on a plate, okay?
I would like mine
with extra cheese.
All right,
then.
Yes.
Oh, and, uh...
Pie.
Well, Donna certainly has
a type.
All right.
? No time left for you ?
? On my way to better things ?
? I found myself some wings ?
? No time left for you ?
? Distant roads are callin' me ?
? Time, time, time, time, time ?
? No time for a summer friend ?
? No time
for the love you send ?
? Seasons change, and so did I ?
? You need not wonder why ?
? There's no time left for you ?
? No time left for you ?
? I got, got, got, got no time ?
? No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no time ?
Hey.
Need a hand?
- Hey, Joe.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
That's new.
What?
You buying food.
I just mean
you usually only pick up
whiskey, pumpkins,
and crossword puzzles.
Well...
crosswords do get better
with whiskey.
Oh.
And I got family
in town.
- Oh, nice. Well, enjoy.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- See you later.
Hey, man. Excuse me.
- Hey. Can I help you?
- Yeah, yeah, I think you can.
I'm looking
for a friend of mine --
Mary Winchester.
Sorry.
I don't know her.
Well, she told me to meet her
here in Hibbing,
so if you could just point me
in the right direction,
we're all good,
you know?
Thanks for nothing,
pal.
Ah...damn it.
Oh, come on, man.
Hiya.
Evening, Officer.
You can't --
I didn't do anything.
Oh, sure ya did.
You see,
I ran the plates,
and this van here?
Belongs to an 80-year-old lady
in Missoula.
Yeah.
My Grammy,
she lets me borrow it.
No.
Grammy reported it stolen
two weeks ago.
And word has it you're looking
for a friend of mine,
Mary Winchester.
No, I -- I-I talked
to the kid
about renting a place
for fishing.
Oh. Huh.
You catch a lot of fish
with that Arkansas toothpick
you got there
on the passenger seat?
So...
what's your name?
"Nunya."
What's that?
- First name, Eat, last name, Me.
- Okay.
You see this?
Mobile
fingerprint scanner.
Cost the force
a pretty penny,
but I figured
it'd come in handy.
You won't
give it to me straight...
...but this will.
Uff da.
You're a long way
from Delaware, Nick.
Ugh. Aah!
Okay, sicko.
That's enough.
Hey.
Hey. What were you doing
out there?
Oh, I, uh...
Oh, here.
You know,
I'm just, uh...
taking a look around.
Come on inside.
I got a surprise
for you.
What's all this?
Well,
I wanted to make sure
everything was ready
for you.
And I thought I'd, uh --
I'd give you a hand, you know?
Two terrible cooks
teaming up.
What could possibly
go wrong?
What?
Nothing.
Listen, Mom, I-I --
I think I should come up.
Uh, there's some stuff missing
from the bunker, and --
Sam, I don't know
what's going on,
but something
is going on.
Just give me
some time.
Let me
talk to him, okay?
Okay, yeah.
Um, yeah.
All right, Mom.
He comes back,
he's standing there,
he's soaking wet,
and he's pulling bologna
and sliced cheese out of his pants.
So, me being the big brother,
I'm the cook.
I take all of that bologna,
all that sliced cheese,
and I put it
onto a hot plate.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- It stunk up that room so bad.
Dad comes home,
and he is so mad.
He picks up everything,
chucks it in the trash.
Probably reminded him of you,
and...
Anyway,
it did not taste right.
It didn't taste
like this.
Oh.
Sometimes I forget just how much
I missed while I was gone
and how much
the two of you just...
But you're here now, right?
And even though
the last couple of years
have been
a little rough,
just knowing
that you're around,
that you're alive...
Mom, that's meant everything
to me.
And everything
to Sam.
And how great
is this, hm?
You, me, sitting here,
eating the real thing,
not some bologna version
of Winchester Surprise?
You know,
we're not fighting any monsters.
There's -- There's no clouds
on the horizon.
Dean?
Mm-hmm?
Whatever
you're going through,
you can talk to me.
Everybody keeps asking
how I am,
and how I am is
I don't want to talk about it.
Please.
No.
No, no, no.
Mnh.
What?
Oh, God.
Hey.
Ah...
Hey, Donna. It's Dean.
What's up?
He got
the drop on me.
Dean,
he's going after your mom.
- He who?
- Uh, some guy named Nick.
Dean! Whoa, easy!
Dean,
what's going on here?
It's Mom.
She's gone.
The demons,
they know where you are.
They keep track of you,
you and your kids.
They're sort of
scared of you.
So wherever you are,
they're not.
So that's how
I got to Hibbing.
I didn't have
an address.
Luckily, that --
that perky sheriff lady --
what's her name?
Deborah? Debbie?
Something? Whatever.
She had, um...
She had some e-mails
on her cellphone
talking about you
and her family cabin.
So, voil? --
here I am.
I know
that's a lot to take in, but...
And if
you feel like screaming,
you can --
you can go ahead,
'cause we're...
pretty remote.
Nick?
What are you doing?
Tonya Baker.
Yeah, you knew her.
You saved her life.
Yeah, her whole Girl Scout troop
was murdered.
She was the only survivor,
thanks to you.
These two demons
were about to finish her off,
and then you came in,
and you chased one away.
But you faced off
against the other one,
a demon
named Abraxas.
I remember.
So?
So,
Abraxas murdered my family
the same way he killed
those girls --
bloody, brutal, slow.
I'm sorry,
Nick.
But you could have
just asked me.
This is...
Crazy?
Hm?
What would you
have told me?
That I killed him.
Abraxas is dead.
So you would've
lied to me.
His friend got away,
but she saw everything.
You didn't kill Abraxas.
You trapped him
in a box.
How'd you do it?
Uh...
Tell me.
Okay,
you're right.
I trapped him.
We fought,
and he was winning.
So I put him in
an Enochian puzzle box.
He's contained.
Do you have him?
No.
But I can take you
to him.
I got his tags,
put my guys on it.
They're running 'em.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault, Donna.
It's mine.
Nick said when he left
he was just gonna go home.
I-I didn't know
he was...
Killing people?
- Sheriff?
- Yeah. Go for Hanscum.
We got that van
you were looking for.
A traffic cam
just caught it
pulling into a storage facility
outside Grand Rapids.
Copy that.
I got it from here.
- How far is Grand Rapids?
- 30, 40 minutes.
We'll be there in 20.
All right,
where is it?
Okay, if you do this,
we're done.
You walk. Okay?
Over there.
You first.
Clever.
All right,
where is it?
In the lockers.
Too bad
I forgot the keys.
Which one?
All right,
fine.
Mnh.
Bingo.
Open it.
Me and 'Brax-y
have to have a talk.
Well,
that's not gonna happen.
I'm sorry?
To talk,
a demon needs a host.
It can't be you.
Can't be me.
Didn't really think
this through, did you, Nick?
So I'll improvise.
Say it.
I can see
you want to.
Might as well
go ahead and say it.
All right.
Nick is not a project.
He's not
a freakin' puppy.
He was Lucifer's vessel
for years.
I know that, Dean.
I thought --
You thought he'd what?
Just walk it off? Come on, man.
You're not that dumb.
It's not about
being dumb, Dean.
It's called compassion.
Look, what happened to Nick
could've happened to me.
It almost
happened to me.
You change one little thing
in our past,
and that was me.
Lucifer wearing me
to the prom.
And besides, since when
do we give up on people?
Since when do we just
cut people loose?
Well, maybe you need
to learn, okay?
'Cause when people are
past the point of saving,
maybe you need to learn
to walk away.
Nick, don't do this.
Do what?
You let
that demon out of there,
he could kill us.
I can handle it.
How do you open
this thing?
I don't know.
Mnh.
I don't like you.
I said
I can handle it.
I think there's only one way
to get into this box.
Come on, baby.
Heya, Blondie.
Missed ya.
Why did you kill
my family?
Who's he?
Sorry, you're gonna have to be
more specific.
Pike Creek, Delaware.
Oh...
no way.
Nick?
What are you doing
walking and talking?
I thought the Big Man
had you on lock.
Lucifer's dead.
Is he?
Cool.
Why did you kill
my family?
Kill your family,
yeah, got it.
Tell you what --
I'll answer that
when you kill her.
She locked me in a box,
and I hold a grudge.
Do her slow and bloody,
then we'll chat.
Nick.
Nick, no.
Nick, hey!
Don't -- Stop --
N-No!
Aah! Aah! Hey.
Get away from her!
Stay back.
Is she all right?
She's good.
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
What I have to.
- No, Nick --
- No!
Showtime.
You want to know
why I gutted your family?
Orders.
I was
following orders.
From who?
Who do you think?
Lucifer planned
the whole thing.
I don't --
I don't understand.
Why my family?
Why -- Why me?
No particular reason.
You were chosen,
but you're not special.
We threw a dart
at the phone book.
Exorcizamus te, omnis immundus
spiritus, omnis satanica --
Naughty.
So...
who dies first?
Aah!
Nick.
Nick,
take it easy.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Donna. Hold on.
Yeah. Sure.
Why?
I needed the truth,
Sam.
I needed revenge
for my family.
You would've done
the same thing.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
I couldn't help you.
I didn't know how.
It's not about you,
Sam.
It's never about you.
You couldn't fix me 'cause
I don't want to be fixed.
I was never broken.
Yeah, Nick, you are.
I don't feel sorry
for you, Nick.
I feel sorry
for the people you hurt,
the people you murdered,
the people whose faces
will haunt you
every night
for the rest of your life.
You can burn.
Mind your head.
I saw, Dean.
Donna's shed.
I know what you've been
building, planning.
And we are gonna
talk about that.
We are all three of us
gonna talk about that.
So if
you don't tell Sam...
I will.
It's a Ma'lak box.
Secured and warded.
Once inside...
nothing gets out,
not even an archangel.
Especially an archangel.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I've -- I've read about these,
but no --
but no one's ever --
They're impossible
to build.
Yeah, well,
not so much.
That's your plan?
You want
to be buried alive?
Buried's not safe enough.
Plan is,
pay a little hush money,
charter a boat to take me
out to the Pacific.
Splash.
You and Michael,
trapped together --
for eternity?
Yeah.
You do realize
how insane this is, right?
It's the only sane play
I've got.
Michael gets out,
that's it for this world.
And he will get out.
Well, how do you know that
for sure?
Because I do.
Because I can feel him
in my head.
That door is giving.
I can feel it giving.
- But there has to be another way.
- There's not, okay?
There --
Sam,
you've tried.
Cass has tried.
Jack...
And I love you
for trying.
But none of it's
gonna work.
- We don't know that.
- Yeah, we do.
- What?
- Billie.
Billie?
She paid me
a little visit.
She said that there's only
one way that this ends right.
And this is it --
this, right here,
this box.
So she gave up
the special recipe,
and all I had to do
was the work.
It's fate.
Since when
do we believe in fate?
Now, Sam.
Since now.
So...
you came out here
to see Donna,
to see Mom on some --
some what?
Some sick,
secret farewell tour?
You were gonna leave,
and you weren't even
gonna tell me.
Me.
Do you realize
how messed up that is,
how unfair that is?
- I didn't have a choice!
Sam, you're the last person
I could tell,
the last person
I could be around,
'cause you're the only one that
could've talked me out of it.
And I won't be
talked out of it.
I won't.
I'm doing this.
Now, you can either
let me do it alone...
or you could help me.
But I'm doing this.
All right.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man