Stacy!
We knew Jack was dangerous.
We always knew.
Jack, stop.
- So, what do we do?
- We fight.
I killed Mary.
- You're dead to me.
- I failed you.
And I failed Jack.
Go to Heaven and find her!
- Where's Naomi?
- Castiel, run!
It's none of your business.
- I'm looking for someone.
- Mary Winchester?
There may be a way
to bring her back.
- "Necromantiorum."
- I don't want your help.
I'm your, you know,
subconscious or whatever.
Y-You whipped me up to
help you figure this out.
You know it's not gonna work.
Admit it.
You don't feel anything anymore.
Jack is using magic
to bring your mom back.
It didn't work.
We know it wasn't easy
for some of you to get here,
and we thank you.
We, uh...
We gave her a Hunter's send-off
a few days ago.
But we know that her family
went beyond just us.
Some of you Hunted
alongside her.
Some of you fought Michael
with her in the other world.
You know,
we lost our mom once before.
But we got a second chance
with her.
And we got to know her
not just as "Mom," but...
as someone who was tough
and strong.
Stubborn as Hell.
Someone who had opinions
and wasn't shy to use them.
She could handle a machete.
She could handle a vampire.
She could handle our old man.
She couldn't cook worth a damn.
Mom, you weren't here
long enough.
But we're, uh...
We're so glad
for the time that we had.
Goodbye, Mom.
Bye, Mom.
To Mary.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
Make sure I get my hatchet back.
Damn wraith.
Knew him from a nest
your mom and I busted up
on our last Hunt.
Probably here to gloat.
The bastard.
Thanks for coming out.
A Hunter's memorial,
complete with monster.
Mary would have
appreciated that.
Now that you mention it, yeah.
How are you?
Hey, you know. It's tough.
And the other one?
Yeah, Dean...
seems to be doing okay.
Hard to say.
Yeah.
Maybe he's like me.
Bein' teary in public's
not my style.
Hey. Uh, most
everybody's headed out,
but Bobby's gonna stick around.
I thought maybe we could open
that Scotch Ketch left and...
hang out, talk about Mom.
"Talk about Mom"?
Yeah.
Isn't that what we've beendoing?
Thanks.
Memory lane?
Yeah.
I mean, Dean couldn't have
been but 4 years old.
I wasn't even 6 months.
Just...
Hmm.
You know, at one time,
you boys were good-lookin'.
Thanks.
Sam.
What exactly happened to her?
Because I'm hearin' the kid...
- Hey.
You need anything?
Yeah, I need a drink.
Bar's open.
Nah, I need to get
outta here for a while.
But, dude, we got to
talk about Jack.
We will.
About that.
I liked the kid.
We fought together.
But there's only
one way this ends.
Bobby's right. We have to
find Jack and help him.
What? That kid...
He killed Mary!
I know that.
Ah-ah.
Don't say "but."
But... he...
Jack may not even realize
what he did was wrong.
If his human side is gone,
you know what's left... Lucifer.
Now, if you boys want to
sit around and talk, fine.
But me?
I'm gonna get on the horn
to some of my people
and go find that boy.
And what then?
An unstoppable monster
who don't know right from wrong
gets put down...
Or the closest we can get to it.
And anybody who don't know that
needs to go back to school.
- Take me home, Jack.
- Tell me it's okay.
If Sam and Dean
saw what you did...
they would be
as worried as I am.
Are you gonna tell them?
- Leave me alone!
- Please!
- Listen! Jack?
- Leave me alone.
- Listen to me!
- Leave me alone!
I wish you were here.
Mom...
I need you to tell me
what to do.
Well...
Next best thing.
You're just in my head.
I'm making you up.
Or you see me because you know
I tell you the truth.
- No.
- Hmm.
And, by the way, buddy.
Um, I'm real.
You're part of my DNA.
I'm locked in your head
and your heart forever.
- I'm not listening to you.
- So what are you gonna do?
You just gonna pine away for
Mommy and the Winchesters?
Only they...
They never loved you.
You're nothing to them.
You're just their... You're
just a little pet monster.
Their... Their muscle.
No, they... They'll understand
about... what happened.
- Are you out of your mind?
- I'll explain it to them.
It... It was an accident.
And I tried to
bring her back, and...
They've made mistakes, too.
Okay. Dude...
They hate you.
Okay? They don't even want you
for a pet anymore.
From here on out,
you're all you got.
Well, and me.
Especially me.
Castiel.
What a pleasant surprise.
It's urgent that I see Naomi.
And, like I told you before,
she is unavailable.
What does that mean?
Just tell me.
It means the Empty invaded.
Under her watch.
We almost died.
Heaven needs a leader.
A leader like you?
Oh, I'm not my first choice,
either, but here we are.
A-And Naomi, she's...?
In a very small cell.
Not that you should care.
She wasn't your biggest fan.
No, but I needed her help.
With?
To find an archangel.
Really?
I mean, 'cause,
after Michael, there's...
There's none of those left.
This isn't exactly a...
It's the Nephilim.
Lucifer's love child.
Jack has grown
massively powerful.
Dangerously so.
And I thought that
it was his "mother's side"
that was supposed to
give him self-control.
Well, in the sense that he
inherited her decency, yes.
But that was before.
Before what?
Before he burned through
his soul.
To save me.
Among others.
So he lost his capacity for good
through an act of goodness.
What about the Winchesters?
Jack's no longer with them.
He's on the run.
He's fearful of their fury.
I bet he is.
But I am hopeful
that he can be salvaged.
He can be rehabilitated, with
patient molding and guidance.
I'll see what I can do.
Hey.
You just getting back?
Yeah.
- How you feeling?
- What you working on?
I, uh...
I'm trying to find Jack.
We got to find him
before Bobby and his crew,
'cause if they find him first...
He's gonna kill 'em all?
I don't know.
You know, I can't stop
thinking about Mom.
Yeah.
I-I can't stop thinking that...
Most people, it's... it's...
It's... it's hope
and faith, right?
That's all they have.
But we know the truth.
We know God is real.
We know angels are real, too.
God writes paperback books
in his underwear, okay?
And angels are dicks.
But they're real, right?
We know that Mom's not sitting
on a cloud playing a harp.
She's in a good place.
Or she's in a greatplace.
She's with Dad.
Hmm.
You know what else?
There wasn't enough left of her
to even try to bring her back.
Hello, Jack.
Remember me?
We met... in Heaven.
Yes, we did.
How did you find me?
Jack, I came here
to tell you something.
Something important.
It wasn't your fault.
What happened
with Mary Winchester.
You know about that?
Jack, it was a mistake.
That doesn't mean that you
don't deserve redemption.
I know...
Heaven knows...
your mother knew that you have
a gloriousdestiny.
I do?
Look at the world
around you, Jack.
You know, there was a time
when Earth had moral order.
When God would punish those
who did wrong
and who didn't respect Heaven.
But when he left,
it all fell apart.
You could change that.
You couldn't save
Mary Winchester, but...
but you can save so many others,
even Heaven itself.
You could make the world
so much better.
And think how happy
that would make Sam and Dean.
Dr. Tate.
You've come about the leak
in my bathroom?
Hardly.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Biblical Lies."
Quite the best seller,
I believe.
People are hungry for the truth.
And your call to
reject God and Heaven...
That is the "truth"?
It's an attempt to replace
wishful thinking
with rational thought.
In more civilized times,
that was called heresy.
And those ideas
were an affront to Heaven.
If there werea Heaven.
Oh, there is.
I've been there.
I see.
And I suppose you saw God?
No.
But he is my grandfather.
Huh. So then that would
make your father...
Lucifer.
Professor Tate,
Heaven is not unreasonable.
You can avoid divine
retribution by announcing
to your considerable audience
that you've had a revelation...
that everything you've
written to date is false...
that God is good.
Yeah. You're insane. And I would
rather call security.
So, the angels...
They're gonna help us?
I was promised every effort
would be made
to, uh, locate Jack.
Oh. Heaven promised?
Great.
Well, we should take that
to the bank.
Jack's powers
could also be a threat.
It serves them to help find him.
Yeah, about that.
Um, I've been looking
for anything weird.
And a university professor
was found dead
in his office in Ohio.
His body was crystallized
into a block of salt.
Salt. Why's that sound familiar?
It's a pillar of salt.
It's Biblical.
Lot's wife.
Punished by Heaven.
This guy was an atheist.
He wrote a bunch
of best-selling books
trying to disprove
God and Heaven.
Okay. So you think
an angel iced him?
No ordinary angel could do
something like that.
Just wait.
There's another.
A few hours after
the professor was killed,
a lady in Texas fell into
a crevice that opened up,
and she was killed.
- Like a sinkhole.
- That's what I thought, too.
But a witness said
it was more like
"a fissure opened under her feet
then closed back up
with her inside."
"And the Earth opened her mouth
and swallowed them up,
and their houses,
and all of the men that
appertained unto Korah."
It's Numbers 26:10.
This lady was a...
A TV evangelist.
Um, she was under investigation
for stealing thousands of
dollars through fake charities.
So either Chuck
came back, which...
That ain't gonna happen, or...
Jack.
You've done
excellent work, Jack.
When God was in his prime,
Heaven was in its glory.
Working as a team,
we can bring that back.
Sam and Dean will like that?
Words can't begin to express
how Sam and Dean will feel.
Now...
here is the real test.
We need more angels.
You're not God. You can't just
make them out of thin air.
But if a human
were predisposed to it,
maybe you could take their soul
and forge them into one of us.
What do you say?
This is where your grandfather
received prayers.
Make yourself still.
And available.
Focus.
You'll hear.
Dear God, please help...
Please, God, let the Giants
win the World Series.
Please, God....
we beseech you
to hear our prayer.
We humbly ask that you receive
our gratitude for your gifts...
and pray that you deliver us
unto Heaven
and the greater glory.
Amen!
Okay. I sure hope everyone
did the reading last week.
- Uh-huh.
- Yes.
Small surprise...
Pastor Ames is coming by
to discuss the Book of Samuel.
Oh! Sorry.
I-I didn't see you come in.
Please. Join us.
Take a seat, mister...?
Jack.
My name is Jack.
Did you mean it when you said
you wanted to go to Heaven?
- Yes.
That's the goal of everyone
in this room.
Mm-hmm.
And you don't mind
becoming angels?
Mind?
Yeah!
That would be a dream.
It doesn't have to be a dream.
I-I'm not sure I understand.
Ohh!
Who are you?
Come with me.
To Heaven.
So, who's ready to take
on the Book of Samuel?
Hello.
I was just taking your friends...
to become angels.
You... What?
Would you like to join them?
Son. This isn't funny.
It's not even possible.
So... you're saying
you don't believe?
It's not that I don't believe.
I just don't believe you.
And...
Shelley?
Sir, please don't interfere
with Heaven's work.
All right. Get out!
"He was eaten by worms
and breathed his last."
Sir...
Pastor Ames? Hi.
Agent Kilmister.
Clarke and Taylor. FBI.
We want to ask you
about last night.
What happened
to your congregation?
You want to know w...
They're all... They're gone.
They're all gone.
We're trying to figure out
exactly what happened.
You're just
gonna think I'm crazy.
The cops did.
About that, uh, the police
report stated that you said
the group "disappeared"
right in front of you.
Yeah.
Did he say where
he was taking them?
To Heaven.
To become angels.
Did he look anything like this?
That's him.
I tried to stop him, but...
And he did all this to you?
He just waved his hand,
and I landed on the floor,
and these cuts opened up
all over my body.
And worms crawled out of 'em.
Worms!
Worms.
He said he was carrying out
Heaven's orders...
and that I wasn't a believer.
- Well, feel better.
- Yeah.
"Immediately an angel of
the Lord struck him down,
because he did not give God
the glory,
and he was eaten by worms
and breathed his last."
Wait. So this is
another Bible thing?
What the Hell is going on?
I didn't want it
to come to this, either.
But I know that that kid's
head's not right.
And now that Heaven
has its hooks in him,
we don't have a choice.
Wait. Come to what?
What are you talking about?
Stopping Jack.
Once and for all.
All right. Fine. Say I agree.
Dean, he can't be killed.
No, but he can be contained.
How are we supposed to do that?
With this.
Are we seriously talking
about locking Jack in this?
No, we're seriously talking
about not having a choice.
We can't kill him, okay?
And this is warded
to lock down an archangel.
Yeah. So... So, what?
We... We just...
force him inside?
How? No. He goes in here,
it's got to be his choice.
He's never gonna
go along with that.
Maybe.
But he might.
He might if he only has to
stay in there long enough
for us to finish the spell
to fix his soul.
Spell?
What spell?
There isno spell.
Weknow that.
So you want to lie to him.
No. Well, I mean, I want
Zeppelin to get back together.
But what I need...
What weneed is to stop Jack.
Big difference.
But here's the deal.
We both got to sign off on it.
This might be our only shot,
and if he even catches a whiff
that this is a scam,
he's off into the wind.
Exactly.
And how do you think he's not
gonna know something's up?
Because you're gonna be
so damn sincere.
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
Why me?
Because you've always been
in his corner, all right?
You're his go-to guy.
Sam, if you reach out,
he'll come.
If I do it, after what happened
to Mom, I could lose it.
I will lose it.
Eremiel, open the portal.
No can do, my brother.
Heaven is now closed.
No, it's not.
I was just there.
I'm sorry.
I said that wrong.
Heaven is closed to you.
Orders.
Eremiel.
I am going to Heaven.
That's what everyone thinks.
Ohh!
It's working, Jack.
Really, Eremiel?
Huh!
Castiel! Good news.
I found Jack.
Cass! Look!
I'm making angels.
Yes, you, uh...
Dumah. A word?
Now!
I-I don't think
this is gonna work.
One way to find out.
Jack.
I hope you can hear this.
Some things...
Some things,
some bad things happened.
But we're family.
We're your family.
A-And bad things
happen in families.
...bad things happen
in families.
But we, uh... We, uh...
We want to talk with you.
That's how we can all...
get through this.
That's how we can all
move forward.
I know what you're doing.
You're using Jack to
solidify your hold on Heaven.
Someone has loose lips.
You're establishing
a reign of terror,
beating humans into submission,
stripping Heaven of its mercy.
Oh, Heaven never really
had any mercy, Castiel.
You know that.
I am savingHeaven.
I am saving our kind.
I am saving the world.
Jack, we want...
We needto see you.
Our mother would want it.
Yourmother would want it.
Your mother would want it.
I can't control Jack.
You've seen his strength.
He's strong, yes,
but still a child
and without a soul to guide him.
I can guide him.
Jack, we just want things
to be the way they were.
We just want things
Are you hearing this? Are you hearing this?
I am.
I'm getting Jack out of here.
No... you're not.
You really want
this fight, Dumah?
Fight? I'm holding
the high cards here.
Ma and Pa Winchester,
they're living in
their own personal Heaven.
One snap of these fingers,
and all of that ends.
Jack? Jack!
Guess he didn't hear.
I heard.
And I was so glad.
I didn't think
I'd ever see you again.
I've been working with the
angels to purify the world.
Oh, and making angels.
Yeah. I make angels.
But... I really
missed you guys.
Yeah. Us too.
Right, Sammy?
Tell Jack how, uh...
How we want to clear things up,
you know, between us.
I know... I know
things have been bad.
A-And, if it helps, I regret it.
The accident.
The... The accident?
What happened to Mary.
She kept talking about my soul,
t-that I didn't have a soul,
and she kept pushing.
Oh, so...
she madeyou do it.
No, it... it was me,
but I didn't want
this no-soul thing to
become an issue between us.
I guess I snapped.
Before I knew it,
it was all over.
"It" being the "accident."
I wish it didn't happen.
Yeah, Jack. So do we.
But...
w-we understand.
And we forgive you.
You know, for the,
uh, "accident."
That's what you want,
right, Jack?
I mean, you... you...
You'd like that?
I'd like for things to
go back the way they were.
I knew you'd understand.
So if we told you
that we were close
to being able to fix your soul,
we just need to keep you safe
until everything is ready,
you... you'd be okay with that?
"Safe"?
What do you mean?
Well, you could hurt
other people.
Have another, uh, accident.
Oh.
We... We want to
keep you safe, Jack.
That also means we... we have to
keep you safe from yourself.
You know,
just so nobody else gets hurt,
just until we get you better.
Well, there she is.
It's actually
kind of comfortable.
Uh, and its best feature
is that it's warded,
so it keeps your powers
below the meltdown level.
Yeah, so you
can't hurt anyone...
and n-nobody can hurt you.
I understand.
So, uh...
Okay.
Um, do I just...
Just hop on in.
Hm. Not bad.
Hey. Told ya.
How long before I can come out?
Not too long.
Jack, we got this.
Okay.
Are you guys still there?
Sam?!
Dean?!
Sam?
Dean? You still there?
So what do we do now?
Just... go on with Jack
locked up in there forever?
If we have to.
I don't know if I can do that.
I tell you what. This stuff
Ketch left, it's not bad.
You know, I never thought it
would end like this with Jack.
Sammy, we knew
from the beginning
it was a long shot with him.
Yeah.
Yeah, but long shots
are kind of our thing.
Guys?
I don't think I like this!
Look at you, buddy.
Ahh.
You got played, man.
Uh, I got to hand it
to the Winchesters.
They still got game.
They... They said
I should trust them.
And you believed that crap?
Buddy, buddy, trust
is a two-way street, man.
If they trusted you,
why did they lock you up?
You, my friend, are screwed.
Sam. Dean.
There's news.
Dumah was manipulating Jack
into doing those things.
She told him
it would please you.
Oh, so now it's ourfault?
I'm just saying it's urgent
that we find him and tell him.
Cass, he's here.
What?
He's locked up, safe.
He's in the Ma'lak box.
No!
And that's where
he's gonna stay.
Am I getting through to you?
Did they tell you the specifics
of their "cure"?
Are you getting a new soul?
Does it have a factory warranty?
Why didn't they tell you
how much time it would take?
I don't know.
You don't know
because you, my friend,
are naive, clueless, trusting.
And you know what?
They suckered you.
"Why," you may ask?
Okay.
One, 'cause you're
no longer useful to them.
And, two, you killed
their mother.
Okay? There's no
coming back from that.
So thisis it,
for the rest of time.
I'm sorry. Is that it?
You have to do way better
than that, buddy.
Even after hearing what I said,
you want to keep Jack sealed
in a living death?
He agreed to it.
Because deep down,
I think he knows it's best.
No. You're doing what Dumah...
You are manipulating him.
Bring it.
Cass.
What? You just want
to forget about him?
I wish I could forget about him!
After what he did?
And you know what he can do.
This is our only play.
Jack.