I am a Winchester!
Jack, no!
I'm me again.
Jack, you have your powers back?
I think so.
And your soul?
You want to know
how much of my soul
I had to burn off
to kill Michael.
Yes.
I don't know.
Nick. He's trying
to resurrect Lucifer.
I can get us to him.
But I need to use my powers.
Do it.
Stop!
Jack, stop.
What are you doing?
- Where's Nick?
- It's over.
- What about Mom?
- She's fine.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Nick, he was a bad person,
a killer. He deserved it.
Not like that.
- Leave me alone!
- Please. Just...
- Jack!
Something's wrong.
- Listen to me!
- Leave me alone!
Mary?
- Yo, Mom!
- Mom!
Jack?
Mom?
- Hey, Jack?
- Jack?
Jack?
Yo, anybody here?
Mom?
Jack?
Nothing.
They probably just stopped
for a bite on the way back.
You know how Mom gets
after a Hunt.
Yeah. True that.
Well, hey, here's to another
miraculous Sam Winchester
survival.
Got to say, man, if Jack
hadn't have healed you...
You know, lately, it feels like
we'd be up the creek
without that kid.
Yep. I mean, first,
he takes care of Michael
and then... Nick.
Kind of sounds like you're
bummed about it.
No. A "get out of
jail free" card?
I'll take that.
Gonna try Mom?
Yeah.
Looks like they left in a hurry.
Try Jack.
...Captions by VITAC...
www.vitac.com
Captions paid for by
Warner Bros. Television
- Yeah. Thanks.
- Okay. All right, thanks.
What did Jody say?
She hasn't heard anything.
You?
Nada. Left voicemails for
Donna, Charlie, Bobby.
- Rowena?
- Yeah.
Just got off the phone with her.
She says she has a spell
that might track them down.
- Okay, well, that's good.
- Yeah.
Hey, Cass.
Castiel:
I got your message.
Nick was trying
to raise Lucifer?
- Yeah.
- Where is he now?
I don't, uh...
Kid said he took care of him.
So, right now, we're just
trying to find Jack and Mom.
- Are they together?
- Yeah.
A-Alone?
Y-Yeah.
W-Why do you...
Yes, Cass, they were
together, alone.
What's he saying?
I don't...
Cass?
I, um...
If you have something to
tell us, now's the time.
I saw Jack. He... He...
He did something
when I got home with Sam.
I went to check on him,
and Felix was sick.
- Felix? You mean the snake?
- Yes.
Jack used his powers.
He killed the snake.
I think Jack
considered it a mercy.
I-I was gonna tell you, but...
You just wanted to wait until
we were already freaked out.
I'm sorry.
I don't think
Jack is well, Dean.
Dean?
- What?
- He said that Jack
went all Kevorkian on his snake.
- Why?
- I don't know. Who cares.
It's a snake.
Right now,
we've got to find them.
I think I have an idea.
This will work?
As long as Jack's battery's
running, probably.
There we go.
Look.
Wait. Is that...?
Nepal?
Wait a second.
W-Where'd he go?
There.
Lima, Peru.
Jack's flying.
Paris, France.
What the hell is he doing?
Jack:
You knew my mother.
I was there when you were born.
Stop!
Jack, what you did
was... amazing.
Jack, please!
Just... Listen to me!
Leave me alone!
Nick?
Mm. Guess again.
"Hello, Son."
No. That's not possible.
You're...
Dead?
All right.
You got me.
I'm not Nick.
I'm not Lucifer.
I'm you.
What?
Yeah. I'm your, you know,
subconscious or whatever.
Y-You whipped me up to
help you figure this out.
Whatever you are...
I don't want your help.
Actually, you do.
So I'm gonna give you a little
piece of advice, bud,
how you can wiggle out of
this little pickle you're in.
You don't.
You won't.
You can't.
All right?
Buddy, you killed
Mary Winchester.
You cannot come back from that,
and you know it.
All right? You've been
flapping your wings all around,
trying to run away
from what you did,
and where'd you wind up?
Right here, right back
to the scene of the crime.
- No.
- Yeah.
Yeah, because somewhere
inside, you realize
that the sooner you accept it,
the easier it'll be.
No, it's...
It was an accident.
Okay.
Tell Sam and Dean that.
I'm sure they'll understand.
It's not like family
isn't everything to them.
- Shut up.
- No, I'm serious.
Pull out your cellphone
right now and call them.
Shut up!
All right.
Cass is gonna meet us there.
You know, maybe Jack
was wrong, you know?
I mean, maybe
Nick pulled it off,
maybe Lucifer's back,
and he took them both.
And... And Jack... I mean...
he must have thought he was
helping, you know, being kind.
What?
With... Felix.
Wait. Really?
With the snake?
I'm just saying, Dean.
I'm trying to understand
Jack without a soul.
We don't know that
he doesn't have a soul!
Okay, I don't want to...
Let's...
Let's just not talk
about it, all right?
Let's just find Mom.
We'll find Jack.
We'll figure it all out.
All right.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
You look inside.
I'll take around back.
Jack?
Mom?!
Dean!
Dean?
Dean.
In the cabin, it's... it's...
Well, that was a close one.
Not that close.
I counted wrong.
I thought there were only
two vamps in the basement.
I handled the third one.
Yes, you certainly did.
Mmm.
You know, I'm no expert,
but I think most humans
would bandage an open wound
before stopping to eat.
It's a scratch.
Still...
I could heal you.
If you'll let me.
I'm... I'm okay.
Are you still afraid of me?
Maybe a little.
I haven't been back that long.
Angels are real.
Angels are friends.
Angels can heal you
with a wave of a glowy hand.
I... It's all pretty new still.
We should get back.
Boys will be waiting.
I know you know this, Mary,
but, um...
Sam and Dean... they're...
They're glad to have you back.
Whatever you still
have to deal with
and however long it takes,
you should know they're happy.
I mean, finally, they don't
have to be so, um...
so alone.
Castiel.
They were never alone.
Dean, if Jack did that...
Hey, we don't know
what happened, okay?
I mean, we don't know
what Nick did.
He probably deserved it.
Dean, look. No one wanted
Nick dead more than I did,
but... I mean, that...
Cass.
Is that Nick?
Yeah.
We looked around.
No sign of Jack or Mom.
There's a, um, blast site
behind the house.
It looks angelic,
just... bigger.
Might have been Lucifer.
Nick was trying
to bring him back.
- Yeah, but Jack said...
- Who cares what Jack said?
We don't know what happened!
But I swear, if he did
something to her, if she is...
Then you're dead to me.
- Dean.
- No, he knew.
He knew something
was wrong with the kid.
He knew it,
and he didn't tell us!
He didn't even tell us!
Castiel:
I was scared.
I believed in Jack
for so long, I...
I believed that he was...
He was good.
I... I knew that he would be
good for the world.
And he was good for us.
My faith in him,
it... it never wavered,
and then I-I saw what he did.
It wasn't malice.
It wasn't evil.
It was like Jack saw a problem,
and in his mind, he just
solved it with that snake.
The snake?!
What he did wasn't bad.
It was the absence of good.
And I saw that in him.
But we were a family,
and I didn't want to lose that,
so I thought I could...
fix it on my own.
Felt like it was
my responsibility.
So I left.
And I didn't tell you.
If I could go back and just...
Just talk to him right
then and there, I would.
But I can't, Dean.
I failed you.
And I failed Jack.
And I failed...
No, no. Don't even say it.
Don't even say her name.
Dean.
Who is it?
Rowena.
Hey.
Hello, Samuel.
I did what you asked.
I used scrying magic on the boy,
tried to find him.
But his energy,
it's too unstable.
It was like looking at the sun.
And Mom?
Say it!
I don't know what happened
or where she is...
but I can tell you
with certainty...
Mary Winchester
is no longer on this Earth.
So, what do we do?
What do we always do
when we lose one of our own?
We fight.
We fight to bring them back.
How?
Billie?
Rowena. She's got
the Book of the Damned.
She's resurrected herself
more times than we can count.
How? We don't even know
where your mother is.
Then go to heaven and find her!
Tell Rowena we're on our way.
"Magice Necromantiorum."
That was fast.
Oh, boy.
Hello, Rowena.
Are you... Are you well?
Sam and Dean
are looking for you.
I-I could call them.
No!
I need help.
I need magic.
Why?
I killed Mary.
I-It was an accident.
I-I didn't mean to.
I just... I just wanted her
to be quiet.
I just wanted her gone,
but only for a second.
And I just..
I thought it.
It all happened so fast.
I need to undo it.
You need to help me undo it.
I, uh...
The magic I've used on myself,
my... my little
subdermal sachets...
They only work as fail-safes.
They have to be prepared
in advance, Jack.
Um...
What about the book?
The book. Yes. Yes.
The... The book.
I mean, there...
There is a spell.
Agnes, the witch
who created the Book,
was a prisoner for years.
She was obsessed
with breaking curses.
What is death
but the ultimate curse?
In captivity, her friends,
her only companions
starved and perished,
so she developed a spell
to bring them back...
The "Magice
Necromantiorum."
Okay.
What will we need?
Oh, well, um...
the Necromantiorum
requires enormous power.
The ingredients are
relatively simple.
Um, nothing you wouldn't have...
handy in the bunker.
Rowena?!
Open up!
You've been stalling me...
- Rowena?!
- ...tricking me!
Just talk to them, Jack.
They're your kin.
Dean:
Come on! Open up!
Hello?
Naomi.
- Jack!
- Come on.
- Okay.
- Outward position.
- Right. Index.
- Index finger.
- Flip.
- Thumb.
No, keep your finger over there.
- All right.
- Thumb.
And then switch it all around.
There you go.
Right.
Outward position.
Index, flip...
That's okay.
That one was close.
That's enough for today.
You're doing great.
It's not easy.
When we get Dean back,
he's gonna kill me for this.
For what?
- Hey.
How's his training coming along?
He's got heart.
He'll get there.
I feel bad. I've been so busy
looking for Dean...
Sam, everyone here understands
what you've been doing
and what you've been
putting yourself through.
Yeah, I know, but Jack's been through
a lot... you know, losing his powers.
And I haven't really
been there for him.
Sorry, Mom. I don't mean
to lay all this on you.
No. Are you kidding?
It's nice knowing
I'm not the only one...
with parental guilt.
How much did the two of you
go through
when I wasn't there for you?
And even when Amara brought me
back and I got a second chance,
things got complicated.
I got complicated.
Mom.
No, I'm just saying...
parenting is always a struggle.
You always feel like
you're failing,
but then you look at them,
and somehow, they're amazing.
And somehow,
they're literally...
...the bravest...
kindest...
...most heroic men
on the planet.
Kids.
They'll always surprise you.
Well, how the hell are we
supposed to keep up with Jack
when he's got wings, huh?!
And now he's got Rowena?
He's got the Book of the Damned?
I don't know what to do.
I don't even know where to go!
Cass.
Cass should have told us.
As soon as he saw Jack
go all Dahmer
on his stupid freakin' snake,
he should have told us.
Dean, it wasn't just Cass.
It wasn't.
We knew Jack was dangerous.
We always knew.
Long before he killed Michael.
You more than anyone.
I mean, from the very
beginning, you knew.
But, you know, we fell for him
'cause he had a good heart
and a good soul.
Then he didn't.
And that's on me, too,
by the way.
I mean, I'm the one who made
the call to bring him back.
He didn't ask for that.
I decided for him.
And you warned me.
No, you didn't know, okay?
We didn't know.
Exactly.
But...
He had become our family.
You know, after Maggie
and the other Hunters died...
I just left.
Just...
dumped Jack on Cass and left.
I knew. I mean,
I knew something...
was gonna...
I just didn't know it'd be this.
I did it, too.
When I talked to Donatello
about Jack,
he said he was good
as far as he could tell.
But then he talked
about how powerful Jack was
and that he could never
really be sure.
And it was a warning.
I just couldn't see it.
Are you done yet?
I said they were
simple ingredients,
but there are a lot of them,
and they need to be
compounded precisely.
You know, I could have
fought you back at my flat.
I'm not saying I would have won,
but I could have tried.
I didn't because
you want the same thing
the boys want, that I want.
No offense, buddy,
but this is just so sad.
Jack?
Bringing the witch bitch into
your desperate little plan?
Why? So you can "make things
right" with the Winchesters?
You stop it.
Excuse me?
It's... It's fine.
Um...
Just...
What do you want?
Forgiveness?
You want gratitude for
bringing Mommy back?
Why? So you can call
this dump home again?
So you can ease your guilt?
But you don't have guilt
anymore, do you, Jack?
Admit it.
You don't feel anything anymore.
Shut up.
Are you okay?
Keep working.
You know this torment
that you're feeling right now?
It's just a reflex.
It's just a habit, man.
It's... It's an echo
from when you actually
could feel something,
when it mattered.
- Mnh-mnh.
- But you know what?
The sooner you give up
this little fantasy,
the sooner this phantom pain
can go away.
- No. Shut up.
- Mnh-mnh. Not gonna.
And you know what, Jack?
It's not gonna work.
You know it's not gonna work.
You know it.
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Are you done yet?
Are you done?!
Yes.
We have everything we need.
All but the last thing.
The last thing.
Her body.
Naomi.
I'm still here,
and I'm not going anywhere,
not until I have a word
with you.
Dumah.
- Castiel.
- Where's Naomi?
Well, I'd tell you
it's none of your business,
but you already know
it's none of your business.
Why are you here?
I'm looking for someone.
Mary Winchester?
If that's why you're here,
then you should leave now.
Why? There may be a way
to bring her back.
Why would you want to do that?
Because she's gone.
She is at peace.
You know, she died painlessly.
Instantly. Completely.
She's in Heaven,
a special Heaven.
Mary Winchester is complete.
You and the Winchesters
may not be.
But she is.
Jack?
I brought you
to the right place.
We have the right ingredients.
Where's the body, Jack?
- We can do this.
- That's...
You will make it work!
It won't. I can't.
Then I'll do it myself.
You're in no condition.
Jack, a cardinal rule
of magic...
Disposition affects execution,
and you are spinning!
Whatever you bring back,
it won't be her.
Then help me!
I won't.
Ugh!
Rowena, hey.
We just left your place.
Well, I'm back!
Listen. Jack is using magic
to try to bring your mom back.
- Can he do that?
- There's no body.
And your boy, he snapped.
He's desperate.
Confused, angry.
You have to try to stop him.
- Why?
- Necromancy is a delicate art.
It's unpredictable
under ideal circumstances.
In his state,
oh, I fear your boy
will bring back
something terrible.
Id quod mortuum, nunc oriatur.
Hoc quod cecidit,
nunc revertatur.
Id quod mortuum, nunc oriatur.
Hoc quod cecidit,
nunc revertatur.
Orimini.
Ori...
mini.
What the hell?
- What are you doing?
- The engine just stopped.
Orimini.
Orimini!
Jack.
It didn't work.
No, no. No.
Mom? Mom.
Well, I warned you.
It's worse...
Trying and failing.
There's no going back.
You realize that now.
Cass, Sam, Dean...
they're never gonna
trust you again.
And you know what that means.
What?
You can never trust them.
Cass.
She's in Heaven.
And she's at peace.
So Naomi told you, huh?
Dumah, actually.
So, what? Are you just gonna
take her word for it?
No.
No, she let me in.
I saw your mother's Heaven,
and she is happy.
She's with John,
and there's no sorrow.
There's no guilt.
Just joy.
I talked to Rowena.
Um, she said
she thinks that what
Jack brought back...
He just brought back a shell.
A body, you know.
That it was empty.
Just a...
a replica.
"Incapable of holding life."
So, what are we
supposed to do now?
What we always do.