Sammy, it's me.
I don't remember most
of what Michael did
because I was underwater,
drowning...
and that I remember.
I felt every second
of it.
Why would Michael
give up his vessel like that?
I don't know.
- Ghosts 101.
- Ghost possession.
Definitely a ghost.
Somebody's spirit
can attach itself
to an object
or a bunch of objects.
Everything has a weakness.
They hate
iron and salt.
Whatever happens,
you stay inside this circle.
- Where's the spear?!
- So Michael wants the spear
because he knows
it can hurt him.
You're no different
than him.
I am nothing like him.
Do you
have unwanted gold
just lying around the house,
collecting dust?
Why not turn that gold
into cash?
Here at Diamond Dave's,
you can have cash
in your hands today.
We'll take anything
you want to sell us.
When Aunt Gloria
passed away,
she left me so much jewelry,
I didn't know what to do.
That's when I called
Diamond Dave.
If it's gold,
it's cash in your hands.
You're watching Shocker TV.
This week on Shocker,
it's gonna be a blood bath.
We've got slicing and dicing.
We've got scream queens
and killing machines,
24 hours a day, all week long.
Time to slice and dice.
Whoa.
Mezco 15" Mega-Scale Panthro.
So handsome.
So angry.
Hey, Sam.
Stuart,
what did you do?
I...
Uh, nothing.
Really?
Because according to Yelp
and this awesome,
one-star review we just got,
you screamed at a customer
and called him a, quote,
"mongoloid Tribble
in a robotic exoskeleton
built by Tony Stark's
inbred third cousin."
Which is not cool,
and weirdly,
creepily specific.
That --
He said I couldn't
beat up Superman.
Okay. Again,
Superman is not real.
Okay.
That's not the point.
And I have seen you
get winded eating a taco.
Okay, that doesn't matter.
If I had kryptonite gloves,
I could beat up Superman.
Anyone could.
That's science, Sam.
Look, I --
I like that you care --
really, really care
about this stuff,
but we need every customer
we can get, okay?
So just chill
a little, please.
Yeah, um...
Okay.
I'm sorry, Sam. I just --
I just get spun out sometimes.
I know.
Coming to game night?
Of course.
I'll see you there.
Yeah, well,
all I'm hearing is excuses.
Okay, look, I don't
care about traffic, okay?!
It has been
over 30 minutes, so --
Hello?!
Free pizza!
The heck?
H-How did you...
? Supernatural 14x04 ?
Mint Condition
Original Air Date on November 1,
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
...brought them back --
back from Hell, again.
It Lives Again."
And now back to
"Hatchet Man: All Saints' Day."
There will be no
further interruptions.
? I get electrified ?
Time to slice and dice.
? You've got the power ?
? When you turn off the juice ?
? My circuits overload ?
? When your body lives ?
Son of a bitch.
? You're electrified ?
Hey, this area's
closed off.
I-I said beat it, buddy.
Time to slice and dice.
Yo.
- Hey.
- What?
Uh, what you doing?
Horror marathon
on Shocker.
Just made my way
through the "Halloweens"
and now I'm about to --
Oh, wow.
What?
Oh, yes, I shaved.
I mean, it's so smooth.
It's like a...
dolphin's belly.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, um...
I wanted to check up on you.
You doing okay?
I mean, y-you haven't really
come out of your room
in almost a week.
Well, since when is "okay"
a part of this job, huh?
Yeah, Cass, is, you know,
showing Jack the ropes
and Dark Kaia and her spear
are in the wind
and we have no clue
where Michael is
or what he's up to.
And, not that
I'm complaining,
but...
the house is full
of strangers, so...
So your plan is
to just lay in here,
watching "Hatchet Man" movies,
seriously?
"All Saints' Day"
is a classic.
Time to slice and dice.
- Oh, is it?
- What do you care?
You don't even like
scary movies.
Well, yeah, Dean,
our life is a scary movie.
Exactly.
I like it when they run.
All right, well,
I hate to disturb your marathon,
but I think
I found us a case.
More Michael monsters?
No.
Killer toy.
What kind of toy?
And then the thing
freakin' jumped me!
I mean, It wouldn't stop!
It was just over and over.
Just...
Panthro kicked my ass.
ThunderCats?
Seriously?
Yeah.
But, I mean,
you got your pizza,
at least eight more
of these movies,
so I'll just
leave you to it,
and I'll get one
of the other guys to --
Oh, hell no.
Hell no.
No.
Panthro is mine.
I wonder if we're talking,
like, one toy gone bad
or if it's like
a whole crew,
you know,
like Puppet Master-style.
Do you actually want there
to be more than one?
I don't know,
just...
- Boo!
Aah.
Still not a fan
of Halloween, huh?
Nope.
So lame.
Happy Halloween.
Hey, I can help you guys
in just a second.
Hm, she's like
your twin.
What? What are you
talking about?
Her -- soft, delicate features,
luxurious hair.
She's like
your Wonder Twin.
Yeah.
All right, okay.
Well, if that's me,
then, uh...
that's you over there.
- That guy?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we have zero in common.
Hatchet Man.
No way. Sam.
Check it out.
It's David freakin' Yaeger.
Yeah.
Press the button.
Hm?
Time to slice and dice.
Oh, dude.
We all do bad things sometimes.
Trick or Treat!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Dude.
- I need this.
- How much?
Not for sale.
Hatchet Man's a classic.
Yeah.
Nothing in common.
Okay, what can
I help you guys with?
Funko Pops,
Magic cards...?
Uh, Stuart Blake --
Vintage Hot Wheels.
I'm sorry.
Uh, were you getting
helped by Stuart
with vintage Hot Wheels,
or...
No, sorry.
Um, my name is Ian Gillan,
and this is...
I'm Ritchie Blackmore.
We're with Campbell & Sons
Insurance.
We heard about Stuart's
little incident with the toy,
and, uh, we're hoping
to speak to him.
Well, he's at home
healing up.
Well, we went
to his place,
and his roommate said
he had moved out.
Kicked out, actually.
Right.
They had a fight.
Over...?
"Fist of
the North Star."
Stuart said that
the dubbed version was better,
but --
You know what, forget it.
Um, I like Stuart,
but he's an acquired taste.
Sounds like a guy
who could make a lot of enemies.
I mean, not real ones.
Maybe online --
He trolls everything.
Okay, uh...
where can we find Stuart now?
He's at his mom's house.
Of course he is.
Thanks.
Stewie will be up
in just a minute.
Thanks.
I can't believe you had her
make us apple cider.
She offered.
No! No!
You stupid, dumb --
That's not how you play
the...
Game over!
I'm done! Done!
Who are you?
Uh, we're from
Campbell & Sons Insurance,
and --
- What are you doing down there?
Fortnite.
Hm.
It's a video game.
It's the video game.
Yeah, well,
I'm a Zelda for life, so...
What, are you burning sage
down there?
So...?
I-I dated this goth chick.
Like, super hot.
Met online, and --
and she was into Wicca.
Said that burning sage
was, like, good luck
or some crap like that.
Hmm.
So, you're not together
anymore?
No.
I broke it off
before we could MIRL.
You know, I mean, who needs
goth-girl drama, am I right?
- Merle?
- Uh, M-I-R-L.
"Meet in real life."
Why do you know
what that means?
Stuart, we're here
to ask about the attack
you reported
with the toy --
I made it up.
You what?
The whole thing.
I lied.
But the video...
That was fake.
I didn't expect it to go viral,
but it did,
and, uh...I just...
I fell.
Hm.
'Cause the hospital report said
that you had marks
on your face, your legs,
your back,
and your...
genitals.
That's not a slip
and fall.
Well, I don't see why
an insurance company
would care, you know?
And I-I think it's time
for you to leave.
- Okay, but --
- Now.
Wow.
Lady-you wasn't kidding.
That guy's a piece of work.
Well, whatever happened
was not an accident.
Okay, but, uh...
Big Bang in there,
not a great liar.
No.
So, what are we thinking?
Spell?
Well, his girlfriend
was into Wicca.
Wicca doesn't always
mean witch.
Except when it does.
All right, let's wait
till they leave,
check out the house
for hex bags.
Deal.
Yeah, find some
lamb's blood.
Right, exactly.
All right, good.
Stay safe.
All good?
Yeah, it was Riley.
He'll be fine.
I don't know who Riley is,
but cool.
Happy Halloween!
So, seriously, what is your deal
with Halloween?
I don't like it.
Yeah, but why don't
you like it? Hmm?
And don't give me
that, like,
"Oh, every day is Halloween
for us" crap, okay?
Because, one,
it ain't.
We don't eat
that much candy.
Two, you've had this hate on
for years.
So...?
Mom's on the move.
All right,
what about our guy?
You know, I think I know
why Stuart changed his story.
Uh, the comments on his video
are all pretty brutal.
People are calling him a liar,
a loser, "ThunderSpaz,"
Snarf's love child,
Panthro's bi...
- Rhymes with "itch"?
- Yep.
Got to love the Internet,
where everyone can be a dick.
Help me!
Help me! Help!
Stay with him.
Okay, uh...
Hang in there. Hey, wait.
We'll get you help.
My poor baby.
Yeah, it was touch and go
there for a while,
but, uh, doctors say
he's gonna be all right.
I'm just grateful
you showed up.
I...
Thank you.
You saved his life.
Oh, I-I should
run back home,
get -- get Stewie
his favorite pillow.
Actually,
you know what? Um...
It's probably better
if you just stay here.
Yeah, just until he wakes up,
you know?
Yeah, of course.
You're -- You're right.
I'm just all flustered.
It's okay.
Everything's fine.
Everything is not fine.
Yeah. My first clue was
the flying chainsaw.
While you were waiting
for the ambulance,
I did a quick sweep
for hex bags, nothing,
but then I pulled out EMF,
went freakin' crazy.
- So it's a ghost.
- Yeah.
Hey, we got to
figure out a way
to keep mom here
while we clear the house.
You know, I don't get
why a ghost would be
gunning for Stuart.
Murder,
grave robbery,
stole his favorite
Pok?mon --
I mean, take your pick.
Yeah.
All right,
you stay here with them.
I'll go check the house,
ask around,
see if anybody --
- Got dead lately?
- Yeah.
- All right.
GI Lab, 6-2-6-7.
Nice, Sam.
Smooth.
What the hell?
Now back
to our feature.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Are you insane?!
They will never understand
that it was an accident.
- Hey.
What are you
doing here?
Just keeping an eye
on Stuart.
He must have
awesome insurance.
Super-awesome.
Yeah.
Trick or treat?
He's still out.
Yeah, the nurse told me.
Babs went out for
a quick bite.
Figured
I'd stick around.
I want to be here
when he wakes up.
He's kind of
my best friend.
Is that right?
Look, I...
I know Stuart has his stuff,
but we all do.
And me and my dad don't
get along so great,
and whenever we --
we really have it out,
Stuart lets me
crash at his place.
No questions asked.
We just eat pizza
and watch movies.
It's...
Zen.
Sounds like
a good friend.
Yeah, but now,
when his mom called,
said someone a-attacked him
with a chainsaw?
Looks like.
Happy Halloween, huh?
Oh, I got to get
out of here.
Cool.
"All Saints' Day Three."
Totally...
Time to
slice and dice!
Like,
creeping me out to the max.
Trick or treat.
Time to slice and dice.
Never gets old.
You know, a lot of people
don't like this one,
but it's actually
my favorite.
I mean, sure.
There's no way a hospital would
ever be that empty.
but that's over-thinking it.
- I don't know.
I've been to a lot of hospitals
at night.
Trust me,
they get pretty empty.
Okay, so,
"All Saints' Day Three" --
That's my top pick.
What about you?
I mean, I like Five,
right --
"Search for
David Yaeger"?
'Cause it's weird,
but it's bloody.
- So bloody.
- Yeah.
In the best way.
But, uh...
I got to go
with number four.
- "Hatchet Man Lives"?
- Yeah.
Nice choice.
"Killed in a prank
gone wrong..."
"Mechanic David Yaeger
comes back every year
on the day after Halloween.
On All Saints' Day,
Hatchet Man takes his revenge!"
You really know
your A.S.D.
Yeah, well...
growing up,
it was, uh...
It was always nice to check out
once in a while.
I like to watch movies
where I know
the bad guy's gonna lose.
Knock knock.
Time to die.
Oh, um, we're, um --
we're closing.
Yeah, right. I-I just, uh...
Sorry.
I'm just here to, um...
Did you hear
about Stuart?
Yeah, his mom
told us what happened
when she dropped off his keys.
- Yeah.
I mean, what happened to him,
that's insane.
Yeah, yeah, so -- so I actually
have a few questions, um...
and they might be
a little different.
- Different like...
- Different like, uh...
Has anyone close to Stuart
died recently?
You're an insurance dude,
right?
Yeah, yeah, and --
and we wouldn't normally
ask these kinds of questions,
but it's a special
circumstance, and...
Well, I mean...
Jordan.
Jordan?
Yeah, he owned the store.
He taught Stuart,
Dirk, and I
everything we know
about comics and games.
He was like our own personal
Willy Wonka.
Huh.
Sounds like a great guy.
He was.
Cancer sucks, you know?
Yeah.
So, who owns
the place now?
Me and Dirk.
Jordan left it to us.
But not Stuart?
Stuart worked here,
but Jordan fired him twice.
He kept catching
Stuart stealing,
and to Jordan,
this place was his life,
you know?
And you hired
Stuart back?
He's my friend.
Right.
Okay, uh...
Where is Jordan buried?
Nowhere.
He was cremated.
Oh, um, right.
Sure, uh, excuse me.
I just have to, uh...
What's that?
Nothing.
It's a, um...
carbon monoxide detector.
Wh-- Is that --
Is that bad?
Yeah, yep.
Pretty bad.
Um...
You know what?
Uh, you should leave now.
- What? No.
- Okay, listen to me.
This is weird,
but I think you're in danger --
Samantha?
Samantha!
Hey!
Hey, are you okay?
No?
What just happened?
I think, uh...
I think a ghost --
A ghost?
Yes, um... All right.
Listen to me.
Ghosts are real,
and they can possess things --
uh, people,
toys, chainsaws,
and, apparently,
life-size figurines.
You are not from
an insurance company, are you?
N-Not exactly.
Listen,
I-I-I'm not sure,
but I think the ghost of Jordan
is trying to kill Stuart.
Wait, what?
Did he hurt you?
No, he just --
He shoved me out of the way,
and then he bolted.
It's locked.
Where are the keys?
Hatchet Man or whatever
took them.
- You sure?
-I --
I was pretty busy
screaming,
but, yeah, I'm sure.
Is this expensive?
What?
- No, don't!
- Eugh!
Yeah,
it's shatter-proof glass.
Jordan's pretty serious
about thieves.
The aerobics instructor
in the giant mixer.
Right, and then the kids
the next morning are
at the rec center,
they're all eating breakfast,
and the one finds a tooth
with all the stringy bits
still hooked onto it.
Oh, come on.
I mean,
forget Freddy and Jason.
That's top-10 horror-movie kill
right there.
Top-five, even.
Oh, and then,
the jock guy's face
when Hatchet Man shoves it into
the engine fan of that truck
and it just, like...
bbl-bbl-bbl-bbl-bbl-bbl...
Did you know that
they made the brain splatter
with saltwater taffy?
I did not know that.
Yeah.
That's pretty cool.
Excuse me.
Yeah, what's up, Sam?
We were right.
It's a ghost.
Guy's name was
Jordan MacNeel.
He used to own
the comic shop.
All right, so we going
to a graveyard or what?
No, no, no.
He was cremated.
And, um...
And what?
So, he possessed the
David Yaeger figure at the shop,
and I think he's coming
for Stuart.
Wait, wait, wait --
Are you telling me that --
that Hatchet Man David Yaeger
is coming here?
Uh, I mean, not --
not literally, but...
Hatchet Man is
coming here?
Trick or treat.
Hey, hey.
Look at that.
Hey, man!
Whoo!
David Yaeger!
Killer costume!
Come on, let's go.
Hey, trick or treat!
If ghosts are real,
does that mean vampires?
Yep.
- Witches?
- Uh-huh.
Werewolves?
Unless it's Godzilla,
it's real.
All right.
Get in.
But --
Now!
Now, listen to me.
Ghosts can't cross
the salt line, okay?
So whatever you hear,
whatever you see,
whatever happens,
stay inside.
Capiche?
What I don't get is,
why is Jordan going
after Stuart now?
It doesn't make
any sense.
Stuart's been
stealing.
- What?
- I mean, not cash,
just stuff that
he thought was cool.
And Stuart doesn't have
good impulse control.
I've been taking money
out of his checks
to make up for it,
but I guess...
a ghost wouldn't
know that.
Yeah, guess not.
Oh, come on.
Damn it.
Yeah.
It's a hardcore lock.
All right.
We got to get out of here.
Okay, how?
Do you have
cleaning supplies?
What the...
Aaah!
Help!
What's happening?
I got to get
out of here!
Hey!
Jordan, I --
I know you're trying
to kill Stuart,
but he's my friend.
He's our friend.
So if you want
to do this,
you're gonna have
to go through me!
Oh, crap.
Hey, Phil.
Hey, where are you?
Come on.
Oh, no.
Run. Run, girl.
I like it when they run.
Now, you see that?
You see that?
That's...
my favorite part.
Stop!
Leave me alone!
Enough talking.
More killing.
You kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
Ooh.
Right?
- She is so slow.
- Come on, man.
Somebody come
and help me please!
Where is everybody?
Ooh!
Run, girl! Run!
Mm!
You got to run, girl.
Come on, man.
My grandmother runs
faster than you.
Help! Somebody!
Anybody help me!
Where is everybody?!
Oh, God.
Jordan, please!
You're dead!
Get away from me!
We killed you.
You're dead!
We all do bad things
sometimes.
Press that button.
He would never catch me,
tell you that much.
No, this can't
be happening.
No. No!
You can't run
from Hatchet Man.
This isn't...
...real!
All right.
Pretty sure
this will work.
Where did you learn
how to do this?
I had a messed-up
childhood.
Okay.
Here goes.
Yep, all right.
Uh, get back.
Get down.
- Cool.           - Cool.
Told you to stay put.
You don't --
He's here.
Where?
Time to slice and dice.
Oh, hell.
David Yaeger was an honest man
making an honest living,
until one night,
when a practical joke...
turned deadly.
One day,
we're gonna have to answer
for the things
we did that night.
It was just a prank.
Now, David Yaeger is back
with his faithful hatchet
to get revenge on those
who took his life.
If the people responsible
for his death
weren't torn up about it...
they're going to be.
Time to slice
and dice.
In this dark, quiet hospital,
they can run, they can hide...
We killed you.
You're dead!
...but there's no escaping
the Hatchet Man.
Trick or treat.
No, this can't
be happening.
We all do bad things
sometimes.
"All Saints' Day III:
The Reckoning,"
coming soon
to a theater near you.
Pray for survival.
All right, look, man.
I know once you go Casper,
things can be a little --
well, a lot crazy.
The way I see it,
you got two options.
One, you let this go,
and you walk into the light.
Or, two...
I send you there.
Time to slice and dice.
I was kind of hoping
you'd say that.
Stay back!
I got this.
Problem is, the ghost is always
tied to an object.
Right? Its bones, something
that meant a lot to it in life.
Whatever that thing is,
the ghost is usually
stuck there, but Jordan,
he's been all over --
the shop, Stuart's house,
so how's he moving around?
- The key chain.
- What?
- It was Jordan's
and then Stuart closed up
the night he got attacked
and he brought
the shop keys home
and then his mom
brought them back after.
I mean, could that --
Does that make sense?
Yeah.
It does.
Come on.
We all do bad things sometimes.
I --
Sorry?
Dean! Key chain!
Come on,
come on, come on.
Here. Here.
Use this.
Ugh!
It's really sunk in deep!
Hurry up!
Time to slice
and Di...
Is it really over?
Just like that?
"Just like that"?
Yeah, you're --
You're all safe now,
even Stuart.
And Jordan,
is -- is he...
He's in a better place.
Thanks, man.
Hmm?
You, uh...
You got me out here
'cause you needed
to get me out of my funk
and get me a win,
and you did.
So...
thanks.
I got to admit,
it didn't go exactly like
I thought it would.
Hey, man. I just went toe-to-toe
with David freakin' Yaeger.
That was awesome.
Yeah, it wasn't really --
Don't ruin this for me.
Hey, Dean...
when we get back
to the bunker, man,
you got to stop hiding out
in your room.
I'm not hiding out.
And I get why
you're doing it.
I-I do.
But...
what happened
with Michael...
You said yes for me, for Jack,
for your family.
You did the right thing.
What happened after,
just because Michael
was wearing your face,
doesn't mean
any of this is on you.
I don't blame you.
No one blames you.
You got to try and stop
blaming yourself,
please.
I'm never gonna get
over it, okay?
I'm just not.
But you're right --
I'm not doing
anybody any good
by just staying couped up
in my room,
so...whatever you need,
I'm there.
All right, chief?
All right.
Well, that is it.
Halloween is
officially over.
Good.
Okay, seriously, why?
Why do you hate Halloween?
What is it?
Was it the time that I --
I ate all your Halloween candy?
- No.
- Was it something Dad did?
No, dude, you don't
want to know.
No, I really do.
Really.
What?
All right.
Remember Andrea Howell?
No.
When I was in sixth grade,
we were living in Bismark.
I had a huge crush on her.
Aww, that's adorable.
Continue.
So, she invited me
to her Halloween party.
I said yes,
and I-I went over,
and at first, everything
was great, um...
And then we started
to play games.
Spin the bottle?
B-Bobbing for apples.
Like I said,
I had a crush,
so the entire night,
my stomach was in knots,
and when it was my turn,
I-I bent down, and...
No.
...hurled.
Everywhere.
Lunch, dinner,
it all came up --
on Andrea, mostly.
Uh, people
ran and screamed,
and it was so bad.
That's great.
I ended up hiding out
in the woods
until you finally
came and got me.
So that's why
you hate Halloween.
- Yeah.
- Oh, come on, man.
You got to get over that.
That's -- I mean...
All right.
This is what we're gonna do.
Next year, we're doing Halloween
right, okay?
I'm thinking matching outfits
like, uh...
Batman and Robin.
No.
- Bert and Ernie.
- No.
- That's weird.
- Yes.
Uh...
Rocky and Bullwinkle.
Dean...
Shaggy and Scooby.
Why would we...
Turner and Hooch.
Ren and Stimpy.
Come on, now.
- Thelma and Louise.
- Thelma and --
We just put it in drive
and go.
What the...
Trick or treat.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man