Let's move.
I know this must be
so hard.
Without your grace,
without your powers.
I can't kill demons.
I can't find Dean and Michael.
I'm useless.
Cops just turned up
a pile of corpses in Duluth,
and their eyes
were burnt out.
So Michael?
It was like
he was experimenting.
Experimenting?
What for?
There are ways
to enhance your talents.
Nothing's working!
Do you propose we wage a war
on the humans?
This isn't just Michael
we're talking about.
It's Dean.
Sammy.
It's me.
It's just every time
I think about it, you know,
it's like a --
it's like a nightmare.
I mean, I can't eat.
I can't sleep.
It's always just there,
watching.
Dean, it's just a beard.
I've been a little busy
lately.
Yeah, well,
that's not an excuse.
You know, 'cause, uh,
"Duck Dynasty" called,
and they just --
they want it all back.
Some people say
I look good.
No. No, Sam.
No people say that.
Hey, hey.
You, uh --
Hey, if you're gonna
ask if I'm okay,
you don't have to.
All right.
It's just, uh,
you know,
you didn't talk a whole lot
on the ride here.
Look, Michael bailed,
all right?
I don't know how.
I don't know why.
He just --
He just cleared out.
And as far
as my memory goes,
I mean, everything
from the second I said yes
to the moment I walked
through those doors is blank,
so I'm good.
I'm just really, really happy
to be...
...home.
Yeah, there have been
a few changes made.
So, uh...
Yeah.
Not Michael anymore.
Right.
Chief told us.
Welcome back.
"Chief"?
Yeah, I-I asked them not
to call me that, but --
Dean?
Hey, kid.
Is it really you?
Yeah.
Dean.
Cass.
Sorry,
I wanted to be there,
but we figured that Michael
would sense my presence, so --
Sam told me.
Ain't no thing.
Where's Mary?
She and Bobby
stayed back in Duluth
to clean up the, uh --
uh, the situation.
Yeah, well,
speaking of cleanup,
I, uh...
I need a shower.
Mm.
Hey, y-y-you --
Still okay.
I promise.
Uh, how's Nick?
He's...
He's gone.
What?
Nick just --
He left a note,
said that he had
some personal business
to attend to,
and he hasn't -- he hasn't been
returning my calls.
He was
in a dark place.
Maybe he just
needed some time.
All right.
Yeah. Maybe.
Sam...
Dean --
how is he really?
I don't know.
Why would Michael just...
give up his vessel like that?
I don't know.
And why was...
Why was Michael
helping monsters?
Cass...
truth is...
we don't know anything.
? Supernatural 14x03 ?
The Scar
Original Air Date on October 25, 2018
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Yeah, I don't know
how I got it.
Well, what could hurt Michael
like that?
Whatever it was
must've been strong.
Right. So, Cass,
I'm gonna need you
to, uh, get in my head.
You know, do the whole
Vulcan-mind-meld thing.
'Cause if I can't remember
what happened,
I need you to drag it
out of me, okay?
W-Wait a second.
You sure about this?
Yeah.
I can handle it.
- Dean...
- Cass, come on.
Hit me.
Anything?
Dean, who was that?
Sam, any news?
Jody, hey, u-uh...
Yeah, uh, sorry.
- Uh...
- Hey, Jody.
I'm back.
Hey, Dean.
It is so good
to hear your voice.
Yeah, you, too.
Um, Jody, that's --
that's the good news.
What's up?
Um, you know the thing
that killed Kaia
in the Bad Place?
- Well, we think it's here.
- What?
Yeah, uh, any chance
you've noticed anything
rift-related over there?
A flare-up or,
um, uh, anything?
No, I -- No.
I have video surveillance
going down at the ferry.
Claire practically sits Shiva
down there.
There's been nothing.
How do you know?
Well, short version --
when Michael was possessing me,
he got hurt.
It left a scar --
uh, two deep gashes.
Stabby, prongy,
kind of like, um --
Like someone stabbed you
with a giant meat fork?
Yeah. Exactly.
How'd you know that?
You're leaving?
Kaia's killer
is in Sioux Falls.
And he, she, or it
can hurt Michael.
We just gotta
figure out how.
I'll get my things.
Uh, Jack, um...
that might not be
the best idea.
Michael's my enemy, too.
I fought him for months,
and Kaia --
I'm the one who brought her
into this.
I'm responsible
for what happened to her.
I want to help.
Yeah, well,
not gonna happen.
Because I'm human now?
Jack, maybe you just need
a little more --
Training?
I've been training
with Bobby.
C'mon, kid.
Look at you.
You're barely 100 pounds
soaking wet.
You know?
Wait. Jack.
Hey, I didn't mean...
I didn't mean
to be a dick.
Little help here!
Jules, what's going on?
Case I was working
in Wichita --
the missing teenagers,
dried-up husk bodies?
Yeah.
Turns out
it was a witch.
She was holding
the girls hostage,
and this...
is the only
survivor.
Took Broom-Hilda down
with that
witch-killing bullet
you gave me,
but soon as I did,
something went wrong.
Didn't even have time
to bury the body before --
Before what?
Lora, darling,
show them.
The witch
must've hexed her.
Looks like an aging spell.
Can you fix it?
I think so.
Cass?
Uh, this might
take a while.
You two, go.
Get to Sioux Falls before
the trail goes cold,
and I'll catch up when I'm done.
- No, no, I don't know.
Yeah, no, Cass is --
Cass is right.
He can handle this.
We need to hit the road.
Let's go.
Sam.
All right.
All right, yep.
Good work.
You're in a hurry.
Shouldn't I be?
If you're worried
about that girl,
- Cass has got it handled.
- Yeah, I know.
Well, then,
what's the problem?
Dean, we still have no idea
why Michael let you go
or where he is now
or what he wants.
Yeah, or who his favorite
Spice Girl is.
Come on, man.
This isn't a joke.
Something huge happened,
and you won't
really even talk about it.
But this whole Michael thing,
we need to deal with it.
Okay, I'm literally going 80
to deal with it.
How can I be running
from something
when I'm racing
towards it?
I don't know.
- Kind of your thing.
- Okay.
Okay, look,
I'm just saying...
You said you let Michael in,
then, bang,
you're back in a blink.
But for me...
you were gone for weeks.
I didn't know if you were alive.
I...
I just need you
to talk to me,
to slow down
so I can catch up.
Call Jody.
Let her know we're almost there.
Dean.
Oh, welcome home.
Thanks.
How'd you do it?
What, me versus some
assbag archangel --
who would you take?
- You, every time.
Hi.
Hey, I like it!
Uh, i-it's, uh...
How are you?
How are the girls?
Surprisingly good.
Alex is still at the hospital.
Patience is still in school.
Claire's still...
Claire.
I, uh...
I haven't been home
since I talked to you.
I may be avoiding her.
It's just, before I tell her
what's going on,
I need to --
You need to know
what's going on.
Yeah. That's it.
Yeah.
Okay, so here are
the locations
of the three bodies we found --
headless, by the way.
Human?
As far as I could tell,
yep.
Until I talked to you,
I thought we were hunting
a human, too,
maybe a serial killer.
It'd be the first one
in Sioux Falls since --
Well, since
Robert Leroy Anderson.
Yeah. Yeah, so, um...
So I figure this area
between the crime scenes,
it's the best place
to start looking
for whatever this is.
Should we wait
till, uh, daybreak?
Why?
No, let's go.
Yeah, uh --
- I can't find it.
- Find what?
The book.
It's got to be around here
somewhere.
She said to look
in the White Magic Lexicon.
Okay, um...
I-Is it this one?
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
Who's that?
It's a girl.
Lora.
She's, um --
She's been enchanted.
Like "Sleeping Beauty."
No. No, not like --
This aging spell, it's --
it's killing her.
- Can't you just heal her?-
No. I tried.
But for some reason, this magic,
it's too knotted.
So we contacted Rowena.
She suggested a reversal spell,
and we're reading up
on it now.
Are you going
somewhere?
No.
We'd make better time
if we split up.
Uh -- Uh, Dean,
w-we'll be safer
if we stick together.
Yeah, if I get a vote,
I'm Team Stick Together.
Fine.
Guys!
Holy mother...
Vampires.
Jody,
these match your vics?
They were John Does.
Hard to tell.
Three heads,
three headless bodies --
the math works.
Except, Sam,
I checked those bodies.
I brought
tissue samples home.
Alex ran them underneath
microscope.
Silver, Dead Man's Blood --
there was no reaction.
What the hell?
It looked just like her,
like...
Kaia.
You saw her die over there,
right?
- Yes, absolutely.
- Then what's happening?
All I know is that thing --
it dressed the same
and it moved the same
as the thing that killed Kaia.
Yeah.
How is that
possible?
I don't know.
But let's find her
and ask.
"Sage, pyrite,
and sheep's eye"?
- We got that here?
- Yes.
Storage room, red cabinet,
bottom drawer.
It's marked
"gross stuff."
Oh, it's okay.
Is that your dad?
One of them, yes.
Do you have parents
or someone we can call?
My mom, but...
she probably hates me.
Why?
Because I left.
I ran away.
I hated school,
I hated our crappy
one-stop-light town,
and I hated her rules.
I was sick of being
treated like a kid.
I thought I could make it
on my own,
but then I met her.
The witch?
She took me in --
me and two other girls.
At first, we didn't
want to leave.
She fed us,
gave us all nice things.
She was...kind.
She said having us there
kept her young.
But then she...
She got mean.
She locked us up.
Rachel started getting sick,
just like this.
And then Talli,
same thing.
They withered away...
to nothing.
When your friend showed up...
I thought I was saved.
But then it started
taking me, too,
even faster
than the others.
Cass is gonna
fix this.
I promise.
Dean?
Dean, what is it?
She's got a light foot,
but she's still leaving tracks.
Okay, hold up, hold up.
Wait -- Wait a second.
What?
Her face.
You saw it, too --
the bruises.
That could've been vamps.
Or it could've been Michael.
Come on.
Three vamps in Sioux Falls
and not a single civilian death.
That's not an accident.
I think they were hunting her.
Why?
I think because
Michael sent them
to finish what he started.
- Okay, we don't know that.
Jody tested the bodies, Dean.
They're different.
They're -- They're
immune to Dead Man's Blood
the same way
Michael's werewolves
were immune to silver.
Doesn't change the plan.
Yeah, but, Dean...
Cantamen solvatur,
cantamen revertatur.
How are you feeling?
I-I-I don't know.
Lora?
No.
Help.
All good?
Ah, the girls are
asking for me.
You gonna tell them?
They have a right to know,
but I can't.
I promised Claire human cases
are mine,
but anything monster-y,
I'd loop her in.
But this...
Aw.
Claire's been doing so good,
and, I mean,
anything connected to Kaia,
she's a powder keg.
Hm.
First love strikes quick,
and to lose it like that...
Oh.
Well, you two are having
a time of it.
Yeah.
He's working something out.
And he's working it out alone.
Only thing I know --
He's not ready
for this case.
Maybe.
Maybe he needs it.
What are you?
If you're asking
if I'm the girl you knew,
your Kaia,
no.
Then what?
You're from, uh...
over there, yeah?
You know I am.
So you're Kaia's double?
Hmm?
Like Bad Cass
or New Bobby.
What I was to her,
she was to me,
you could never
understand.
Why did you kill her?
That was an accident.
I was trying
to kill the blonde.
All right.
How'd you cross over?
How'd you open a rift?
Okay.
Why are you here?
You mean right here?
'Cause of him.
Yeah, not him,
not Michael,
not anymore.
I know.
You're much weaker.
Maybe.
But you're still scared.
Not of you.
Of them --
the monsters
he sends after me.
Every time I slow down,
there's more.
There's always more.
Jack...
We let her die.
I'm --
I'm sorry.
If -- If I still had my powers,
I could've saved you.
I...
Jack,
what are you doing?
The witch.
Where's her body?
Guys, we should move this,
take her to the station
just to be safe.
No, we need to break her
right here, right now.
Break her?
What do you mean "break her"?
For what?
He wants to know
where I hid my weapon.
That's all he wants.
That's what this
is all about.
The witch-killing bullet --
It's still in her.
Guess so.
Jack,
what is this about?
Dean, what,
you're gonna hurt her?
Torture her?
That pig-sticker
she's hiding --
it is the only thing that
we know that hurts Michael.
I'm gonna do
whatever it takes.
Where is it?
Where's the spear?
Where is it?!
The witch told Lora
she and the others
"kept her young."
I thought
it was a metaphor,
but the witch was
stealing their youth.
When you killed her,
maybe the magic kept working,
sucking Lora's life-force,
trying to keep the witch young,
to keep her alive,
but it couldn't work
because the bullet
was still inside her.
So the magic worked
harder and harder
and consumed more and more
of Lora.
That's why the reversal spell
didn't work.
She wasn't cursed.
This was.
- Where is it?
- Dean...
You're no different
than him --
threats, violence,
anything to get what you want.
I am nothing
like him.
Yeah, you are.
You always have been.
Lora's life-force --
It's in here.
Jack, are you sure?
No.
What happened?
I saw what
you did to her.
When you got angry,
you shoved your gun
in her face.
Get in the damn car!
How do you know
about that?
Wait a second.
You're a dreamwalker, too.
Your powers --
They connected you.
Our whole lives.
What she saw, I saw.
I know where
it comes from --
your anger,
your impatience.
It's fear.
You're scared.
And you're weak.
All right. Shut up.
Michael hurt you.
He hurt me, too.
I didn't come here
to fight.
Not if I don't have to.
This face you know,
but I'm just borrowing it.
We haven't met.
But I've sensed you
ever since I came
to this world.
You're like me.
You bleed new energy.
So does that.
I'm here
to make you an offer.
There's a war coming,
and I'm building an army.
You can join my side,
the winning side,
if you give me that spear.
Or you can fight,
definitely lose,
probably die,
and then I'll just take it.
So, Wild One...
what's it gonna be?
Stop.
You remember now?
So Michael wants the spear
because he knows
it can hurt him,
and that's why his monsters
are coming after you.
Yes.
Dean, we should get
out of here.
Unh-unh. Guys...
Too late.
We only came for her,
but I was never one
to turn down a buffet.
Those spiked bullets
don't hurt us anymore.
Now you're in trouble.
Or not.
Slippery one,
isn't she?
Aaah!
You saved us.
You didn't have to.
I came back for them,
not you.
You know, as long
as you have that spear,
you're gonna be
a target --
for Michael,
his monsters.
They'll keep chasing you.
I'm used to it.
- Jody...
- Dean Winchester,
you have
nothing to apologize for.
- How is the arm?
- Yeah, you sure
you don't want a ride
to the hospital or --
I've driven with
a broken arm before.
More worried about
what I'm gonna tell Alex
when I get there.
And then,
once I get home...
Claire?
Yeah.
I'm dreading
those consequences.
She's got to know.
She's got to know
that Kaia's killer
is still out there.
You all right?
It's just, you know,
seeing her face again.
Raising three Hunters
and fearing every day
that I might lose
one of them...
Didn't really even get
a chance to know Kaia
before she Di--
I just feel
like I already lost
before I ever even began.
Come in.
Well, uh...
Jules is off.
She's taking Lora back home
to her mother.
Jack, I just wanted to say,
I'm -- I'm sorry.
I know that you've been
going through a lot lately.
We've all been going
through a lot.
It's just no excuse.
I-I just haven't
been there for you,
not the way I should've.
Cass, it's okay.
Well...
what you did today,
you just
made me so proud.
You know, learning
to hold your own in a fight
without your powers,
that takes time
and -- and training,
but today, you --
you proved that you have
the mind of a Hunter
and the heart of a Hunter.
I was thinking, um...
I mean, I'll talk
to Sam and Dean,
but, um, I thought maybe --
maybe we could
go on a Hunting trip.
I mean, if you want to.
Yeah.
Yes.
Sorry.
You okay?
I'm fine.
I'm human now.
Must be getting
my first cold.
Well, I'll make you
some soup, then.
I put us all in danger
today.
Stupid danger.
Dean...
You were right.
I didn't want to look at it,
what Michael used me for.
I just wanted to race ahead,
you know,
skip to the end of the story,
the part where I get the weapon
and I take out
the bad guy --
the part where
I kill Michael.
Yeah, I know.
You know, I said yes to him
because I thought...
It was stupid.
I was stupid.
Dean...
you did what
you had to do.
And it wasn't a blink,
being possessed.
I made it sound like that,
but it wasn't.
I don't remember most
of what Michael did with me
because I was underwater,
drowning,
and that I remember.
I felt every second
of it --
clawing,
fighting for air.
I thought I could make it out,
but I -- I...
I couldn't.
I wasn't strong enough.
And now he's gone
and he's out there
putting an army of monsters
together
and he's hurting people.
And it's all on me, man.
I said yes.
It's my fault.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man