I can feel him
in my head.
Michael gets out,
that's it for this world.
Billie. She said that
there's only one way
that this ends right.
Ma'lak box.
Secured and warded.
Once inside, nothing gets out,
not even an archangel.
Plan is, charter a boat to
take me out to the Pacific.
- Splash.
- You and Michael,
trapped together --
for eternity?
When Jack's grace
was taken from him,
his being fell into chaos.
The cells are gobbling
each other up.
He's gone.
My magic draws power
from the soul.
- It could save him.
- How much of it?
As long
as he's only using it
to sustain his body,
it won't cost much.
He'll never miss it.
We're the guys
who save that world.
Sam, I have
tried everything.
- I believe in us.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Why don't you
believe in us, too?
Okay, Sam.
Maybe Billie's wrong.
But I do believe in us.
And I'll keep believing
until I can't.
But when
that day comes --
if that day comes...
...Sam, you have to take it
for what it is --
the end.
All right. All right.
Now, we keep getting
interrupted, don't we, Felix?
So let's just make sure
we have enough time
for a proper supper tonight,
shall we?
They're on their way again,
Felix.
Time to go.
A snack for later.
? Supernatural 14x14 ?
Ouroboros
Original Air Date on March 7, 2019
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh, no.
He's cooking the body parts...
again.
I got nothing.
Aw, come on.
Seriously? How does this
keep happening?
I thought we had him
this time.
Look at this.
He's all cut up.
No restraints,
like last time.
And he was
killed recently.
I suspect he was very much alive
when the cutting started.
I don't understand.
Why don't any of them
fight back?
Yeah. Who would just let
themselves be eaten?
Hey, I'll say it again.
My money's on witchcraft.
Och, you.
Always blaming witches.
'Cause a lot of times
it's witches.
Rowena, your tracking spell was
supposed to make this easier.
Huh!
There I was, in the middle
of a glorious
rosewater and vanilla-oil
massage,
hidden away at an exclusive
desert spa,
when you called me,
begging for my help.
Well, because we've been chasing
this guy for weeks.
What's your point?
My point, Dean,
is that you asked for my
assistance, and I obliged.
And while the killer
eluded us,
it certainly looks as if
he was here quite recently.
I'd call that a success.
Oh, yeah, that's a success.
Sam.
Hello, Castiel.
Okay, looks like
our dinner guest here,
his name is Dennis Barron.
He's 43, and this is his house.
No signs of forced entry
and no restraints.
- It's all the same.
- Yep.
Well, not...everything.
Maybe it's his pet.
I mean, no pictures
in his phone.
And, uh, this place doesn't
exactly scream "snake guy."
Not enough Pantera posters,
for one.
There was some pepper
on something.
I don't know. I'm fine.
I'm not dying.
Okay, so, what?
This guy's some real Houdini?
Well, however he's avoiding us,
he's now claimed the lives
of at least six people
in northern New Mexico.
That we know about.
Aye, but this is the first one
I've seen in the flesh.
Did they all have these
blackened lips?
Yeah, or just
black patches of skin
around their face and neck.
Yeah, but we've been
more focused on
the "missing eyeballs
and cannibalism" angle.
Do the black lips
mean something?
Darling boy,
everything means something.
Be a dear and bring
the snakeskin.
You know, the last time I saw
Jack, he was on death's door.
You say, "Oh,
it's just some magic,"
and you think
I'll leave it at that?
Okay, listen.
Jack is all right.
You don't need to worry.
Oh, I wouldn't say worried.
More curious.
Speaking of which,
I'm also curious
as to how your brother is
managing to keep an archangel
locked away
inside his mind.
Because...he's Dean.
And Dean is Dean.
He's fine.
For how long?
We're working on it,
Rowena, another way to --
to keep Michael locked up
or -- or kill him --
But?
But, for now,
staying busy is good.
For all of us.
Okay.
You know, I got to say, I got
a pretty good feeling
about bringing Rowena in
on this one.
I think her and Sam have
a chance of cracking it.
They do have many books.
Yes, they do.
Hey, Dean?
I'm fine.
What you're doing,
even just sitting here
and having a cup of coffee,
is a Herculean feat.
I can't imagine
the willpower
it's taking to...
keep Michael imprisoned.
Are you really fine?
I don't know, Cass.
But that's what I'm
supposed to say, right?
"I'm fine,"
keep on moving?
That's what we all say.
No, Dean.
Okay.
There's this pounding
in my head.
It never stops.
Michael's in there,
and he is fighting hard
to get out.
And I can't let
my guard down...
not for a second.
I'm barely even sleeping.
Well, that's not
sustainable.
No. No.
It's probably not.
But...no point in
complaining about it.
It's on me.
No. It's on us.
We are here to help you.
I know.
I know that.
And I appreciate that.
I do.
Look, before the kid
gets back --
I know I agreed
to give you guys time.
Hey, Dean, and we will
find a solution.
Okay. But if --
if you don't...
we still have Plan B.
Dean, come on.
Coffin. Ocean. Done.
Here's an order for 18.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Hey, see? Look at that.
Everybody's fine.
- What?
- Nothing.
Okay, um...
these killings --
it seems like there's
a ritualistic quality
to the crime scenes, right?
It's almost liturgical.
It means religious.
Ah. Yeah.
See, that one I knew.
Ah.
Maybe we're wrong and --
and this isn't
a monster at all.
Maybe this is just a deranged
person who's been getting lucky.
Anyone who could do this
is a monster...
I mean,
even if they're human.
Kid's not wrong.
Yeah.
Okay. Got it.
Looks like Sam and Rowena
have something.
Okay, so, we've made
some progress.
This is like an A.V. Club
presentation.
What's an A.V. Club?
It's a special group for people
who do not play sports.
Yeah, him.
He's A.V. Club.
Excuse me, boys, but this is
a bit more pressing
than your
hilarious banter.
I believe we are
hunting a gorgon,
an ancient, cursed being
with an affinity for snakes
and a hunger
for human flesh.
Snakes for hair?
That's like Medusa.
You know about Medusa?
Oh, yeah.
"Clash of the Titans"?
Turns guys to stone?
Oh. That's the exaggerated
version. It's not stone.
More of a venom-induced
paralysis.
Hence,
the blackened lips.
And the fact that the victims
didn't fight back.
And the snakeskin, which,
frankly, was a bit on the nose.
Yeah.
So we expanded our search
based on this new information,
and we found 17 unexplained
deaths that could fit our guy,
last three months, moving west
across the southern U.S.
- 17 people.
- Yeah.
Legend has it,
every few months,
the gorgon goes on a spree
and gorges itself.
Like a snake.
That makes sense.
So, is there
anything in there
that explains why this gorgon
keeps eluding us?
Uh...
some lore says that a gorgon
can tell people's fates,
and, by consuming
human eyes,
they may
"glimpse the future."
Yeah. We think that's how
he sees us coming.
So, then even if we use
your tracking spell again,
he'll know.
So...
how do we get him?
I don't know.
Need something, fella?
I really need a ride.
Not a taxi.
And some food.
I'm kind of starving.
I'm not a cook,
either.
Really appreciate
any help.
And I'd find a way
to pay you back.
Yeah?
Definitely.
Anything you want.
And I've always had
a sense about people.
And I can tell
that you...
definitely...
want things.
Get in.
We'll work it out.
So, uh...
you ready to do,
uh...anything?
You're gonna have
to do better than that if --
I'm so glad
we got in the truck.
So much easier this way, isn't it?
Right now, my poison --
it's paralyzing you.
But, sadly, the numbing takes
a little while to kick in.
So, uh,
you're gonna feel this.
- Agents Page and Jones, FBI.
- Why is the FBI --
We had a few more of these
across state lines.
Anything unusual?
Other than the guy
missing his eyes?
Is this amusing to you?
Uh...n-no, sir.
Sorry.
I, uh...
I'm just
a little freaked out.
I've never seen
anything like this.
And, uh...
Yes, there is
one other thing --
a note on the body.
A note?
Yeah.
It's made out
to some guy named Dean.
Can I see that?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
What does it say?
"Dean, I see you standing alone
by the truck reading this note."
"I see you and the tall man and
the red-headed witch chasing me.
I will always see you.
Stop, or I will make you stop.
Regards, Noah."
I'm on a first-name basis
with some psycho pen pal.
That's aces.
Somehow he knows you.
But you're not standing alone.
Why doesn't he mention me?
Maybe you're not his type.
So, Noah can see
you, me, and Rowena.
For the record, I don't love
being included
on his little hit list.
But can't see
Cass and Jack?
It's an odd and glaring
omission.
No.
It's our shot.
I mean, this guy --
for some reason,
he -- he can't see angels.
I'm not an angel.
Well, apparently
you're close enough.
So, if Jack and I approach
Noah on our own,
we -- we may
surprise him.
Yeah. I-It's risky.
But I-I think
it's probably our best play.
Rowena, get your
tracking spell ready.
Okay.
- Everything you need?
- Aye, but I should mix up
an antidote
to the gorgon's poison
in case one of you boys
gets sloppy.
I'll just need a wee bit
of antivenom.
Antivenom is a controlled substance.
How do you --
Don't worry.
I have a plan.
Help!
Please help us!
It's our wee doggie --
he's so sick!
He's not responding.
He's lethargic.
We -- We think he might have
eaten something.
"We think"? "We think"?
He means that
it's my fault for not keeping
an eye on the poor dear.
He thinks that everything
is my fault.
Can we not fight
in front of the vet?
I mean, I guess it's not
entirely your fault
that you looked away!
He blames me
for everything!
I let his mother ride
the Jet Ski one time!
Here, I'll just --
Let me take him.
Yeah. Great. Thanks.
What's his name?
Jack.
Jack. Wee Jackie boy.
His breathing's okay.
Let me set him down in the back,
check his vitals.
Ah. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Please help him. Oh.
What are you doing?
Oh, I mean,
I realize it's not...
...pretending to be the FBI.
But there are other ways
of doing things, Samuel.
Plus...
I thought my performance
was quite magnificent.
Well, that was easy, wasn't it?
You're the sweetest boy,
aren't you?
I'm going to have Mommy
and Daddy fill out some forms.
You wait right there.
Well, he seems okay, but we're
gonna do some blood work
just to --
Jack?! Jack?!
- Oh, this will work perfectly.
- Great.
Just wish I could've got it
before she took my temperature.
Ohh.
Right.
All right. Let's get.
Oh, uh, a moment, Samuel.
What?
What did you do
to that boy?
When I cast
the transformation spell,
I felt something
else pushing back,
some other thing
inside him.
It's volatile magic,
powerful,
and it's stitched to him
like some kind of parasite.
I was curious before,
but now I am worried,
so I'll ask you again, Sam.
What did you do?
Okay, listen.
Jack's being careful.
We're all being careful.
That's all you need to know.
Fine.
Don't tell me.
But using dangerous, mysterious
magic, regardless of the cost,
that's a very on-brand
me thing to do.
Well, thank you.
Of course, Samuel.
Until very recently,
I was the villain.
Mmm!
He's being good and quiet,
isn't he, Felix?
Because we made a deal,
didn't we?
He stays quiet,
no talking, no screaming,
and he doesn't have to die
like all those other men.
Oh.
Do you think he has
any vegetable oil?
'Cause Felix can't actually
talk, so you should respond.
It's in the cupboard...
by the oven.
Oh, that's perfect.
Honestly, it's not like
I enjoy eating people.
It's a lonely way to live,
and there's only so many ways
you can cook human.
But sometimes fate
is cruel and boring.
Am I right?
You're not --
You're not serious.
Maybe you just have
a concussion.
Maybe this is all
a hallucination?
Ha! "Serious"?
Ask the men of New Mexico
if I'm serious.
That's a pretty biased sample
at this point, really.
The men of...
You're just preying on --
on helpless men?
"Helpless men" --
that's rich.
No, I do eat ladies, too,
but women have become
so cautious lately.
Must be all that
finally waking up
from centuries of
misogynistic oppression.
Good for them.
Bad for you.
It's so bad for him,
isn't it, Felix?
No! Help!
Help! Someone!
Ohh! Unh-unh-unh, ohh!
you know the rules.
Help me!
Screaming's
a deal breaker.
I --
Now let's go figure out
how to work that oven,
shall we, Felix?
- Do you have it?
- According to the lore,
the only way
to kill a gorgon
is by cutting off its head
with a silver blade.
Great.
Why couldn't it just
be bullets, right?
Yeah.
What about over there?
Everything okay?
It's quiet. We're good.
Oh, and Mary checked in.
She finished up
that case in Oregon.
She's starting
her drive back tonight.
Great. Maggie, hey,
I really appreciate
you stepping up and handling
things while we're gone.
- Be safe.
- You bet.
All right.
- Everybody ready?
- Yes.
He's less than an hour
west of us and not moving.
All right, well,
break out the silver blades.
Maggie says decapitation
is the only way
to kill these things.
But if we cut off
their head,
then is more creatures
gonna crawl out?
Wait.
Other creatures?
H-He's talking about
"Clash of the Titans" again.
We don't know.
A few drops of this concoction
should counteract any poison.
Theoretically.
"Theoretically."
That's comforting.
Yeah, well, assuming you're not
all paralyzed or eaten...
off with his head.
I'm not expecting anyone.
Are you?
Oh, no fair.
You're not human.
And you're a monster.
Demi-god, technically.
You stay where you are.
Hey.
I'm a lover, not a fighter.
Jack, watch him.
I didn't see you coming,
but I see you now.
Shut up.
Have you ever heard the story
of the black snake?
Hey! Hands up.
Once there was
a crafty black snake
who kept eating this
poor chicken's eggs.
She couldn't watch them
all the time, you see?
The black snake would wait
until she was gone...
...and then slide one of
the eggs into his mouth
and crush it
in his throat.
Now, this went on until
there was only one egg left.
But when the chicken
left that egg,
just for a moment,
the snake swallowed it up.
But for some reason, he couldn't
crush it in his throat.
The chicken had hard-boiled
her final egg
just to choke the snake.
And the snake died.
Why are you telling
this story?
Because
I can't quite tell
if he's the chicken...
or the snake.
We're done here.
Cass!
Hello, Dean.
Wish I could say it's nice
to meet you in person.
Yeah.
It's a real pleasure.
Dean!
Ready?
Check on Cass.
I got Dean.
Cass, can you breathe?
Hey, hey, hey.
Dean?
It's not working.
Why isn't it working?!
Cass?
Jack, what are you doing?
You're okay.
Wake up!
Hey! Dean?
Guys!
Hey. Wake up. Dean.
W-Why won't he wake up?
Is he --
- It's a head injury.
- I'll get ice.
Cass, do it.
Well?
I still can't heal him.
I can't even see what's
going on inside his head.
I can help.
No. Jack.
I appreciate what
you did for me,
but you cannot afford to burn
off any more of your soul.
So that's what
you have him doing?
We'll talk about it later,
Rowena. Now is not a good time.
Maybe the gorgon did something
to Dean before he --
Smashed his face
into the wall?
What do I do?
Clean his wound.
Make him comfortable, then...
...we'll see.
Hey! Hey!
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Jack.
I hate seeing him
like that.
But he's gonna
be okay, right?
I mean, it's Dean.
He...
It was a fight.
It was --
It was just a fight.
Every time we go out,
there's always a risk.
I-I can't...
think about losing him
or -- or Sam or you.
I-I just -- I hate --
I hate thinking about it.
Yeah. So do I.
But, Jack...
you know, Sam and Dean,
they're human,
and they're
very extraordinary,
brave, special humans,
but they're --
they're still humans.
And humans burn bright,
but for a very brief time
compared to, you know,
things like us.
And eventually, they're gone,
even the very best ones,
and we have to carry on.
It's just --
It's part of growing up.
Losing people?
Yes.
What's the point?
The point?
What's the point of
being a cosmic being
if everyone I care about
is just gonna...leave?
The point is that
they were here at all
and you got to
know them, you --
When they're gone,
it will hurt,
but that hurt will remind you
of how much you loved them.
That sounds...
...awful.
It is.
But it's also living.
So when Dean wakes up --
and he will wake up --
we just have to
remember to appreciate
the time that we all have
together now.
What if he doesn't
wake up?
What about Michael?
What if --
I don't know, Jack.
Okay, but I could use
my powers.
No, Jack, I know you want
to help, but you cannot --
What is the good of
having these powers
if I can't help
the people that I love,
if I can't help them
when they need it?
Jack --
It's selfish of me not to.
I understand how
frustrating it is.
I know.
You're keeping the snake?
Yeah.
Rowena said that the gorgons
can see people's fate.
And Noah said
he could see me.
That -- That story.
The story about the chicken
and the snake?
It was just...
He was stalling.
What does it mean?
Well, it's a story
about greed mostly.
But I guess it's also --
it's also about being willing
to give up the thing you love...
in order to kill
the thing you hate.
He said that he didn't know if
I was the chicken or the snake.
Does that --
Dean.
Where is he?!
No, wait!
Dean! Dean!
No! Stop! Dean, stop it!
It's -- It's me!
- You're in the bunker!
- I know where I am!
That's not --
Dean.
He's gone.
Michael. He's gone.
How?
This is my fault.
I let my guard down.
- No, Dean --
- I told you!
I told you to let me
take that coffin ride
to the bottom
of the ocean!
Okay, Dean, j-just --
Maggie?!
Sam!
Maggie!
No. No.
No.
Hello, boys.
I could've
burned them all,
but I'm feeling
very hands-on.
Michael.
That's right.
I thought you'd appreciate
this vessel.
You let her go.
Oh. Please.
She's much sturdier
than she looks.
Must be the hundreds
of years of magic.
Rowena never
would have let you in.
She didn't want
to say yes, but...
Hello, Rowena.
This is all
in your mind.
You're not Dean.
I was...for a while.
But it didn't work out.
It was him, not me.
And now I'm looking
for a new home.
- A-And you think --
- If you say yes,
I'll make you
this promise --
I'll leave you alive.
I'll live either way.
Excuse me?
Fate says Sam Winchester's
going to off me,
which makes dinners
a bit awkward,
but does give one a certain
sense of...security.
So whilst I'm flattered,
I think we can both do better.
Hmm.
Fine.
Then how about this --
I'll leave you alive,
find another host,
and then I'll kill every one of
the people in this bunker...
everyone you care about.
And you do care
about them,
no matter
what you tell them,
no matter what
you tell yourself.
So...
say yes.
Choice is yours.
I had no
intention of keeping my word,
but I think she knew that.
If only Dean had used that
coffin when he had the chance.
Never too late
for a good idea.
Sam, get the cuffs.
That's not very nice.
And if we're not
being nice,
what if...
you couldn't breathe?
That's a terrible feeling,
isn't it?
What if you were also blind?
Sam.
And what if
you just hurt?
But...fun as this is,
I think...no more games.
This time, you all die.
This time, the world burns.
Michael!
Let them go.
You think you can
match me, boy?
This power you have now --
it's nothing, just a crutch.
How dare you!
Burning off your soul?
You'll run out soon enough.
It's worth the cost.
I should have killed you
when I had the chance.
I feel the same.
I am the commander
of the host!
I am the cleanser
of worlds!
I will not be challenged
by a child!
I'm not a child!
I'm the son of Lucifer.
I'm a Hunter.
I am a Winchester!
Jack! No!
You won't hurt anyone
ever again!
Jack?
Michael.
He's dead.
Jack, a-are you, uh --
I'm me again.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man