Remember when you asked
if we could stop it...
all the evil
in the world...
if we could
really change things.
Maybe we can.
We're going
to that place,
and we're gonna
save Jack and Mom.
Let's do this.
I'm Jack.
? Laid it right on the line ?
? When a guy with a chip
on his shoulder said ?
? “Toss off, buddy,
she's mine” ?
? Shot down in flames ?
- You sent me to kill him.
I can hardly
look at the kid!
? Shot down in flames ?
All I see is
everybody we've lost.
? Ain't it a shame ?
? Yeah, to be shot
down in flames? ?
I killed my Lucifer.
? Shoot me, shoot ?
Gabe! No!
? Whoa ?
No.
I saw how
they do the spell.
We could've been something.
I just need your power.
If we do this,
you're the engine,
but I'm behind the wheel.
It's a one-time deal.
? Shot down in flames ?
We had a deal!
Michael.
Thanks for the suit.
? Ain't it a shame ?
? To be shot down in flames? ?
? Shot -- ?
Hello, Jamil.
Who are you?
Oh, we've never met.
But you've read
all about me.
How does it go?
You're...God?
Close, but...
not quite.
Gabriel?
The other one.
The better one.
- Michael.
- There we go.
No, no, no, no.
Why are you here?
Well, that is the question,
isn't it?
Why are we here?
I know why I'm here --
to ask you a question.
What question?
The same question
I've spent weeks
traveling
around this world
asking all sorts
of people --
holy men, leaders,
killers.
And now
I come to you,
Jamil Hamed.
What do you want?
What?
Do you want?
Exactly.
If you could
have anything,
name it.
Peace.
And love.
If you cared
about peace,
you never
would have left Syria.
You never
would have ran
and abandoned your friends
to die --
and they did die.
No.
And if you
cared about love,
you never would have gone into
that broom closet with...
What was her name?
No.
Darlene?
Your wife
never would have left,
and you wouldn't be
living in this...rat hole.
No!
And that's the problem
with you.
You're lost...
...and not worth saving.
Wha--Wha--What
do you want?
What I have always
wanted...
...a better world.
? Supernatural 14x01 ?
Stranger in a Strange Land
Original Air Date on
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hi.
You got silver.
Devil's Trap.
Holy Oil.
And these here, they're dipped
in Dead Man's Blood.
Basically,
you need
some freak dead?
I got you.
A rawhead
did this?
Yeah.
Outside Phoenix.
They're faster
than they look.
Meaner, too.
So, so gross.
Soup's on. Who's eating?
- Oh, I am.
- Right here.
Yeah, I'll --
Yeah, right here.
- How 'bout you guys?
- I'll have soup.
Sam.
Hey, Mom.
How was Atlanta?
It was, uh --
It was a bust.
The woman who claims
she saw an “angel”...
...was...
Let's just say I think
she had one too many hits
of the brown acid,
you know?
Sam, we're gonna
find him.
Ketch is working
that thing in London.
Castiel
is in Detroit.
I know it's been
three weeks since Dean...
Something will break.
It has to.
Yeah. Yeah,
you keep saying that.
Have you slept?
At all?
Sam, you need to rest.
Go and lay down.
- Mom --
- Chief.
Hey.
Good to have
you back.
Thanks.
Don't thank me yet.
Word is we got some vamps
heading East on I-90.
Gypsy types.
Pickin' off truckers mostly.
Last body got drained and
dropped just outside La Crosse
six hours ago.
Okay. Um...
All right.
Get me teams of two.
I want watch points
every 50 miles.
If you see something,
say something.
Maggie, can you hack
the traffic cams on the freeway?
Um...
no.
Right. Right.
Of course. Sorry.
Um, I got it.
Thank you. Uh, please.
Would you call in
Sharon and her crew?
We're gonna need
all hands on deck here.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Sam --
I'm good.
I'm good. I am.
Hey, how's Jack?
Watch for that left.
I never
had to fight before.
Mm-hmm.
Life's a little different
when you can't just
zap people around, huh?
A lot different.
Yeah.
You'll
get used to it.
Truth be told,
this stuff didn't come
all that easy for me, either.
Had my ass handed to me
more times than I can count.
But you kept fighting?
You got to.
As a wise man once said,
“It ain't how hard ya hit.
It's how hard you can get hit
and keep moving forward”.
Was that Gandhi?
Probably.
Yeah, somethin' like that. Yeah.
So, what are you
gonna do?
Watch the left.
Attaboy. Attaboy.
Ah, that's it.
Castiel, darling.
Oh, God.
Sweetie, fix me
a coffee, black,
and a Texas Trinity,
necked,
with some bark.
Sure.
And for my friend...
Water.
- Water.
- All right.
What did you
just order?
Oh, sausage and brisket,
pork ribs, no sauce,
well done.
My apologies for the lingo,
but when in Rome...
I was surprised you wanted
to meet here.
I'm surprised you wanted
to meet at all.
Didn't think that you
consorted with...
my kind.
Yes, well...
I need information.
Of course, you do.
Does any demon
know where
Dean Winchester is?
I'm sorry, did you just say that
you lost a Winchester?
Because, one --
that's...interesting.
And, two, how is it
that you lost Dean?
I thought the two of you
were joined at the...
...you know,
everything.
Thank you, darling.
Just answer
the question.
You see,
I could...
...except,
not to be crass,
but what's in it
for moi?
Your life.
Come again?
I'll speak slower...
Mm.
...and you will tell me
everything you know,
or I will burn you
to ash
right here
and right now.
I think
we can do better.
“We”?
We.
You saved me,
Sister.
Thank you.
God bless you.
He does,
every day.
Hey, Jo.
Who are you?
You don't recognize me
with this pretty face?
You're not --
You're not
Dean Winchester.
You're...
Oh, God.
People keep
calling me that.
Ah, ah.
We need to talk.
You're the Archangel Michael,
from another world,
and you're possessing
Dean Winchester.
Sounds more complicated
than it is.
Why would he
say “yes” to you?
Love.
Really?
That's very
Hallmark Channel.
So, I'm just
gonna go now.
No, you're not.
Not until I ask you...
...what do you want?
I don't know.
Chanel, Dior,
Louis Vuitton.
You think
this is a joke?
I don't know
what this is.
You asked,
I answered.
We done?
No.
I asked,
and you lied.
I didn't.
I know
about you, Jo.
Because he knew
about you.
You're the rebel,
the angel
who doesn't like
playing by Heaven's rules
or whatever.
You pretend to care
about these things --
pretty things.
But that's all it is --
pretending.
These trinkets,
they don't make you happy.
They just
pass the time.
They're not
what you really want.
And if you're so smart,
what do I really want?
Love.
To belong,
to have a place --
a home, a family.
It's very...
very human of you.
And so...
...so disappointing.
I can sense how many angels
are in this world.
There aren't many left.
I thought...
maybe I could help.
But if they're all these
sad, lost,
fallen things --
things like you --
maybe they're not
worth saving, either.
Hey.
I, uh...
...chatted
with Bobby.
He said you may have
had a rough day today.
It was fine.
Okay.
Jack...
...I know this must be
so hard.
Without your grace,
without your powers,
it's a lot, I'm sure.
But you can get past this.
I know you will.
I have faith
in you, Jack.
And I believe in you.
And --
Hey.
Sam, um,
he's awake.
I have to, uh --
I know.
We'll talk later,
all right?
Did he say anything?
I didn't talk
to him.
I can barely
look at him.
Thanks.
Oh, hey, Sam.
Hey...
Nick.
Nick...
I'm an angel.
My name is Lucifer.
I need to take control
of your mind and your body.
Nick, I need you
to say yes.
Then yes.
How'd you sleep?
Uh, yeah. Um...
Okay. I didn't
wake up screaming,
so that's a plus.
Yeah.
So, no more nightmares?
They're getting better.
Good.
May I, uh --
May I see it?
Oh, look at that.
Looks like
it's healing.
Yeah, it itches a lot.
Doesn't really, uh,
hurt! Aah!
Sorry.
Ow.
I don't get it.
I don't understand
how Lucifer could die
and I could live.
Yeah, um...
I think that maybe it's
because the archangel blades
were made to kill
the archangel inside
a-and not the person
they, uh --
Possesses and uses to almost
end the world twice?
Yeah. That.
It must be weird, you looking
at me and seeing him.
Yeah.
But...
I'm really glad
it's you.
I'm glad
Lucifer is dead.
Me, too.
You still, uh --
Y-You still remember --
Oh, I mean, just little bits
and pieces here and there.
Nothing -- Nothing
about your brother.
Okay.
And, uh, Michael?
Did he tell Lucifer
anything?
Anything
about his plan?
I mean,
I remember him saying
he wanted to do it right
this time.
- Hey, Cass.
- Hello, Sam.
Who is this?
Oh.
I'm the boy
who's got your angel.
And if you want
to see him again,
you know, alive,
we should
probably chat.
It's a trap.
Yep.
- This guy's a --
- Demon.
He just told you
he was a demon?
Yeah.
He seemed pretty proud
of it, too.
Yeah, they ain't
a real humble bunch.
So, what do we do?
We get Cass back.
All right, grab holy water,
Devil's Trap bullets,
angel blades, because whatever
we're walking into --
It's gonna suck.
Exactly.
Maggie,
you're with Bobby.
Mom, you're with me.
I'm coming, too.
I know I'm not as strong
as I used to be,
but I can help.
I have to.
Listen, kid --
Okay.
Grab your gear.
Sam, I mean --
Jack's a worker,
but he ain't ready
for a full-on
demon smackdown.
So...
we keep
an eye on him.
He needs this, Bobby.
And danke,
sweetie.
Castiel, you sure I can't
get you anything hot
and black?
Coffee has
no effect on me.
Hm.
Me either.
You know,
not anymore,
but it's like
saltwater taffy
or infants -- you know,
I just like the taste.
Why are you
doing this?
I'm just trying
to be a good host
like Mother
would have wanted.
No, w--
Why are you using me as bait?
I mean, it's kind of what
you're for, isn't it?
And I need something
from Sam Winchester.
You really think that he's
gonna make a deal with you?
Oh, he's dealt with worse.
You see, recently,
I had a revelation.
You know, somebody asked me
what it was
as a demon
walking the planet,
destroying,
drinking, defiling --
you know,
the Three D's --
I didn't know.
So, I sat back,
and I gave it a good think,
and I realized
exactly what I wanted.
And what is it?
Everything.
Sam, it's gonna be fine.
Stop saying that,
please.
What?
“It's gonna be fine,” that
everything's gonna be fine,
we're gonna
find Dean, and --
We are.
You don't know that.
Dean's gone, and we have
no idea where he is
or -- or if he's
even still alive.
You know,
Michael could have...
burned him out
or worse, and...
I know.
I know he's out there,
scared and alone.
I know.
I know he might
never come back.
Never think
I don't know that.
But I can't...
I have to think
about the good, Sam,
because, if I don't,
I will drown in the bad.
For Dean's sake,
I can't do that.
We can't do that.
Listen, Jack.
On the other side,
you saved me and mine
a dozen times.
Now, things
may have changed,
but whatever happened --
whatever happens --
we got your back.
Here.
The Demon Killing Knife.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
They'll search me.
It's safer with you.
All right.
You know what to do.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the great
Sam Winchester.
I have heard
so much about you.
You are
a damn legend, Sam --
a-an icon.
Th-The shoulders,
the -- the hair.
Mm-mm!
You are my Beyonc?.
Cass, you okay?
Of course he is.
I don't damage
the merchandise.
I'm more embarrassed
than I am hurt.
And you are?
Kipling.
Uh, “Kip” for short.
Cool. Kip.
I'm here
like you asked, so...
Yeah, you're here,
but not exactly as I asked.
You see, I told you
to come alone.
But...
Found them outside.
They didn't even
put up a fight.
I'm sorry, Sam.
It's fine. You tried.
But I'm gonna need
a little bit more now,
you know, not to...
eat them.
I-It's just, you know,
late capitalism.
You understand.
So, Sam,
let's make a deal.
You're looking
to make a deal?
I'm a demon.
That's how we do.
Please.
Sit.
No?
Suit yourself,
barbarian.
What do you want?
That is a very good question.
What do I want?
You know, I don't know if
you're aware or not, Sam,
but Hell's in a bit
of a pickle,
you know, with Crowley dead
and Asmodeus Kentucky fried,
which means --
- I don't care.
Yes, you do.
Or you will.
You see, for the first time
in a very long time,
Hell is without a King.
And that --
that's just not right.
- So, I --
- So, you volunteer.
Exactly.
Why are you
telling me all this?
Because I want to work
with you, Sam,
not against you.
And is that why
you took me hostage?
It's exactly why
you're still breathing.
It gives me a chance to show
Sam and friends
that I can hurt them...
...but choose not to.
You see, I want
the Crowley Deal.
I give you
information,
a spot of help
every now and again,
and in return, you choose
to turn a blind eye
to the crossroads deals,
the demon-on-demon violence,
et cetera.
We never gave Crowley
that deal.
How exciting.
Then I would be
breaking new ground.
All right.
You got some good lines,
I'll give you that much,
but you're no Crowley.
I know that.
And so do they.
Ouch!
Owie!
I know
that I'm not that
ponce-y
son of a bitch.
You see, in life,
I rode with Genghis Khan,
and I burned half the world.
So, please,
do you think that I like
prancing around like this?
Please.
If I had it my way,
I would eat
your heart.
But a King
has an image to maintain.
And I'm not
afraid of you.
But...
they are.
So, take
the deal, Sam,
before I stop
trying to be Crowley
and I show you
who I really am.
So, what do you say,
darling?
No.
A-Are you sure,
because I know things --
a-all sorts of things.
- Yeah.
So do I.
Like?
Sam!
How smart.
Hey. Stay low.
Hey!
Get away from him.
Aw, balls.
Take this.
You know how to use it?
Uh, stab them
with the pointy end?
- Pretty much. Okay.
- Okay.
Cool.
Enough!
There will be
no new King of Hell.
Not today.
Not ever.
And if anybody
wants the job,
you can come through me.
Understood?
So, what's it gonna be?
That's what I thought.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. I --
No, I don't care. I --
Just keep looking.
Yeah. Thanks.
Who was that?
Uh, Ketch.
He's in London
searching for the Newton-Dee
Hyperbolic Pulse Generator.
The what?
It's the --
It's the magic egg
that kicked Lucifer
out of the President.
I thought we could use it
on Michael, but
Ketch can't find it.
So, that's another dead end,
which is just awesome.
Sam, are you all right?
Yeah,
I've been better.
I've been worse.
You?
I'm -- I'm just sorry.
I should never have gone
to those demons.
Cass, I --
No, I-I-I don't blame you.
I...
Honestly, I-I
wish I'd have thought
of it first.
If it meant
finding Dean, I-I'd...
work with...
I'd do anything.
Not bad today, old man.
You, too, sunshine.
- Hey, Jack.
- I'm fine.
You did well.
All I did
was get punched...
in the face.
Well, to be fair, we all
got punched in the face.
That's not -- Before,
when I had my powers,
I-I could
have done something, and --
Jack.
You don't -- You --
You don't have your powers.
And you --
Your grace should
regenerate in time,
but until then --
I'm useless.
I can't kill demons,
I can't find Dean,
and Michael
is in our world,
and I can't stop him.
I can't do anything.
I don't have anything.
Oh, Jack,
that's just not true.
You've got me.
You have all of us.
You have your family.
And -- And we are
going to find Dean
and we are going
to beat Michael
and we're going
to do it together.
We --
Because
that's what we do.
Hello?
Sam?
Jo?
Yeah.
We have a problem.
Now, you --
you know
exactly what you want.
You don't pretend
to want to help people...
or save the world.
Your want
is pure and simple...
and clean.
And that's why you
are worth saving.
That's why we are going
to work so well together.
Because you --
you just want to eat.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man