Michael.
He's dead.
Jack, a-are you, uh...
I'm me again.
You want to know
how much of my soul
I had to burn off
to kill Michael.
Yes.
I don't know.
Don't be afraid.
You're an angel.
You're special because you
heal people for money.
You may have noticed,
around here,
good life ain't cheap.
I was a so-so angel,
but turns out,
I am an excellent businesswoman.
Why? Nick: I needed the truth.
I needed revenge for my family.
You would've done
the same thing.
I don't feel sorry
for you, Nick.
I feel sorry for
the people you hurt
and the people you murdered.
You can burn.
When am I getting out of here?
Listen, you piece of crap.
You're gonna be locked up
for the rest of your life.
You chose Lucifer.
He chose me.
Reject him, Nick.
I can't.
Where are you going?
Wherever it's darkest,
wherever he is.
Our field trip
is to see Donatello?
We're worried about you.
How do you feel, Jack?
I don't know.
I know I don't
feel... nothing,
but I don't feel
the same, either.
Dean and I, we...
We want to talk to you
about your powers.
W-What about them?
You know, you just
got 'em back, Jack.
We want to make sure you're
comfortable with them again
before you...
Before you go all X-Men.
You understand that?
I understand.
I won't use my powers
without permission.
Promise.
? Raindrops keep fallin'
on my head ?
? Because I'm free ?
? Nothing's worryin' ?
Hold your haystacks!
I'm coming!
Geez! I'm coming!
Holy Christmas.
Hello.
Can I help you?
? Raindrops keep
fallin' on my head ?
? But that doesn't mean ?
? My eyes will soon be
turnin' red ?
Please.
Shh.
No. Oh, no.
? I'm never gonna
stop the rain ?
No, no, no, no, no.
Ah-ah-ah-ah, ah!
? Nothing's worryin' me ?
... Captions by VITAC...
www.vitac.com
Captions paid for by
Warner Bros. Television
Come on.
Do you think we have enough?
Son of a bitch!
What...
I thought this was
supposed to relax him.
Um, it will...
I hope.
I just thought it would be nice
to stay in for a change.
You know, this was his favorite
game when he was little.
How about you?
Feeling better?
Everybody keeps asking me that.
We're family.
It's our job.
Well, it's annoying.
Jack...
if you ever want
to talk or... vent...
You're here. I know.
All right.
Winchester game night is a go...
Soon as Sammy gets back here
with the two double-pepperoni
meat blasters
and a pineapple.
I like it.
Yeah, it's like
a crime against humanity.
You missed a call.
Oh.
Dean.
What's wrong?
Help me, please!
- Dean.
- It's me.
It's Donatello.
Donatello?
I need help.
You and Sam.
Help me, please!
Hith-'o-rehr, shqodh...
ki'o-yivkha has-sa-tan,
k'ar-yeh sho-'ehgh,
mith-hal-lehkh,
u-mvaq-qehsh 'eth asher
yval-leha'.
You've reached Sam Winchester.
If this is an emergency,
call my brother.
Sam's not answering his phone.
This whole damn town's
a dead zone.
All right.
We got to go.
What do I do?
Stay here.
When Sam gets back,
play him that voicemail
and have him call me
on my spare.
- Got it?
- Got it.
So much for game night.
? We had a quarrel ?
Wow. This place is so...
Ugh.
I appreciate you coming.
Well, you said
you had something for me.
Hi. Can I get you
some coffee?
No. Thank you.
Yes.
? For I still love you ?
16th-century
Burmese blood rubies.
Five carats.
Excellent clarity.
Castiel,
where did you get these?
On a case.
They are lightly cursed,
but it's nothing
that would affect an angel.
Uh-huh.
And you're giving these to me?
No. No.
I-I need something.
I need your help.
To contact God.
Yeah.
Good luck with that.
You forget, Anael, I know you.
I know what you did
before your demotion.
When you were Joshua's
right hand.
And I know that God spoke
to Joshua.
And only to Joshua.
Now, he's dead, but...
But you understand
how they communicated.
Why do you want to know?
There's a nephilim... Jack.
Lucifer's son?
Yes.
Jack killed Michael.
Good night, sweet prince.
But to do so, he... he used
magic that consumed his soul.
Not all of it, I hope,
but we just don't know
how much Jack has left.
And I've been looking
through all the lore,
and it all says the same thing.
Only God can restore a soul.
And that's why you need him.
Right.
The Winchesters... they don't
know you're here, do they?
Why do you say that?
Oh, I don't know,
just a general reek
of ill-conceived
lone-wolf desperation.
Will you help me or not?
Not. Sorry.
You see,
Joshua never spoke to God.
God spoke to him.
There's a big difference.
I see.
But...
there was a rumor.
A whisper, after the Fall.
Joshua placed a long-distance
call, and God picked up.
Okay. How?
I don't know.
I wasn't there.
But I know someone who was,
and I can take you to them.
I should be there with you.
It's fine.
No, it's not.
You heard Donny's
message, right?
Yeah, I did.
He sounds like he's
speaking in tongues...
Like he's possessed again.
No, that's not...
It's not Enochian. I-I-I think
it's Ancient Hebrew.
- What's he saying?
- We don't know yet.
I'm still working on it.
- All right, well, work fast.
- Watch your back.
That's the plan.
Ancient Hebrew.
What the hell?
Sammy sounds stressed.
It's not just Sam.
It's Jack...
it's you.
I just wish there
was something that I c...
Hey. You're here, okay?
You're here.
But I should've been here more.
But I know how I am.
I can be closed off...
and hard.
Yeah, well, that's where
I get it from.
Listen.
I just need you to know...
I'm grateful.
For every day I get to
spend with you and Sam.
Hith-'o-rehr, shqodh...
ki 'o-yivkha has-sa-tan,
k'ar-yeh sho-'ehgh...
Wait a second.
Wait, wait, wait.
...mith-hal-lehkh...
This...
...u-mvaq-qehsh...
I know this.
...'eth asher yval-leha'.
What?
Donatello's message... i-it's...
It's from the Bible.
It's... it's Peter.
Peter 5:8.
Here.
"Be sober, be vigilant,
because your adversary
the Devil,
as a roaring lion,
walketh about,
seeking whom
he may devour."
Donatello?!
Oh, please!
Dean! Please!
Donatello?!
Help me, Dean! Help!
Ohh! Oh! Sam! Dean!
Help! Help me!
Good. You made it.
Where's Donatello?
What, no "hey"?
"How ya been"?
So it's just you, huh?
Sammy's home sick?
How are you even... Here?
Instead of rotting away in
a jail cell where you left me?
Sort of a funny story...
and by "funny,"
I mean a lot of people died.
No one's here, but...
I saw this in the trash.
Dumpster diving.
Classy, Mamabear.
What did you do?
Nothing.
I mean, I sort of injected
your friend with poison...
Thallium, to be exact.
So he's got about a day
before his internal organs
start shutting down.
But that's just sort of
a "guesstimate."
Why?
To get your attention.
I mean, he was...
Is, sorry is...
One of your friends, right, and
you don't have a lot of those.
I'm not buying a word of this.
No?
Hit the live-stream button.
You can save him
if you can find him.
Where is he?!
Ooh, the angry voice.
Hey, if you kill me,
you kill him.
Do it.
What do I got to live for?
Go.
What do you want?
I want to talk.
We're closed.
Even for us, Methuselah?
Yeah.
We're friends of Joshua.
Joshua didn't have any friends.
Except you.
You sheltered him
after the Fall.
I didn't "shelter"...
We were roommates.
Okay?
He made a mean lasagna.
You saw him try to contact God.
How did he do it?
Yeah.
Maybe try asking him.
Can't. Dead.
Well, guess you're outta luck.
No. You'll tell me, or I'll
burn this place to the ground
and you with it.
Kiddo, how old am I?
Go for it.
Put me out of my misery.
Is that really what you want?
The, um, thingamajig he used,
it's around here somewhere.
Where?
I don't know.
Somewhere.
You're angels, right?
I'm sure you'll know it
when you see it.
Or not.
Whoa! Hey. Hey!
Not now. Okay?
Not yet.
But he was... He was just
sitting there waiting for you?
That doesn't make any sense.
What kind of game is he playing here?
I don't know. If you ask me,
that psycho's seen
way too many
'90s serial-killer movies.
Nick doesn't even know
Donatello.
Lucifer did.
It doesn't make any sense to me,
either, but Donatello...
We're... we're running
out of time.
The poison we can handle...
Thallium.
The antidote is Prussian Blue.
We have some of that here.
A-And the live feed
Nick showed you,
um, maybe I can hack that?
Good. Great.
But it's gonna take time.
Maybe more than we have.
All right, well, Nick said
he wanted to talk.
So let's talk.
Yeah, let's talk.
Hey, hey.
No, no, no.
What?
I need you to stay here.
Why?
The way you are right now...
If Nick looks at you wrong,
you're gonna waste him.
That can't happen!
All right. Yeah. Sure.
Not yet.
Right.
Sam...
Donatello's in this
because of me.
A police officer is dead
I'm the one who let Nick go,
I'm the one who...
What was I thinking?
You thought
he deserved a chance.
Yeah, well, he didn't.
Sam, look at me.
Nick's choices are his.
Just his.
You didn't know th...
That's not an excuse.
No one's making excuses, but...
You gave him a chance
because you felt for him...
...because
you're a good man.
You are.
It's one of the reasons
I'm so proud of you.
Are you insane?
This is Mulberry silk.
Sorry.
So, Methuselah said...
We'd know it when
we'd see it. Right.
No.
Well, you might.
When you were working
for Joshua, did you ever...
Even if we found
Joshua's batphone,
God's not gonna care.
- You wanna know how I know?
- How?
You ever wonder
why a vaunted apprentice
became a lowly button pusher?
Well, I heard that Joshua
offered you more responsibility,
and you just walked away.
I believed in Heaven.
You know, our mission.
I believed, Castiel.
But then I got to Earth, and I saw that
it wasn't the paradise God promised.
I mean, there was
so much hate...
so much suffering.
So I asked Joshua...
I mean, these were
God's creations...
His perfect people.
Why wasn't he helping them?
And do you know what he said?
No.
"God doesn't meddle."
He doesn't meddle?
Well, I do.
So I do.
And here I thought you just
performed miracles for the money.
Well, you haven't been
paying attention, then.
I do them for me.
I don't need Heaven.
And I don't need God.
And...
I'm happy, Castiel.
Really?
Because that sounds lonely.
We're all lonely,
because we're all alone.
From ant to lion
to human to angel.
Every last one of us.
You know, he does meddle.
God reached down,
and he brought me back to life.
So he saves one angel...
and watches millions of people
die screaming, every day.
What does that say about him?
Where's Donatello?
You having fun?
Oh, yeah.
Having a riot.
I get you, Dean.
You and me,
we're almost like brothers,
you know.
Michael, you, Lucifer, me...
We both know what it's like
to be hog-tied
to a nuclear warhead, man.
Mm.
Cut the crap.
Where is he?
You're never the same after
something like that, are ya?
Being one with one of them.
It changes you.
Makes you more than human.
Come on, Dean, admit it.
With Michael, you were a prince.
Now you're just a broken Hunter.
You're too stupid
to know you've been beat.
Beat? What are you
beating me at?
Hmm?
Come on, Nick.
What's this all about?
I want to see my son.
His son?
He said that?
He says he wants to
talk to Jack... alone.
No.
Absolutely not.
I'm not afraid of him.
Nick's cracked. He's friggin'
Cocoa Puffs, okay?
Sam?
I mean... "I mean"?
What do you mean, you mean?
I-I mean...
Look, finding Donatello
is going slowly, Dean,
and Nick is locked
down in our bunker.
How's he even a threat?
He's always a threat.
Donatello helped me,
and now he needs my help.
He's my friend.
And I don't think
we have another choice.
Hey, sonny boy.
Where's Donatello?
Wow.
You're so tough.
That's your pop, you realize.
My father was a monster.
Everybody's a monster.
Even your three dads...
How many innocent people
you think they've killed?
Answer the question!
He loved you.
You know that?
He did.
I felt it.
He loved you so much...
and you broke his heart.
Of course, I'm talking
about the old you.
You with the soul.
Yeah. Kermit the Prophet
told me all about your sitch.
What's that like, not having
a soul? Must be relaxing.
I have a soul. I don't know.
I don't... I don't see it.
I'm looking right at you,
and I see nothing.
I have a soul!
Y-You good?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm s... sorry.
I'm serious.
How'd it go?
Did he...?
Nick. He'll show us
where to find Donatello.
Mama!
Mama.
Ugh!
Yeah. I'm done.
Look, I just stepped
on a rat, so...
Anael... Skip it.
Skip the whole judgmental crap
designed to play
at my insecurities,
and I will skip
my inevitable witty reply
about the real reason
you're doing all this.
What do you mean
the real reason?
I'm doing this for Jack.
No, you're not.
You're doing this
because you're afraid.
Because in your mind,
it'd be easier to call God
than to tell Sam and Dean
Winchester the truth.
The truth?
Jack's soul is gone, Castiel.
And there's nothing
you can do about it.
Look. I don't want to say all
that and hurt your feelings,
so... what do you say
we call it a night?
Boy, that Jack has...
got issues, right?
You throwin' in the towel?
Hey.
Our deal?
I've seen that before.
Where?
Crystal shop? A dollar store?
Ren fair?
No.
The one I know, it... it glows
in the presence of... of God.
- This is what we're looking for.
- Good eye.
Joshua forged it after he Fell.
That thing talks to God?
Only one way to find out.
God...
I don't know where you are.
I don't know if you can hear me.
But please.
Sam, Dean... we need you.
Please.
Yeah, it never worked
for Joshua, either.
So, the warehouse
is just down there.
Want me to show you?
No.
You're gonna stay here.
All by my lonesome?
Look, you try anything funny,
Sammy's gonna shoot you.
Anything happens to me...
Wait. Let me guess.
Sammy's gonna shoot me.
Yeah, to start.
Here. Antidote.
Donatello.
It's too bad.
I would have really enjoyed
giving God a piece of my mind.
But what can I say.
I'm always right.
So, what are you gonna do now?
Go home.
Go home and tell Sam and Dean
the truth.
And then?
I don't know.
Oh.
Thank you.
It's been swell.
Do you need a ride?
I'll call a cab.
Anael.
You know,
you're not always right.
Just because God's not with us
doesn't mean we're alone.
Why? Because we all
have each other?
Yes.
You hear from Sam and Dean?
No, not yet.
What's all this?
Some stuff we found
at Donatello's.
It's not helping.
This...
this was grace.
Can't you feel it?
This was filled
with angelic grace.
It's nice that
we're finally alone.
I feel like I never get a chance
to talk to you anymore.
? Oh, Sammy boy, Sammy boy ?
? Your phone,
your phone is calling ?
Mom?
Mom? Hey.
? Sammy boy,
oh, Sammy boy ?
? The phone is calling ?
No. He's not back yet.
Yeah.
Hey.
All right.
He's sure?
Damn it.
Out of the car!
Get out of the car!
All right, all right, all right.
Whoa. Whoa!
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Was that Mamabear?
There was never any poison.
You injected Donatello
with angel grace.
Why?!
Wow.
She figured it out.
That's good.
Talk!
Prophets are sort of
like old CB radios.
You boost their power or you
mess with their frequency...
CB radio?
Y-You trying to communicate
with someone?
Who?
Search your feelings, Sam.
No. No.
Lucifer's dead.
He's in the Empty.
Yeah, and he's awake...
...and with the help of
your little prophet friend,
I was able to have a convo
with him,
and he told me
how to bring him back.
It won't be easy.
You'll have to prove yourself.
The Winchesters
will be a problem.
But you can use that,
twist it...
find a way to get to my son.
His blood.
You need his blood.
Come on, Sam.
Nobody stays dead anymore.
You know that.
All you need is a little
elbow grease, some new friends.
Where you think
I got that angel grace?
Who do you think hid me
after I carved up that cop?
Demons. Yeah.
They want Lucifer back
almost as much as me.
So, thanks.
Dean!
Lucifer's perfect vessel.
Not so perfect now, are ya?
Come on, Sam.
Hit play, baby.
Come on, Sam!
Come on!
Dean!
Dean.
Sam?
Hey, hey, hey.
Sammy. Yo...
Hey!
Nick... he's trying
to resurrect Lucifer.
How?
I don't know!
I don't know.
He played us.
- Oh, God. Help me.
- Hey! Hey!
We have to stop him.
Thanks.
Yeah, well, we don't
even where he is, okay?
And he hurt Sam.
He got him in the head.
I don't even want to move him.
We called an ambulance,
but they said 20 minutes.
It's not good, Mom.
It's really bad.
We're on our way.
What is it?
I feel... It feels
like my blood's burning.
He has it.
I have a soul!
This was about you, Jack.
All of it.
He needed your blood.
I feel it.
I can feel him.
...qui dormiunt,
ad dominum formosum.
Nexus noster, restitutus est.
Where? Where is he?
I think I know... I think
I-I can get us to him.
But I need to use my powers.
Do it.
Surgas ex abysso,
in lumine exsistas!
Lucifer.
I'm here.
I'm ready.
Your vessel.
Your perfect vessel.
Make me strong again.
Make me you.
No!
No, wait! Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
What did you do?!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Jack!
Aah!
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
Stop! Stop!
Jack, stop it!
Hey. Hey. Come on.
Stay with me now.
We're just gonna play
a little game.
We're gonna count, okay?
We're gonna count.
Count with me. One...
two...
Two.
Yeah, there you go.
...three.
Come on. Come on.
You... You always put...
You always put me first.
No, no. Shh, shh.
Come on. Come on, man.
Your whole life...
Okay. All right.
All right. Come on. Come on.
Just count with me.
Sammy. Hey! Sam!
Mary?
I had to.
Uh...
Sam... Uh, he's hurt.
Help him.
Dean?
Sam.
Nick. Where's Nick?
I stopped him.
It's over.
What about Mom?
She's fine.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I healed Sam.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Good.
That's good.
Mary.
Nick...
he was a bad person, a killer.
I had to stop him.
Not like that.
He deserved it.
Take me home, Jack.
I-I will.
I will. I-I just...
Tell me it's okay.
It's not.
You're not.
You...
It's not your fault,
but the Jack I know
would never have done that.
You... You're...
Something's wrong.
No, I'm not.
You're wrong.
Sweetheart.
You know I'm not.
You know, Sam and Dean,
they were grateful.
If Sam and Dean
saw what you did,
they would be
as worried as I am.
Are you gonna tell them?
You need help, we'll help you.
We're your family.
You can't.
We care about you, Jack.
- No, just leave me alone.
- Jack.
Leave me alone.
Please, just...
Leave me alone!
- Please.
- Leave me alone.
Leave me alone.
What's happening?
- Leave me alone!
- What's going on?
- Jack, just...
Listen!
Jack? Please!
Listen to me!
Leave me alone!
Mary?