TED; Previously on How I Met Your Mother.
TED; She was completely amazing,
She was amazing and funny and,,,
- You have feelings for Ted?
- Maybe.
I've just been offered a fellowship
at a culinary institute in Germany.
- Do you wanna try long distance?
- Yes!
"This long distance thing sucks, huh?
"And I really need to talk to you tonight."
- She's gonna dump me!
- She's not gonna break up with you, Ted.
Hello?
Do you want to come over?
OLDER TED; Kids, your grandma
always used to say to me,
"Nothing good happens after 2,{{{{{00 a, m,"
She was right,
When 2,{{{{{00 a, m, rolls around,
just go home and go to sleep,
Case in point,,,
(PHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
- Hi, Ted, it's Robin.
Listen, I know it's late,
but do you want to come over?
OLDER TED; Let's back up a little bit,
Sit.
Good boys. Okay.
Remember, stay out of the liquor cabinet.
See you tonight.
So, the life of a television reporter
is very rewarding,
and I strongly urge you
to consider it as a career.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Do you have a fianc??
Marshall was here yesterday.
They just learned the word "fianc?."
No, I don't have a fianc?.
Then who do you live with?
Well, actually, I've got five dogs.
Don't you get Ionely?
No, I've got five dogs.
My Grandma has five cats
and she gets Ionely.
Well, yeah, that's cats.
I'm not some pathetic cat lady.
Not that your grandmother is...
Does anyone else have a...
- Yes.
- Are you a lesbian?
No, are you? Just because a woman
lives alone doesn't mean she's a...
Okay. Let's have a big hand
for Robin the reporter!
All right, our next guest is another friend...
So, Robin, you ever report on train wrecks
'cause I just saw one. What up. Tiny five.
Laugh now. Those kids are monsters.
They're gonna eat you alive.
He has a job doing...
- What do you do?
- Please.
Kids, let's rap.
You guys don't give half a brown Crayola
what I do for a living, do you?
- KIDS: No.
- No, no. I know what you want.
- Magic.
- Yeah!
- Hello?
- Why hasn't she called yet?
Okay, you're making yourself crazy.
It's Saturday night.
Go out and do something.
No, what's the point of going out?
I got a girlfriend. For now.
Besides, if I go out,
who's gonna watch the news?
I'm like half your viewership.
I'm flattered
you think we have two viewers.
MAN: And, we're clear.
So, Scherbatsky. Got a boyfriend?
No, and why does this
keep coming up today?
I just thought that guy you
were on the phone with...
What? Oh, no. That was Ted.
He's just a friend.
I mean, there was this moment
where we almost dated,
but we want completely different things.
Anyway, now he has his girlfriend
in Germany
and he thinks she's calling
to dump him tonight,
but I don't think she is.
And, besides,
we want completely different things.
- We should have sex.
- What?
Why not?
We're both available. We're both
attractive. We're both good at it.
At least, I'm good at it.
And even if you're not, don't worry.
I'll have a good time either way.
Well, moving past the horrifying image
of your hair helmet
clanging against the headboard,
I don't get involved
with people I work with.
Get involved? Who said get involved?
I'm just saying we should have sex.
- MAN: We're on in five, four...
- It'd be fun.
Having sex is fun.
Home number. Call me anytime.
A lot of local teams in action tonight.
Hey, guys.
Miss me?
I missed you, too.
Hi, Ted, it's Robin.
Listen, I know it's late,
but do you want to come over?
- Ted?
- Yeah. Hi, I'm here.
- Do you want to come over?
- Why? What's up?
Well, I just finally set up my new juicer,
and I was gonna make some juice.
And I was like,
"You know who likes juice? Ted."
I love juice.
Great, so you want to come over
and make juice?
When it's after 2,{{{{{00 a, m, just go to sleep,
Because the decisions you make after
2,{{{{{00 a, m, are the wrong decisions,
Okay, sure, I'll come over, we'll
- juice.
- Yes, we'll juice.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
Bye.
This is fine. This is totally fine.
What's fine?
Oh, I'm going over to this girl's house
to make some juice.
Nice.
No, it's not like that.
We're juicing as friends.
See, I have this girlfriend.
I would never cheat on her.
She lives in Germany.
See, she was supposed to call me
four hours ago to have a serious talk.
I still haven't heard from her. I don't know.
Sorry to bug you with my problems.
Guess cab drivers
are the new bartenders, huh?
You ain't kidding, kid.
Want a nip?
You could just let me out right up here.
- Where are you going to buddy?
- Park Slope, Eighth and Eighth.
Okay, here's where I left off
with the last guy.
See, I have a girlfriend, but I'm going over
to this other girl's house...
And you're wondering if I'd be upset.
Hi, Ted. Remember me? Your girlfriend.
Okay, relax. Robin's just a friend.
Right. You're gonna go make some juice.
Yes, yes. Juice is perfectly harmless.
In fact, it's healthy.
Oh, yeah? Then why are you wondering
what she looks like naked?
I am not...
Okay, even if I am wondering that,
it's only 'cause you put it in my head.
But I am just a manifestation
of your subconscious,
so actually, you put it in your own head.
Damn it!
Nothing's gonna happen.
- Right.
- Okay, okay. You want a second opinion?
Fine.
(DANCE-MUSIC RINGTONE PLAYING)
Hey. Did she call?
No. I need a ruling.
I'm... Yeah, this is stupid.
It's not even a big deal,
but I'm on my way over to Robin's
right now.
She got a new juicer. Whatever.
We're gonna test it out.
Let me call you back.
Honey, there's a situation developing.
Do you remember the huge secret
that you told me
that you weren't supposed to, but you did?
The thing about Robin?
You mean, how Robin's in love with Ted?
- What?
Yeah. She told me already. Go on.
Wait. So I'm the only one
that she didn't tell?
She told you and not me?
Well, I guess I'm just better friends
with her than you are.
Well, I'm better friends with Ted
than you are.
- That is a lie.
- It is not a lie.
- Okay, that's it. You and me.
- You think you can take me? Come on!
I'm not afraid of you!
You're embarrassing your...
I'll show you things
you've never seen before!
(BOTH SHOUTING)
Come on. Pick up.
Damn it, Victoria. Where are you?
Pick up! Pick up!
- Cupcake?
- No, thanks.
Where are you? Why haven't you called?
I'm out hooking up.
With three other guys.
Or maybe I'm a devoted girlfriend
and I'm calling you right now.
Yeah, why do I doubt that?
(PHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
- Ted. I just saw the news,
and a truck carrying sulfuric acid
overturned right in front of Robin's house.
And it's melting through the sidewalk,
You can see straight down into Hell.
It's bad. You should go home, dude.
Marshall, it's fine.
Nothing's gonna happen.
- Ted, what does your Mom always say?
- Nothing good ever...
Nothing good ever happens after 2:00 a.m.
Go home! It's too late for juice.
Dude, Robin and I are just friends.
She doesn't even like me that way.
Yes, she does! She likes you. She told me.
- What?
- It's a big secret.
So don't tell her I told you,
but she's very vulnerable right now.
And you have a girlfriend. Go home, Ted.
- She likes me?
- Yes,
So you see why it would be
a very bad idea for you to go up there,
Go home, Ted,
She likes me?
Go home, Ted.
You're right, I'll see you at home.
Good. He's going home.
He is so not going home.
I cannot believe you just told him that.
- What do you mean?
- Lily, here's what you just said,
"Ted, whatever you do,
"don't go up there. There's a beautiful girl
who wants to have sex with you."
And then she's gonna
make you some delicious juice!
No. He's not going up there.
He has more sense than that.
OLDER TED; I did
have more sense than that,
- Keep the change. Thanks.
- Thanks.
But after 2,{{{{{00 a, m,,
my good sense was sound asleep,
So, you're doing this?
You're going up there?
You want to get out of the way?
I'm not in the way.
You know, if you had just called me, I...
(EXHALES)
- Hi!
- Hey.
I got some vegetables. I got carrots.
I got beets.
Or we could just drink wine.
Wine not. Wow, that's the stupidest thing
I ever said.
Thanks.
Make it a big glass.
Sure.
So, how's it hanging? "How's it hanging?"
Haven't you ever had one of those days
where nothing at all
that monumental happens,
but, by the end of it, you have no idea
who you are anymore,
or what the hell you're doing
with your life?
Do you ever have one of those days?
About once a week.
I don't know. It was just a rough day,
and the only person I wanted to see
at the end of it was you.
So, how was the big phone call
with your girlfriend?
OLDER TED; When the clock strikes two,
just go to sleep,
We broke up.
What?
Yeah. Yeah. She finally called.
We talked for a while.
How hard long distance is,
and then she dumped me.
Ted, I'm so sorry.
That's just terrible.
I feel awful.
You're smiling.
Am I? No, I'm not.
Well, I'm a news anchor.
Smiling is a part of the job.
Thousands died
in a tragic avalanche today.
See?
You're smiling, too.
Yeah.
I have no idea what that's all about.
(SINGING)
How much does Korean Elvis rock?
I'll answer that. Infinity.
He rocks infinity.
Okay, it's time for bed.
What? No. It's 2:30.
And nothing good ever happens
after 2:00 a.m.
You know, I have found in my travels
that all the best things in life
happen after 2:00 a.m.
When I look back
at the best stories of my life,
the Liberty Bell incident, the little scrape
I got in at the Russian embassy,
- the almost four-way.
- You never had a four-way.
- I said "almost"!
- Well, all right.
All those things happened after 2:00 a.m.
Because after 2:00 a.m. Is when things get,
audience, say it with me, legendary!
- We gotta go.
- What's that? "Interesting theory, Barney,
"but I'll need some proof." Okay.
Korean Elvis. How would you like
to have a drink with me and my friends?
Rock 'n' roll.
And it begins.
So, hey. I got a new phone.
Same as yours. Look.
Oh, yeah, do you like it?
Yeah. Yeah.
This is some solid small talk.
I had that other phone, and it was good,
but I think, the whole time,
a little part of me
wanted this phone instead.
This phone
feels right.
(PHONE RINGING)
Oh, wow. Weird.
Yeah, I should probably take this.
I'll be here.
- Hello?
- Ted. This is your main man K.E.
I want you to shake your tail feather
down here ASAP. You dig?
Okay. Sorry about that.
Who... Was that Korean Elvis?
I'll explain later.
Hey, we're heading down to MacLaren's.
Actually, I'm at Robin's.
Yeah, and I might have done
something bad.
I just lied and told her I broke up
with Victoria.
Ted, I don't want to swear
in front of Korean Elvis,
but what the bleep are you doing, dude?
What do you expect from me? It's Robin!
Victoria's great, but it's Robin!
I've made up my mind,
I'm gonna end it with Victoria.
- Gonna?
- Yes. First thing tomorrow.
Okay, but as of right now,
at 2:45 a.m. You still have a girlfriend.
Ted, I love you. I love Robin.
But if you do this right now,
your entire future with her
will be built on a crime!
Just go home, Ted,
Don't do this the wrong way!
I hate how you're always right.
It's my best and most annoying trait.
Okay.
I'm coming home. I'll see you soon.
- Hey.
I should probably get going.
It's pretty late.
- I'm sorry. I...
- Oh, no. I understand. It's fine. Yeah.
- Can I call you tomorrow?
- Totally.
- Totally. Call me tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Good night, Robin.
- Good night, Ted.
Oh, my God! We're making out.
- Right!
- This is crazy.
Right! Right!
Should we go to my room?
I mean, there's five dogs in there, but...
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
I just, I have to run to the bathroom.
Real quick.
Okay.
(EX CLAIMS)
Stop doing that!
What are you doing?
I'm calling you.
We're breaking up.
I'm doing this right now.
I'm coming out of this bathroom
a single man.
Okay.
Say, Ted, how long do you think
that conversation's gonna be?
Length of an average pee? No.
We're gonna be on the phone
for at least 20 minutes.
Robin's out there. She's gonna think
you're in here taking a massive...
What do you want from me?
People break up. It happens.
Not like this.
Not from the bathroom of the girl
that you're about to sleep with.
It's not ideal.
OLDER TED; Meanwhile, back at the bar,
Barney was still trying to prove that
good things can happen after 2,{{{{{00 a, m,
Come on, Lily!
How many women can say they've been
personally serenaded by Korean Elvis?
Barney, you tried. I think that's great.
But we're going.
- No. No, come on!
- Yes!
Dude. We haven't hit legendary yet.
We're only at the "le."
We still got the "gen," the "da," the "ry."
Okay, if we're at the "le,"
then I say we follow it up
with a "t's go home."
Oh, wow! You just got burned.
Phonics style!
No, no, no, no. Baby, baby, baby, don't go.
- Just one dance, huh?
- Okay, seriously.
Hey, I know what you like.
OLDER TED; And so, Barney was right,
The night was legendary,
It would come to be known as the time
Lily kicked Korean Elvis in the nards,
Hey, you guys remember that time
that Lily kicked Korean Elvis in the nards?
You're right.
I owe you a real breakup call.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Good. So, you're gonna go home?
Why should I have to go home?
You know, there's every chance
Robin's the woman I'm gonna marry.
- Ted.
- It could happen!
And so, really, what's it gonna matter
in 50 years if I jump the gun by one night?
Look, I know this is a moral gray area, but
it's Robin.
And I'm exhausted.
I am. I'm exhausted from pretending
I'm not in love with her.
I think that makes this okay.
Oh, please. You just want to get laid!
Yes, I do. You got me.
That is exactly what I want right now.
And so what?
I want this. She wants this.
It's happening. And if you have a problem
with it, don't be in Germany!
It's been nice pretending to talk to you.
Thanks for not calling me and good night.
That's not your phone.
This isn't my phone.
Okay. Bye.
I thought it was mine, so I answered it.
- Was it...
- It was your girlfriend.
You might want to call her back.
OLDER TED; I called Victoria from the cab,
and we broke up,
Yes, I'm...
And there you have it, kids,
The stupidest thing I've ever done,
In one night, I managed to hurt
two people I cared about,
And none of it would've happened
if I had just listened to my mom,
So, I guess if there's a lesson
to be learned here, it's this,
when it's after 2,{{{{{00 a, m,,
just go to sleep,