www.YYeTs.net
www.unioncast.tv
i know about sam's visions.
i know everything.
gordon should be reaching for the soap
for the next few years,at least.
you were right about everything.
sam winchester is
more than a monster.
i'm not even sure he's human.
we got to get me the hell out of here.
it's rude to sneak up on people.
bela talbot.
you have me at a disadvantage.
i don't know who you are.
gordon walker.
i've heard of you.
heard you were in prison.
got out.
released early on good behavior?
you looking for this?
i know you were just
in massachusetts,
and i know you were with
the winchester boys.
tell me where they are.
i don't think i know.
why don't you think a little harder?
put that down.
what's so pressing about
finding the boys,anyway?
sam winchester's the antichrist.
i'd heard something
about that... it's true.
... from my good friend,
the easter bunny,
who'd heard it from the tooth fairy.
are you off your meds?
the world hangs in the balance.
so you go ahead and be
a smart-ass,
but tell me where they are,
or i shoot.
gordon,you and i don't know
each other very well,
so let me tell you a little
something about me.
i don't respond well to threats,
but you make me an offer,
and i think you'll find
me highly cooperative.
okay.
how about...
you tell me where they are,
or i kill you right now?
kill me.
good luck finding sam and dean.
i can wrangle up three grand.
i don't get out of bed for three grand.
you...
scratch that.
give me the mojo bag,
and we'll call it even.
oh,hell,no.
this thing's a century old. it's...
priceless.
believe me,i know.
now,how badly do you
want the winchesters?
hello,dean?
hey,where are you?
supernatural season 3 episode 7
hey,hey. don't worry.
we're gonna call you some help,okay?
where is she? where'd she go?!
smell that?!
come and get it!
that's right.
come on.
i smell good,don't i?
i taste even better.
come on!
free lunch!
what?
cutting it a little close,
don't you think?
ah,that's just chum in the water.
worked,didn't it?
you with us?
oh,yeah,sorry.
you're not going anywhere.
where's your nest? what?
nest... where you and your
bloodsucking pals hang out.
i don't know what
you're talking about.
please!
i don't feel good.
yeah,well,you're gonna feel
a hell of a lot worse
if we give you another shot
of dead man's blood.
just let me go.
yeah,you know we can't do that.
i'm telling you the truth.
i'm just... i took something.
i'm freaking out!
i don't know what's going on!
you took something? yes!
i can't...calm down.
i just want to calm down.
what's your name?
lucy.
please,just let me go.
all right,lucy,how about this?
if you tell us what happened,
we'll let you go.
you will?
uh,i don't really...
um,it's not that clear.
i was at spider.
spider?
the club on jefferson.
and there was this guy...
he was buying me drinks.
this guy... what's he look like?
he was old,like 30.
he had brown hair,a leather jacket...
deacon or dixon or something.
said he was a dealer...
he had something for me.
- something?
- something new.
"better than anything you've ever tried."
he put a few drops in my drink.
was the drug red and thick?
well,genius move there.
that was vampire blood he dosed you with.
what?
you just took a big shot of
the nastiest virus out there.
you're crazy!
he gave me roofies or something!
no...
the next thing i know,we're at his place,
and he says he's gonna get
me something to eat,
just wait.
but i get so hungry.
so you busted out?
but it won't wear off...
whatever he gave me?
lights are too bright?
sunshine hurt your skin?
yeah...
and smells.
and i can... hear blood pumping.
i hate to tell you this,sweetheart,
but your blood's never pumping again.
not mine...
yours.
i can hear a heart beating from
half a block away.
i just want it to stop.
it's not going to stop.
you've already killed two people...
almost three.
no,i couldn't.
- i was hallucinating!
- you killed them,all right?
we've been following a sloppy
trail of corpses,
and it leads straight to you.
no. no,it wasn't real!
it was the drug!
please!
please,you have to help me!
no,no.
poor girl.
we don't have a choice.
no...please!
sir,a few questions about the attack.
i already talked to the cops.
well,we're not cops. we're fbi.
fbi?
can you describe your attacker?
she was crazy.
she had that,uh,super-pcp strength,you know?
she gnawed on my neck.
and did she bleed on you?
on me,no.
in your mouth,open wound,anything?
- you sure about that?
- yeah,i'm sure. why?
this woman has a very dangerous virus.
what? she bit me in the neck.
the bite doesn't matter.
you have to actually ingest
the blood to be infected.
good thing,too. we'd have had to kill you.
the attack?
she jumped me,then bit me.
then those two guys found me
and chased her down the alley.
- what did they look like?
- i didn't get a good look.
think.
one of them was real tall.
that was a big,fat waste of time.
look,three blondes have gone
missing,including lucy...
all last sighted here.
i'm telling you,dean,this is the hunting ground.
you're sick.
you ready,sweetie?
one taste of this,you'll never be the same.
get out of here. go! go!
dean!
i'm good. come on.
all right. run. i'll draw them off.
what?! you're crazy!
there you are!
yeah.
sorry,i stopped for a slice.
nice move you pulled back there,dean...
running right at the weapons.
well,what can i say? i'm a bad-ass.
so,i guess gordon's out of jail.
uh,yeah,i guess so.
how the hell did he know where to find us?
that bitch.
- hi,bela.
- hello,dean.
question for you.
when you called me yesterday,
it wasn't to thank me for
saving your ass,was it?
gordon walker paid me to tell
him where you were.
excuse me?
well,he had a gun on me.
what else was i supposed to do?
i don't know,maybe pick up the phone
and tell us that a raging
psychopath was dropping by!
i did fully intend to call.
- i just got a bit sidetracked.
- he tried to kill us!
i'm sorry. i didn't realize
it was such big deal.
after all,there are two
of you and one of him.
there were two of them.
bela,if we make it out of this alive,
the first thing i'm gonna do is kill you.
you're not serious.
listen to my voice and tell me
if i'm serious.
i know you're uncomfortable...
but this is just temporary.
the hunger will pass,and then
you'll feel much better.
- you're awake.
- who are they?
family.
you always keep your family in shackles?
we're still getting to know each other.
they've just been reborn.
you mean you grabbed some
poor girls off the street
and made them monsters like you.
i do what i have to.
we're a dying breed.
but,then,you know that,
don't you,gordon?
gordon walker...
one of the greatest
living vampire hunters.
in the flesh.
you're a big part of why my
people are nearly extinct.
your "people" are going extinct
because you're a bunch of mindless,
bloodthirsty animals.
right.
we're so much more bloodthirsty than you.
hunters slaughtered my entire nest
like they were having a party...
murdered my daughter.
i can't tell you how satisfying this is...
catching a hunter
responsible for so many deaths
and making you lunch for my new daughters.
"daughters?"
try "fang whores."
watch your mouth.
oh,did i hurt your feelings? i'm sorry.
i forgot you're just a
misunderstood victim...
even though you murder and
spread your filthy disease
on pure base instinct.
you got less humanity
than a sewer rat.
i'm sorry you have such
a low opinion of my people.
oh,you have no idea.
sorry,change of plans.
i'll be going out to get your lunch.
i've got a better idea for you.
no!
no!!
that vampire's still out there,dean.
first things first.
gordon.
about that... when we find him,
or if he finds us...
i'm just saying he's not leaving
us a whole lot of options.
yeah,i know. we've got to kill him.
really?
just like that?
i thought you would have been like,
"no,we can't. he's human. it's wrong."
no,i'm done.
gordon's not gonna
stop until we're dead...
... or till he is.
what?!
i don't like it when people
hold grudges against me,
and more to the point,
i'd rather you didn't kill me,
so i went ahead and found gordon's
exact location for you.
you're a hundred miles away.
how the hell did you...
hello?
purveyor of powerful occult objects?
i used a talking board to
contact the other side.
- and?
- warehouse.
two stories,riverfront,
neon sign outside.
thanks. one more thing...
the spirit had a message for you.
"leave town,run like hell,
and whatever you do,
don't go after gordon."
for whatever that's worth
please  help us
please
go ahead
do it
kill me
what happened here?
gordon walker
i never should have brought a hunter here
never
i just
i just wanted some kind of revenge
stupid... exposing him to my family
oh,yeah,you're such a family man
you don't understand
i don't want to understand,you son
i was desperate you ever felt desperate?
i've lost everyone i ever loved
i'm staring down eternity alone
can you think of a worse hell?
well,there's hell
i wasn't thinking
i just
i didn't care anymore
do you know it's like
when you just don't give a damn?
it's like
it's like being dead already
so just go ahead
do it
dean
head wasn't cut off,it was ripped off
with someone's bare hands
Dixon,what did you do to gordon?
Gordon
you okay?
not even close
i thought maybe you were dead
what is it?
something happened
what?
they turned me
those fangs?
I'm sorry
you know what this means
It means you have to kill me
but not yet
what do you mean?
you have to let me do
one last thing first
what?
- kill sam winchester
- gordon
it's the only...
it is the one good thing
to come out of this nightmare
gordon i'm sorry
you know i can't let
you walk out of here
listen to me
there is nothing more important
please
i can do one last good
thing for the world
yeah i hear you
you know gordon
you're right
one last good thing
i'm sorry
man,i must have checked three dozen motels,
empty buildings,warehouses
yeah,me too
big city
it's like a giant haystack
and gordon's a deadly needle
we're running out of daylight
won't have the sun slowing him down
yeah,he'll be unstoppable
hey,give me your phone
what for?
well,if gordon knows
our cell numbers
he can use the cell
signal to track us down
oh,yeah thanks
sammy,stay here
what? where you going now?
i'm going after gordon
what?
you heard me
not alone,you're not
sam,i don't need you to sign
me a permission slip,okay?
he's after you,not me,
and he's turbocharged
i want you to stay out of harm's way
i'll take care of it
you're not going by yourself
you're gonna get killed
just another day at the office
it's a massively dangerous
day at the office
so you're the guy with nothing
to lose now,huh?
oh,wait let me guess because,uh
it's because you're
already dead,right?
- if the shoe fits
- you know what,man?
i'm sick and tired of
your kamikaze trip
whoa,whoa kamikaze?
i'm more like a ninja
- that's not funny
- it's a little funny
no,it's not
what do you want me to do,sam,huh...
sit around all day writing sad
poems about how i'm gonna die?
you know what? i got one
let's see what rhymes with "shut up,sam"?
dude drop the attitude,dean
quit turning everything into a punch line
and you know something else?
stop trying to act like you're not afraid
- I'm not!
- You're lying
you may as well drop it 'cause
i can see right through you
you got no idea what
you're talking about
yeah,i do you're scared,dean
you're scared because your
year is running out
and you're still going
to hell and you're freaked
- and how do you know that?
- because i know you!
really?
yeah,i've been following
you around my entire life!
i mean,i've been looking up
to you since i was four,dean...
studying you,trying to be
just like my big brother
so,yeah,i know you...
better than anyone else
in the entire world
and this
is exactly how you act
when you're terrified
and,i mean,i can't blame you
it's just
what?
i wish you would drop the
show and be my brother again
cause
just 'cause
all right,we'll hole up
cover our scent so he can't track us,
and wait the night out here
you've had that phone two hours,dean
who'd you give the number to?
nobody
- hello?
- dean
how'd you get this number?
your scent's all over the cellphone store
of course,i can't smell you now
- where are you?
- I guess you'll just have to find us
i'd rather you come to me
what's the matter,gordo?
you're not afraid of us,are you?
we're just sitting here bring it on!
i don't think so
please
shh
factory on riverside off the turnpike.
be here in 20 minutes
or the girl dies.
- gordon,let the girl go.
- bye,dean.
gordon! don't do this.
you don't kill innocent people.
you're still a hunter.
no...
i'm a monster.
hey,we got you.
don't worry. we're gonna
get you out of here.
get up. watch your head.
watch your head.
sam,stay close.
- sam!
- dean!
damn it,sam!
gordon...
you got me where you want me.
you might as well come out and fight!
i'm right here,sam.
what's the matter,sammy?
so,this is really the way
you want to do it,huh?
damn right i do.
you have no idea what i faced...
to get here.
i lost everything...
my life.
but it's worth it cause
i'm finally gonna kill
the most dangerous thing i ever hunted.
you're not human,sam.
look who's talking.
you're right.
i'm a bloodthirsty killer.
- don't talk about it like you don't have a choice.
- i don't.
yes,you do,gordon.
you didn't kill that girl.
no,i didn't.
i did something much,much worse.
i got to hand it to you,sam.
you got a lot of people fooled,
but,see,i know the truth.
i know what it's like.
we're the same now,you and me.
i know how it is
walking around with something
evil inside you.
it's just too bad you won't
do the right thing
and kill yourself.
i'm gonna...
as soon as i'm done with you.
two last good deeds...
killing you...
and killing myself.
no!
you just charged a super-vamped-out
gordon with no weapon.
that's a little reckless,don't you think?
- there you go.
- thanks.
figure out what's making that rattle?
not yet.
give me a box wrench,would you?
yeah.
- there you go.
- thanks.
sam.
- wrong one?
- no,come here for a second.
yeah.
this rattle could be a couple of things.
i'm thinking it's an out-of-tune car.
okay.
all right,see this thing?
it's a valve cover.
inside are all the parts that are on the head.
hand me that socket wrench.
all right,you with me so far?
yeah,uh,valve cover covers the heads.
very good.
this is your intake manifold,
and on top of it?
it's,uh,a carburetor.
carburetor... very good.
what's with the auto shop?
you don't mean you want...
yeah,i do.
you fix it.
dean,you barely let me drive this thing.
well,it's time. you should
know how to fix it.
you're gonna need to know these
things for the future.
and,besides,that's my job,right?
show my little brother the ropes.
put your shoulder into it.