It's pretty late.
You think I've got time
to run some more simulations
on the cooling system?
Sure, I'm still figuring out
the thermo-acoustic expander.
SHELDON:
Oh, while you do that
I am going to pump
cerebral spinal fluid
through my brain cells to remove
the metabolic by-products
of the day's thoughts.
What?
It's called sleep
and it's my bedtime.
Nighty-night, y'all.
Hey, hey, hey,
you're not going anywhere.
We only have two months to
deliver this to the Air Force
because of you.
(yawning):
I know, I was there.
Well, wake up!
We're gonna put in
a lot of late nights.
How late?
Well, I don't know,
midnight, 1:00.
One o'clock?
I'm not a raccoon.
If you're tired,
have some coffee.
What?
You have some coffee.
I am having coffee!
And look how irritable
it's making you!
Guys!
We're not gonna get anything
done if we start fighting.
Now, can you please try
to soldier through?
(sighs)
Fine.
(clock ticking)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I don't think
I can go much longer.
It's been three and a half
minutes, wake up!
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 10x03 ?
The Dependence Transcendence
Original Air
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
SHELDON: I had a bad dream that
my best friend became a tyrant
and forced me to stay
up all night to work.
Oh, I had a good dream that
when I carried you to bed,
I let your head hit
the wall and I laughed.
Good morning.
What is this?
Well, we didn't see you
last night,
we're not gonna see you today,
so we thought we could have
breakfast together.
Oh, that is so nice.
Ow, it does hurt!
So, what are you guys
gonna do today?
Well, Sheldon was supposed to go
to this party with me
this afternoon,
but I don't think
that's happening.
Oh, that was never happening.
Oh, I'll go.
I like a party.
Well, to be honest, it's not
like a "party" party,
it's more like a gathering
where scientists of different
disciplines get together
to share their work
and keep current
on what's going on
in other fields.
I don't know why
I called it a party, sorry.
It's okay, I'll still go.
You don't think you'll be bored?
Oh, I'll have some wine
and listen to people go on
about crap I don't understand.
I mean, how is it any different
than every
single day of my life?
I won't be there.
Look at that, it is a party.
PENNY:
Oh.
Sorry I have to work
all weekend.
It's okay.
Thanks again for breakfast.
Well, I didn't get to
see you last night.
It was the least I could do.
You shouldn't have made
the alarm code his birthday.
So, what should we do today?
Oh, I appreciate it,
but you don't have to
spend your day off with me.
Well, I don't mind.
Oh, you want go to the mall
and look at baby stuff?
Not really.
Oh, come on,
we could share a pretzel
and get sideways glances
from racist old ladies.
I get enough of that
when I take Howard
to my grandmother's
for Christmas.
Oh,
I know, why don't we get started
on clearing out the baby's room?
Isn't it
a little early for that?
You have to
get to it eventually.
Oh, there's so much junk
in there, it's embarrassing.
How can you be
embarrassed around me?
I'm gonna be in the room
with you when you give birth.
I don't think you are.
You didn't think I was gonna be
in your kitchen this morning,
yet here I am.
MAN:
Psst, hey, kid.
Huh, what?
You look tired.
Why don't you have
an energy drink?
Everyone's doing it.
Oh, no, thank you,
those have caffeine in them.
Oh, sorry,
I thought you were cool.
I am cool.
This is Yoo-hoo,
chocolate milk's
delicious watery cousin.
All right.
But if you ever want to feel
like you have superpowers,
try one of these.
Superheroes take
performance-enhancing chemicals?
You bet.
You know why Hulk
is so strong?
Steroids.
You know why Batman
wanders around at night
getting into fights?
Scotch.
I am facing
a great deal of work.
And I do like things better when
famous people also like them.
Here.
It's on the house.
The first one's free?
Flash, how do you
stay in business?
You want to know my secret?
I bought stock in Marvel.
Hi, Bert.
This is my friend, Penny.
Hi.
Hey, come on in.
I'll gonna go turn on
some rock music.
(Amy chuckles)
That's a geology joke.
Bert's a geologist.
And a joker.
How early are we?
Oh, actually,
we're an hour late.
I suddenly wish
Sheldon was here.
I don't even
know where to begin.
Well, in The Sound of Music,
Julie Andrews says,
"Let's start at
the very beginning.
A very good place to start."
Oh, I was gonna start
at the end.
Thank God you're here.
Well, I think the first thing we
should get rid of is that tone.
Sorry.
I should probably keep this
in case we have a girl.
Oh, that's a nice one.
Was it yours when
you were little?
My dad built it for me.
Wow, it's so cute.
This was the husband
and this was the wife.
They'd go out on
adventures together.
Cruises, skiing,
horseback riding.
That was really me just
duct taping them to our dog.
Oh, and did they have kids?
They did, but the mommy
and daddy didn't like them,
so they shipped them off
to an orphanage
I made out of a shoebox.
Yeah, that's not worrisome
at all.
Not every girl dreams
about being a mom.
Sometimes you think
you're never gonna have kids
and one day you wake up
and you're pregnant.
And it doesn't matter that your
career's going great right now
and that you and your husband
never even got to go anywhere
taped to a dog!
I skipped spin class for this.
Why is it taking him so long
to get a drink out
of a vending machine?
Oh, it's complicated.
He finds pushing
that little door
and reaching up into the machine
uncomfortably intimate.
(door opens)
Gentlemen, I am ready to work.
To quote The Martian, "Let's
science the feces out of this!"
That's The Martian the book
and The Martian the movie,
not Marvin the Martian.
Although to quote
Marvin the Martian,
(as Marvin the Martian):
"I claim this planet
in the name of Mars."
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm fantastic,
never been better.
I had my first energy drink
and I feel great.
Hey, you guys want to wrestle?
We can do arm,
thumb, mud, sumo.
Nah, we're not fat enough,
or wearing diapers.
You wanted him awake.
(rock music playing)
So should we talk
to each other or mingle?
I don't know where everyone is.
Yeah, I mean,
I could see him eating
one or two guests,
but not a whole party.
Well, I guess this is
kind of a bust.
You don't have to stay.
I'm gonna start cleaning up.
Okay.
I feel so bad about
leaving him here.
Oh, it's funny, I was just thinking
the same thing about you.
BERT:
Hey, listen,
could you not
say anything about this
to the people at the university?
You know, 'cause...
you're you and I'm me,
and it's kind of embarrassing.
Wait, what do you mean
"she's her"?
Well, you know how Amy's the
coolest girl on campus, right?
No.
Oh yeah, everybody thinks so.
What?
You tell me about your foot
fungus, but this is a secret?
I'm sure it's just
'cause I'm dating Sheldon.
Mm, actually, I think Sheldon's
popular because he's dating you.
Now Sheldon's popular?
What is happening?
(groans)
Maybe we should break for lunch.
What time is it?
(moans twice)
According to the world's worst
cuckoo clock, it's 2:00.
My head hurts
and I'm more tired than ever.
Why don't you just go home?
No, I can do this.
I just, I just need
another energy drink.
Oh, no.
What?
I want another one.
So?
That's a craving.
That's a sign of
chemical dependency.
You only had one.
No, I know,
but plenty of
things are addictive
after a single exposure.
I mean, crack cocaine,
nicotine, Pringles.
You know once one pops
one just can't stop.
You can't develop
a problem that fast.
You want to bet?
Oh, great,
now I'm addicted to gambling.
We can't afford to lose
any more time.
Well, this probably won't
work, but has anyone ever tried
to just haul off and
whoop the crazy out of him?
That's not helpful.
It's fun to think about,
but it's not helpful.
Hey, Sheldon, we are on
a serious time crunch.
We can't do this
without you.
Can you please
pull it together?
I'm sorry.
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
Just, please, bear with me
if I display symptoms
of caffeine withdrawal.
No worries.
You guys stink.
Sorry I flipped out on you.
I think it's just hormones.
I think you were mean
before you were pregnant,
but it's fine.
So, uh, instead of
cleaning out the room,
why don't we just decide
on a theme for the nursery?
Does it really need one?
Of course it does.
Didn't your baby room
have a theme?
Well, it doubled
as my dad's office,
and he was a cop,
so I guess the theme was
bloody homicide photos.
Oh. Mine was
Winnie the Pooh.
But anyway...
why don't we just
take a step back
and start with a color?
Right? There are
so many amazing ones.
Red, blue, green, purple...
Are you just gonna name
all the colors?
Well, not now.
I don't care what color
the room is.
Okay, well, I'm just
trying to help you.
Well, you're not,
so just drop it!
I'm clearly upset.
Why aren't you following me?
Sorry! Sorry!
And when Amy started using
a solution of chromic acid
and white vinegar to clean
all her lab equipment,
all of a sudden,
everybody was doing it.
You trend setter!
Just the right idea
at the right time.
Okay, okay, so Amy's cool,
Sheldon's cool.
Tell me about Leonard.
Who?
Leonard Hofstadter.
Oh, him.
I guess he's all right.
Apparently he tricked some
hot girl into marrying him.
That's me, I'm her.
You know, he
didn't trick me.
He just wore me down.
It makes sense
you two are friends.
I mean, hot girls
always stick together.
And you thought this
wasn't gonna be
a great party.
You know, I had no idea
Caltech is exactly
like my high school.
Well, it's not
exactly like it.
We're all
extremely smart.
Wow... you popular
girls are mean.
I'm gonna get some coffee.
You want some?
Uh, you're really going to
have caffeine in front of me
when I'm trying to get
my life back on track?
Uh, okay, let's pretend
you do have a problem.
I do.
You don't.
Yeah, but I do.
No, you don't!
But let's say you do.
And don't say you do,
because you don't!
Now, wouldn't you think
that throwing yourself
into your work would be
the best way to deal with it?
With what?
Your problem.
I thought I didn't have
a problem.
That was painful
to watch.
So where are we going?
I don't know.
Okay.
How Thelma and Louise of us.
Raj, why don't I care
about anything?
I'm sorry?
It's my baby.
I-I should care about
nurseries and colors,
and I don't--
what's wrong with me?
Well, crime-scene photos
near your crib spring to mind.
I keep waiting
to feel excited,
but it's not happening.
What if it
never happens?
Bernadette,
come on, look,
you're overthinking this,
okay?
You're gonna be
an amazing mom.
Even if you don't
believe it,
I know you have
maternal instincts.
Once, I was supposed
to babysit my brothers.
Our neighbor found them
naked in the backyard
eating crickets.
Happy and well-fed.
You see, that's what
I'm taking from that story.
Leonard, can I ask you
a question?
Is it about the
rotational symmetries
you should be
figuring out
or your fake
caffeine problem?
Howard, can I ask you
a question?
No.
All right, I'll just
toss this out to the room.
Um, I was thinking
that the best way
to fight my addiction is by
weaning myself off in steps.
Now, I couldn't find
a caffeine patch,
but I did find
what claims to be
a mind-boosting
caffeine suppository.
Yeah.
You know, the interesting fact
about the rectum...
Sheldon!
We are dealing with
an impossible deadline
from the Air Force
because of you.
So have an energy drink,
don't have an energy drink.
Order suppositories
and shove 'em
wherever you want,
I don't care!
You don't shove them.
They come with an
easy-glide applicator.
Right.
Listen to me.
We can't do anything
until you do your part.
So get up in front of
this whiteboard and do it!
I can't.
Yes, you can.
No...
I can't figure out
the math.
I've been racking
my brain for days,
and I've got nothing.
Seriously?
I can't do it.
I'm not as smart
as I think I am.
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
It's okay, we'll
figure something out.
But what if we can't?
It'll be fine.
You'll see.
Sheldon?
Buddy?
(snoring)
When the baby gets here,
you gotta teach me that.
Thank you so much, Bert.
This was great.
My pleasure.
You girls want
to take home
a two-gallon tub
of potato salad?
I think we're good.
Okay, well,
thanks for coming by.
You're nice people.
Well, so are you.
In fact, you know what?
We will never
take you for granite.
Did you get that?
Granite?
A little geology joke.
You need to leave.
I'm in love
with both of you now.
Okay.
Bye.
Uh, pull over.
What? Why?
Who are you calling?
You're gonna rat me out
to Howard, aren't you?
You're such a snitch,
no wonder I don't like you.
Whoa, I'm calling
my dad, okay?
He's got experience
dealing with pregnant ladies
because he's an OBGYN.
And experience
with crazy ladies
because of my mom.
(Facetime ringing)
Hello, Rajesh.
Are you calling
to ask for money?
What? No.
Are you calling to ask
for things
that cost money?
No.
Great. What's up?
This is my friend,
Bernadette.
She's pregnant,
and she's a bit worried,
so I thought maybe
you could talk to her.
Of course.
What seems to be the trouble?
Something's wrong.
I don't care about
any of the baby stuff
every other mom is so into.
Honestly, I'm not even sure
I like babies.
Look, some people are
baby people,
and some people
are not baby people.
It doesn't mean you won't
love your own baby.
But I thought I'd be
more excited.
Oh, being excited
isn't a guarantee of anything.
Rajesh's mother was thrilled
when she was pregnant with him.
After he was born, she doted
on his every move.
And you know what happened?
He broke her heart,
moved halfway around the world,
and dates only
poor white women.
So you never know.
Thank you.
I feel better now.
I don't!
FATHER: Good.
Bernadette, I hope
you have a daughter.
Um, I don't really know
how to say this.
Well, you could try
starting with "sir".
Right. Sorry, sir.
He said start with it,
not end with it.
- Sir...
- Hmm?
We've hit a bit
of a snag.
We're already behind schedule.
The computations required
to overcome
the deployability issues
are more significant
than we thought.
I understand that
we're under contract,
and I don't know what
the consequences
of violating that are,
but, uh...
we're not gonna
be able to deliver
in the time we promised.
(sighs)
How long do you need?
(Wolowitz clears throat)
We-We're thinking...
two years.
All right.
(chuckles)
That's it?
You're okay with that?
(scoffs) You think you're
the first government contractor
who isn't gonna deliver
on time?
We're still waiting
for a big space laser
Reagan ordered
to beat the commies.
Thanks for understanding,
sir.
Yes, thank you
so much.
We-We really
appreciate it.
LEONARD: All right,
pressure's off
WOLOWITZ (sighs):
Wanna see a movie?
SHELDON:
Popcorn's on me.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org