Hey, Dean.
It's me.
- How long you been back, Sam?
- About a year.
You been back practically this whole time?!
You finally had what you wanted, Dean.
I wanted my brother, alive.
You wanted a family.
You only gave it up
because of the way we lived.
But you had something,
and you were building something.
You got out, Dean!
You walked away from the life.
And it's as close to happiness
as I've ever seen a hunter get.
I hooked up with some other people.
- You? Working with strangers?
- They're more like family.
Gwen Campbell. That's Christian and Mark.
Campbell? Like...
Like your mom.
I'm your grandfather.
Samuel?
You can't be.
We're guessing whatever
pulled Sam up pulled me down.
- But you don't know what that is.
- Bingo.
Sam: Shape-shifter? Something that
can make itself look like anyone?
Legends of creatures
who can transform themselves
into animals or other men.
When the shape-shifter changes
shape, maybe it sheds.
You coming with me?
No, I'm going back for Lisa and Ben.
You'll be putting them in danger.
So, what, it's better to
leave them alone, unprotected
and then they're not in danger?
I made them vulnerable the
moment I knocked on their door.
Keep in touch, you hear?
'Course.
[Fire crackling]
[Breathing rapidly, sobbing]
[Static]
No!
[dialing]
[Static]
[Footsteps approach]
Shh, shh.
Okay.
[door opens, closes]
[Breathing heavily]
[Sniffles]
[Door opens, closes]
Shh!
[Footsteps depart]
[Exhales sharply]
Shh, shh.
[Muffled] Aah!
Aah!
[Baby fusses]
[Sobs]
[Gasps]
[Screaming]
Season 6 Episode 2
"Two and a Half Men"
[birds chirping]
[Trunk creaks]
[Sighs softly]
What's up?
Nothing.
At least wait till
you've checked the place out
before you hate it.
Open mind. That's all I ask.
[Sighs]
Yeah, all right.
I'll be back.
Whoa, hey, where's the fire?
I'm just going to check out the block.
And let your mom unpack the
kitchen by herself? Come on.
We'll go for lunch later, scope
out the neighborhood. Right?
Yeah, sounds like a plan.
Come on, why don't you give me a hand?
[Police radio chatter]
Sam: Where'd you find them?
We found the parents upstairs.
Pretty brutal.
Break-in?
Eh, alarm never went off.
Any leads on the baby?
- None yet.
- So what do you think?
You think it's okay? Alive?
I did yesterday.
[Sighs]
Thank you.
[Dog barks in distance]
[Doorbell rings]
- Hi.
- Hey.
Uh, one cheese, one everything?
Yeah.
Thank you.
There you go. Keep the change.
- Thanks.
What?
I thought we were going out.
Oh, yeah, I forgot. I'm sorry.
Sure.
I'll look for plates.
[Police radio chatter]
Hey.
So, I've been all over this...
No sulfur, no EMF.
Starting to think maybe
it's not our kind of thing.
Four couples slaughtered,
one part of the state,
within days of each other.
[keys thudding]
That's four babies taken
from locked houses.
Damn it!
[Sighs]
Explain to me how any version
of that is natural.
No, no, I agree. It's awful.
I'm just saying,
this one might be on the police.
Okay, so, either we got monsters
grabbing babies
to make baby stew
or we got a bunch of
psychotic yokels grabbing babies
to make baby stew.
Either way, it's baby stew, which is bad.
So... am I boring you?
You got someplace you need to be?
- No, no, no. I get it.
- Good.
Sometimes I wonder about you, Sam.
Sometimes I wonder about me, too.
[Chuckles lightly]
Well, I will go back over everything,
see if there's anything we missed.
Hey, Detective said the alarm
in the house never went off.
You mind taking a quick look,
see if anybody else had a system
from Harper Caine security?
Yeah, sure.
Any chance I get to hop on a computer.
[Chuckles]
[Cellphone beeps]
What the hell?
Hey, hey, give me that!
- What do you think you're doing?
- I just wanted to see it.
[Sighs]
Listen to me...
don't ever open this trunk.
You understand me?
Okay. Sorry.
But I don't get it.
You had your own rifle
when you were my age.
Ben, mark my words...
you will never, ever shoot a gun.
Ever.
I know what's going on.
You think something
might be coming for us.
There's nothing coming for us.
I could do what you do! You
could teach me how to shoot...
Shut up about the freakin' gun, okay?!
Okay.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
[Cellphone rings]
You were right. Every family that got hit...
Harper Caine Security.
So I pulled the client records.
Right, to see
if there's any other families
who fit the profile.
And there is another happy
couple, walking and talking.
6-month old baby...
like all the others.
What's the address?
Hey.
What happened?
Ben's been locked in his room for hours.
Says you yelled at him.
[Sighs]
What did he do?
Nothing.
What did you do?
He got into my tools.
I shouldn't have got mad.
You want to talk about this?
About?
Yelling at Ben,
keeping us in the house.
- I'm trying to keep us safe here.
- I'm not arguing, okay?
You're the expert. I'm just asking.
You said that you and your brother
killed whatever was after us.
And then... and then we moved,
just to be sure.
So what is it, Dean?
A monster? Or monsters in general?
I don't know.
- Something might come.
- What?
I don't know. I can't predict
what's gonna come after me.
Well, I'm gonna need some parameters.
We have to live our lives here.
I mean, at some point, I have to work.
Ben has school.
But if something happens on my watch...
I know you're trying to protect us,
but you're kind of scaring me a little, too.
[Car door opens]
[Car door closes]
[Trunk closes]
[Lock rattles]
[Door creaks]
[Groans]
[Crash]
[Cellphone rings]
Sam?
- I need your help. Now.
- What's wrong?
- I'm working this job...
- Dude.
Look, I just need you
with me on this, okay?
I'm out. I'm staying out.
- Make an exception!
- For what?
Look, I'm 30 minutes away,
and I will drive to your door
if you don't meet me.
And what's so nuts you got to
threaten a damn drive-by?
Where is it?
Strapped down in the back seat.
Welcome to the party, Guttenberg.
Okay.
Show me.
I got it. We've been over this.
- Humor me.
- Load clip.
Pull slide.
Safety off, safety on.
- And salt the windows and the doors.
- Of course.
Maybe I shouldn't go.
It's okay. You want to go, so go.
- You know what? Sam can handle this.
- Dean!
No offense, but if you don't
walk out that door,
I'm gonna shoot you.
Bet you're missing your ex
right about now...
the, uh, boring one.
God, shut up.
Just be careful, okay?
[Grunts]
Bye.
[Door closes]
[Engine shuts off,
truck door opens]
All right, so what do we know
about this thing?
Well, uh, it was fast.
And it freaked when I cut it with silver.
All right, so that narrows it down to...
A ghoul, a zombie,
a shifter, or about a dozen other things.
I don't recall seeing
baby-napping in the profiles.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Well, feel free to speak up
if you know anything.
[Engine turns over]
[Car dinging]
Seatbelt.
What am I, in the third grade?
A car should drive, not be a little bitch.
[Baby coos]
[Farts]
Yeah, don't take it personal.
[Sighs]
Well, we need to get some supplies.
I got an arsenal in the trunk.
Not that kind.
[Baby laughs]
All right, I'm pretty sure
that there's some kind
of, like, paste or jelly
you're supposed to put on their butt.
Like, uh, like that?
Yeah. Grab that.
So how do you know all this?
Uh, Lisa's got a baby niece,
so I've been on a few milk runs.
- Huh.
- Shut it.
- I just said "huh."
- I just said "shut it."
[Baby fusses]
All right, we got to get moving.
We got the waterworks
in like t-minus 10, so...
- Yeah. Okay.
- Go.
[Baby cries]
Hi.
[Crying intensifies]
Shh!
Come on, hang in there, buddy.
Hang in there, man.
Dean, make it stop.
How?
Everyone's staring at us
like we're child abusers.
[Crying continues]
Feed it.
We fed it!
Then what?
I don't know. You think I speak baby?
Maybe he needs a diaper change.
Oh, God. I hope not.
[sighs]
[Crying continues]
[Crying]
[imitates crying sarcastically]
Aww.
What's the matter?
What's his name?
- John.
- Bobby.
[Clears throat]
Bobby John.
Hi, Bobby John.
Aren't you handsome?
May I?
Oh. Uh...
Ohh.
I see now. Bobby John's a little wet.
[Sighs]
No offense... you two look exhausted.
I... I don't mind.
Lord knows I've changed a million diapers.
[Chuckles]
That's...
That's... that's a really nice offer.
Thank you.
But, uh [Clears throat]
I think we've got it.
Oh, it's nothing. Happy to help.
Give me the baby before
I stab you in your neck.
Dean!
[Grunts]
Help me!
- Hey!
- He's hurting me!
Get off of her!
Okay. All right.
All right.
[Tires squeal]
What the hell's a shifter
want with a baby, anyway?
You tell me.
And how the hell did it find us?
God, who the designed this thing, NASA?
You know, it could have been
following me this whole time...
- Since the baby's house.
- All right, you know what?
We got to get off the road,
get, uh, Bobby John here someplace safe,
figure this thing out.
[Bobby John fusses]
Okay, all right. Shh! Shh! Easy, kid.
Dispatcher: Control, 86. Go ahead.
Officer:
I need a 10-28 on Illinois plates...
"I" as in India, 4, Zulu, Oscar, 8, 9, 2.
[Police radio chatter]
Okay. All right. You know what?
I'll pay you money if you sit still.
[Laughs]
This is like defusing an I.E.D. with poop.
[Bobby John fusses]
Okay. All right, all right.
All right.
[Strained] You are golden, Bobby John.
Time to hit the hay.
[Hums Deep Purple's
"Smoke on the water"]
Dean, you're just gonna
make it cranky again.
Shh! It's working.
[continues humming]
Okay, if I put you down,
you gonna be a man about it?
Hmm?
Huh.
What?
You... You're just, uh,
actually... not awful at that.
Dude, I'm barely keeping that thing alive.
No, no, no, seriously.
You got a whole Dr. Huxtable
vibe coming off of you.
You're like... father material.
Yeah, well, I kind of had to be
lately, you know?
Sink or swim, right?
You mean Ben.
Yeah, I mean Ben.
I mean, I know he's not my kid,
but... I don't know,
I'm starting to feel like...
Yeah, he is.
[Chuckles]
When I think about the way we grew up...
I don't know.
I kind of feel like I have a chance
to do something different
with Ben, you know?
You sure about that?
What do you mean?
[Sighs heavily]
Look...
You clearly care about the kid.
But?
But... Moving them around,
keeping them on lock down...
I mean, you do have them
on lock down, right?
How is any of that different
from how we were raised?
So you're saying...
[Exhales sharply]
I'm not shoving anybody
into this life, okay?
This is temporary.
[Scoffs]
Dad always said it was temporary, Dean.
He said it for 22 years.
Look, I get it.
You want to watch out for them.
That's great.
I'm just asking...
how do you do that
and not turn into dad?
[Sighs lightly]
[Sighs]
[Paper rustles]
Crap. I can't believe I missed this.
What?
This house on Elm,
the... the mother was killed,
baby was grabbed,
but daddy wasn't living in the house
at the time, so he's still alive.
What do you say we
go and have a chat?
I say let's.
[Bobby John cries]
[Sighing] Oh.
You go.
You sure?
Unless you got a badge for Bobby John,
yeah, I'm sure.
[Crying continues]
[Door closes]
[Crying stops]
It's good, isn't it?
[Bobby John coos]
I just...
I still can't believe it.
I mean, I... it's one thing
to die like... that.
[Sighs]
Poor baby.
Just into thin air.
No thanks to you guys.
Well, that's why I'm here.
[Sighs]
You had filed for divorce?
It's important. I'm sorry.
She, uh...
She cheated on me.
And, well, I caught her.
And did you know the other man?
No, I... I mean, I didn't
catch her, catch her,
but she lied to me.
Okay.
[Sighs lightly]
We hadn't...
- you know, in a while.
- Ahh.
And... and then...
then she's pregnant.
- What did she say?
- She said it was mine.
I know.
And... and I said, "that's impossible,"
and "what is she talking about?"
And she says, "don't you remember
when you went out of town and
you came back early and we..."
But you didn't?
No.
I was at a damn softball tournament.
Whoever he was, he's the father.
[Buzzing]
[Inhales deeply]
[Pop]
[Bobby John cries]
[Cellphone rings]
Yeah?
Sam: I talked to the father.
He checks out, but the baby...
Yeah?
I think the shape-shifter is its dad.
[Wails]
You think?
Man: Manager. Everything okay in there?
Yeah. No, we're... we're...
we're fine, thank you.
Good night.
There's been complaints.
You mind opening the door, sir?
Uh, it's not a good time.
Just... just got out of the shower.
[Crying continues]
Shh.
- Get out of the way.
- Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
A child should be with his father.
Well, I got to be honest... I'm not
really seeing the family resemblance.
I'm not just talking about me.
I'm talking about our father.
[Gunshot]
[Bobby John cries]
Well, there goes our deposit.
You know, it's pretty smart, actually.
I mean, shifter poses as a guard
for the security company
to get near the house.
Then it scopes out the fam.
Yeah. Then daddy takes off,
and the shifter becomes daddy.
Few glasses of wine, shakes mama's trees,
comes back in nine months
to collect its prize.
I didn't even know they had babies.
I thought they were
just freaks of nature,
like... like X-Men style.
Yeah, you learn something new
every day, huh?
I've never seen a baby monster before.
Yeah.
Of course, it's not really a monster.
I mean, it's still just a baby.
It's not its fault its dad's a shifter.
Right, but it's a shifter, too.
It still doesn't change the fact
that we've got to...
we've got to look after this thing.
But what the hell
are we gonna do with it?
We can't actually drop it off
at an orphanage.
They might get upset
when it turns Asian.
Samuel.
What?
He'll know what to do.
You want to bring it to a bunch of hunters?
They're not just hunters, Dean.
They're our family.
- We don't know them.
- I do.
Not every hunter is a head case.
I mean Samuel is
actually a lot like you.
I'm a freakin' head case.
Well... pitch a better idea then.
Great. Samuel it is.
Well, aren't you just the best
disguise a monster ever wore.
[Chuckles]
I'm kidding, Dean.
Relax.
Oh, you got something to say?
No? All right. Well, you just
stand there and think at me.
So, what's our next move?
Well, I got a couple ideas.
Dean, let me see the little guy.
That's all right. I got him.
What do you think I'm gonna do?
You really don't want me
to answer that question.
Christian: Well, I'm curious.
Who exactly do you think we are?
Hunters.
That's funny.
Here I've been thinking we're family.
Hey. Let's not get worked up.
Yeah, yeah. Let's not.
Here, Dean.
It's fine.
Let me take him.
It's okay.
Oh, you're a big fella, aren't you?
Yeah. I haven't held
one of these in a long time.
Your mom was the tiniest.
She was bald as a cue ball.
All right, so what the hell
are we gonna do with him?
- Raise him?
- Raise him.
- What, you got another suggestion?
- But...
It's dangerous out
there for him, Dean.
And what about in here?
What are we gonna study him, poke at him?
Your mind goes right to torture, Dean.
Don't assume that for everyone.
- What exactly are you trying to say?
- Sorry, I heard about what you majored in,
down in the pit?
What the hell is your problem, man?
[Sighs] You're starting
to become a pain in my ass.
Christian, take it easy, man.
He's my brother.
Samuel:
We all done bristling up here or what?
Nobody's doing anything to him, Dean.
When he's old enough,
we throw it to him.
He wants to volunteer
to help out, that's fine.
Could be great.
How?
Think of the kind of hunter
he'll grow up to be.
You all are joking, right?
I mean, come on!
You can't... Angelina Jolie a shape-shifter.
Give me the baby.
Why can't you give me
an inch of trust, Dean?
Maybe because you two
are suddenly back from the dead,
and I seem to be the only one who wants
to know how the hell that happened!
You're not the only
one who wants to know.
There's just a little too much
mystery with this family
for me to get comfy.
Then don't, but don't put it on us.
All we're trying to do is invite you in.
- Christian.
- Yeah?
You and Arlene...
still no luck on the baby front?
Not yet, no.
But you want one?
[Chuckles lightly]
Yeah, we do.
- Wait, hold on.
- It's okay, Dean.
It's all right.
Congrats.
It's a boy... sometimes.
[Laughs]
The crap I do for this family.
- You're kidding, right?
- Go to hell, Dean.
Well, you have no business
raising anything.
Sam: Why, Dean?
'Cause he's a hunter?
[Dog barks]
Check the back door.
Downstairs... panic room.
He'll be safe there.
Go.
We got it! Go! Now!
[Door closes]
[Rifle cocks]
You have something of ours.
I know he's here.
I can feel him.
[Bones crack]
Run!
[Bones snap]
- No!
- Mark!
[Gwen coughs]
Easy, tiger.
Get the silver nets.
We're gonna box him up.
[Bobby John cries]
Come on, Bobby John.
You have got to keep quiet.
[Gunshots]
That does not sound good up there.
[Gwen screams]
[Glass breaks]
[Sighs]
All right.
I'm going up.
Stay with the baby.
[Bobby John cries]
[Grunts]
What the...
- Give me the baby.
- No way in hell.
[Groans]
[Gasps]
[Coughs]
Pretty sure it's not a myth now.
Sam: Yeah.
What the hell was that thing?
- We think it may have been an Alpha.
- An Alpha? Like...
Like all monsters
come from somewhere, right?
And you think that this one was the...
King shape-shifter.
The first one who spawned all the others.
There's tons of lore about it.
The first one?
Sam: That's why it was so strong.
And why nothing we had stopped it.
And he said that he could
find the baby anywhere,
that he could feel it,
like there's a connection.
That's in the lore, too.
What the hell's it want
with babies, anyway?
Softball team?
[Sam sighs]
I got no clue.
Great.
Well, then, how do we kill it?
I don't know if we can.
[Door creaks]
You know, it's funny.
What's that?
Just before you, uh, ganked
that shifter in the motel,
he mentioned a father,
which makes sense now,
'cause he meant the Alpha.
- Huh. Yeah, I guess so.
- Did you hear him say that?
Uh...
I don't know.
Kind of a hot moment, you know?
Why?
Well, 'cause if you heard him,
then... then you knew
the Alpha was out there.
Okay.
And if you knew the
Alpha was out there,
then you knew he
might come after the baby.
In which case, you were using
the baby as bait.
So, was that the plan,
- to use the baby as bait?
- Of course not.
[Chuckles]
Dean, I just thought Samuel's
was the safest place.
That's all.
Right. Of course.
[chuckles]
[Car door closes]
Samuel: No, I didn't catch it.
It killed three of my people.
I shot it full of elephant
tranquilizer and it chuckled!
[Sighs]
To be honest, I'm not sure
I want to find it.
But, yeah,
we will find a way to catch it.
Yeah, sure. I'll bring it
right to you... gift-wrapped.
[Beep]
[Sighs]
[Footsteps approach]
Hey.
Hey. Where's Ben?
Bike ride.
What?
I don't... I don't know
what to do here, Lis.
I mean, if I knew for sure
what the safest thing was,
then I'd do it.
Stay here and look after you guys...
or get as far away as
I possibly can, but...
I don't know.
And I get what I've been doing
lately, you know,
with the yelling and the...
acting like a...
like a prison guard.
It's just... that's not me.
You tell yourself you're not
gonna be something, you know?
You know, my dad was exactly like this,
all the time.
- And it scared the hell out of me.
- Dean.
[Sighs]
Can I be honest?
Maybe we're safer with you here.
Maybe gone.
I don't know.
The one thing that I do know
is, that you're not a construction worker.
You're a hunter.
And now you know your
brother's out there.
Things are different.
- You don't want to be here, Dean.
- Yes, I do.
Okay.
Okay, but... but you also
want to be there, and...
I get it.
You're white-knuckling it,
living like this.
Like what you are
is some bad, awful thing,
but you're not.
But I'm not gonna have this discussion
every time you leave.
And this is...
this is just gonna keep happening, so...
I need you to go.
I... I can't just lose you and Ben.
- That's not what I'm saying.
- You're saying hit the road.
Dean, if there's some rule
that says this all has to be either, or...
How 'bout we break it?
Me and Ben will be here, and...
you come when you can.
Just...
just come in one piece, okay?
And you really think we could
pull something like that off?
It's worth a shot, right?
[Chuckles lightly]
[Intro to Deep Purple's
"Smoke on the water" plays]
# We all came out to Montreux #
[engine revs]
# on the Lake Geneva shoreline, #
# to make records with a mobile. #
[car departs]
# We didn't have much time, #
# smoke on the water, #
# a fire in the sky. #
sync by Rafael UPD, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com/
Edited by Scooby