It's Sam, Bobby.
He's just... he's different.
Something's not right to me.
I... I can't just lose you and Ben.
Me and Ben will be here,
and you come when you can.
Just come in one piece.
And you really think we could
pull something like that off?
It's worth a shot.
What the hell's wrong with you, Sam?
You knew about the cure.
- - No I didn't.
- 'Cause if you had known,
it'd be almost like you
let him get turned.
Just tell me what the hell is going on.
- Dean?
- Ben, just stay there.
- I thought I heard you.
- ...I said stay back!
Cure's an old Campbell recipe.
Nobody's tried it since God knows.
From what I hear,
the stuff is a bad trip.
At least, uh...
You got my back.
No matter what happens,
I can always count on you,
- right, Sammy?
- Of course, Dean.
I'm Ashley Frank, and I will...
He said he'd call,
but of course he never did.
But... I don't know.
I just... we had such a good time.
I... I should call him, right?
Do you think?
I mean, should I call him?
I don't know, it's...
Oh. Uh, Olivia, just hold on a sec.
I just need the truth. That's all.
I really gotta go, okay?
Call you later.
- I pity you.
- I'm sorry?
You're sad and pathetic,
and I pity you...
only reason I'm giving you
a head's up.
Stay away from the clam chowder.
I flavored it with my own...
seasoning.
Hey, Jane.
You know that new girl, Misty?
- Way hotter than you.
- Excuse me?
Basically, she's an eight,
and you're a...
a three.
Can I get you anything else, ma'am?
No, thank you.
I ran over a homeless man once
and I never even stopped
to see if he was alive.
I hate mommy.
I want to burn her in her sleep.
I don't know what it is,
but you just give me the creeps.
Like I get physically nauseous.
You're pathetic.
Loser.
- Desperate.
- Stupid.
Mousy.
You're a desperate, pathetic loser.
You're gonna die alone.
Hey, can you come get me?
You sound awful.
Have you been drinking?
I think I'm going crazy.
I'm freaking out.
Of course you are.
'Cause you are a freak.
You're certifiable.
Every time the phone rings,
my stomach drops.
Jane with another crisis.
You're a walking disaster.
The whole family's just waiting
for your next big breakdown, Jane.
We're like hostages.
Why don't you just go ahead
and kill yourself already?
Season 6 Episode 6
"You Can't Handle the Truth"
I know what I saw, Bobby.
We tested him.
Salt, silver... everything.
He threw me to that vamp.
I'm telling you,
it's not my brother.
Well, then he's something
we ain't ever seen before.
Yeah, or it's freakin' Lucifer.
Did you call Cass?
Of course I called Cass.
He's not answering.
Screw him. I can't wait anymore.
Look, I get it. You're rattled.
You're right to be,
but let's be professional...
Professional?
He watched me get turned!
What you saw...
are you sure that's what you saw?
Damn it, Bobby! Yes, I know.
Well, "you know"
ain't the same as proof.
'Cause we're talking about...
We're talking about doing
something about this, and fast.
It's not just the vamp.
He has been different from the jump.
All right. I'm with you.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
I'll hit the books, hard.
Just don't shoot him yet, all right?
Watch him. We need facts.
'Cause if it ain't Sam...
we don't know what it is.
And if we're gonna put him down,
we need to know how.
I don't even want to ride
in the same car with him,
much less work a damn case.
Get in the car. He's your case.
Hey. I was just, uh,
I was leaving Lisa a message.
- Still hasn't called you back, huh?
- No.
- Sucks.
- Yeah.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
How are you?
Me? Great.
Here, look. Check this out.
Think it might be something.
Four people, out of nowhere,
all in the last couple of weeks.
What do you say?
Yeah. Sounds like a plan.
Let's go.
I don't understand.
Why would Federal Investigators
be interested in a suicide?
Well, um...
It's a new, more caring administration.
Well, I already told the cops.
Jane was having a really bad day,
so I... I did what
any sister would do.
I... tried to cheer her up, you know?
Told her to hang in there.
You know what a "tell" is?
Excuse me?
It's a poker term...
for when you're bluffing.
Like what you just
did with your hair.
What are you trying to say?
You're lying.
What?!
Tell us what you
did to your sister.
Okay. You're right.
I was lying.
I wanted to tell her, "I love you".
"I'm here for you."
Oh, but what came out was...
"you're a burden.
Just kill yourself."
Who says that?!
I... I... I just couldn't stop!
See anything in the house?
No hex bags,
no sulfur, no EMF. You?
A tuba and an issue
of Crochet Today.
So, what, already kinda suicidal?
Right, and then big sis's
taxicab confession
sends her over the edge.
Question is, what made big sis
open her big, fat mouth
in the first place?
Yeah, that is the question.
Are organic fruits and veggies
worth the high cost?
Thanks. Uh, can you grab
some gauze, please?
Mm-hmm.
Should've had you
prescribe me a Valium.
Just relax.
- What is the truth?
- It'll be fine.
I'm Ashley Frank.
I got to be honest, Paul...
I don't really want to be here.
You and most people,
but you know what?
I don't take it personally.
Okay, open up.
You and Donna should
come over for supper.
How long has it been?
There. Worst part's over.
I'm not really into Donna anymore.
She's old.
Your wife looks great for her age.
Her saggy skin makes me want to hurl.
I have urges, you know.
Okay.
Remember that camping trip
I missed 'cause I was sick?
Well, I wasn't.
I was just afraid to be around Melissa.
My daughter Melissa?
But then...
she spent the night
for Jill's slumber party.
Oh...
it just seemed so easy, you know?
What are you saying?
It's not so much I
couldn't control myself.
I just knew I wouldn't get caught.
And I didn't get caught.
Hey. You got anything?
I've been
up all night lookin'.
Nothing fits.
Awesome.
You got anything else to go on?
Yeah, my skin crawls being
in the same room with him.
Why don't you look that up?
I'm working on it.
I don't know how much longer
I can do this, Bobby.
You got to figure out
what the hell he is and fast.
I'm trying.
But, Dean, there's a
worst-case scenario.
What, Satan's my
co-pilot? Yeah, I know.
Well, that'd be the
other worst case.
Well, then what?
Maybe it's just Sam.
I gotta go.
Dean. You got a day, Bobby,
and then I'm handling this.
There was another one.
Yeah? What?
Dentist drilled a guy to death.
You mean the... non-sexy kind
of drilling, right?
50 bucks says he's mixed up
in all the crazy.
- You think?
- Yeah. Let's go talk to him.
Okay. Uh...
Why don't you go ahead? I'll catch up.
I'm gonna do a little research.
You sure?
Yeah. We got to know
what we're up against, right?
Yeah. Yeah, good idea.
Thanks a lot.
Anything from marathon man?
Not exactly.
He hung himself in his cell
before I could get to him.
Yikes.
But he was definitely involved.
Just got the scoop from his assistant.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Let's say the stuff that his
patient was confessing to...
I'd have murdered him, too.
So, root canal and Russian roulette...
both of 'em, it's like
they were cursed, right?
I mean, people are just compelled
to puke the truth all over 'em?
Oh, getting hit with
the ugly truth, you go postal?
I'd call that a curse.
Do me a favor...
I'm going to the morgue
to check out the body.
Why don't you take the dentist's
office, see what you see?
Yeah. No problem.
Jane and Dr. Conley.
I heard. Awful.
What do I have to do with it?
Honestly? You're the only thing
they have in common.
Did they say anything to you
before they, uh...?
Sorry. Not really.
Right.
Ah, I was just fishing.
Thanks.
Hey, by the way,
how 'bout my horn?
Sorry?
Stolen horn?
Right. Yeah. We're...
we're working on it.
Well, I hope so.
Thing's one-in-a-billion.
What makes it
one-in-a-billion again?
It's a museum piece.
And near as anyone can tell,
about a thousand years old.
Where's it from?
No one knows.
When did it get swiped?
About...
two weeks ago,
same day Jane died.
Castiel? Hello?
Possible loose nuke down here.
Angelic weapon.
Kinda your department.
You hear that, Cass?
Hello, Dean.
Are you kidding me?
I have been on red alert about Sam,
and you come for
some stupid horn?!
You asked me to
be here, and I came.
I... I've been asking you to
be here for days, you dick!
I didn't come about Sam
because I have
nothing to offer about Sam.
Well, that's great,
because for all we know,
he's just gift wrap for Lucifer.
No, he's...
he's not Lucifer.
And how do you know that?
If Lucifer escaped the cage,
we'd feel it.
What is wrong with him?
I don't know, Dean. I'm sorry.
What happened to you, Cass?
You used to be human,
or at least like one.
I'm at war.
Certain...
regrettable things are
now required of me.
And Gabriel's Horn of Truth?
That's a real thing?
- You've seen it?
- We think it's in town.
Something's forcing people...
Oh, well, you're welcome!
It isn't the Horn of Truth.
What are you talking about?
You were gone for like two
seconds. Where did you look?
Everywhere.
Right.
Well, nice seeing you, anyway.
Dean.
What?
About your brother.
I...
I don't know what's wrong with him,
but I do want to help.
I'll make inquiries.
Yeah. Thanks.
Now, I'd actually like to see
all the suicides
that came in this week,
not just Dr. Giggles.
Is that gonna be a problem?
Well, they're... they're already gone.
As in transferred?
Yeah, not exactly.
Would you like to tell me
what's going on here,
or should I have a little chat
with your supervisor?
They're gone.
As in... gone, gone?
...Predatory prices.
Here's the facts.
Tune in weekdays
for the newest addition
to our award-winning local team.
Find out the truth
about your layaway living room.
Another one?
Uh, no, thanks. I'm working.
Hey, what's up?
All the bodies are gone.
What do you mean, they just vanished?
That's what the coroner said.
But I got a lead.
One of the missing bodies,
She died a whole week
before everybody else.
Suicide?
Reported as a car accident,
but no reason it couldn't have been.
So then that would make her
our patient zero, right?
I'm thinking maybe.
Whatever got this whole curse
thing rolling started with her.
I'm at her place now,
corner of Burnham and 159th.
Yeah, give me 10.
You know what?
I will have that other one.
Thought you were working.
I am working up to it.
You okay?
No, not really.
I talked to local experts
to bring you the truth.
On me.
Anything else I can get you?
I'd just like the freakin' truth.
But I'll settle for another one.
Sometimes I think
I can't get pregnant
'cause God knows
my marriage is a sham.
Why'd I say that?
I mean, I've been
snorting oxy all day.
Why'd I say that?
I'm pretty sure I know.
I've got to go.
Thank you.
I'm sitting like this
so you'll look at my breasts.
I just bought them.
I need a lot of attention.
Good luck with that.
Hey, anything you're
itchin' to tell me?
Not really.
Sorry to disappoint.
Ah, that's all right.
I'm just testing a theory.
Well, I'm here hittin' the books
while drinking a nice glass of milk
and watching "Tori & Dean."
Wh... wait, w... who and Dean?
Tori Spelling.
I'm a huge fan.
Girl's a real talent.
Oh, I guess it does
work over the phone.
You know what else?
I get a pedicure once in a while...
this nice Vietnamese joint.
Okay. Okay, please stop.
This one gal, Nhung Phuong...
her name means "Velvet Phoenix."
Tiny thing, but the grip on her.
She starts on my toes,
and I feel like I am gonna...
Whoa, whoa! Hey, come on, m...
Now I'm scarred for life.
Thank you.
I never told anyone that.
Why am I telling you?
Maybe 'cause you're my favorite.
Although, Sam's a better hunter.
Lately, anyway.
Whoa. Why the hell
am I tellin' you this?!
Because I'm cursed.
- Cursed?
- Yes.
How is it...
That half the time you clean a mess,
you end up dirty?
Actually, this might be the best thing
that's happened to me in a while.
What do you mean?
Dean...
Dean, what damn fool move
are you about to...
I gotta go.
Okay.
But did you know my first
girlfriend turned out to be a...
No, no.
Mnh-mnh. Mnh-mnh.
It's Sam. Leave me a message.
Sam, it's me.
Listen, I'm on my way to you,
but if you get this before then,
give me a call back.
There's a few things I want to ask you.
So, why is there an investigation
for a car accident?
It wasn't an accident.
Corey committed suicide.
You know...
I wondered.
I... I'm sorry.
I just...
So, you had some idea Corey
might have taken her own life?
Well...
She had been going through
a bit of a hard time lately...
at school. And then,
um, her cat, Mittens,
had just ran away.
But, really...
it was her boyfriend.
She was sure that
he was cheating on her,
but he was just very good
at covering his tracks.
Which, of course, made her
completely obsessed with...
Finding out the truth.
Yeah.
You mind if I check out her room?
Hey.
So.... I saw you called.
Yeah, it's been crazy.
Ben won't even talk about it.
Lisa, I'm sorry,
but this is actually the...
worst time in the universe to talk.
Ca... can we do this later?
You shoved my kid, Dean.
How about we do this now?
It wasn't like that.
Then how was it?
I can't really explain.
You want to know the truth?
Probably not.
You've got so much buried in there,
and you push it down,
and you push it down.
Do you honestly think
that you can go through life
like that and not freak out?
Just, what, drink half a fifth a night
and you're good?
You knew what you signed up for.
Yeah, but I didn't
expect Sam to come back.
And I'm glad he's okay. I am.
But the minute he walked
through that door, I knew
it was over.
You two have the most unhealthy,
tangled-up, crazy thing
I've ever seen.
And as long as he's in your life,
you're never gonna be happy.
That came out so
much harsher than I meant.
It's not your fault.
I'm not saying don't be close to Sam.
I'm close to my sister.
But if she got killed,
I wouldn't bring her
back from the dead!
Okay, Lis...
I'm not gonna lie.
Okay, me and Sam, we...
we've got issues.
No doubt.
But you and Ben...
Me and Ben can't
be in this with you.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Mittens.
Hey, where you been? I found something.
It can wait. We got to talk.
Yeah. What's up?
There's a few things I want to ask you,
and, uh, you're
gonna tell me the truth.
Uh, yeah, Dean. Of course.
What are you talking about?
Whoa. Are you saying you're...
I asked for the truth.
And you know what? I'm getting it.
So, like I said,
I have a few questions for you.
When that vamp attacked me,
why did you just stand there?
I... I didn't.
I froze.
You froze.
You have been Terminator
since you got back.
I don't know. Shock?
And then it was too late.
I feel terrible about it.
Believe me.
Dean...
I can't lie here.
Do you really think
I would let something like that
happen on purpose?
You're my brother.
H... how could you even...
Okay.
Sorry.
I... I thought...
I thought I saw something.
I...
I guess I was wrong.
It's just been a
really, really bad day.
Hey. It's okay.
I got your back, all right?
I always have.
Thanks, Sammy.
So this was the chicks pet?
Well, she was obsessed.
I think you mean crazy.
All right, so cat skull,
uh, grains-of-paradise seed,
devil's shoestring.
Mix 'em well, you got yourself
a summoning spell.
Demon?
God.
Corey was so desperate for the truth
about her boyfriend's cheating heart,
she went digging around.
Nothing panned out,
so she went looking
for a different kind of help.
- Opened a door she couldn't close.
- Yeah.
Now anyone in town
who asks aloud for the truth
invokes Veritas.
And she doesn't
just give it to you,
she slams you with it
until you kill yourself.
And she gets her tribute.
So, all that "tribute"
vanishing from the morgue.
What do you think, uh,
Soylent-Green situation?
Gods got to eat, too.
Which means we got to take her
out or you're on the menu.
All right, well, what do we know,
besides crazy cat lady?
- Well, dogs are her Achilles heel.
- Naturally.
And she was a pretty hands-on
goddess back in the day.
Her thing was coming
down from the mountain
to speak truth to the masses.
She wanted more than tribute.
She wanted to be worshipped.
An attention whore.
If you want to put it that way.
And what is the 21st-century version
of speaking truth to the masses?
So you really think
this God is slumming
as some farm-league Diane Sawyer?
Eh, call it a hunch.
I'm Ashley...
I'm Ashley Frank,
bringing you "Frank Talk."
Let's do that again.
I'm Ashley Frank,
bringing you "Frank Talk."
Again.
I'm Ashley Frank.
Are organic fruits and veggies
really worth the cost?
She's creepy.
I mean, the hair alone.
I don't know, man.
Maybe there's nothing here.
Are we... we're spinning?
Do the new rent-to-own prices...
...A recent trend
in furniture stores...
...But think twice
before you decide to buy...
Before you make that big purchase...
Okay.
We'll ask the councilman
ourselves.
Are we still rolling?
Hold on.
Check this out.
Zoom in on that.
Looks pretty normal, right?
I'm sure inside it's
chock full of creep.
Ready?
Yeah.
- And that's...?
- Dog's blood.
Do I even want to know
where you got that?
Probably not.
Ugh.
All right, let's do this.
So where is all the creep?
You came for dinner.
Mm. Sit tight.
You're up next.
The tongue...
is the tastiest part.
It's where the lies roll off.
Mmm.
Mmm!
I cannot wait to eat yours.
I mean, I've seen liars before,
but you two?
Gold standard.
Point of professional pride.
I wouldn't be so
cocky if I were you, Dean.
You know what happens when you
base your life on lies, right?
The truth comes along and...
So, while you've
still got your tongue,
God knows you've got an earful.
I think it's your
turn to spill some.
How 'bout we play a
little truth or truth?
What should we
ask Dean first, hmm?
Something...
personal about you?
Hey, Dean, I'm curious.
What do you really
feel about your brother?
Better now.
As of yesterday, I wanted
to kill him in his sleep.
I thought he was a monster.
But now I think...
Now you think what?
He's just acting like me.
What do you mean?
It's the gig.
You're covered in blood until
you're covered in your own blood.
Half the time, you're about to die.
Like right now.
I told myself I wanted out...
That I wanted a family.
But you were lying.
No.
But what I'm good at...
is slicing throats.
I ain't a father,
I'm a killer...
and there's no changing that.
I know that now.
So, Sam walking back into your life
must have been a relief.
Hmm?
Mallory to your Mickey.
And how do you feel about
the band getting back together?
Hmm, Sam?
Look...
what we do...
is hard,
but... we watch out for each other
and that's what's important.
And that's it.
That's the truth.
No.
No, it's not.
- You said yourself... I can't lie.
- How are you doing that?
That's not possible.
You're lying to me!
No, I'm not!
What are you? What is he?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Really? I doubt that.
I doubt anything that comes
out of your mouth right now.
You're not human.
What?
You didn't know that?
Now, that I believe.
Dean, it's me.
You are not my brother.
Just listen.
What are you?!
I'm me, Dean.
Look, please, just let me explain.
Why the hell should I believe
anything you say?
Okay, okay. You want
the truth? Here it is.
Here it is. God's honest.
She was right.
There's something wrong
with me, really wrong.
I've known it for a while.
I lied to you. Yeah.
And... I let you get turned
by that vamp.
Because I knew there
was a cure, Dean,
and we needed in that nest!
- And I knew you could handle it!
- Handle it?!
I could've died!
I could've killed Ben.
And that should stop me cold.
But I... I just don't feel it.
You what?
Ever since I came back,
I am a... a better hunter
than I've ever been!
Nothing scares me anymore!
'Cause I can't feel it.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I think...
I need help.
sync by elderman, corrected bygloriabg
for www.addic7ed.com...
Edited by Scooby