DEAN: A freak animal killing
machine by moonlight.
I mean, werewolves are bad-ass.
We already know how to
bring these suckers down.
One of these bad
boys right to the heart.
There's something wrong with me,
really wrong. I need help.
[Grunts]
- CASTIEL: How much do you sleep?
- SAM: I don't.
DEAN: At all?
- It's his soul. It's gone.
- So, where is it?
Still in the cage
with Michael and Lucifer.
What the hell was that thing?
- SAMUEL: It may have been an Alpha.
- An Alpha? Like...
The first one who spawned all the others.
There's tons of lore about it.
CROWLEY: Bring me creatures.
Aim high on the food chain, please.
- We ain't your employees.
- Of course you are!
You're nothing but a
punk-ass crossroads demon.
Was a punk-ass crossroads demon.
Now? King of hell.
I snap my fingers,
Sam gets his soul back
or I shove Sam right back in the hole.
[Electricity buzzes]
[Thunder rumbles]
Did he eat?
You gave him a bath, right?
Well, did you take him to the park?
And did he make
pee-pee and poo-poo?
Good.
Tell him Daddy loves him.
Be home soon.
[Branches snap]
[Car alarm deactivates]
[Thunder rumbles]
[Creature snarls]
[Creature growls]
What the...
Season 6 Episode 8
"All Dogs Go To Heaven"
[blues music plays]
I know, Bobby, but there's
got to be another way.
I don't know, keep digging.
I mean, if Crowley
thinks we're just gonna...
Crowley thinks you're
just gonna what, Dean?
Is that Bobby Singer?
Give him a kiss from me.
I'll call you back.
Good news, boys!
[Sighs]
I've got a job for you.
I'm gonna say this once.
You can take your job
and shove it up your ass.
Is that any way to talk to your boss?
You're not my boss, dick-bag.
Dean, Dean. Been through this.
Quit clutching your pearls.
You've been working for me
for some time now. Sam here, longer.
We didn't know.
Like that makes a difference to you.
You'd sell your brother
for a dollar right now
if you really needed a soda.
- Look, I'm sending you...
- No.
Beg pardon?
I've done some shady stuff in my time,
but I am not doing this.
No.
10 quid says you will.
SAM: Aah! Aah!
[Grunting]
You like pain, Sam?
You like hell?
You need to stop thinking
of this as some kind of deal.
This is a hostage situation,
you arrogant little thug.
I own your brother!
Do you understand me?
[Grunts lightly]
Come on, Dean, smile.
It's not that bad.
Here's incentive...
You bag me a live Alpha,
and I'll give you little Sammy's
soul back, with a cherry on top.
What, Alpha vamp not
good enough for you?
Best mind where you poke your nose,
if you want to keep it.
Your merry little hike up
the food chain starts here.
Businessman found dead in his car...
chest ripped open, heart missing.
- Sounds like?
- Werewolf.
No, it's not a full moon.
Werewolves turning on
the full moon... so '09.
He's right.
Samuel and I ganked one about
six months back on a half-moon.
Things have been out of
whack for a while now, I guess.
Yeah, I guess.
So, it's settled then.
You bag the howler,
bring it home to papa.
See you soon, boys.
So, the vic's a real class act.
Owned a bunch of
slum-grade apartments.
Couple of houses, too.
So this is it? This is...
this is what you're gonna do?
What am I doing?
Crowley. He's so far up our asses
we're... we're...
we're coughing sulfur,
but you... you're
just gonna work the case?
Well, he's got us
by the short and curlies.
What else are we supposed to do?
It's just... you know, man, I...
I'm working for a demon now.
I don't even know who you are.
I just...
I just need a second to adjust.
[Sighs heavily]
Look... this is a crap situation.
I get it.
But, Dean, I am still me...
same melon, same memories.
I-I still like the same music.
I still think about Suzie Heizer.
Biology class Suzie Heizer?
Can you blame me?
Look, I know you don't trust me
and I can't take back what I did,
but I'm going to prove it to you.
I'm still your brother.
[Police radio chatter]
How you doing?
Agents Holt and Wilson.
Feds?
Yeah.
What are the Feds doing here?
Oh, we're specialists.
They call us in to answer the questions
of mouth-breathing dick monkeys.
So, you gonna walk us through this,
or, uh...
Dock worker.
Guy on the morning shift found him...
chest ripped wide open.
Same as the body in the car?
Yeah, second one in two days.
SAM:
Internal organs missing on both vics?
Like their hearts?
Uh... Looks like it, yeah.
How'd you know?
So, this guy, he...
he have any enemies?
Yeah, plenty, but, uh,
I don't think it was a
wolf or possibly a cougar
that had a beef with the guy.
You do realize these were animal attacks?
An animal out here.
What, you think it came for the sailing?
[Papers rustle]
[Snorts lightly]
[Sam scoffs]
Morning.
You didn't sleep.
'Cause you don't... sleep.
Right.
Yeah. That's not creepy at all.
Not like I can help it.
So, you gonna just lay
there staring at me,
or you want to hear what I dug up?
All right.
So, we know that werewolves
are basically Ed gone wild, right?
I mean, whoever they hate,
they kill when they wolf out.
So, I've been playing connect the victims.
And?
And I think I found
a common denominator.
So come on. Uh...
Get the lead out, huh?
Let me get dressed, Robocop.
Yes, can I help you?
Is Cal Garrigan at home?
We've got a few questions
we'd like to ask him.
Yeah. Um, come in.
Honey, um,
why don't you go play in your
room for a little while, okay?
[Sighs]
Excuse the mess.
Please sit.
Um... Can I get you guys anything?
No, thank you.
Um, so Cal is your boyfriend?
That's right.
And where is he?
Uh, sleeping, I think.
You mind telling him up and at 'em?
He's got some guests.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Cal...
[Dog Snarls]
Lucky, shh!
These are Agents...
Holt and Wilson. Morning... ish.
Hey.
What's this?
You out late last night, Cal?
Just, uh, you know, a
couple beers with friends.
How many's a couple?
I don't know. Three, four tops.
If all you had was beer,
then how come you're sweating vodka?
And looks to me like you slept
in those clothes. Am I right?
[Chuckles]
I don't know. I-I guess.
So what you're saying is,
you got blind drunk, you blacked out.
Something tells me this
isn't the first time.
So, Cal, truthfully,
who knows what you've
really been up to at night?
[Exhales sharply]
[Mug thuds]
Look, what's this about?
We're investigating the
death of Ronald Garrigan.
My brother?
Sorry for your loss.
Yeah, I thought that was
some kind of animal attack.
No love lost between
the two of you, huh?
Look, we had our
differences, I guess.
You love your brother,
of course, but...
Ron had a lot of problems.
He was, uh, volatile.
Last time he was here,
you called the cops?
Yeah, look, he came
in here all messed up
and he was yelling.
He shoved Mandy.
So, yeah, I called the cops.
I don't see how that has to do with...
Your landlord was found dead this week.
Were you aware of that?
Saw it in the papers. Why?
Well, you two were pretty
far behind on your rent, right?
He had sent eviction papers?
[Laughs]
I-I'm sorry.
That was an animal attack.
Funny enough, yeah... both of 'em were.
So, great, great. Yeah, guys.
What in the hell do you
think I had to do with 'em?
Just following procedure.
Had to ask.
You two have a good day.
So, Cal's a prince.
Yeah, doesn't even know
where he was last night.
Bag him now?
No. We make sure.
Really?
Before we hand him over
to a lifetime of demon rape?
Yeah, really.
[Sighs]
[Engine shuts off]
[Country music plays]
SAM: Boy, Cal just doesn't
know when to quit.
Three scuzzy bars,
one scuzzy strip club,
a chili-dog joint,
seven or eight nightcaps,
and now... scotches in the library.
I'm getting cirrhosis just watching this.
Other than that, we got squat.
Let's just see.
Dude, sun's up.
This guy's still on two legs.
In theory.
He ain't wolfing out.
Well, not tonight anyway.
Let's head back.
We can re-attack this
in a couple hours.
[Engine turns over]
Catch you later, man.
[Car door opens, closes]
[Engine turns over]
[Groans lightly]
CAL: Lucky.
What are you doing?
No!
No! [Screaming]
[Lucky snarling]
[Bones crunching, flesh squishing]
[Breathing heavily]
MANDY: Lucky, that's enough.
[Inhales sharply]
[Groans lightly]
Cal?!
[Clicks tongue]
Typical.
Oh, Lucky.
Honestly.
You are the only decent
boyfriend I have ever had.
[Shower running]
[Police radio chatter]
I'm gonna go out on a limb
and say that it's not Cal.
[Scoffs]
Masterful deduction, Sherlock.
I mean, a werewolf attack in daylight?
This whole thing is just weird.
Dogs and cats living
together... mass hysteria.
So, you know this means
that we're down to one suspect, right?
I know.
I mean, Mandy is right at
the deep end of the vic pool.
Can you do it?
Do what?
Shove her in the trunk,
serve her up to Crowley.
Yeah, Sam, I can do it.
You still feeling hot, baby?
Here, have some juice.
Make you feel better.
Okay?
[Gasps] Hey, see?
Lucky knows you're not feeling well,
[Toy squeaking]
and he wants you to feel better.
[Whines]
He loves you, doesn't he?
There's a good boy.
[Toy squeaks]
- He loves a squeak.
- Yeah.
[Laughing]
The leg broke off.
Lucky, look what you did!
Reporter: Next up
on the Buffalo midday news,
we'll talk to animal control
about the recent
animal attacks.
But first, the weather.
What,
am I interrupting the morning show?
Come on. Let's go for a walk.
Hey, is that blood?
Have you killed a bird again?
Bad dog!
[Engine shuts off]
Okay, okay.
- See you later.
- Bye. Bye-bye.
Ma'am?
Agents.
What are you doing here?
Nobody called you?
Called me about what?
I'm sorry.
I just can't believe it.
I'm really very sorry.
Ma'am, I know this isn't the best time,
but we'd like you to come with us.
Why? You think I have
something to do with this?
With Cal?
Of course not.
We just got a few
questions... I's and T's, mostly.
I, uh...
Could we do it later?
I'm afraid not.
Oh...
My... my kid has the flu, um,
and he was up all night, so...
Well, is there a neighbor or a friend
who can watch him while you're gone?
I'm sorry. You said
your boy was up all night?
Uh, yeah.
Were you with him all night?
Well, I had, um, half
an hour of sleep, maybe.
- Can I talk to your son?
- Why?
Yeah, what difference
does that make, Agent Holt?
Trust me. It's important.
Please?
DEAN: Well, it wasn't her.
[Scoffs]
You don't know that.
She's got an alibi.
She's lying.
You heard the kid, dude.
She's not lying.
Fine. She still had
time to wolf out, Dean.
The last werewolf was in bed with me,
and she wolfed out.
Don't make this personal.
Look, all I'm saying is,
that between this and
the daylight attacks,
something's not adding up.
I'm not just gonna hand
her over to Crowley
until we figure out what.
You understand?
[Sighs]
Okay. Okay. I understand.
How 'bout you go check
out Cal's crime scene.
See if we're missing anything.
I'll come back and
keep an eye on Amanda.
How 'bout you go
and I'll stay here?
Dean, I still know
how to do my job.
[Scoffs]
I'm just gonna watch her. That's all.
Trust me.
Uh-huh...
[Bones crunching,
flesh squishing]
[Sniffs]
[Grunts]
[Tires screech, thud]
MAN: Thank God
he's still breathing.
[Lucky whimpering]
You okay, boy?
Gotta find a Vet.
Hurry.
Hey!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait! Mister!
Hey, mister, wait! That's my dog!
That's my dog.
[Exhales sharply]
[Rain falling, thunder rumbling]
[Blows]
[Cellphone rings]
Hey.
SAM: Hey, it's me.
DEAN: Well, I got bupkes here.
I definitely got something.
It ain't a werewolf, for one.
Yeah, what is it?
Skin-walker.
A skin-walker?
As in...
As in, the family dog
seriously needs a neuter.
Wow.
I haven't heard of a
skin-walker in years.
I'm actually a little
rusty on the profile.
You and me both.
Uh, I just got the low down from Bobby.
They can change anywhere, anytime.
Skin-walkers infect you with a single bite.
Otherwise, they're
basically a werewolf cousin...
Silver will drop 'em, they
chow hearts like snausages.
So what happened?
Did you catch him?
Not exactly,
but I have some idea where he might be.
Hiya, Lucky.
Bad dog.
First thing's first.
[Gun clip disengages]
You see this? This is silver.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
[Clip engages]
[Whines]
Okay, time to go.
Now, we can either do
this the easy way... hmm?
[Chain rattles]
Or the hard way.
[Sam laughs]
What? Soul or not, that's funny.
[Barks]
Well, I got to tell you, Lucky...
you got us stumped.
I mean, why shack up with the family?
Is it a kinky thing?
Do you like to play with your food?
Roll over, Lucky. Speak.
Go to hell.
Already been. Didn't agree with me.
So, look, how about I
take this silver knife,
and start carving some
dog until you behave?
You do what you got to do.
Hang on, Sam.
Listen, you don't have to
tell me why you're with the family.
I get it.
Oh, you do, do you?
You killed every threat
that came near them.
You care about them,
in your own whack-a-doodle kind of way.
It's obvious.
What I want to know is,
who was that guy you
were kibitzing with?
He a skin-walker, too?
Look, I can't say anything.
But if you don't,
then you're gonna put
the girl and the
little boy in danger.
And sooner or later, all this
crap is gonna come for them.
Now, look, we don't give
a rat's ass about you.
We want to help them.
That's our angle. That's it.
Yeah, that guy, he's a...
whatever it is I am.
And he's not the only one.
How many are you?
About 30.
We were all... we were kind of recruited.
Recruited?
Yeah. Me, I was living on the streets.
They found me.
They told me one small bite,
I'd be strong, I'd be fast.
Sniffing people's butts?
Yeah, that's a real step up.
Well, it was for me.
Where is this little
Scooby gang of yours?
Everywhere.
We're out there finding families,
and once they take us in, we lay low.
"Lay low"? What the hell's that mean?
- Well, we're waiting for the word.
- What word?
Once we're settled, we get the signal...
...and we all turn on our families.
[Sighs]
We change them, all in one night.
30 becomes 150.
God, you're a sleeper cell.
Yeah, well, that's one way to say it.
So you're waiting for word from who?
Who organized you?
There's a pack leader.
Your Alpha?
What's an Alpha?
The... the first skin-walker, the strongest.
Well, he's plenty strong,
but, no, I-I don't think so.
I'm pretty sure there's
guys like him in other towns.
We're not the only pack out there.
Fantastic. Then you
can help us stop him.
Oh, no, I can't. No.
Yes, you can.
No, you guys don't get it. No one can.
These guys who turned
me... they're ruthless.
[Sam whistling]
Sam, not helping.
Fetch this, dick.
Listen to me.
What are you gonna do
to that family, really?
You gonna put your jaws
around that little boy's throat?
Clamp down, listen to
him cry for his mom?
'Cause I'm gonna guess
that these are the only
people who in your pathetic life
have ever showed you any kindness.
So it's either that...
or you can help us stop it.
So...
how are we supposed
to get near something
that can smell us 100 yards off?
We don't.
The pack leader.
We're taking him down?
Yeah. Got a better idea?
No, I...
Crowley's not gonna be
too happy about that.
Who gives a rat's ass?
We let that thing live one second,
and it sends out that
psychic dog whistle and pchew!
On the other hand, it could
lead us to an Alpha,
then Crowley would
give me my soul back.
Are you kidding?
150 people turned into monsters.
That's what you want?
No. Of course not. I...
I'm just asking.
All right, you know what? That's it.
What?
You say you're "Just folks," Yeah?
That... that you like baseball
and apple-pie or whatever.
But truth is, I don't know what you are
- 'cause you're not Sam.
- Dean, come on.
I mean, it's your gigantor body and...
and maybe your brain,
but it's not you.
So just... stop pretending
and do us both a favor.
He looks nervous, right?
Wouldn't you be?
I'd double-cross us.
I mean, he's got to realize
that's his best bet,
if he wants to keep breathing.
Nah, he'll go through with it.
You mean 'cause he
loves that family?
Yeah.
I'd double-cross us.
Thanks, Dexter. That's reassuring.
Just making conversation.
Here we go.
That big guy, the driver...
that's the guy Lucky met in the park.
And there's El Jefe.
Take him out.
It's not clean.
We got one shot at this... literally.
Take the shot.
I'm trying!
- She's in the way.
- Take it anyway!
Come on, come on, come on. Ahh.
So, plan "B"?
We've got one?
[Voice breaking]
Please, whatever you want.
Just please let my son go.
[Whispering indistinctly]
Look, man, there's nothing I can do.
The boss is pissed.
These murders that you've been doing?
You didn't ask for permission!
Now you're gonna screw up
the whole damn plan.
- I tried to warn you.
- I know. I'm sorry.
There... there's been a mistake.
T-This has got nothing to do with us.
It has everything
to do with you, sister.
So, you with us or not?
Yes, of course I am.
Fine. Prove it.
Turn them. Now.
Both of 'em, while we watch,
or I'll kill you all.
Oh, my...
[Sniffing]
What is that?
[Screams]
[Gunshot]
- Mommy!
- It's okay.
[Sobs]
Mandy! Come on, come on.
Who are you?!
I don't even know you!
Yes, you do. Trust me, I'm trying to help.
Come on, come on!
[Whimpers]
[Grunts] Get in there.
- But I don't...
- Get in there!
Bolt it! Bolt it!
Here, baby, go under here.
Okay, stay there, honey.
You'll be safe.
[Dog barking, snarling]
You're protecting them?
After what I did for you?
I gave you your life back!
[Echoing] Them?
You're nothing to them.
You're a dog.
Ohh.
[Laughs]
I-I was gonna turn them.
But now I'm gonna kill 'em.
Aah!
[Bones crunching, flesh squishing]
[Barking]
Lucky?!
So you think this is
gonna be a dogfight?
[Barking continues]
I got a better idea.
[Whimpers]
Ohh!
Silver bullet, Lucky.
[Gunshot]
[Sighs]
[Exhales sharply]
Ugh.
Hi.
Look... [Sighs]
I'm not here to bother you.
I just... uh, I just
want to say one thing.
You and Aidan...
you're the only family I ever had
[Scoffs]
And I know...
I know that sounds... I know...
I know what I am.
It...
it's just that no one has ever
been so nice to me before,
so...
so, thank you.
Get away from this house,
you psycho.
And if you ever,
ever come near me or my son again,
so help me...
I know I probably deserve...
[Flesh squishing]
I'll never look at a dog the same.
Makes you wonder though, huh?
What?
How many packs are out there.
What if they're all just waiting
for the signal, you know?
So... I was thinking.
[Sighs]
You were right.
About?
I'm not your brother.
I'm not Sam.
Okay.
All that "Blah, blah, blah,"
about being the old me?
Crap.
Like Lisa and Ben, right?
I've been acting like I care about them,
but I don't, I couldn't care less.
Is this supposed to make me feel better?
You wanted the real me. This is it.
I don't care about them.
I don't even really care about you.
Except that...
I need your help,
and you're clearly not gonna
stick around for much longer
unless I give it to you straight, so...
I've done a lot worse than you know.
I've killed innocent people
in the line of duty.
But I'm pretty sure
it's not something the
old me could've done.
And maybe I should feel guilty,
but I don't.
Sam, get to the punch line.
I don't know if how I am
is better or worse.
It's different.
You get the job done
and nothing really hurts.
That's not the worst thing.
But I've been thinking,
I was that other
Sam for a long time
and it was...
it was kinda harder.
But there are also things
about it I remember that I...
[Sighs]
let's just say
I think I should probably
go back to being him.
That's very interesting.
It's a step.
So?
We do what we got to do.
And we get my brother back.
Edited by Scooby