- Now, you're sure it's vampires?
- Definitely.
Their Alpha's building an army.
We don't scare them anymore.
I'm your grandfather.
Samuel?
We all thought you were dead.
We're guessing whatever
pulled Sam up pulled me down.
So, whatever this is,
we're both a part of it.
But you don't know what that is.
- Dean, you all right?
- It's Sam, Bobby.
He's just... he's different.
Something's not right to me.
What is wrong with him?
I don't know, Dean.
I'm sorry.
It's like you let him get turned.
Get a man on the inside,
help us find that Alpha vamp
we've been looking for?
You think I'd do something
like that, risk my own brother?
You got my back.
No matter what happens,
I can always count on you,
right, Sammy?
Yeah. Of course, Dean.
What are you? You're not human.
Please, just let me explain.
Why the hell should I believe
anything you say?
There's something wrong
with me, really wrong.
I need help.
You're right. He looks terrible.
You did this?
Cass?
What's...?
Let me go.
- Has he been feverish?
- Have you?
No. Why?
Is he speaking in tongues?
Are you speaking in tongues?
No. What are you...
are you diagnosing me?
You better hope he can.
You really think that this is...
What, you think that
there's a clinic out there
for people who just
pop out of Hell wrong?
He asks, you answer,
then you shut your hole.
You got it?
How much do you sleep?
I don't.
At all?
Not since I got back.
And it never occurred to you
that there might be
something off about that?!
Of course it did, Dean.
I... I just never told you.
What?
Sam...
What are you feeling now?
I feel like my nose is broken.
No, that's a physical sensation.
How do you feel?
- Well, I think...
- Feel.
I... don't know.
What? Uh...
- This will be unpleasant.
- What...
Bite down on this.
If there's someplace
that you find soothing,
you should go there.
In your mind.
Did you find anything?
No.
So that's good news?
I'm afraid not.
Physically, he's perfectly healthy.
Then what?
It's his soul.
It's gone.
Season 6 Episode 7
"Family Matters"
Um...
I'm s... I'm sorry.
One more time, like I'm 5.
What do you mean, he's got no...
Somehow, when Sam was resurrected,
it was without his soul.
So, where is it?
My guess is...
Still in the cage
with Michael and Lucifer.
So, is he even still Sam?
Well, you pose an interesting
philosophical question.
Well, then, just get it back.
- Dean.
- Well, you pulled me out.
It took several angels to rescue you,
and you weren't
nearly as well guarded.
Sam's soul is in Lucifer's cage.
There's a difference, a big difference.
It's not possible.
Okay, well, there's got to be a way.
- So, are you gonna untie me?
- No.
- Listen, I'm not gonna...
- Sam, how am I even
supposed to let you
out of this room?
Dean, I'm not some psycho.
I didn't want you to get hurt.
I was just trying to stop the vamps.
I'm sorry.
It won't ever happen again.
Please let me go.
You're kidding, right?
Well, what are you gonna do, just
keep me locked up in here forever?
You say that like it's a bad thing.
Okay, fine. Look, I get it.
I get it, Dean. I was wrong.
But I'm telling you,
I... I'm trying to get right.
It's still me.
- Is it?
- Yes.
So just let me go.
No way in hell.
I didn't want it to come to this.
You're not gonna hold me, Dean...
not here, not in a panic room,
not anywhere.
You're stuck with the soulless guy,
so you might as well work with me.
Let's fix this.
I'm gonna be watching
every move you make.
Fine.
Sounds about right to me.
Cass, clean him up.
All right, if we're gonna figure out
what happened to your soul,
then we need to find
who yanked you out.
You say you don't know?
- No idea.
- Then we start a list.
If it's so hard to spring
someone out of the box,
then who's got that kind of muscle?
I don't know.
You have no memory
of your resurrection?
I woke up in a field.
That's all I got.
No clues? None?
I've got one.
Gramps throw a barbecue,
leave us off the e-vite list?
Sam!
Ahh.
- Dean.
- Hello, Newman.
Where's the man?
Come right on in.
Need to ask you a few questions.
What's wrong?
The day you got back,
what happened?
We've been over this.
Well, recap it for our wingman.
This Castiel?
You're scrawnier than I pictured.
This is a vessel.
My true form is approximately
the size of your Chrysler building.
All right, all right.
Quit bragging.
So, you were dead, and...
And, pow, I was on Elton Ridge.
Don't know how. Don't know why.
I got nothing to hide, guys.
Well, you mind if Cass here
double-checks?
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's okay. It's okay.
- It's okay.
- What the hell?
Angel cavity search.
I'm fine, Christian.
Just give us a minute.
But...
What the hell was that about?
His soul is intact.
What?
Of course I have a...
What's going on, Sam?
Whatever dragged me out...
left a piece behind.
Did you know?
No, but I...
I knew it was something. I...
You're a hell of a hunter, Sam, but...
the truth is,
sometimes you scare me.
So, what's the deal here?
How do we fix this?
How do we get his soul back?
We don't know yet, but we have to.
Well, I'm here to help, of course.
What leads you working?
A bunch of dead ends and you.
Well, then, we'll just have to dig.
Sam, Dean...
I have to get back.
You're leaving?
I'm in the middle of a civil war.
You better tear the attic up,
find something to help Sam.
Of course. Your problems
always come first.
I'll be in touch.
Would've asked him
to stick around for a beer.
So, what's with
the book club outside?
Putting together a hunt.
That's a lot of guys for one hunt.
You found him, didn't you?
Who?
He's got a lead on the Alpha vamp.
Do you?
Maybe.
Yeah.
How'd you track him down?
We're good.
- That's all I get? "We're good"?
- When's the run?
Dawn.
You didn't call me? Why?
'Cause of me.
You don't trust me very much,
do you?
Especially when it comes
to big game like this.
That's not true.
Okay. Well, then, we're in.
- No offense, but...
- So you don't trust me.
No, I just don't know you.
Not like I know Sam.
All right.
You call the plays.
100%.
I'm here to listen.
Since when?
Big daddy bloodsucker?
I ain't gonna miss that.
But this is your deal.
Okay? I get it.
I'll follow your lead.
I trust you.
I don't trust him.
Dude's hiding something.
- What?
- I can feel it.
And if you weren't Robo-Sam,
you'd feel it, too.
Huh.
What?
Just... you...
saying you don't trust family.
Look, we hang close, we blend
in, we see what we can pick up.
You think Samuel's connected
to this whole soul thing?
I still think he's
the only lead we got.
You lost, Dean?
Had to make a phone call.
Just needed some privacy.
Oh.
Samuel's locked office
is pretty private.
- Wasn't locked.
- Who you calling?
Your wife. Let her know I'm not
gonna make it over tonight.
You know, I've tried
playing nice, Dean,
- but I think I'm done.
- Wait, are you trying to tell me
that you're a bigger knob
than you've been letting on?
I'm the guy who's been here,
doing my job.
Who are you?
You think we need you here?
You walk around like
you're playing pro tennis.
Only action you seen lately
is between your
slut girlfriend's legs.
You sure you want to come
with us tomorrow?
Accidents happen.
Hmm.
Don't worry, man. I got your back.
The house is just over the hill.
About a dozen vamps and the Alpha.
We got one shot at
this son of a bitch.
Christian, take flank.
The rest of you are with me and Sam.
Dean, Gwen...
Hang back, sweep any stragglers
we flush out.
Problem, Dean?
No, sir.
I'm in the rear with the reject?
All right, let's go.
Don't worry. It's fine.
No, nothing's fine. You're not fine.
Go. Go.
Sorry about the "reject" thing.
Ah, I've been called worse.
Just, uh, get sick
of getting left behind.
Think it's probably
'cause I remind him
of his daughter or something.
Well, you do speak your mind.
- I'll take that as a compliment.
- You should.
You're welcome.
We're supposed to wait here!
Dean!
Sam!
- Careful, now!
- Yeah. Got him.
Alright, get him in there.
Get in.
Get him in there, strapped down...
Where were you?
Everything all right here?
Just, uh, chopped up a runner.
No big deal.
How'd it go?
Rough, but one Alpha down.
Where is it?
Want to pay my last respects.
Well, bring marshmallows.
Already on the pyre.
Things go okay back there?
Fine.
Nothing weird?
I saw you walk that Alpha
out the door, Sam.
Now, call me crazy...
But that seems weird.
Oh.
"Oh".
You weren't supposed to
know about that.
- Know what?
- It's just something Samuel's been doing.
Catching things,
taking them somewhere,
grilling them for info.
Grill.
Torture, right?
And not telling me...
that was his idea?
No, it was mine.
Why?
Honestly?
'Cause you'd mess it up.
You shoot first,
ask questions later,
and we needed to ask questions.
You know, I... I don't care
if you've got soullessness
or the freakin' mumps, man...
You know better than this!
Do you even want your soul back?
How does that have anything to do...
have you been to the place
where Samuel takes them?
I mean, have you been in
on these interrogations?
No, but I hear...
And what does he want? And why?
And did it ever occur to you
that this is really shady?
He's our grandfather.
Yeah.
Yeah, a guy who talks a great game.
But you can't assume
that family means
the same thing to him
as it does to us.
He's not dad.
Wow.
- You don't see it, do you?
- What?
You've got no instinct.
I mean, you are seriously messed up.
- Thanks.
- I'm not kidding, man.
Nobody's forcing you
to work with me, okay?
But if we do this...
I drive the bus, I call the shots,
and you tell me everything,
whether you think
it's important or not,
because, trust me...
you can't tell the difference.
Or, you know what, go...
go with Samuel.
See how that goes.
It's up to you.
Samuel?
Damn, kid. Learn how to knock.
Where's your brother?
Gone.
What do you mean, "gone"?
I mean he left about an hour ago.
He and I just weren't
seeing eye-to-eye anymore
I guess.
That's too bad.
I want in.
In?
On the interrogations,
on everything.
I can help.
This family...
this is it for me now.
Whatever you need, I'll do.
- Yeah, I know you will.
- Great.
But until we can figure out
this soul business of yours,
I need you to keep doing
what you're doing.
But I can...
No. You can't.
I'm sorry.
Right.
Hey.
You didn't think I'd come back.
I figured 60/40.
So, Samuel didn't take the bait.
So I went with plan "B".
We had a plan "B"?
Fired up the GPS
on one of his cellphones.
We should be able to track him
right to the Alpha.
- The old man won't notice?
- Trust me.
He thinks Velcro is big news.
There. Got him.
Dead man's blood?
Smart.
Lock the place down
with vamp repellent.
Where is it?
Answer the question.
Where is it? How do we find it?
Ouch. Stop. That hurts.
Now, this...
this is Club Med compared to
what we have planned for you.
- Oh.
- I got... I got all the time in the world.
Well, that makes two of us.
Are you two going to hide all night?
Come on out, boys.
How can I help you?
We got some questions
for you, Skippy,
since you're going nowhere fast.
Don't be so sure.
Yeah?
Locked down pretty tight.
And with all that dead blood
rushing through your veins,
not sure you got enough juice
to fire up that psychic
bat-signal of yours, do you?
True.
Not near enough juice for that...
Dean.
I didn't realize
we were on a first-name basis.
Of course we are.
After all, you were my child...
for a time.
Dean, tell me...
Did you enjoy it?
I'm asking the questions here,
fright night.
When your kind first
huddled around the fire,
I was the thing in the dark!
Now you think you can hurt me?
I have all night, boys.
You do not.
Anyway, I'm happy to tell you
whatever you want to know.
Why?
Because soon, I'll be
ankle-deep in your blood,
sucking the marrow from your bones.
So you're really it.
The first of your species.
The very first.
But if you're the first...
who made you?
Well, we all have our mothers.
Even me.
What does that mean?
And what's with the big surge
of vamps lately?
I mean, it's like...
Like we're going to war.
Why? What's going on?
Why did Samuel bring you here?
You smell cold.
You have no soul.
What an oddity.
Do you feel how empty you are?
What is it like to have no soul?
- Answer my question.
- You first.
You're the one in the cage.
The thing about souls,
if you've got one, of course...
is they're predictable.
You die, you go up or down.
Where do my kind go?
All right, enough with
the sermon, freak.
I'm trying to answer the question.
Now, when we "freaks" die...
Where do we go?
Not Heaven, not Hell.
So?
Legoland?
Little rusty on our Dante, boys?
Purgatory.
Purgatory? Purgatory's real?
Oh, stupid cattle.
Of course!
And it is filled with the soul
of every hungry thing like me
that ever walked this Earth.
Now, where is it?
That is the mystery.
And that is what
your kindhearted granddaddy
is trying to beat out of me.
Samuel brought you here...
To find out where Purgatory is?
I keep telling him...
How would I know such a thing?
But he refuses to untie me.
You know exactly where it is.
Why does Samuel care
about any of this?
He doesn't care.
He does as he is told.
Well, if the old man's Kermit...
Whose hand's up his ass?
Evening, guys.
Wow, you know, I have seen
some stupid in my time,
but you take the crown.
Putting jaws in a fishbowl?
How do you think that's gonna end?
I don't know what kind of game
you're running...
What, do you think
I'm doing this for kicks?
I think you got the rest of these feebs
convinced that you're John Wayne.
So whatever you're doing,
whatever you're hiding...
It's gonna put you and everyone
around you in the ground.
Hi.
Gwen.
And I thought we had
something special.
Are you scared of me?
I would be.
Go ahead.
Grab your stuff.
How much dead mans
blood we got left?
How long till the Alpha's 100%?
Hour. Maybe less.
We need to get him dosed up
and back in the cage.
No.
What do you mean, "no"?
I mean, I don't know
what your big plan was,
but playing catch
is not on the table.
- Dean...
- We take the thing's head off,
or it kills us all!
You know that.
Okay.
We split up. Clear every room.
You get a shot, you take it.
It's not gonna kill him, but dude will move
a lot slower without any kneecaps.
And if we make it through this,
you, me, and Sam
are having one hell
of a family meeting.
You think he ran out?
No!
The boy with no soul.
I've got big plans for you.
It's amazing how that pesky,
little soul gets in the way.
But not for you.
You will be the perfect...
animal.
Christian?
Well, that was dramatic.
Crowley?
Hello, boys.
What an unexpected treat.
Bring Christian back now.
- I'm sorry?
- My nephew!
The one you just
crammed a demon into!
Oh, no. I had him possessed
ages ago.
Samuel, really.
I keep an eye on my investments.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
You two know each other?
Not in the biblical sense.
More of a business
relationship, I'd say.
You're Crowley's bitch.
It's not what you think.
It's precisely what you think.
That Alpha he's caught me
is getting him a gold star.
Since when do you give a crap
about vampires?
Since, uh...
What's today... Friday?
Since, let's see...
mind your business.
You may as well share
with the class, Crowley.
We know you're looking
for Purgatory.
So you heard about that?
Yeah. You want to tell us why?
Isn't it obvious?
Location, location, location.
I'm a developer.
Purgatory is vast,
underutilized, and Hell-adjacent,
and I want it.
- What for?
- Best shut your gob.
Employees don't question
management.
- We ain't your employees.
- Of course you are!
Have been for some time now,
thanks to gramps.
I don't keep Captain Chromedome
around for his wit, do I?
Samuel knows things.
More than any of you, actually.
Walking encyclopedia of
the creepy and the crawly.
And I knew...
you two are so hung up
on family-loyalty nonsense,
he said jump, you'd get froggy.
Yeah, well, the game's over.
Yeah, well, afraid not,
not if you want to see
Sam's soul ever again.
You're bluffing.
Tell them, Samuel.
He pulled us both back, me and Sam.
What? You knew?
No, Cass says it takes big-time mojo
to pull something like that off,
and you're nothing but
a punk-ass crossroads demon.
Was a punk-ass
crossroads demon.
Now? King of Hell.
Believe me, I've got the mojo.
I snap my fingers,
Sam gets his soul back.
Or you can be... you,
and I shove Sam
right back in the hole.
Can't imagine what
it's like in there...
And I can imagine so many things.
So, we clear?
Me, Charlie... you, Angels.
Job's simple enough...
Bring me creatures.
Aim high on the food chain, please.
Everybody wins.
It's been a pleasure.
See you soon.
It's time to go. Get the van.
You're letting a demon call the shots?
Nothing's changed.
We hunt. Period.
Don't worry about him.
We'll take care of it.
You trust me or not?
Get the van, Gwen.
Working with a demon, huh?
You're not who I thought you were.
You don't know anything
about me, son.
So, what's so important
that you're the king of hell's
cabana boy, huh?
What'd he offer you?
Girls? Money? Hair?
I got my reasons.
You gonna make a move, go ahead.
Or what?
Or nothing.
I'm not gonna do anything
to you, Dean.
You boys...
you're my family.
So the way I see it,
you got two choices...
put a bullet in your grandfather
or step aside.
He sold us out.
I know.
Let it go.
Why?
Get out of here.
So, what now?
We can't work for Crowley.
Are you sure about that?
I don't think you understand.
Demons bone you every time.
Oh, no, I get it. I do, believe me.
Just running the math...
do we really have another choice?
- We could stab him in his throat.
- And get my soul back how?
I'm just saying,
seems like we got to play ball,
at least for the moment.
I have done some stupid things
in my time,
but punching a demon's clock?
Look, just till we find another way.
And then?
And then we track Crowley down
and give that son of a bitch
what's coming to him.
You with me, Dean?
...Sync by Rafael UPD ...
www.addic7ed.com/
Edited by Scooby