- Rufus Turner is a hunter.
- One of your old friends?
Oh, good. You're home.
Listen, you got to help me
bury a body.
It's just something
Samuel's been doing.
Catching things,
taking them somewhere,
grilling them for info.
Grill.
Torture, right?
You sold us out?
What exactly are you
supposed to be to me?
I'll tell you who I am.
I'm the guy
you never want to see again.
The next time you see me,
I'll be there to kill you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Gwen Campbell.
Third cousin.
They grew up in the life,
like us.
I'm thinking you know
"Purgatory."
This is all about opening a door
to let something in.
- What?
- I'm working on it.
Could you give us something?
I got a name.
"Mother of all."
We have so much to do.
Let's get started.
Whoa.
I'm sorry.
Did I scare you?
You okay?
You look a little...
Well, I could use a ride.
Okay.
So, what's your name,
sweetheart?
- Eve.
- Eve. I'm Rick.
So, how far you going, Eve?
However far you want.
Whoa, whoa. Eve.
Look, you're very pretty,
but this is not
what's right for you.
Trust me.
Then what's right for me?
This emptiness
you feel inside...
it's really a hunger for him.
You do know that Jesus
was just a man.
Sure, but he was
also the son of God,
sent here because he loves us.
- God doesn't care about you.
- Sure he does.
Your father made you
and then abandoned you,
so you pray.
You see signs
where there's nothing.
But truth is,
your apocalypse came and went,
and you didn't even notice.
A mother would never abandon
her children like he did.
You'll see.
See what?
Can I tell you a secret?
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Season 6 Episode 16
"And Then There Were None"
I've been getting blasts
from hunters all week.
Nest of vamps.
Werewolf dance party.
Shifters, six of them.
Two hunters died
taking them out.
Ghouls, ghouls.
Ghoul-wraith smorgasbord.
Is it just me, or is that
a straight kick-line down I-80?
Exactly.
Looks to me like it's
a Sherman march monster mash.
Yeah, but where are they
marching to?
What is it?
Guy bashes in
his family's heads.
It's like I told the cops.
I blacked out.
Well, just tell us
what you do remember.
Driving my regular route,
and then I... I woke up
in my truck at work.
And where's work?
Starlight Cannery.
I... I didn't remember
how I got there...
So I called home.
When no one picked up,
I... I went there,
and I found...
Anything unusual
before you blacked out?
Sights, smells,
anything off the routine?
No. Basic night.
I was giving some kid
from the truck stop a ride.
She took off.
I... I think she took off.
Anything else?
I swear...
I didn't mean to do it.
I... I loved them.
So, demon possession or ghosts?
I thought this was
a monster thing.
All right, here we go.
Truck stop,
night of the murders.
That's him.
Hmm. Hello.
Freakish nightmare.
What the hell was that?
Bobby?
I've never seen that
in my life.
All those vamps and ghouls
out on I-80...
maybe they're coming in
for mother's day.
Um...
Okay, well,
if that is big mama...
whatever she is,
we got zero on ganking her.
So what are we gonna do if we
run into her? Throw salt and hope?
No, we're gonna turn tail and run,
because we're in over our heads.
I mean, we better get
some real info on this bitch...
...before we do run into her.
Hey, let's go.
What's the ruckus?
A guy just went postal
down at the cannery.
Okay, I'll go.
You finish here.
Excuse me.
FBI. Willis.
- How many in there?
- Six dead.
- What happened?
- Apparently, a guy walks in,
pulls a hunting rifle,
just opens fire.
Captain!
This is agent...
What? There a fed convention
in town or something?
I beg your pardon.
Agent Willis?
Am I right?
Agent.
I wasn't expecting you... yet.
Well, apparently,
you didn't get the call.
Gentlemen, can you excuse us?
What in the high holy
are you doing here, Rufus?
Same as you...
tracking 31 flavors of crazy,
which led us both smack
into the middle of this.
Right. Huh.
Can we talk to the perp?
Well, we can give it a shot.
I don't know if he's gonna talk
back to us, though.
Cops put eight bullets in him.
So...
So what?
So are we partnering
on this or not?
Come on, man.
It's not rocket surgery.
We're here.
Let's do this.
Just like old times.
Long as I get to drive.
Hell no.
So, do you think the mother
of whatever the hell
is wrapped up in this, Bobby?
Looks like.
These are just guys
going berserk, Bobby.
How is that a monster thing?
I don't know. That's why
we're hacking him open.
Hand me one of those
swab things over there.
What have you got?
That ecto?
That's not ecto.
What the hell is that?
It's something new.
New?
No such thing as new, Bobby.
Well, it's something.
Those guys who snapped,
one thing they had in common...
they both worked
at that cannery joint.
I don't even know
why you have a driver's license.
Well, look
what the cat dragged in.
It really is good
to see you, Rufus.
I can believe it.
It must get old
dealing with this miserable
cuss here all by yourself.
Is it that obvious?
Why don't you three get a room?
- All right, we all pack a snack?
- Yeah.
Let's see what we can see.
- Gwen?
- Dean.
Welcome to the "next time."
No, no, no, no!
Hold on!
- I said I'd kill him!
- Look, just a second.
I take it you know each other.
- He's our grandfather.
- Oh.
Somebody needs a hug.
Why are you here?
We're working. You?
None of your damn business!
Sam, take Dean for a walk.
- You got to be kidding me.
- Look, Dean, it's fine.
How?
- What is wrong with you?
- Look, maybe he knows something.
- You don't remember what he did. I do.
- I know.
I'm not saying don't.
I'm saying not yet.
So... you're Samuel.
You must be the guy
pretending to be their father.
Well, somebody ought to.
Sam.
You're looking well.
Save the small talk, all right?
You seem different.
I got my soul back.
No thanks to you, I hear.
You hear?
You don't remember.
I remember enough.
I, uh, really hate to break up
this little circle of love,
but why don't we
talk shop, huh?
How about you tell us
what it is you're hunting?
A creature from Purgatory.
She calls herself Eve.
- Eve?
- Yep.
They call her Mother.
She was here
about 10,000 years ago.
Every freak that walks
the face of the earth
can be traced back to her.
And she's back.
How the hell
do you know all that?
You don't know half the things
that I know, kid.
Hell, until recently,
you didn't even know about us.
I now know that you'd throw
your own kin to hungry ghouls.
I think I know enough.
- You what?
- Dean lied to the man.
- How about you ask Dean?
- Good idea.
Dean.
- Is it true?
- What?
Did Samuel really try to...
Kill me? Yes.
He didn't even blink.
That's the guy
you're rolling with.
He didn't tell me
anything about that.
I didn't know.
I know.
Honestly, there's something
I need to tell you.
What?
See if you can plug
that hole up, Bobby.
Come on, girl!
Come on!
She's gone.
Ah, damn it.
I'm sorry... if you care.
Screw you. I care.
Is she, uh...
Yeah.
- Where's Dean?
- I couldn't find him.
Whatever got into those guys
must have got into Dean.
Rufus, help Samuel
move her somewhere.
Sam and I will lock down here.
We're gonna want to find Dean
before he finds us.
We're gonna find him
alive, Samuel,
or I'm gonna put a bullet
into your head.
Dean, put that damn thing down.
Dean, put it down.
You're the least of my worries
right now, Rufus.
Hey, hey, hey.
Okay, both of you.
- Both of us, my ass.
- I'm not in the mood.
I just had a 12-inch... herpe
crawl out of my ear.
- What?
- You heard me.
I just woke up on the ground,
just in time to see this...
this... worm thing
sliding out of my freaking ear
and into that vent.
So you tell me
what the hell's going on!
You killed Gwen.
That's what's going on.
We were just talking
out in the hallway.
That's the last thing
I remember.
That thing must have jumped me.
So, we're talking about, like,
a monster that gets in you?
It's like a Khan worm
on steroids.
You mean like a parasite, something
that took over your body.
Worm crawls in you,
worm crawls out.
Monster possession?
That's novel.
Or that thing's still in you, and we
can't trust a word that you're saying.
- It's not!
- Check your ear.
What do you mean, check my ear?
Check my ear for what?
Hey! What?
Why don't you buy me
a drink first?
Second date.
Oh, yeah, we're goo positive.
What does that mean?
That means it was in you,
all right.
- Or it still is.
- It's not in me!
Okay.
- Everybody, give up your guns.
- What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
think about this for a second, Bobby.
I'm thinking we don't know
who is and who ain't got
the damn Khan worm
up inside his melon.
It's not in me!
I didn't say it was.
Point is we don't know
who it is.
It could be any one of us.
So the best we can do...
is to make it that much harder
for that thing to blow
our fool heads off.
Are you waiting for
a handwritten invite, Campbell?
Okay.
We need some time to breathe,
make a plan.
A plan?
Based on?
I'm gonna make
a few phone calls,
see if anybody ever heard
of anything like this.
Hmm. Ditto.
Got a few trees I can shake.
Oh, balls, Callard.
No, I told you that.
Oh, Damn it.
Relax.
Bathroom break.
So unless you want
to hold it for me...
Well, I got a dump truck
full of bubkes.
Nothing here, either.
You call Willie?
Of course.
Think I'm an idjit?
How about Rodg?
Wouldn't talk to me.
Yeah, me neither.
Okay, plan "B."
Let's just go
and grab the thing.
And then what, exactly?
Well, we sit on our thumbs,
or we go in guns blazing.
Like Omaha?
You know what?
Screw you for bringing up Omaha.
That's just low.
What?
Nothing. I'm just wondering
how you sleep at night.
Like a baby.
Thanks for asking.
You fed us to Crowley.
True, but what am I gonna do
about it now?
Do I blame you
for wanting to kill me?
Of course not, Dean.
What I did was...
But I'm not apologizing.
I did what I did.
I don't cry over spilled blood.
So you really can
just go on, like...
Just because you're Dr. Jekyll
at the moment
doesn't mean you can get
all high and mighty.
Don't forget,
we spent a year together.
Yeah, we did. We're blood.
And you still sold me out.
Trust me, what I did pales
in comparison to what you did,
and on more than one occasion.
All right, tell me what I did.
No. Sam, come on.
The only reason
you're alive right now
is because we're working a job.
The minute we kill this thing...
you're next.
Okay, then.
We'll just see.
I heard a shot.
Samuel!
I'm gonna be needing
my gun back now, Bobby.
- You think?
- Yeah.
Hey, don't feel bad.
You know, it was a good plan,
except for the part
where a monster
would definitely, definitely
not give up all his weapons.
Shut up.
We lost him.
- So, what's the plan?
- We stick together.
We got to keep track
of this thing, who it's in.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hold on. Look.
Booby trap.
I'll be damned.
Hey! Hey! Whoa!
Dean!
Sam!
Damn it.
Son of a bitch.
- Dean?
- Sam!
I'm gonna go around, okay?
All right.
Watch yourself.
Yeah.
Come on.
Don't move.
Sam.
Put your gun down.
What you gonna do, son?
You're not gonna shoot me.
You got your soul back.
You gonna shoot
your own family?
Yeah, I wouldn't go
with the family thing.
Try again.
Mary's still my daughter.
I said don't move.
You're still named after me.
I said don't move!
Appears to be our moment, Sam.
You still want to know
about your summer vacation?
I'll tell you all about it.
You're dying to know, huh?
Yeah, I am.
Well, then, let's just
put these down and talk.
Stop.
It's all right, Sam.
Sam.
Sam!
Oh, thank God.
Drop the gun, Sam.
It's me.
Okay.
That's great, Sam.
Just got to cuff you, uh,
till we can be sure, okay?
You understand, right?
It's in him.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah, I think.
You see anything come out of him...
after he dropped?
Tell me you got something.
Nothing.
What?
So... so you mean he wasn't
a monster when I ganked him?
One way to find out.
Bobby, you got a cranial saw
in the car?
Of course.
You're not going alone.
Oh, no, he won't.
He won't.
We will both go grab some tools
and see about getting
some power in this place.
And I want you and you to...
Okay, I want you and you
to watch him and him and...
all right, if anything crawls
out of anybody,
somebody step on it.
Yeah, don't worry.
I'll watch Samuel.
Dean will watch me.
You did the right thing,
you know.
You mean you think I did,
if it's in him and I'm me.
This thing's playing
three-card Monte with us.
Well, I'm just gonna assume
you're you.
You want to take this
off, then?
Not till we get that sucker
out of his walnut.
I don't know.
I mean, I barely remember him,
and what I do remember...
it's not good.
And what he did to us...
But...
There's a "but"?
I mean, I just can't help
but think...
What would mom say?
You know what I think
mom would say?
She'd say just 'cause you're
blood doesn't make you family.
You got to earn that.
Well...
All right.
Let's play operation.
- You boys want to take a breather?
- We're good.
We're about to crack open
your grandpa's grapefruit.
Take a breather.
What is this? Have you been
dumpster-diving again?
What? It still works.
Yeah, right.
Hope so.
Listen, Rufus,
I've been thinking.
Yeah, will wonders never cease?
Yeah, s... shut up a minute.
I'm trying to say something.
It was my fault...
Omaha.
No. No, it wasn't.
No, I should... I should
have listened to you.
Well, hey,
that's categorical, Bobby.
I... l... let me
just get this out.
Bobby, we've had this
conversation already, okay?
No, we haven't.
I never said I'm sorry, Rufus.
I... you lost her
because of me, and I...
Bobby, I said we've had
this conversation already.
And you could blabber all day...
And it wouldn't
change a thing, Bobby.
I will never forgive you
for what happened.
You got that?
Never.
So change the subject, Bob.
Dean.
Jesus!
Bobby, you okay?
Rufus.
- Rufus. Rufus.
- Hey, you all right?
Wake up.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- It's all right.
- I got you.
Come on.
You okay?
This can't be my afterlife
'cause the three of you
are here.
What happened?
Well, when we left,
he was dead on the table.
Yeah, till he wasn't.
So how did he get double dead?
Bobby threw him against that.
I guess it was a live wire.
It shorted, and he went ape.
Then that thing
crawled out of his ear.
At least we know
what tickles it.
Electricity.
Yeah. Now the question is,
where'd it go?
- You see?
- No.
- You two were down for the count.
- Yeah.
Well, either it bailed
or it's in either one of you.
Or... it's in one of you.
No, we were awake.
- Did you have eyes on each other?
- Yes.
100% of the time?
Define a 100.
Like I said.
All right, how about, uh,
check for goo, right?
Nothing.
It might just be gone.
No.
It might have wised up
and covered its trail.
All right,
let's settle this... 100%.
How?
You're live.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm not a doctor, but I'm gonna
go ahead and call this one.
Yeah. All right, who
wants to go first?
- Come on.
- You sure?
Hurry up before I start
thinking...
Son of a...
Whew. Awesome.
Here, you want me to...
Let's go.
Yep.
Uh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Uh, no, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
No passes, Rufus.
Come on.
- I got a damn pacemaker.
- Well, you better hope it's a good one.
Since when do you got
a pacemaker?
Since Bush Jr. Term one.
I'm down three toes,
too, F.Y.I.
All right, come on.
Just make it quick.
God!
Damn it! Damn it!
- You okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
Give me that.
Okay.
All right, my turn.
Well, it ain't inside me,
so go right ahead.
All right, then just
stand still, Bobby.
Okay, sure.
- I'll make this quick.
- No problem.
All right?
Let's do this.
Okay, uh, just a second, Rufus.
Just a second nothing,
whatever you are.
I'm Bobby.
Bobby, my ass.
Bobby!
Rufus!
Bobby, there are two of us
and one of you.
Well, hey, there,
you little herpe.
Why do you keep talking
about herpes?
What?
I don't. Shut up.
Shut up.
Now, don't you even think
about shagging ass out of here,
'cause we got every crack
in this room sealed.
So get comfy.
I am comfy.
It's nice in here.
And you love this guy,
don't you?
You really want to kill me
and take him with me?
Haven't you lost
enough pals today?
We'll do what we have to do.
And we got some questions
for you,
so you can either play ball,
or we could fry up a little
shrimp on the Barbie.
Ask. Been waiting
for you to ask.
What the hell's
that supposed to mean?
It means I got nothing to hide.
What are you?
You haven't got a name
for me yet.
I'm new around here.
Eve cooked me up herself.
Who is she, this Eve bitch?
The mother of all of us
and the end of all of you.
By the time she's done,
there'll be more creatures
than humans.
You'll live in pens.
We'll serve up your young
and call it veal.
And what's your deal
in all of this?
I mean, how's jumping
a few truckers gonna help?
You think I'm here
to mess with a couple
of cannery workers?
We led you here.
Why?
She has a message for you.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
You're all gonna die.
She's pissed. She's here.
And it's gonna be
nothing but pain
for you from here on in.
Well, here's my response.
Dean.
Dean!
How much more do you think
he can take?
You can't kill me,
not without taking him with me.
Well... we'll just have to do
what Bobby would want us to do.
No way out now, slug-o.
Bobby, hang on in there.
Bobby?
Is he, uh...
Hey, hey.
Whoa.
Bobby.
Bobby, hey.
He's not breathing.
Bobby!
I got to say,
I never figured Rufus
for the religious type.
Well, he didn't
exactly keep kosher.
He always used to pull
the old "can't work
on the sabbath" card
whenever we had to bury a body.
You know, I... I was just a job.
I was Joe mechanic.
Then my wife got possessed...
went nuts on me.
I stabbed her,
and that didn't stop her.
Next thing I knew,
this guy comes busting in,
soaks her with holy water,
and sends that demon
straight to hell so fast.
I'd have gone away
for killing her.
But...
Rufus cleaned up everything.
Taught me a thing
or two about...
what's really out there.
Pretty soon,
we were riding together.
Worked like that for years.
Kind of like
you two knuckleheads.
So, what happened?
It was Omaha.
It was my fault.
And he never let it go.
Well, he should have.
You don't know
what I did, Dean.
Doesn't matter.
What do you mean, it doesn't...
I mean at the end of the day,
you two are family.
Life's short, and ours
are shorter than most.
We're gonna spend it
wringing our hands?
Something's gonna
get us eventually,
and when my guts
get ripped out,
just so you two know,
we're good.
Blanket apology
for all the crap
that anybody's done
all the way around.
Some of us pulled
a lot of crap, Dean.
Well, clean slate.
Okay.
Sync and corrections by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
Edited by Scooby