You finally had a family.
And you were building something.
And it's as close to happiness
as I've ever seen a hunter get.
Dean?
- Ben, just stay there.
- I thought I heard you...
I said stay back!
Ben won't even talk about it.
This is the worst time
in the universe to talk.
Can we do this later?
You shoved my kid, Dean.
How about we do this now?
- But you and Ben...
- Me and Ben can't be in this with you.
Lucifer's cage.
Sam's soul is stuck in that box.
Nasty, those memories.
You don't want to know
what they'll do to him.
- Don't do his.
- Don't scratch the wall.
Death didn't just shove
your soul back in, okay?
He put up the great wall of Sam
between you and the things
that you don't remember.
And trust me when I say that
the things you don't know could kill you.
Sammy?
Sammy?!
Sammy, talk to me!
Sam?
Sam.
S... Sam?
Oh, come on.
Sammy!
Come on, come on.
Come on, damn it.
Hey, hey, hey, you with me?
Okay.
Come on. Come on,
got to get you out of here.
What the...
Who's there?!
Season 6 Episode 14
"Mannequin 3: The Reckoning"
How you feel?
Like I got hit by a... planet.
Well, lucky for you,
I'm a doctor.
I got Joe, grub, and...
What are they?
Effective.
I'm okay. Thanks.
Suit yourself.
So, how long was I out, again?
I'm telling you,
like two or three minutes.
Why, what'd it feel like to you?
About a week, give or take.
You want to talk about it?
"It"?
Yeah, whatever that was.
I mean, it was like
you were freakin' electrocuted.
Look I mean,
it wasn't fun,
but I... I'm... fine.
Fine.
It was Hell, wasn't it?
You got a big, fat
faceful of Hell.
Ever cross your mind
that you could've died?
- Oh, come on.
- I'm serious.
And none of this
"it's just a flesh wound" crap.
'Cause we did it your way.
We let you go explore,
and every bad thing that
I said would happen happened.
So guess what...
past stays past.
We're not
kicking that wall again.
So I'm supposed to
just ignore it?
Yes.
Dean...
I might've done...
who knows what,
and you want me
to just forget about it?
You shove it down,
and you let it come out
in spurts of violence
and alcoholism.
That sounds healthy.
Well, works for me.
It's not a joke.
Your life
is on the line here, Sam.
This is not a debate.
I mean, first you were
a... a soulless dick-bag,
and now you're not.
So we good?
Yeah. Sure.
Good.
Well, let's get your mind
off it, shall we?
You, uh, up for a job?
Well, what do you got?
Janitor murdered
in a college lab last night.
Doors were locked, nobody else
in or out of the building.
Great. Where to?
Paterson, New Jersey.
Hey, maybe we'll have
a Snooki sighting.
What's a Snooki?
That is a good question.
Check it out.
This thing's friggin' awesome!
Be my Valentine.
Dude, we're working.
Put it back.
- Have a heart.
- Dean!
Buzz kill.
You smell sulfur?
Yeah, we're in a science lab.
Right.
Who is it?
So, Lisa?
Maybe you should
mind your own business.
What's wrong with just
talking to her, Dean?
Thanks, Dr. Laura.
That's... that's very insightful.
Look at that...
our time's up.
Hey.
Whoa. Ghosts gone wild.
Something's up in here.
Question is, what?
Sam, good news.
Big Brother's watching.
Hey.
So, what'd you find out from the,
uh, mop jockey's girlfriend?
Nothing.
Just how great he was...
went to church,
donated to charity,
rubbed her feet during "Glee."
I just threw up in my mouth.
Sorry. Anyway, I checked
his record... spotless.
What about the science building?
Anything?
Built in '05.
Nothing weird about the land.
Before this, the biggest mishap
was some genius
accidentally spilled
sulfuric acid on his crotch.
They don't even dissect
anything good in there.
Anything bigger than Kermit,
they use an iPad.
So we got nothing?
Yeah,
a big steaming pile of it.
Hello?
Who's there?!
Jonny?!
Is that you?!
Okay.
Ha ha, very funny.
What the hell?
Oh!
- You got it?
- Yep!
- I'm backing up.
- Yeah.
Dean?
Yeah?
This thing's humming.
Hmm.
Wait.
That anatomy dummy you were
molesting at the lab.
Excuse me?
What if that's what
this is about?
What exactly
are you accusing me of?
I don't mean that.
I mean, there was
an anatomy dummy there,
and here...
You're joking.
You're not joking.
Okay, uh, so, what,
we've got... we've got
a bunch of killer dolls
like... Chucky?
I mean, come on,
that's... that's just...
friggin' creepy.
I mean, if ghosts
can possess humans
and... and move objects,
why can't they possess this?
I suppose.
But riddle me this, bat boy...
ghosts aren't exactly known
for hopping county lines, right?
True.
This one hits up a college
and now a factory,
what, three towns over?
Doesn't add up.
So we dig.
Over there.
I don't like the way
Kim Cattrall's lookin' at me.
Well, this dead guy's as squeaky clean
as the last dead guy.
I can't find a speck of dirt
on him. You?
Nothing.
Hmm.
Well, here's a speck.
Uh, seamstress named Rose Brown
went missing over a year ago.
Uh, cops just gave up on her.
Last seen at the factory,
presumed dead.
Survived by sister Isabel.
50 bucks...
vengeful spirit.
Pay sis a visit?
All right.
Answer it.
Lisa?
Finally.
I've been calling.
Ben?
- What are you...
- Something's wrong with mom.
What are you talking about?
- It's bad, Dean.
- Define "bad."
I... I don't know.
S... she won't talk to me.
- All right, put her on the phone.
- She won't come to the phone.
Ben, get your mom
and put her on the phone.
I... I... I can't.
Her door's locked.
She barely gets out of bed.
I'm not kidding.
Please just...
just come help me.
I... I don't know what to do.
All right,
let me call you back.
- Dean...
- Five minutes.
Come on, man,
I... I can't just leave.
Dude, you got to leave.
Yeah, but we're talking
life or death here.
Right. I can handle it
for 24 hours, Dean.
I get you want to bury it.
But I had to deal with my past year.
You got to deal with yours.
Oh, yeah, and that worked
so great for you.
Come on.
So, you and Rose
were close, huh?
Very.
Our parents died
when we were little,
so we had each other.
What was she like?
Um, kind...
giving.
She had the biggest heart.
But people gave her a hard time.
How come?
She was shy, a little awkward.
I guess that made her
an easy target.
I feel like I've been
defending her my whole life.
I'm sure she appreciated it.
Well, it went both ways.
She did more for me
than anybody else ever could.
I just miss her.
Um, may I?
Sure. Please.
Oh, it's a company Christmas
party a couple years back.
Wait, you work
at Salzman & Sons, too?
Well, everybody works
at the factory, yeah.
That's Rose.
Dean, hey, get this.
That college janitor?
He worked at the factory, too,
until last year.
Apparently, he quit right after
Rose's disappearance.
So fair bet something happened
to that girl around that factory,
so let's call that joint
ground zero.
Right, but it still
doesn't explain
how a ghost ended up
at a college in another zip code.
It's not like
she hopped the blue line.
I'm headed to the factory now.
I'll call when I get
the whole scoop on Rose.
So, how long have you been here
with the company?
I've been here
about three years now.
I'm sorry, w... what's this
got to do with me?
Relax.
Just a routine questioning.
Oh. Okay.
Uh, did you know Rose Brown?
Uh...
Maybe.
Uh, the name
sounds kind of familiar.
She was a seamstress here.
She went missing
about a year ago.
Here.
You mind taking a look?
Uh, yeah, I s...
I saw her around.
Anything you can tell me
about her that might help?
Look, I'd love to help,
but I don't know anything.
And, uh, I'm about to be
late back from break, so...
You seem nervous, Jonny.
Well
those guys that died
were my friends.
O... of course
I'm gonna be upset.
I didn't say upset.
I said nervous.
Here.
In case you remember anything.
Dean, what are you doing here?
Well, you look absolutely fine.
What's going on?
We've been "parent trapped."
What?
Ben sent out a 911.
Why would he do that?
You're going on a date, huh?
Come in.
You want to sit down?
Not so much.
So, who's the guy?
"Who's the guy?"
His name is Matt.
He's a doctor.
Oh, Dr. Matt.
How respectable.
Really? That's how
this is gonna be?
Look, I... I...
I called you six times, Dean.
And I almost called
you back about 100.
Good to know.
Lis, Ben called me.
I dropped everything and ran.
If you want to know
if I care...
Doesn't help me.
What do you want from me?
I'm not asking for anything.
Well, then ask for something!
Um...
- Go to your room!
You know, I... I can't...
ask for something.
I know what I want.
But I can't have it...
not how you live.
My phone rings, I think...
tiny chance it's you,
big chance it's Sam calling
to tell me you're dead.
- Lis...
- No, don't.
Don't apologize or anything.
It's just...
It's just I get to this place
where I'm okay,
and then you show up
at our door.
You keep doing that,
every time I think
I'm never gonna see you again.
I'm trying to get over you.
What are you trying to do?
What do you want
from us, Dean?
Why am I flipping out?!
I... I don't know,
maybe 'cause of the feds!
Maybe 'cause Dave and Steve
are freaking dead.
Look... no. No.
Just... call me later.
Come on.
What's going on?
That was a ghost trying
to kill you for being a dick.
What?
You know what?
You're lucky you are
the most suspicious interview
of all time.
I figured something like this
would happen.
Figured something like what
would happen?
Buddy, look, I don't have time
for the big speech, all right?
So, brass tacks...
Rose is back.
That's crazy!
Look, you're gonna end up
like your friends
unless you tell me
what you did to Rose.
Do you want me
to help you or not?
It was just a stupid joke.
You know, I mean, you...
you... you play jokes.
We didn't think
it was that big of a deal.
What did you do?
We made Rose think
she had a secret admirer.
I don't think the girl had ever
been asked out in her life.
Honestly, we just thought
she was kind of pathetic...
so we knew
she'd take the bait.
She was so excited.
The poor girl
never saw it coming.
Look, Rose,
I think he likes you.
It was mean.
But you know how it is when
a group of guys get together.
They... they act like jackasses.
Aw, don't be like that.
Come on, Rosey,
it's just a joke!
Go to hell.
It happened so fast...
Hey, take a joke, Rosey.
Seriously.
We didn't mean
for it to happen.
And then it was too late.
- What are you doing?
- I'm calling the cops.
- Are you crazy?
- It was an accident.
We tricked her here.
I grabbed her.
That's involuntary
manslaughter at least,
and that's if they even
believe us.
You understand?
Steve said there was
only one option.
I wish I could
take it all back.
I'm sure you do.
I didn't kill her.
Okay.
Look me in the eyes
and tell me
none of it's on you.
Look, I'm not saying
you deserve to die.
I can help you.
How?
You have to tell me
where she's buried.
In the woods,
a clearing off Canyon Run Road.
- No, no, no, no. You're not going anywhere.
- But I...
you need to stay inside the salt line
until I tell you you're safe.
You just want me
to stand here all night?!
Consider it getting off easy.
Well, that's ridiculous.
Plants could never
kill a zombie.
You think
I'm gonna say "I'm sorry"?
And why would I think that?
Because you lied
to get me here?
It was an emergency.
A date's not an emergency, Ben.
It is if it's the third one.
I watch TV.
I know what that means.
Well, your mom's a grown-up.
She gets to go out.
Why won't you come home?
Can't you just say "I'm sorry"
and then come back?
I'm sorry. I can't.
- Can't or won't?
- Both.
- So, you hate mom now?
- What? No, come on.
- So it's me.
- Ben, stop it.
Whatever I did, I'm sorry.
Listen to me.
You didn't do anything.
You understand that?
Look, one day you'll, uh...
you'll get this
when you're older.
Don't talk to me like I'm six.
Okay, fine.
It's like this, then.
Just 'cause you love someone
doesn't mean you should stick around
and screw up their life.
So I can't be here.
You think something
will follow you home?
No.
No, I don't, but I think my job
turns me into somebody
that can't sit
at your dinner table.
And if I stayed,
you'd end up just like me.
Why do you say it
like you're so... bad?
Well, trust me, I'm not someone
you want to aim to be.
- Don't I get a vote?
- No, you don't.
I'm sorry, Ben.
But, you see,
this way you got a shot
at living
whatever life you want.
You know, pick one.
Pick five.
'Cause with me,
there's just the one road.
- You're a liar, Dean.
- Excuse me?
You say family's so important,
but... but what do you call
people who... who care for you,
who love you
even when you're a dick?
You know you're walking out
on your family, right?
All right, it's over.
You're safe.
And, Jonny?
Look at this
as a new beginning.
Lot of chances
not to be a jackass.
Jenny?
Hon... we're leaving...
Tonight.
So, pack up.
Just the essentials.
All I want is for us
to move on with our lives.
I love you.
You know that.
It's been...
it's been really hard, Jen.
This is Dean's
other, other cell,
so you must know what to do.
Hey, it's not over.
Burning the remains
didn't stop her.
She's got to be
hooked to something else.
I'm gonna head
to the sister's now.
Call me.
So, um, this is it?
I gave most of her clothes
to the Goodwill.
She didn't have much.
Those yours?
Yeah.
- Are you in school?
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
- Where?
- Uh, Great Falls.
So let me guess...
Um, you were at the chem lab
and the factory this week.
Well, yeah.
Did you happen to stop by a bar
called McOwen's last night?
Everybody from the factory
goes there.
I stop in
maybe three times a week.
Why?
That's it.
- So this is all about you.
- What? What is?
The murders... your co-workers,
your college janitor.
What, you... you think
I could do something like that?!
No, no, no, no, no.
But... but I think
you're at the center.
Me? How?
What are you wearing of Rose's?
A ring? A bracelet?
- Her baby teeth in a locket? What?
- You're scaring me.
Just think, please.
- What... what do you have of Rose
that you carry with you? - I... I'm...
What?
Well, the only thing I have
of hers is a part of me.
When I was 16, she gave me
one of her kidneys.
- Her kidney?
- Yeah.
You're kidding.
Will you please tell me
what this is about?
Yeah. Um...
But I'm gonna need you
to come with me.
So, that the girl
with the haunted kidney?
Yeah.
Well, just when you think
you seen it all.
What do you want to do?
Can't exactly burn the thing.
I mean, she kind of needs it.
Well, she can't just
walk around with it, Dean.
The spirit's attached.
It's gonna use her to get close
to anyone it wants revenge on.
It's not gonna stop killing.
Okay, so what are you suggesting,
that we cut it out of her?
And then what?
Leave her in a tub of ice
with a phone taped to her hand?
Maybe we should
call Dr. Robert.
Might have some leads on some
non-haunted, black-market
replacement kidneys.
He works out of a butcher shop.
It's pretty clean.
You'd be surprised.
No. I think
we have to go hoodoo.
- Hoodoo?
- Yeah.
That's more of a band-aid,
not really a cure.
It buys us a minute.
All right, Louisiana it is.
Voodoo?!
What the hell
are you talking about?
Actually, it's "hoodoo."
It's a little different.
- Hold on, Isabel.
- You're not Feds.
Just let us explain.
No.
No way.
That's impossible.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
She possesses sex dolls!
This... this is not a sex doll!
Hey, you leave my baby alone!
She's got
nothing to do with this!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Okay, here, here, here.
Get in.
Son of a bitch!
I'm so sorry, baby.
Okay.
You all right?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
You guys?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm...
Isabel?
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for this.
How's it look?
Well, considering she got
carjacked by poltergeist,
could be worse.
I mean, what exactly
did we do back there, Sam?
Yeah, I'm not putting it
in the win column, either.
We saved a few dicks,
a... a... and we killed
an innocent girl.
I got a heartbroken kid
and a woman
who's so pissed at me...
I see what you mean
about facing your past.
It's, uh...
- It's awesome. Thanks.
- Dean.
- I mean, all we do is make a mess.
- That's not true.
We do save lives,
now and again.
Yeah, I guess.
I'm just...
I'm just tired
of all the bad luck, you know?
Well, you know, number one,
bad luck is kind of
in the job description.
And two, it's not all bad.
Really. Look at me.
I mean, at least
Satan's left the building.
Yeah.
It's the little things.
And I have a soul
because of you.
I never thanked you
for that, did I?
Ah, it's all good, man.
Well, thanks.
You'd have done
the same for me.
I mean it.
Look, we keep our heads down,
keep swinging.
We'll lose some.
Hopefully, we'll win more.
And...
I don't know.
Anyway, for what it's worth,
I got your back.
Yeah, I know.
== Sync by elderman ==
== corrections by elderman & gloriabg ==
== www.addic7ed.com ==
Edited by Scooby