Hey, Dean.
It's me.
How long you been back, Sam?
About a year.
You been back
practically this whole time?!
You finally had what you wanted.
You wanted a family.
I need you to go.
You're a hunter.
# I'm back #
DEAN: It's Sam. He's different.
# I'm back in the saddle again #
It's his soul.
It's gone.
# I'm back #
CROWLEY: You bag me a live Alpha,
and I'll give you
little Sammy's soul back.
# I'm back in the saddle again #
MAN: We're waiting for the word.
DEAN:
Their Alpha's building an army.
Like we're going to war.
Bring me creatures.
# I'm back in the saddle
again #
But if you're the first...
who made you?
We all have our mothers.
When we freaks die,
where do we go?
Not Heaven, not Hell.
- Purgatory.
- And I want it.
- I want my soul back.
- I can't.
Sam's soul has been
locked in the cage
with Michael and Lucifer.
Putting this thing back in
would smash me to bits.
CASTIEL: We have no idea
what will happen.
Paralysis, insanity,
psychic pain so profound
that he's locked inside himself
for the rest of his life.
BOBBY:
Death, the Horseman.
Hello, Dean.
- Death said he can put up a wall.
- A wall?
You wouldn't remember Hell.
What's the bet?
DEATH: I want you to be me
for one day.
It's my life. It's my soul.
I don't want it.
You need to scar your vessel.
Sorry.
Don't do this.
Don't scratch the wall.
[Screaming]
[Thunder rumbles, rain falling]
[Thunder crashes]
[Breathing heavily]
STAN:
How you doing?
I'm great.
This is great.
Penny, it's gonna be okay.
You know, a lot more people die
in the shower.
Good to know.
Thanks.
I didn't think we'd run into
any weather, though.
[Gasps]
[Thunder crashes]
Look, can we just land?
- Please?
- Couple minutes. All right? We're close.
[Sighs]
I'm sorry.
- What was that?!
- What?
Something just flew by
the window! It was huge!
Probably just a bird, okay?
No! No, Stan,
that was not a bird.
Well, then, what was it?
I don't know.
[Sighs]
Penny, there's nothing out there.
[Thunder crashes]
I promise.
Hey, just close your eyes, okay?
It's okay.
Just lean back.
Try to relax.
[Thunder crashes]
Think of some place nice.
Waves on a beach.
Oh ...
[Glass shatters]
Stan?!
Ohh!
Oh, my God!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
[Screaming]
Season 6 Episode 12
"Like a Virgin"
[Door opens]
DEAN: Well?
His soul is in place.
Is he ever gonna wake up?
I'm not a human doctor, Dean.
Could you take a guess?
Okay.
Probably not.
- Oh, well, don't sugar-coat it.
- I'm sorry, Dean,
but I warned you not to put
that thing back inside him.
What was I supposed to do?
Let T-1000 walk around,
hope he doesn't open fire?
Let me tell you what his soul
felt like when I touched it.
Like it had been
skinned alive, Dean.
If you wanted to kill
your brother,
you should have done it outright.
[Wings flapping]
[Sighs]
Like my daddy always said,
"just 'cause it kills your liver
don't mean it ain't medicine".
Sam still asleep?
Yeah.
He'll wake up.
Dean, he's been through
how much?
Somehow, he always bounces back.
He's never been through this.
- Job?
- Might be.
Can I help?
Send me to the library?
Anything?
Couple goes up in a light plane.
- Wreckage was just found in the woods.
- Couple of Buddy Holly's?
Doesn't really seem
like "news of the weird".
Pilot was found
17 miles away, flamb?ed.
Girl's just gone.
No body, no nothing.
Okay, I'm not changing
the channel.
Dean.
Sam?
Are you...
[breathing deeply]
Good to see you.
Wait.
I saw you...
I... I felt
Lucifer snap your neck.
Well, Cass kind of...
Cass is alive?
Yeah, Cass... Cass is fine.
Sam, are you okay?
Actually, um...
I'm starving.
So, Sam...
Yeah?
What's the last thing
you remember?
The field.
And then I fell.
Okay, and then?
I woke up in the panic room.
That's it?
You really don't remember...
Let's be glad.
Who wants to remember
all that hell?
Well, how...
how long was I gone?
- About a year and a half.
- What?
I was downstairs...
I don't remember anything.
S... so, how'd I get back?
Was it Cass?
Not exactly.
Dean, what did you do?
Me and Death...
Death?!
The Horseman?
I had leverage.
It's done.
- You sure?
- It's over.
Slate's wiped.
Well, isn't this
just neat and clean?
Yes, it is... for once.
Is there anything else
I should know?
No.
Another beer?
Uh, yeah.
[Ratchet clicking]
DEAN: Hey.
How is he?
He's, uh...
He's good. Really good.
Better than I could have hoped.
Uh-huh.
What?
Why the poop-face?
I'm glad he's better.
I really am.
But...
That kid went straight-up
Menendez on me not 10 days ago.
And now it's all just...
erased?
Sorry. I'm having a bit of
a hard time even looking at him.
It wasn't Sam.
Well, maybe it wasn't all Sam,
but it was him, Dean.
Well, what do you want to do, Bobby?
We tell him everything?
No. Just wish I could,
that's all.
Yeah, but if we start throwing
that crap at him,
we don't know
what's gonna happen.
- It could ... it could crack the wall.
- I know. I know.
So, you know what?
As far as I'm concerned,
it's a gift horse,
and I'm not looking for teeth.
I'm sending Death
a damn fruit basket.
He's gonna find out, you know.
One way or another,
someone will tell him, or
he'll figure it out on his own.
He's not dumb.
He should hear it from us.
Can we just leave it alone
for the moment, please?
Okay.
But you better prep
for the "B" side,
'cause when Sam realizes
we're shining him...
it ain't gonna be cute.
Sam still asleep?
Yeah, let him rest.
We'll call him later.
Call me from where?
Oh.
Uh, there's this thing in Oregon.
- Great. I'm in.
- Whoa, whoa.
You just got vertical.
Exactly.
I'm up. I'm good.
Well, a few more days
of crap cable couldn't hurt.
Right. Because that's what you did
when you got back from hell.
All right.
You, me, and Bobby.
Oh, you two go on ahead.
You got this covered.
I, uh, forgot I promised
that idjit Rufus
I'd work the phones
for him, so...
You sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You two enjoy catching up, okay?
What was that?
One part age,
three parts liquor.
[Intro to Jethro Tull's
"New Day Yesterday" plays]
Uh, you got it, officer.
Thank you.
You too.
So, get this...
besides the crash,
there were two other
disappearances in town this week.
- Really?
- Yeah, last weekend,
a college girl vanished
from her apartment.
On the 17th floor.
Then, three days ago, another girl
didn't make it home from school.
- They know each other?
- No. No connection.
Just young and female,
like the plane-crash girl.
What would disappear a girl
out of the sky, anyway?
Good question.
- So you never even tried, huh?
- Tried?
To go live a life... after.
You do remember
you promised that, right?
Yeah, I remember.
So, why didn't you try?
What makes you think I didn't?
'Cause look at you.
Look at this.
You're exactly the same.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I was with them for a year...
Lisa and Ben.
A year?
So then what?
Didn't work out.
# It was a new day yesterday #
# But it's an old day now #
You're, uh... Penny Dessertine's
sister, right?
Mm-hmm.
Uh, we'd just like to ask you
a few questions.
Look, the cops already came by.
I'm tired.
So, if you don't mind...
I... I understand.
Really, I do.
I know how hard this must be.
We'd just like to figure out
what happened.
This will be quick.
I promise.
Okay.
Fine. Come in.
Penny was very shy.
To herself.
Not at all
what you'd call adventurous.
What, like flying through a
lightning storm in a two-seater?
She was terrified of that thing.
She just did it for Stan.
Stan?
They were just starting
to get serious.
She didn't want to seem,
you know... not interested.
I just wish
I'd told her to stay home.
We don't even have
a body to bury.
[Sighs]
SAM: Hey.
- What do you got?
Uh...
Well, looks like
those other two missing girls
both baked cookies
for the Lord.
- What is that? Code?
- No.
Church choir, bake sales,
promise-ring clubs... the works.
They were good girls.
But Penny wasn't even
a Christian, so...
I have another theory.
Penny's diary.
Did you steal that
from her room?
I love that
you even asked me that.
- And why wouldn't I?
- No reason.
So, girls kidnappings.
What if its not about religion?
What if it's about purity?
You think they're all...
Virgins, Sam. Virgins.
Penny was 22.
- Yeah, with a pink room.
- So?
And stuffed teddy bears.
Fine.
But you really think...
"I've decided I'm going to give
Stan my most precious gift".
Wow. That sounded really creepy
coming out of your mouth.
I think I delivered it.
You know, you... you could have
led with the diary. You know?
Anyways, let's say
you're right. Fine.
Who would want virgins?
You got me.
I prefer ladies with experience.
[Branches cracking]
Ohh!
Aaaaaaaah!
It happened so fast.
It's all right, Melissa.
What came at you?
You can tell us.
Woman on P.A.:
Paging Dr. Stathem.
It... it looked like a...
a giant bat.
You think
I'm making it up, right?
That's what the other man said.
Well, I'm not the other man.
It came right at me.
It was huge. I swear.
That's how I got this.
[Grunts softly]
[Sighs]
So, it attacked.
And then what happened?
I don't know.
I passed out,
and when I woke up, it was gone.
Is there anything else
you can think of?
Anything you can tell us,
even if it doesn't seem important?
Well, my ring got lost.
Or else that thing stole it,
if that makes any sense.
- What kind of ring?
- Gold.
Promise ring.
So, uh...
from, like, a church?
Like... like a purity ring?
Yeah. Why?
[Clears throat]
I got to ask.
Uh, Melissa...
Look, nobody is, uh,
judging anybody here, okay?
Believe me. But...
Should you really
be wearing that ring?
- Well, I... I mean, I... I am...
- Really?
Matt Barne didn't count.
[Siren wails]
So, what, you think
Batman tried to rape her?
Well, he does carry
a lot of rage.
But he rejected her because
she was already dehymenated, huh?
You think?
I think it just goes to show
that being easy's
pretty much all upside.
[Scoffs lightly]
So, what kind of thing
likes virgins and gold?
P. Diddy?
- You know, it's comforting.
- What's that?
I died for a year, came back,
and you're still not funny.
Shut up.
I'm hilarious.
[Scoffs]
[Ominous music plays]
This can't be possible.
Try me.
Um, I googled "fire",
"claws", "flying",
"stealing virgins", and "gold",
and it all takes me
to the same place.
Where?
"World of Warcraft" fan-sites.
I don't know what that means.
Dragons, dude.
See? Told you. Not possible.
Actually, it might be.
How? In what reality?
It's been a strange year.
We should get a second opinion.
[Telephone rings]
[Telephone beeps]
[Sizzling]
BOBBY: Yeah?
What do you know about dragons?
What? Nothing.
Seriously.
Well, they're not like
the Loch Ness monster, Dean.
Dragons aren't real.
- Could you make a few calls?
- To who? Hogwarts?
Humor me.
Fine.
You're a gentleman
and a scholar.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, how's "memento"
doing over there?
He caught you in any lies yet?
Everything's fine.
Sam says hey.
[Dial tone]
[Phone clatters]
You okay?
Yeah.
Bobby say anything?
Nope.
[Sighs]
[Sighs] Dad never wrote
anything about dragons.
I promise.
I'd remember if I read
"The Neverending Story" in there.
Hey, did we hunt
a skin-walker lately?
Doesn't ring a bell.
Why?
I don't know.
Just... d?j? vu or something.
- Are you sure? I could have sworn...
- You got to remember
your eggs are still
a little scrambled, right?
But, yeah, I'm sure.
[Sighs]
All right.
Yeah. Never mind.
[Cellphone rings]
[Cellphone beeps]
Hey, Bobby.
What do you got?
Can't believe
she didn't jump right to mind.
Dr. Visyak.
Medieval Studies, S.F.U.
Dr. Visyak, S.F.U.
Got it. Thanks.
[Telephone beeps]
All right.
I'm going to San Francisco,
figure out how to kill
these things.
You figure out where they are.
Wait... did... did Bobby say
where they like to park?
- No
- Great. Back to the lore.
Which says what?
That they live in Middle-Earth?
No. Caves.
You're such a nerd.
[Door closes]
[Woman whimpering]
[Wings flapping]
Please!
Please let me go!
No!
Aah! No!
[Bones crack]
Shut up!
Shut up,
or I'll break the other one.
Now, get in there.
Come on.
[Women whimpering]
[Metal creaking]
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
[Engine shuts off]
[Doorbell buzzes]
WOMAN: Yes?
Dr. Visyak.
My name is Dean Winchester.
Office hours
are Monday and Friday.
Bobby Singer sent me.
Hello?
[Sighs]
Hi.
Bobby Singer.
Tell him something for me
next time you see him.
Hmm?
Actually,
just kick him in the jewels.
That's more poetic.
No love lost
between you two, huh?
[Chuckles]
No. Just the opposite.
Oh?
That's his story to tell.
He's the idiot.
So, what's this about?
Well...
[Clears throat]
Uh... dragons.
Really?
What, no 12-sided-dice joke?
We can joke about them
because they've disappeared.
But they aren't funny.
At all.
Well, one just flew in
state-side.
Are you sure?
Fits the lore to a "T".
But how? I mean, why?
It's been 700 years.
Banner crop of crazy all the way
around these days, doc.
- So you want to know how to kill it.
- That's right.
Well, you need a blade.
Uh...
[Clears throat]
Okay. What kind of blade?
One forged with dragon's blood.
[Chuckles]
So you need one to kill one,
but you got to kill one
to make one.
How does that work out?
Well, there aren't many
dragon swords around anymore.
Five or six, tops, worldwide.
I mean, there's
the sword of St. George,
and, of course,
there's Excalibur.
- And there's...
- You know a lot about
- this stuff, don't you?
- Well, I sure as hell better.
I have one in the basement.
You have one.
Finding it took two decades,
countless hours,
and some really bad sex with
an eastern European ambassador,
but, yeah.
[Sighs]
[Chuckles softly]
That is not real.
Is that real?
Is it Excalibur?
[Chuckles] No.
This...
is the Sword of Bruncvik.
Love of my life.
So, uh, what's with
the [knocks] cement shoe?
You know, binding sword to stone
used to be all the rage.
To protect them.
All right, well,
how do we get this puppy out?
[Laughs]
Well, come on.
You know this one.
We need a brave knight
who's willing to step up
and kill the beast.
Right.
All right, well, I'll, uh...
Give it a whirl.
- Do you mind?
- Oh.
[Dramatic music plays]
[Thud, music stops]
[Clears throat]
You okay?
[Grunts]
Never better.
[Dramatic music resumes]
[Music stops] Oh, son of a bitch!
That's really on there!
[Sword vibrates]
Yeah, afraid so.
- Well, I have another idea.
- What?
[Chuckles softly]
Well, you're not gonna like it.
[Sighs]
[Cellphone beeps]
[Telephone rings]
[Sighs]
Sam.
Where's Dean?
SAM: Hey, um...
He went to go see your friend.
So, look, I'm trying to figure out
where this thing lairs up.
Uh, little help, maybe?
What are the parameters?
Caves, basically.
But there's nothing
around for miles.
So, less literal, then.
What else you got local
that's cold, dark, and wet?
Huh.
Well, um...
There's no subway lines.
Sewers.
[Chuckles]
That could be it. Thanks.
- All right.
- Wait, Bobby.
Wait. Um...
You okay?
Yeah, of course.
Why? What's wrong?
Besides the way you been
acting and talking? Nothing.
- Is there something I should know?
- No.
All you need to know
is where Godzilla's holed up.
Well, Bobby,
what happened this last year?
It had its moments.
No more than usual.
It's got nothing to do
with you, Sam. How could it?
Right. 'Course.
- Call me if you need anything.
- Yeah...
[telephone beeps]
[Sighs]
Castiel, um...
I'm back.
So, if you got a minute...
Sam.
It's so good to see you alive.
Yeah.
You too.
Um...
Look, I... I would hug you, but...
That would be awkward.
Um...
Was a crazy year, huh?
I... I... I just talked to Bobby.
He... he told me
everything that happened.
Frankly, I'm surprised
that you survived.
I was begging Dean
not to do it.
Yeah. No,
I... I... I can understand that.
You know, it's a miracle
it didn't kill you.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a miracle, all right.
So, how does it feel?
What?
Well, to have your soul back,
of course.
Right. You... you mean 'cause
I was walking around with no soul.
Uh...
Really good, Cass.
I'm real good.
You know what?
I'm... I'm just hazy
on a few of the details, though.
Um...
You think maybe you could...
walk me through?
You know what?
I... I... I don't like this at all.
You do realize that this
is the single most valuable artefact
you have ever touched.
It's also the only weapon we got.
Look, I know
what I'm doing, okay?
I actually learned it all
from Bobby.
Hey, whatever happened there,
you know he's at least
a genius at this.
Do you want me to kill
that dragon or not?
[Sighing] Okay.
Trust me.
You rocks think you're so smart.
All right.
Welcome to the 21st century.
All right, stand back.
[Explosion]
[Detonator clatters]
Okay. Now...
[Sword unsheathes]
[Clatter]
You've got insurance
for this, right?
[Chuckles softly]
[Coughs]
And what are we supposed
to do with this, Dean?
Give it a booster shot?
It's what we got.
All right?
We're just gonna have to get
a little closer. That's all.
Where are we on the caves?
Nowhere.
Sewers, on the other hand...
Here. Check this out.
So, two of the disappearances
happened within a mile of here.
So I think we start there
and work our way around.
Awesome.
Who doesn't love sewers?
Let's go.
[Sighs]
What?
Nothing.
Uh, yeah, let's go.
Ugh! God.
Just when I get used to a smell,
I hit a new flavor.
Dude, we have been
here for hours.
There is nothing.
I think the lore is off.
Hey, what if, uh...
What if dragons like
nice hotels?
- What is that?
- What?
Holy crap.
Okay, maybe
there are dragons here.
Wait. Dean...
Not now.
Check this out.
A little arts-and-crafty
for a giant bat, right?
WOMAN: [In distance]
Hello? Is someone there?
[Water trickling]
Hello? Over here.
Hey.
We're gonna get you out.
Quick. He's coming back.
[Metal clatters] [Whimpers]
Where do you think
you're gonna stick that?
Aah!
- Where did you get that?
- Comic-Con.
[Grunting]
Come on, come on.
Aah!
[Thud]
[Wings flapping]
[Car door closes]
Hey, Sam. [Clears throat]
Ask me what time it is.
[Scoffs lightly]
Why don't you cut to the chase
and just roll in it?
I rarely have wealth.
[Chuckles]
Dean...
Yeah?
I am so...
so sorry.
I can't even begin to say.
For what?
You know what.
- Did Bobby...?
- Cass.
Cass.
Friggin' child.
You should have told me, Dean.
- You weren't supposed to know.
- What I did?
To Bobby? To you?
Of course I should know.
Sam, Death didn't just shove
your soul back in, okay?
He put up the great wall of Sam
between you and the things
that you don't remember.
And trust me when I say
that the things you don't know
could kill you.
That's not a joke.
All right.
But I have to set things right.
Or what I can, anyway.
It wasn't you.
You know, I kind of feel
like I got slipped
the worst mickey of all time...
And I woke up to find out
that I had burnt
the whole city down.
And you can say
it wasn't me, but...
I'm the one with the zippo
in my pocket, you know?
So I'm not sure
it's that cut and dry.
And, look, I appreciate
you trying to protect me.
I really do.
But I got to fix...
what I got to fix.
So I need to know what I did.
But you don't know how dangerous
that could be.
What would you do?
Right. Same thing.
Sam...
[Footsteps approach]
Boys, something I think
you ought to see.
BOBBY: Now, as near
as I can figure it,
this dates back
around the 14th century.
What language is it?
Da Vinci code.
Real obscure Latinate.
Gonna take me my golden years
to translate it all.
Oh, and, uh, F.Y.I...
that ain't paper.
What is it?
It's human skin.
Okay. I'm fairly clear
on this first bit.
It basically describes this place.
It's like the backside
of your worst nightmares.
It's all blood and bone
and darkness.
Filled with the bodies and souls
of all things hungry,
sharp, and nasty.
[Truck door closes]
Where are they?
[Sighs]
I ran into trouble.
You're damn lucky I got enough.
This is your lucky day,
little girl.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
SAM: Monsters?
It's monster-land.
According to this,
it goes by many names...
most of which
I can't pronounce...
but I'm thinking you know
"Purgatory".
Purgatory?
Awesome.
Well, that is
[Clears throat]
good to know.
So, you're saying
that these, uh, dragon freaks
were squatting in the sewers
and reading tone poems
about Purgatory?
Oh, no, no, no.
They're reading
an instruction manual.
What?
Yeah.
If you're nuts enough to want
access to a place that gnarly,
this book will show you
how to open a door.
Door to Purgatory.
Well, I know a demon
who would have loved
to have known about that.
So, how do you open the door?
Ask Cloverfield.
I'm pretty sure
he's got that page.
[Rumbling, wind howling]
"Ego coniuro vos,
insolubiliter
ad mei potenciam alligati"!
[Rumbling intensifies]
[Crying]
[Sizzling]
"Ad me...
- sine prestolacione venire...
- Let me go! Please stop!
- ...debeatis aperiat"!
- No!
- Please don't!
- It'll go easier if you relax.
[Screaming]
"Huc sine mora
debeas mater"!
[Flames crackling]
BOBBY: It gets worse.
SAM: Worse?
This ain't talking about how
to take a vacation over there.
This is all about opening a door
to let something in.
Bring something here.
What?
I'm working on it.
Could you give us something?
- I got a name.
- Okay.
"Mother".
Mother? M... mother of what?
Mother of dragons?
I wish.
It says it a few times here.
"Mother of all".
Welcome.
You kept me waiting.
DEAN: What the hell
does "mother of all" mean?
I don't know.
MOTHER:
We have so much to do.
Let's get started.
== Sync by elderman ==
== corrections by elderman & gloriabg ==
== www.addic7ed.com ==
Edited by Scooby