I don't believe it.
Wyoming?
What does that mean?
Each of these X's is an
abandoned frontier church...
all mid-19th century,
built by Samuel Colt.
Samuel Colt...
the demon-killing,
gun-making Samuel Colt?
Yep.
He built private railway lines
connecting church to church.
It just happens
to lay out like this.
It's a devil's trap.
A 100-square-mile
devil's trap.
1973.
- What is this?
- What does it look like?
- Is it real?
- Very.
Okay, so, what, angels got
their hands on some DeLoreans?
How did I get here?
Time is fluid, Dean.
It's not easy, but we can
bend it on occasion.
But I'm thinking you know
"Purgatory."
This is all about opening a
door to let something in.
- What?
- I'm working on it.
- Could you give us something?
- I got a name.
"Mother of all."
We got zero on ganking her.
We have so much to do.
Let's get started.
She has a message for you.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
You're all gonna die.
Season 6 Episode 18
"Frontierland"
Hyah!
It's here, somewhere.
I know it.
Help me move this.
Well, I'll be damned.
Welcome to the Campbell
family library.
So, Samuel collected
all this stuff, huh?
Apparently.
Wow.
All right, well,
what are we looking for?
Well, anything that'll put a run
in the Octomom's stockings.
Pick a row.
Bingo.
Either of you jokers ever heard
anything about a Phoenix?
River, Joaquin,
or the giant flaming bird?
It says here
that the ashes of a Phoenix
can burn the mother.
The mother?
Great.
Where do we get one?
You got me.
I thought it was a myth.
All right, great.
Well, let's see if we can find
something out about a Phoenix.
Guys.
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys,
check this out.
"March 5, 1861.
"Sunrise, Wyoming.
"Gun killed a Phoenix today.
"Left a pile
of smoldering ash."
Really? Whose gun?
Colt's.
Colt? Colt like --
Like the Colt.
From...
...Samuel Colt's Journal.
What?!
- That's his?
- Yeah.
- Dude, no.
- Dude, yes.
- Well, let me see it.
- Get your own.
Well, what else did he say
about the Phoenix?
What does it look like?
Has it got feathers?
It just says "Phoenix."
- Did he say where he tracked it?
- No.
All right, so I guess
we got to find one of our own,
whatever it is.
I know where we can find one.
March 5, 1861.
Sunrise, Wyoming.
We'll "Star Trek IV"
this bitch.
I only watched
"Deep Space Nine."
It's like I don't even
know you guys anymore.
"Star Trek IV."
Save the whales.
We hop back in time,
we join up with Samuel Colt,
we hunt the Phoenix,
and then we haul the ashes
back home with us.
- Time travel?
- Yeah.
That's a reasonable plan?
We got a guy who can swing it.
Castiel.
The, uh, fate of the world
is in the balance.
So, come on down here.
Come on, Cass,
"I Dream of Jeannie"
your ass down here pronto.
Please.
Jeannie?
Rachel.
I understand
you need some assistance?
How can I help you?
Well, uh, we kind of need
to talk to the Big Kahuna.
I'm here on Castiel's behalf.
Where is he?
Busy.
- Busy?
- Yes.
Well, we've got a line
on the mother
of freaking everything, so --
I'm sure your issue's
very important.
But Castiel is currently
commanding an army, so --
So we get stuck
with Miss Moneypenny.
So you need
to learn your place.
Look, I don't know who you
think you are --
- I'm his friend.
- What, you think we're not?
I think you call him
when you need something.
We're fighting a war.
We get that.
Clearly you don't,
or you wouldn't call him
every time you stub your toe,
you petty, entitled little piece...
Rachel.
That's enough.
I told you
I'd take care of this.
It's all right.
You can go.
- You're staying?
- Go.
I'll come when I can.
Wow.
Friend of yours?
Yes.
She's, uh, my lieutenant.
She's...
committed to the cause.
Now, what do you need?
Where the hell's Dean?
Supply run, he said.
I don't know.
Um, about your plan.
You'll only have 24 hours.
Wait, what?
Why?
Well, the answer
to your question
can best be expressed
as a series of partial
differential equations.
Yeah, aim lower.
The further back I send you,
the harder it becomes
to retrieve you.
24 hours is all I can risk.
If I don't pull you home
within that time,
you'll be lost to me.
Well, then we better
get you a watch.
What the hell's all that?
We are going native.
Got to blend in.
Uh, no, thanks.
I'm fine.
- Sam.
- Dean, I can... I can wear this.
And look like a spaceman?
Look, just because you're obsessed
with all that Wild West stuff...
- No, I'm not.
- You have a fetish.
Shut up.
I like old movies.
You can recite every Clint Eastwood
movie ever made, line for line.
Even the monkey movies?
Yeah. Especially
the monkey movies.
His name is Clyde.
At least wear the damn shirt.
Dean, this is stupid.
I look stupid.
You going to a hoedown?
Now, is it... is it customary
to wear a blanket?
It's a sarape.
And, yes.
It's, uh...
Never mind.
Let's just go.
What's this?
Where you're goin',
they don't take plastic.
I'll send you back
to March 4th.
That should give you time
to find the Colt...
...and this
Phoenix creature.
All right, well,
see ya at High Noon tomorrow...
Partner!
Oh, now we're talking.
I have to go.
What about
getting the boys back?
Pray for me in 24 hours,
and I'll return.
I'll pray for all of us.
All right.
Let's go find Samuel Colt.
Hey, we should
try the Saloon first,
uh, see what we get
from the locals.
Sure.
Whatever, Sundance.
Think we'll have time
to hit on saloon girls?
I'm kidding.
Come on.
Oh, damn it.
You know what that is?
Yeah, it's horse...
Authenticity!
We stand here today...
March 4th, 1861...
to execute justice
upon Elias Finch
for the murder of his own wife.
Wow.
Talk about authenticity.
Sentence handed down
by myself,
Tye Mortimer, duly appointed
judge of the Wyoming circuit.
You will be hung by your neck
until you die.
You got anything to say?
You're gonna burn for this.
Every one of you.
Good times.
So where do we find Sammy Colt?
No idea.
Huh.
I think I know
who to ask, though.
Nice blanket.
Sheriff?
Can we have a word?
Depends who's askin'.
Marshal Eastwood.
Clint Eastwood.
This here is, uh, Walker.
He's a Texas Ranger.
So, what can I do for you boys?
Uh, we're looking for a man.
I'll bet.
Nice shirt, there.
What's wrong with my shirt?
You're very clean.
It's dirtier than it looks.
We need to find Samuel Colt.
Do you know him?
- The gun maker?
- Yeah. Is he in town?
Not that I know of.
Might try asking Elkins
over at the Saloon.
Been here longer than God.
This is not awesome.
Hi.
What'll you have?
Oh, uh, okay. Great.
I'll have
your top-shelf whiskey.
Only have the one shelf.
That'll do just fine.
And he'll have a sarsaparilla.
You Elkins?
One and only.
You know a man
named Samuel Colt?
He passed through here
about four years ago.
He still around?
Rumor is, he's building
a railroad stop
20 miles out of town,
just by the Postal road.
Middle of nowhere.
The Devil's Gate?
Location fits.
Howdy, boys.
Darla's my best girl.
Try me.
You want a kiss?
S-so much more germier
than I pictured.
Darla!
Ah.
Judge.
Nice to see you.
I thought we had a date.
Wow, that was a close one.
I guess it's good to be judge.
Yeah.
Ohh. It's like gasoline.
Sarsaparilla ain't half bad.
- You okay, Sheriff?
- 'Course I'm okay.
It was a ghost!
It wasn't a ghost.
Unless ghosts leave footprints.
I am telling you,
Elias Finch was here.
He did... that,
and then he walked
out that door.
Rope didn't kill him.
Seen it before.
Well, you got any idea
where he could be?
Could be a thousand places.
Well, you got a way
to flush him out?
'Course.
We're gonna form a posse.
Then we're gonna
string Finch up right.
Put a bullet in his head
for good measure.
That actually sounds
like a good plan.
You two should come along.
Meet downstairs at dawn.
Yeah, we'll be there.
Get yourselves
some real gear first, huh?
Well, I think we ought
to pay our respects to Finch.
I was thinking the same thing.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Rose from the ashes,
burned up its victim?
You know, maybe we're not
looking for a flaming bird.
Maybe the Phoenix is actually
walking around in cowboy boots.
That makes sense, right?
Could be Finch.
So, question is,
how do we put this thing out?
Well, we do know one thing
that'll kill friggin'
anything, right?
Yeah, the Colt.
So, you go get the gun.
But isn't the gun coming here?
I mean, according
to Samuel Colt's journal?
Yeah, but people here
barely even know who Colt is.
Maybe you got to go find him
and make history.
I'll stay here,
hook up with the posse.
'Cause you know me...
I'm a posse magnet.
I mean, I love posse.
Make that into a t-shirt.
You done?
Look, the problem is,
Colt's 20 miles outside of town.
How am I supposed to get
there and back before noon?
Ride 'em, cowboy.
Wh... uh, try...
try the other side.
- Yeah, good boy.
- Right. Yeah. Right.
Hey.
This actually feels all right.
All right, take it...
just take it easy.
Yeah, you bet. I'm good.
- All right, 11:00 A.M., right?
- Don't be late!
- Okay.
- All right.
Go on. Go.
Hyah!
I'm okay!
That poor horse.
Forgive me! I'm sorry!
You had your chance.
Tell it to the judge.
We need to talk.
You summoned me here?
Castiel,
I've been hearing things.
Things I don't want to believe.
Just tell me if it's true.
If what's true?
You know.
Your dirty little secret.
I have to defeat Raphael.
- Not this way, Castiel.
- Rachel.
We put our faith in you, and...
...look what
you're turning into.
I don't have a choice.
Then neither do I.
I'm sorry.
What the hell is going on?!
Cass?
Are we running or fighting?
We're...
Balls.
New hat.
I look good.
Where's the posse?
I must be early.
Or you're the only greenhorn
dumb enough
to go chasing after a ghost.
What are you talking about?
Sheriff's tough as nails.
He'll be here.
Oh, God!
The Sheriff's dead!
Or not.
Great.
Who's the Sheriff now?
What. What...
Now...
Congratulations, Sheriff.
Ahh.
Samuel Colt?
You have the wrong drunk,
gentlemen.
Have a nice day.
We've been looking
for you, Colt.
And who might "we" be?
Listen...
I've long since hung it up.
I'm tired,
and I'm too damn old for this,
and I'm sure as hell
not looking for any trouble.
Well, it's found you anyway.
We know you built
that Devil's Gate, Colt.
So you're gonna open it for us.
That is, if you fancy keeping
your lungs in your chest.
Walk away, gentlemen.
Well, I think we'd rather rip
you to ribbons, you soft...
Ah, that's a shame.
A damn shame.
Who's there?
Candygram for Mongo.
Howdy, pilgrim.
I ain't no pilgrim.
All right, back up.
Is that any way to, uh...
Greet your new boss?
Missed you at the posse
this morning.
I was a one-man wolf pack,
thanks to you.
What's going on here?
Going to visit my sister.
- Well, she'll have to wait.
- But if I don't...
Finch said he was coming back
for the former Sheriff...
Judge Mortimer...
and you.
That's two down and one to go.
Then just let me go!
You really think
you can outrun him?
He is going to kill you.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless we gank him first.
"Gank"?
What's "gank"?
Mister, you're crazy.
No way.
You're on your own.
I'm not asking you
to throw down with him.
I'm asking you
to play your part.
- My part?
- Yeah.
Bait.
Hello?
Okay, not a demon!
Not a demon!
Just...
just a hunter. Sheesh.
You're what?
You Samuel Colt?
My name is Sam Winchester.
I'm... I'm a hunter
from the year 2011.
Prove it.
All right.
A-all right?
That's... uh, that's it?
Well, when you've done this
job as long as I have...
...a giant from the future
with some magic brick
doesn't exactly
give you the vapors.
I need your help
killing a Phoenix.
A Phoenix? They exist?
Well, you shoot one
in about three hours.
If you say so.
I don't.
You do.
That's...
I'm either too drunk
or not drunk enough.
So what is it
I'm about to exactly do?
Well, the Phoenix
is in Sunrise,
so, uh, if we leave now,
you can...
I appreciate your situation,
but I'm not gonna be
of any help to you.
I'm booked.
Right, but... but
you say right here...
Don't believe
everything that you read.
But you're a hunter.
Retired.
- There's no such thing.
- I'm out.
There is
no getting out.
Look, for what it's worth,
in my time, you're a hero.
- Me?
- Yes, sir.
Now, look, we... we need
to kill this Phoenix.
Its ashes are the only thing
that can kill
the monster I'm hunting.
So stow your crap
for a few hours, and let's go.
We got to go now.
So, either you're coming
with me, or I need the gun.
What gun?
The gun.
Oh, that gun.
I lost it in a game of Stud.
You're lying.
Am I?
Now, that doesn't
sound like me.
You shot a couple of demons
with it less than an hour ago.
How do you figure?
Two pairs of bootprints.
Cabin reeks of sulfur.
Not bad.
You don't want it.
It's a curse.
Believe me.
Great. Then let me
take it off your hands.
You go put on a few more miles
and come back,
and we'll talk.
Trust me,
I've got plenty of mileage.
I'm doing you a favor.
Believe me.
So, what?
You can really just sit there?
I've given my whole life
to this.
I'm done.
- So it doesn't matter what happens.
- No, it doesn't.
So everything you did,
it all means nothing?
Give me the gun.
Cass, you... you like you went
12 rounds with truckasaurus.
What happened?
I was, uh...
I was betrayed.
Rachel, uh...
Raphael...
He corrupted her.
She turned on me.
Sorry.
Girl was a real... peach.
She's... dead.
I... was wounded.
I needed... safety.
Thank you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
What's with the finger painting?
It's a warding symbol
against angels.
How bad's it hurt?
I'll heal.
Well, good...
'Cause we got less than an hour
before you pick up the kids
at Frontierland.
I can't.
Come again?
This fight...
drained me.
Well, if you're up on blocks,
then call in another halo
who can get the job done.
I can't.
Well, there's got to be something
that can juice you up.
A spell... something.
There is one thing
that might work, but...
it's extremely dangerous.
Shocker.
So, lay it on me.
It's your soul.
What do you want me to do?
Make another deal?
Seal it with a kiss?
I need you to let me touch it.
Touch it?
The human soul...
it's pure... energy.
If I can siphon
some of that off,
I-I might be able
to bring Sam and Dean back.
And the catch is...?
Doing this is like...
putting your hand
in a nuclear reactor.
I have to do it very gingerly.
Or...?
Or you'll explode.
Well.
Keep both hands on the wheel.
Let's do this.
Never been late
in your damn life, Sam,
and now you're dragging ass.
So this is your big plan, huh?
Just let me rot in here
till Finch comes?
Pretty much.
Why's he gunning for you,
anyway?
I guess you missed the part
where we hung him?
No, I'm thinking to a thing like
Finch, that's no big whoop.
He would've just blown town,
but he came back.
That seems personal.
I'll tell you what...
you let me out of here,
and we'll talk.
No can do.
Open up that cell.
Open it yourself.
You melt people's faces off.
I'll bet you got the juice
to tear that apart easy, don't you?
Unless you can't.
Just like you couldn't
break those cuffs
when they strung you up.
Aah.
Iron shackles...
...iron bars, iron nail.
See a pattern?
Don't worry. Most creatures
I meet can't get it up for iron.
It's a common monster problem.
So you're a hunter.
Slash sheriff.
You know
what this son of a bitch did?
Do tell.
I was married to a woman.
Good woman... human.
We lived outside of town,
didn't bother anyone.
Sure, freak with
a heart of gold.
You want
to call me "monster," fine.
But all we did
was go into town.
I go into the bank
for five minutes.
I come out, she's gone.
And then I heard her scream.
This... man
had her pinned in the alley.
I go to stop him,
he pulls his gun,
shoots me, then her.
She died in my arms.
'Course, I don't die.
The shots brought the Sheriff.
Next thing I know, I'm in iron.
That's why I want him
just where he is...
trapped, scared.
I saved the best for last.
Is that true?
So tell me...
are you really
willing to die
to protect this piece of filth?
Honestly, I could
care less about him.
- He's a dick and a coward.
- Hey!
But this ain't about him.
I know what you are.
Really?
Yeah.
So...
I got to kill you.
Well, if you know what I am,
then you know you can't.
Wow, I should've
seen that coming.
Dean!
Sam, come on, come on!
Hey, where's Colt?
- He's not coming.
- What?!
But he sent this.
Ohh.
Hello, beautiful.
All right.
- Come on. Go!
- Yeah.
Are you sure?
Well, we can't just
strand those idjits
in Deadwood, can we?
The risks...
Just... don't explode me.
Get out here, Finch!
What are you doing?!
Come on!
Let's do this!
So, this is
how you want to die.
Fine.
Yippee-ki-yay, mother...
Dean!
The ashes!
You gotta send us back.
Dean, look at him.
He's fried.
I never want to do that again.
Bobby, you...
I'm still kickin',
Annie Oakley.
Be back good as new in...
a decade or two.
And we screwed the pooch.
Bobby, I'm sorry.
Is there a Sam Winchester here?
Who's asking?
Look, this is nuts...
me and a couple guys
made a bet.
So... this thing's been laying
around the office since...
ever!?
Uh, with a note on it
saying to bring it here today.
It's from a-a Samuel Colt?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
that's... that's mine.
Great. Thanks.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
"Dear Sam,
I got this address and date
"off your thingamajig,
"and I thought the enclosed
might come in handy.
Regards,
Samuel Colt."
Is that what I think it is?
Ashes of a Phoenix.
You know what this means?
Yeah, I didn't get
a "soulonoscopy" for nothing.
Yes.
And... it means
we take the fight to her.
Corrected by www.addic7ed.com
Thanks to gloriabg and elderman.
Edited by Scooby