Sam!
"Carry On Wayward Son." Performed by Kansas
You got to promise
not to try to bring me back.
# There'll be peace
when you are done #
# lay your weary head to rest #
Sammy!
# Don't you cry no more #
You're a hunter. Now you know
your brother's out there.
I need you to go.
It's Sam.
He's different.
It's his soul. It's gone.
I'm going to go to hell
to fetch your brother's soul.
I don't remember anything.
# Once I rose
above the noise and confusion #
# just to get a glimpse
beyond this illusion #
# I was soaring ever higher #
Finding Purgatory's
important to me...
an untapped oil well
of every fanged, clawed soul.
Do you have any idea
what souls are worth?
What power they hold?
Raphael
and his followers,
they want him
to rule heaven.
The last thing we want
is to let him take over.
That little limey mook
roasted months ago.
Crowley's alive.
I want to discuss
a simple business transaction.
With me?
You and Crowley have been
going after Purgatory together?
I can stop Raphael.
You have to trust me.
# Don't you cry no more #
We're closed.
Just, uh...
Just give me a second.
Sorry, pal.
We... we open at noon.
Look,
you don't understand.
Okay, I-I think
I understand... just fine.
Look, I-I don't need
this kind of hassle,
so, seriously,
just get the hell out.
Please. Please, just give me
a minute to think, that's all.
Then I'm out of your hair.
One minute, please.
What's your name?
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
I mean I don't remember.
I don't remember anything.
Season 6 Episode 22
"The Man Who Knew Too Much"
Come on.
You're dickin' with me.
Nothing?
I'm telling you... blank slate.
Well, you got
a wallet, I.D.?
I wish I did.
Okay, what's the last thing
you remember?
Um...
I woke up on a park bench,
cops shoving a flashlight in
my face, trying to take me in.
- So you ran.
- No, I, um...
I knocked them out cold,
both of them.
No, look,
I didn't mean to.
It just happened really fast,
you know?
I-I think instinct
or something, I guess.
That's some instinct.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I mean, who even knows
how to do something like that?
We'll get you to the E.R. the...
the quacks will hash it out.
No.
Try "yeah."
Look, the bats
have flown the belfry.
- You need to see a doctor.
- No, I...
I don't have time.
Time for what?
Look, it's hard to explain.
I just feel like
I-I have to... be somewhere.
There's s-something
I got to stop.
Oh, like a wedding?
A train?
No, something important,
something like...
- Life or death, like...
- Hey, hey, hey.
Just relax.
Y-you can't poop it out.
So, just... it'll come to you.
What is it?
You a horror fan?
Yeah, um, I think so.
You know,
I really think so.
Something...
something about this.
Phillips ain't
his last name. It's Lovecraft.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Seriously,
we are taking you to a doctor.
Have you got a computer?
What?
That's it. It exists.
Look... two towns over.
- You think you're staying in this dump?
- Maybe.
Maybe you're a hooker.
I guess I'll find out.
Look, um...
I don't know how to say, uh...
thanks for everything.
Where do you think you're going?
I'll be fine.
Says the head case that
just slumped over a minute ago.
Look, is there any way I can
convince you to go to a hospital?
No.
Apparently, I'm stubborn.
Well...
So am I.
I'm driving.
Look, that's really nice of you
but not necessary.
Really? Okay, look,
your eggs are scrambled.
But...
But nothing.
No, I mean,
I'm... I'm just some guy.
I-I could be anybody.
You got to be nuts.
I've been called that.
Look, if I let you
go off alone,
I won't be able to sleep
at night.
And, honestly, I'm dying to know
how it all turns out.
So, uh,
where do we start?
Uh, ground floor,
corner room...
nearest
to the fire escape.
That's the one I'd pick...
quickest getaway.
And why do you know that?
I just do.
Hey, you got
a credit card?
Uh...
Why?
Are we, uh, checking in?
Sort of.
Dude...
Who are you?
Good question.
This all yours?
I don't know.
I guess.
Well, I love what you've done
with the place.
It's very "Beautiful Mind"
meets... "Se7en."
Sorry.
I talk when I'm nervous.
Hey, well,
I guess we know your name.
Nice to meet you,
Jimmy Page.
And, uh, Neil Peart.
And Angus Young.
Okay, listen, no offense,
but I'm... really starting
to freak out.
You and me both.
Where is she?
She said to
meet her here.
I'll try her again.
- Elle?
- Hey.
I guess I could have used
your help after all.
Just be still.
- What happened?
- They took me.
I got away.
Oh, Ellie.
Oh, what have they done
to you?
Everything.
The demon I could have handled,
you know?
But when
the Angel stepped in...
I told him, Bobby.
They have enough
to crack Purgatory wide open.
Tell me.
I need to know.
They need virgin blood.
That's a milk run for them.
And they need the blood
of a Purgatory native.
Well, they've got
plenty of that now.
Have they opened it yet?
Mnh-mnh. Tomorrow.
The moon and the eclipse.
I'm sorry, Bobby.
- No, it's okay.
- I'm sorry, really.
Just tell us where they are.
Elle?
I'm sorry
this had to happen.
Crowley got carried away.
Yeah, I bet it was all Crowley,
you son of a bitch!
You don't even see it,
do you?
How totally off the rails
you are.
Enough!
I don't care
what you think.
I've tried to make you
understand. You won't listen.
So let me make this
simple.
Please go home
and let me stop Raphael.
I won't ask again.
Well, good, 'cause I think
you already know the answer.
I wish
it hadn't come to this.
Well, rest assured,
when this is all over...
I will save Sam,
but only
if you stand down.
Save Sam from what?
Hey, hey.
Are you okay?
Sam.
My name is Sam.
So, uh,
what do you remember?
Well
It might sound pretty strange
if I said it aloud.
Oh, it... it couldn't get
any stranger.
Yeah?
Don't be so sure.
Look, I-I don't know.
I mean, it's all pretty spotty,
you know?
I just remember I was...
I was with, uh... with two guys.
One was, like,
a male-model type,
and the other was
an older guy named, uh...
Bobby.
Okay. Well,
what are you looking for?
Here. Bobby Singer.
That has to be it.
Is there a phone number?
No, just an address.
Sioux Falls, South Dakota.
South Dakota.
Okay, uh...
L-listen, Sam...
- Sam, right?
- Yeah.
Look, I'm really sorry,
but this is...
is where I got to get off.
Oh, no. Of course.
No problem.
Okay. Well, how are you
gonna get there?
I guess
I'll take my car.
That's mine.
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah.
Look, Sam,
I don't feel right
about you going off like this.
Oh, look, don't worry.
Y-you've done way too much
for me already.
That's not what I mean.
What I mean is, uh...
I've got a bad feeling,
you know,
with those I.D.s
and that shady-ass hotel room.
Whatever you're looking for...
you might not like what you find.
What other choice do I have?
You could stick around here
a little bit longer,
get your head straight,
instead of going off,
flying blind into...
What the hell was that?!
Stay down.
Sam!
Sammy. Sammy?!
Sammy?
Come on.
Snap out of it.
Anything?
I can't just sit here, Bobby.
I've got to help him.
Dean.
You know, "Dreamscape"
his noggin... something.
You know what Cass did.
The dam inside
your brother's head is gone,
and all hell's spilling loose.
- We don't know what's going on inside.
- I don't care.
- We have got to do something!
- And we will.
But right now, we got 16 hours
till they pop Purgatory.
I'm down one man.
I can't afford to be down two.
Yeah, and how's that going, huh?
We've got no line on Crowley.
We got no line on Cass.
Balthazar's M.I.A.
I mean, all we've got
is Sam going through
whatever the hell this is!
You know...
...this is exactly
what Cass wants...
for you
to fall to pieces.
Just try to think
of what Sam would want.
Find Cass, Bobby.
Find him now.
Do you smell whiskey?
Okay, Sam,
would you focus?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Okay, so, who shot at us?
I-I didn't really get a good look.
Okay, we got to go
to the cops.
No. Look, if we can just get
to my friends,
they can help us...
I know it.
Okay, you don't know
if they're your friends, okay?
You don't know anything
about anything.
- Just turn around.
- No.
- Look, you're safer with me.
- How do you know that?
You're scaring me.
What? No way.
What was that?
What do you mean?
It's daylight.
Yeah?
It was night,
and now it's day.
It was always day.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, it wasn't. It...
what the hell
is going on here?
Okay, so I am all filled up
on crazy for today.
You know what, Sam?
I'll... I'll see you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, hey, hey.
Get in the car.
Wow.
My God.
Am I really that gawky?
Howdy.
This is impossible.
Cold. Try again.
I'm, uh...
I'm hallucinating.
Warmer.
But see, normally,
you're awake
when you're tripping balls.
I'm dreaming?
And someone just won a copy
of the home game.
We're inside
your grapefruit, Sam.
Son...
You've been juiced.
I-I-I don't remember
anything.
Well, your B.F.F. Cass brought
the hell wall tumbling down,
and you, pathetic infant
that you are,
shattered into pieces.
Piece... Piece.
I-I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Why would you?
You're jello, pal,
unlike me.
What are you?
I'm not handicapped.
I'm not saddled
with a soul.
In fact, I used to skipper
this meat-boat for a while.
It was smooth sailing.
I was sharp, strong.
That is, till they crammed
your soul back in.
Now look at you.
Same misty-eyed milksop
you always were.
That's because
souls are weak.
They're a liability.
Now, nothing personal,
but run the numbers.
Someone's got to take charge
around here
before it's too late.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
You think I'm bad?
Wait till you meet
the other one.
Sammy!
Sam!
I remember who I am...
Everything I did this past year.
And I remember you.
Walk away,
or the girl dies.
There goes your leverage.
Didn't I tell you
to turn back,
that you wouldn't like
what you found?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Not as sorry
as you're gonna be.
Look what the cat
dragged in.
Well,
at least you mud-fish
finally got
the angel-proofing right.
How's sleeping beauty?
You didn't steal any kisses,
I trust?
What the hell took you so long?
Honestly?
I was having second thoughts.
About?
About
whether to help you.
I was thinking maybe...
maybe I should rip out
your sticky bits instead.
And what did you decide?
Well...
Cass and Crowley are there.
That's where
the show gets started.
All right, well, give us a minute
to pack up and then zap us there.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I don't think so.
Balthazar.
I'm betraying a friend here...
a very powerful friend.
We all are.
So I think I've stuck
my neck out far enough already.
Good luck.
Your Purgatory
power shake, monsieur...
half monster, half virgin.
Thank you.
You seem even more constipated
than usual.
Maybe get you some colon blow?
I'm renegotiating our terms.
Is that so?
What terms do you propose?
You get nothing.
Not one single soul.
Can't help notice...
seems a bit...
unfairly weighted.
Castiel... you wouldn't dare.
I brought you this deal.
You think I'm handing
all that power...
to the King of Hell?
I'm neither stupid nor wicked.
Unbelievable.
Have you forgotten that you're
the bottom in this relationship?
Here are your options.
You either flee, or you die.
We made a pact.
Even I don't break contracts
like this.
Flee...
or die.
Boy, you can't trust anyone
these days.
Hey.
Hey!
Oh.
Hi, Sam.
So?
Which one are you?
Don't you know?
I'm the one
that remembers Hell.
Time's up, Dean.
Just a second.
All right, this is
where we're gonna be, Sam.
So you get your lazy ass
out of bed and come meet us.
Sammy, please.
I wish you hadn't come,
Sam.
I had to.
I'm here, right?
Out there in the real world,
I'm at Bobby's, aren't I?
How do you know?
This whole time,
I smell nothing
but old spice and whiskey.
I figured
if I could get back here,
back to my body,
I could...
I don't know...
I could snap out of it somehow.
First, you have to
go through me.
Why?
Humpty-dumpty has to put himself
back together again
before he can wake up.
And I'm the last piece.
Which means...
I have to know what you know...
What happened in the cage.
Trust me.
You don't
want to know it.
You're right.
But I still have to.
Sam...
you can't imagine.
Stay here, go back,
find that bartender,
go find Jess, but don't do this.
I know you.
You're not strong enough.
We'll just have to see.
Why is this so important
to you?
You know me.
You know why.
I'm not leaving my brother alone
out there.
I'm not gonna fight you.
But this is your last chance.
Good luck.
You're gonna need it.
You rang, Cass?
Yeah.
We have a problem.
Dean Winchester
is on his way here.
Really? Oh. How'd he even
know where we were?
Apparently...
We have a Judas in our midst.
Ah.
Holy hell.
Who is it?
I bet it's that
bloody little cherub, isn't it?
I don't know.
But I-I need you to find out.
Of course.
Um, right away, right away.
Uh, but what do you
want me to do about Dean?
Nothing.
I'll handle him myself.
Castiel?
Are you all right?
First Sam and Dean,
and now this.
I'm doing my best
in impossible circumstances.
My friends... they...
abandon me...
plot against me.
It's difficult to understand.
Well, you've...
you've always got little old me.
Yes.
I'll always have you.
Cass...
I count a dozen mooks,
probably more.
Demons?
Angels.
Well, how the hell are we
gonna take out that many Angels?
We don't.
We'll ninja our way in.
Awesome, yeah...
till they hear your knee squeak.
Shut up.
Oh, what,
now you got thin skin?
No, shut up.
You hear that?
What the hell is that?
Oh...
T. Rex, maybe?
Holy mother of...
Get to the car.
Never underestimate
the King of Hell, darling.
I know
a lot of swell tricks.
Now, I think it's time
to re-renegotiate our terms.
Sweaty hands, mate.
I don't understand.
You can palm me
all you want.
I'm safe and sound under
the wing of my new partner.
Hello, Castiel.
Raphael.
Consorting with Demons.
I thought that was beneath you?
Heard you were doing it.
Sounded like fun.
You know, Castiel,
y-you said all sorts
of shameful,
appalling, scatological
things about Raphael.
I found him... her...
to be really... quite reasonable.
You fool.
Raphael will deceive and destroy
you at the speed of thought.
Right, right, 'cause
you're such a straight shooter.
She... he...
has offered me protection
against all comers.
In exchange for what?
The Purgatory blood.
Castiel, you really think
I would let you open that door?
Take in
that much power?
If anyone is going to be
the new God, it's me.
He's gonna bring
the Apocalypse and worse.
Hey, this is your doing,
mate.
I'm merely grabbing
the best offer on the table.
Now,
you have two options.
Flee or die.
Ianua magna purgatorii,
clausa est ob nos,
lumine eius
ab oculis nostris retento.
Bobby.
Bobby?
Huh?
Come on.
We got to go.
Sed nunc stamus
ad limen huius ianuae magnae
et demisse, fideliter,
perhonorifice,
paramus aperire eam.
Creaturae terrificae,
quarum ungulae et dentes,
nunquam tetigerunt
carnem humanam.
Bit busy, gentlemen.
Be with you in a moment.
Aperit fauces
eius ad mundum nostrum, nunc,
ianua magna aperta tandem!
Mm-hmm.
Maybe I said it wrong.
You said it perfectly.
But what you needed
was this.
I see.
And we've
been working with...
dog blood. Naturally.
Enough of these games, Castiel.
Give us the blood.
You...
Game's over.
His jar's empty.
So, Castiel,
how'd your ritual go?
Better than ours, I'll bet.
You can't imagine
what it's like.
They're all inside me...
millions
upon millions of souls.
Sounds sexy.
Exit stage Crowley.
Now, what's the matter,
Raphael?
Somebody clip your wings?
Castiel, please.
You let the Demon go...
but not your own brother?
The Demon I have plans for.
You, on the other hand...
So, you see...
I saved you.
You sure did, Cass.
Thank you.
You doubted me...
fought against me.
But I was right
all along.
Okay, Cass, you were.
We're sorry.
Let's just defuse you,
okay?
What do you mean?
You're full of nuke.
It's not safe.
So before the eclipse ends,
let's get them souls
back to where they belong.
Oh, no.
They belong with me.
No, Cass, it's
scrambling your brain.
No, I'm not finished yet.
Raphael had many followers,
and I must...
Punish them all severely.
Listen to me.
Listen...
I know there's a lot
of bad water under the bridge.
But we were family once.
I'd have died for you.
I almost did a few times.
So if that means anything
to you...
Please.
I've lost Lisa,
I've lost Ben,
and now I've lost Sam.
Don't make me lose you, too.
You don't need this kind
of juice anymore, Cass.
Get rid of it
before it kills us all.
You're just saying that
because I won...
Because you're afraid.
You're not my family,
Dean.
I have no family.
I'm glad you made it, Sam.
But the Angel blade
won't work,
because I'm not an Angel
anymore.
I'm your new God.
A better one.
So you will bow down
and profess your love unto me,
your Lord...
...or I shall destroy you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Edited by Scooby