We're gonna find a way
to beat the Devil, okay?
What if you guys lead
the Devil to the edge...
...and I jump in.
Yes!
Sammy's long gone.
What are you
gonna do now?
Return to Heaven, I suppose.
Heaven?
With Michael in the cage, I'm
sure it's total anarchy up there.
So, what, you're
the new sheriff in town?
It's civil war up there!
If we can beat Raphael,
we can end this!
When the oil burns,
no angel can touch
or pass through the flames,
or he dies.
It's his soul.
It's gone.
When we freaks die,
where do we go?
Not Heaven, not Hell.
- Purgatory.
- And I want it.
The human soul is more valuable
than you can imagine.
This is about the souls.
That Angel went and created
50,000 new souls
for your war machine.
Eve, the mother of all of us.
- It's Crowley I want dead.
- Well, you're too late there.
That little limey mook
roasted months ago.
Crowley's alive.
Aah!
Really, Cass...
this is getting ridiculous.
How many times
am I gonna have to
clean up your messes?
You know, I've...
I've been here
for a very long time.
I remember many things.
I remember being at a shoreline,
watching a little gray fish
heave itself up on the beach
and an older brother saying,
"Don't step on that fish, Castiel,
big plans for that fish."
I remember the Tower of Babel...
all 37 feet of it,
which I suppose was impressive
at the time.
And when it fell,
they howled "Divine Wrath".
But come on.
Dried dung can only be stacked
so high.
I remember Cain and Abel...
David and Goliath...
Sodom and Gomorrah.
And, of course,
I remember
the most remarkable event...
Remarkable
because it never came to pass.
It was averted by two boys...
an old drunk...
and a fallen Angel.
The Grand Story.
And we ripped up the ending
and the rules...
and Destiny...
Leaving nothing
but freedom and choice.
Which is all well and good,
except...
Well, what if I've made
the wrong choice?
How am I supposed to know?
I'm getting ahead of myself.
Let me tell you my story.
Let me tell you everything.
Season 6 Episode 20
"The Man Who Would Be King"
Hello, Dean.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm...
I'm fine.
How are you?
Just wanted to check in.
So, any word on, uh,
Satan Jr. Being alive?
I'm... looking, believe me.
I just don't understand
how Crowley could've tricked me.
Well, he's a tricky
son of a bitch, that's how.
Doesn't matter.
But if he is up and kicking,
then what does matter
is finding him,
ripping his head off,
and shoving it up his ass.
What about you?
Have you found anything?
No, nothing yet.
Where's Sam?
He's keeping busy.
He's tracking a Djinn in Omaha
as we speak.
In fact, I'm heading out there
right now to meet up with him.
Well, I'd come if I could.
Yeah, no, I-I get it.
No worries.
But, Cass, you'll call, right?
If you get into real trouble?
Howdy, partner.
What have you found?
I've found a lot of things.
For example...
Eve's brain?
Dead as a tinned kipper.
And yet...
for some reason...
she keeps laying eggs.
Watch this.
Chocula here
feels every tickle.
What is that good for?
Apart from the obvious
erotic value, you got me.
You said Eve could open
the door to Purgatory.
Correct. I did.
And I'm confident
that she could have
if she was still alive!
Single best chance
to get over the rainbow,
and the Winchesters killed her!
It was unavoidable.
You screwed up, Cass.
You let the hounds
mangle the pheasant,
and now
I am up to my elbows in it.
What is your point?
The point is...
you're distracted,
and that makes me nervous.
I am holding up my end.
Ah, yes.
But is that all you're holding?
See...
...the stench of that Impala's
all over your overcoat, Angel.
I thought we'd agreed...
no more nights out
with the boys.
I spoke with Dean.
I needed to know
what they know.
About what?
About me, maybe?
'Cause I happen to have it
on good authority
that your two little pets
are currently trying
to hunt me down!
Forgive me, but...
I think you might have a little
conflict of interest here.
Crowley had a point, of course.
My interest was conflicted.
I still considered myself
the Winchesters' guardian.
After all...
they taught me
how to stand up...
Hey! Ass butt!
Aaaaaaaahh!
...what to stand for...
and what generally happens
to you when you do.
I was done.
I was over.
And then the most extraordinary
thing happened.
I was put back.
And we had won.
We stopped Armageddon.
But at a terrible cost.
And so I knew
what I had to do next.
Once again,
I went to harrow Hell
to free Sam
from Lucifer's cage.
It was nearly impossible,
but I was so full
of confidence, of mission.
I see now that was arrogance...
hubris...
Because, of course,
I hadn't truly raised Sam...
not all of him.
Sometimes we're lucky enough
to be given a warning.
This should have been mine.
Please.
I'm begging you, Castiel.
Just kill the Winchesters.
- No.
- Fine.
Then I'll do it myself.
If you kill them, I'll just
bring them back again.
No, you won't.
Not where I'll put 'em.
Trust me.
I said... no.
Don't worry about them.
Don't worry about...
What, like Lucifer didn't worry?
Or Michael?
Or Lilith or Alistair
or Azazel didn't worry?!
Am I the only game piece
on the board
who doesn't underestimate
those denim-wrapped nightmares?!
Just find Purgatory.
If you don't, we will both die
again and again,
until the end of time.
The Winchesters
won't get to you.
Let them get to me!
I'll tear
their friggin' hearts out!
I got to tell you, Redd...
For a filthy,
lower-than-snake-spit hell-spawn,
you seem to have turned yourself
into a damn fine hunter.
I don't know whether
to kill you or kiss you.
Oh, please, kill me.
That was you that dug out
that nest of vamps
back in Swan Valley, wasn't it?
That was nice work.
Eight of 'em in one go,
roped and tied.
And then you brought them
to Crowley, right?
Read the papers, redneck.
The king is dead.
Ugh! Nng!
Crowley's alive.
You prove it just by being,
you poor, dumb jackass.
Crowley's alive.
His nets are still out.
Except now he's using you
schmucks to hunt his monsters.
Mm.
Up yours.
Redd...
where's Crowley?
No? Nothing?
Oh, okay, then.
Here, hang on to this
for a bit.
Aaaaaaaaaaahh!
Aaaaaaaaaaaahh!
So, what'd you tell him?
Nothing. Just relax.
What's the hub-bub?
I saw Cass.
He popped in on me
about two hours back.
What'd you tell him?
Nothing, all right?
Told him we were
on some crap monster hunt.
He doesn't know that
we're getting close to Crowley.
You know, he's our friend...
and we are lying to him
through our teeth.
Dean... so he burned
the wrong bones.
So Crowley tricked him.
He's an Angel.
He is the Balki Bartokomous
of Heaven!
He can make a mistake!
Nobody's saying nothing yet.
You think that Cass
is in with Crowley.
Crowley?
Look, I'm just saying
I don't know.
Now, look, I hate myself
for even thinking it.
But I don't know.
Look, Dean,
he's our friend, too, okay?
And I'd die for him.
I would, but...
Look,
I'm praying we're wrong here.
But if we ain't...
If there's a snowball
of a snowball's chance here...
that means we're dealing with a
Superman who's gone dark side...
Which means
we've got to be cautious,
we got to be smart,
and maybe stock up
on some kryptonite.
This makes you Lois Lane.
Look, one problem at a time here.
We got to find Crowley now,
before the damn fool
cracks open Purgatory.
So they already suspected.
- Where's Crowley?
- Up yours.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaahh!
And the worst part was Dean
trying so hard to be loyal.
With every instinct
telling him otherwise.
I don't know where Crowley is!
Are you sure about that?
'Cause we can twist again
all the way to next summer.
Oh, God!
I never even met him!
I don't deal
with Crowley direct.
Well, who do you deal with?
The dispatcher.
A demon named Ellsworth.
If there was a demon
counterpart to Bobby Singer,
Ellsworth would be it.
No, listen to me.
No. I don't care.
I want you to get down
to New Mexico
and bag me that wendigo!
Hell. Hang on.
- What?
- No more vampires.
Because the boss says
we're done with them.
FBI. Thomas speaking.
Absolutely, I sent them.
Thanks for calling to check.
You too.
Have a nice day, now.
Bye-bye.
Hey, hey, hey! No!
Not in here, you friggin' yeti.
Out back!
These demons would lead
the Winchesters to Crowley,
and Crowley would
tear their hearts out.
Oh, hell.
I had no choice.
I did it to protect the boys.
Or to protect myself.
I don't know anymore.
Hey.
Clear from the back.
Demons get tipped
and bugged out?
Maybe they run from us now.
I mean, that would be
a nice thought, right?
Yeah, if that's what happened.
Yeah.
Hiding...
lying...
sweeping away evidence.
And my motives
used to be so pure.
After supposedly "saving" Sam,
I finally returned to Heaven.
Of course,
there isn't one Heaven.
Each soul
generates its own paradise.
I favored
the eternal Tuesday afternoon
of an autistic man who drowned
in a bathtub in 1953.
You're alive.
Yes.
Castiel, we saw
Lucifer destroy you.
Well, I came back.
But Lucifer? Michael?
They're gone.
It was God, wasn't it?
No.
It was the Winchesters.
They brought down
the Apocalypse.
But you beat the archangels,
Castiel.
God brought you back.
He chose you, Cass...
to lead us.
No.
No one leads us anymore.
We're all free
to make our own choices
and to choose our own fates.
What does God want?
God wants you to have freedom.
But what does he want us
to do with it?
If I knew then
what I know now...
I might have said...
"It's simple.
"Freedom is a length of rope.
God wants you
to hang yourself with it."
Those first weeks
back in Heaven
were surprisingly difficult.
Explaining freedom to angels
is a bit like teaching poetry
to fish.
And then there was Raphael...
You came.
I appreciate
the courage that takes.
Whose Heaven is this?
Ken Lay's.
I'm borrowing it.
I still question
his admittance here.
He's devout.
Trumps everything.
What do you want?
Tomorrow...
I've called for a full assembly
of the Holy Host.
You'll kneel before me
and pledge allegiance
to the flag, all right?
And what flag is that?
Me, Castiel.
Allegiance to me.
Are you joking?
Do I look like I'm joking?
You never look like
you're joking.
You rebelled...
against God, Heaven, and me.
Now you will atone.
We'll start by freeing Lucifer
and Michael from their cage.
And then we'll get our show
back on the road.
Raphael... no.
The Apocalypse
doesn't have to be fought!
Of course it does.
It's God's will.
How can you say that?!
Because it's what I want.
Well, the other angels
won't let you.
Are you sure?
You know better than anyone,
Castiel.
They're soldiers.
They weren't built for freedom.
They were built to follow.
Then I won't let you.
Really?
You?
I'm not ashamed to say
that my big brother knocked me
into next week.
Tomorrow you kneel, Castiel...
or you
and anyone with you dies.
Hey...
The place is clean.
Yeah, but it's...
it's like "Mr. Clean" clean,
you know?
It's kind of OCD
for your average demon.
Yeah. So what now?
- We'd call Cass.
- What?
This is usually the point where
we would call Cass for help.
We talked about this.
Yeah, Dean.
No, you talked.
I listened.
This is Cass, guys.
I mean,
when there was no one...
and we were stuck...
and I mean really stuck...
he broke ranks.
He has gone to the mat
cut and bleeding for us
so many freakin' times.
This is Cass!
Don't we owe him the benefit
of the doubt at least?
Castiel...
this is really important, okay?
Um...
we really need to talk to you.
Castiel...
Come on in.
But I didn't go to them...
because I knew they would have
questions I couldn't answer...
Because I was afraid.
Cass is busy.
That's all right.
We are, too.
Come on.
Back to square one.
Great.
Well, what do we do now?
Well, we caught
one hunter demon before.
- We can do it again.
- Dean!
Crowley says "hi."
Crowley sent his very best.
I was caught as much
by surprise as the rest of them.
And it left me
with yet another choice.
I could reveal myself
and smite the demons.
Of course,
Crowley wouldn't like it.
But on the other hand,
they were my friends.
For a brief moment...
I was me again.
It is good to see you, Cass.
You all right?
Yeah.
Perfect timing, Cass.
I'm glad I found you.
I come with news.
Yeah? What?
I firmly believe
Crowley is alive.
Yeah.
You think, Kojak?
Well, Bobby, what do we think
about Cass saving our asses...
again?
I think we owe you an apology.
Why?
We've been hunting Crowley
this whole time...
And keeping it from you.
We thought...
you were working with him.
You thought what?
I know. It's crazy, right?
It's just that
you torched the wrong bones.
It doesn't matter.
We... we were wrong.
You know...
You could've just asked me.
And we should have.
We never should've doubted you.
It's...
I just hope you can forgive us.
Wonders never cease.
They trusted me again.
But it was just another lie.
It's forgotten.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Thanks, Cass.
It is a little absurd, though.
I know, I know.
Superman going to the dark side.
I'm still just Castiel.
I guess we can put away
the kryptonite, right?
Exactly.
Of course, I didn't realize it
at the time.
But it was all over.
Right then... just like that.
You sent demons after them?
You kill my hunters.
Why can't I kill yours?
They're my friends.
You can't have friends,
not anymore.
I mean, my God.
You're losing it!
I'm fine.
Yeah.
You're the very picture
of mental health.
Come on. You don't think I know
what this is all about?
Enlighten me.
The big lie...
the Winchesters still buy it.
The good Cass,
the righteous Cass.
And long
as they still believe it,
you get to believe it.
Well, I got news for you,
kitten.
A whore is a whore is a whore.
I'm only gonna say this once.
If you touch a hair
on their heads,
I will tear it all down.
Our arrangement...
everything.
I'm still an angel,
and I will bury you.
I asked myself,
"what was I doing
with this vermin?"
This is not how synergy works!
As if I didn't already know
the answer.
Raphael was stronger than me.
And I wouldn't survive
a straight fight.
So I went to an old friend
for help.
But watching him, I stopped.
Everything he sacrificed,
and I was about to ask him
for more.
Ah, Castiel.
Angel of Thursday.
Just not your day is it?
What are you doing here?
I want to help you help me
help ourselves.
Speak plain.
I want to discuss
a simple business transaction.
- That's all.
- You want to make a deal?
With me?
I'm an angel, you ass.
I don't have a soul to sell.
But that's it, isn't it?
It's all of it.
It's the souls.
It all comes down to the souls
in the end, doesn't it?
What in the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about
Raphael's head on a pike.
happy endings for all of us,
with all possible entendres
intended.
Come on.
Just a chat.
I have no interest
in talking with you.
Why not?
I'm very interesting.
Come on. Hear me out.
Five minutes.
No obligations.
I promise...
I'll make it worth your while.
I was no fool.
I knew who Crowley was
and what he did.
But I was smarter than him,
stronger.
I see now that I was prideful.
And in all likelihood,
I was a fool.
Where are we?
You don't recognize it, do you?
It's Hades, new and improved.
I did it myself.
This is Hell?
Yeah. See,
problem with the old place
was most of the inmates
were masochists already.
A lot of "Thank you, sir.
Can I have another
hot spike up the jacksie?"
But just look at them.
No one likes waiting in line.
And what happens
when they reach the front?
Nothing.
They go right back
to the end again.
That's efficiency.
You have four minutes left.
What are you planning to do
about Raphael?
What can I do
besides submit or die?
Submit or die?
What are you, French?
How about resist?
I'm not strong enough,
and you know it.
Ah, not on your own,
you're not.
But you're not on your own,
are you?
There's a lot of angels
swooning over you.
"God's favorite."
Buddy boy, you've got
what they call sex appeal.
Thank you.
Get to the point.
Angels need leaders, so be one.
Gather your army
and kick the candy out
of each and every angel
that shows up for Raphael.
Are you proposing that I start
a civil war in Heaven?
Ding! Ding! Ding!
Tell him what he's won, Vanna.
You're asking me
to be the next Lucifer.
Please.
Lucifer was a petulant child
with daddy issues.
Cass, you love God.
God loves you.
He brought you back.
Did it occur to you
that maybe he did this
so you could be
the new sheriff upstairs?
This is ridiculous.
I mean, the amount of power
that it would take
to mount a war...
More than either of us
have ever seen, yeah.
But what if I said
I knew how to go nuclear?
What do you mean?
Purgatory,
my fine feathered friend.
Purgatory.
Just think about it.
An untapped oil well
of every fanged, clawed soul.
I mean,
what's that over the years?
30 million?
40 million?
Just sitting there,
plump and rich for the taking.
How would you even find it
when no one ever has?
We'll need expert help.
From whom?
From experts, of course.
I know of two eerily suited
teen beat models
with time on their hands.
No. Not Dean.
He's retired,
and he's to stay that way.
Fine.
Then I know of
a certain big, bald patriarch
I can take off the bench.
The point is...
they can get us
to the monsters.
The monsters
can get us to Purgatory.
I know it.
And what's your price
in all of this?
- Just half.
- Half?
My position isn't
all that stable, ducky.
Those souls would help,
just like they'd help you.
Besides, wouldn't you rather
have me in charge down here?
The devil you know...
This is pointless.
Your plan would take months,
and I need help now.
Granted.
Yes.
But just to show you how serious
I am about this scheme...
how about I float you
a little loan?
Say, 50 large?
50,000 souls from the pit.
You can take them up to Heaven.
Make quite a showing.
It's either this
or the Apocalypse
all over again.
Everything you've worked for...
everything that Sam and Dean
has worked for... gone.
You can save us, Castiel.
God chose you to save us.
And I think... deep down...
you know that.
I wish I could say,
'I was clean of pride
at that moment...
...or the next.'
There will be no Apocalypse.
And let it be known...
you're either with Raphael
or you're with me.
And so went the long road
of good intentions...
the road that brought me here.
Castiel, uh...
we need you for a little pow-wow
down here,
so come on down.
Hello.
Oh, Johnny on the spot.
You're still here.
Yeah,
we had to bury the bodies.
And we found a little whiskey.
Thanks for coming.
How can I help?
Oh, look.
We, um... we have a new plan.
We think we've finally
figured out a way
to track down Crowley.
- What is it?
- It's you.
What are you doing?
We got to talk.
About what? Let me go!
About Superman.
And kryptonite.
How'd you know what I said?
How long you been watching us?
You know who spies
on people, Cass?
- Spies!
- Okay, just wait.
I don't even know
what you mean.
What about this demon crap-hole?
How is it so, uh...
next to godliness clean in here?
And how exactly did Crowley
trick you with the wrong bones?
It's hard to understand.
It's hard to explain.
Just let me go.
Let me out and I can...
You got to look at me, man.
You got to level with me
and tell me what's going on.
Look me in the eye
and tell me you're not
working with Crowley.
You son of a bitch.
Let me explain.
You're in it with him?
You and Crowley have been going
after Purgatory together?
You have, huh?
This whole time.
I did it to protect you.
I did it to protect all of you.
Protect us how?
By opening a hole into monster-land!
He's right, Cass.
One drop got through,
and it was Eve.
And you want to break down
the entire dam?
To get the souls.
I can stop Raphael.
Please, you have to trust me.
Trust you?!
How in the hell are we
supposed to trust you now?
I'm still me.
I'm still your friend.
Sam...
I'm the one who raised you
from perdition.
What?
Well, no offense...
but you did
a pretty piss-poor job of it.
Wait.
Did you bring me back
soulless...
on purpose?
How could you think that?
Well, I'm thinking a lot
of things right now, Cass.
Listen.
Raphael will kill us all.
He'll turn the world
into a graveyard.
I had no choice.
No, you had a choice.
You just made the wrong one.
You don't understand.
It's complicated.
No, actually, it's not,
and you know that.
Why else would you keep
this whole thing a secret, huh,
unless you knew
that it was wrong?
When crap like this
comes around,
we deal with it...
like we always have.
What we don't do
is we don't go out
and make another deal
with the devil!
It sounds so simple
when you say it like that.
Where were you
when I needed to hear it?
I was there.
Where were you?
You should've come to us
for help, Cass.
Maybe.
It's too late now.
I can't turn back now.
I can't.
It's not too late.
Damn it, Cass!
We can fix this!
Dean, it's not broken!
Run.
You have to run now!
Run!
My, my.
Playing with fire again?
If you touch the Winchesters...
Please,
I heard you the first time.
I promise... nary a hair
on their artfully tousled heads.
Besides, I think they've proven
my point for me.
It's always your friends,
isn't it, in the end?
We try to change.
We try to improve ourselves.
It's always our friends
who got to claw into our sides
and hold us back.
But you know what I see here?
The new God and the new Devil,
working together.
Enough!
You stop talking.
And get out of my sight.
Well...
glad I came.
You're welcome, by the way.
You know the difference
between you and me?
I know what I am.
What are you, Castiel?
What exactly
are you willing to do?
Hello, Dean.
How'd you get in here?
The angel-proofing
Bobby put up on the house...
he got a few things wrong.
Well, it's too bad
we got to angel-proof
in the first place, isn't it?
Why are you here?
I want you to understand.
Oh, believe me, I get it.
Blah, blah, Raphael, right?
I'm doing this for you, Dean.
I'm doing this because of you.
Because of me.
Yeah.
You got to be kidding me.
You're the one who taught me
that freedom and free will...
You're a freakin' child,
you know that?
Just because
you can do what you want
doesn't mean that you get to do
whatever you want!
I know what I'm doing, Dean.
I'm not gonna logic you, okay?
I'm saying don't...
just 'cause.
I'm asking you not to.
That's it.
I don't understand.
Look, next to Sam,
you and Bobby are the closest
things I have to family...
That you are
like a brother to me.
So, if I'm asking you
not to do something...
...you got to trust me, man.
Or what?
Or I'll have to do
what I have to do to stop you.
You can't, Dean.
You're just a man.
I'm an angel.
I don't know.
I've taken some pretty big fish.
I'm sorry, Dean.
Well, I'm sorry, too, then.
So, that's everything.
I believe
it's what you would call a...
tragedy, from the human
perspective.
But maybe the human perspective
is... limited.
I don't know.
That's why
I'm asking you, Father.
One last time.
Am I doing the right thing?
Am I on the right path?
You have to tell me.
You have to give me... a sign.
Give me a sign.
Because if you don't...
I'm gonna ju...
I'm gonna do whatever I...
whatever I must.
Sync by Alice | Corrected by Gloriabg
| www.addic7ed.com
Edited by Scooby