LISA: But I didn't expect
Sam to come back.
But the minute he walked
through that door, I knew.
It was over.
SAM: There's something
wrong with me. I need help.
CASTIEL: It's his soul.
- It's gone.
- DEAN: So, where is it?
Still in the cage
with Michael and Lucifer.
- Well, then, just get it back.
- That's not possible.
You've got no instinct.
I mean, you are
seriously messed up.
I don't know what you are
'cause you're not Sam.
Dean, come on.
Stop pretending.
- You were right.
- About?
I'm not your brother.
Like I don't even
really care about you.
And maybe I should feel guilty.
But I don't.
[Theme from "The X-files" plays]
[Crickets chirping]
# I'd like to see you
out in the moonlight #
# I'd like to kiss you
way back in the sticks #
# I'd like to walk you through
a field of wildflowers #
# and I'd like to check you
for ticks #
[corn rustles]
Did you see that?
See what?
There's something out there.
Patrick!
Something out in the corn.
[Corn rustles]
Patrick, you're freaking me out.
I'm just having a quick look.
Patrick!
[Breathing heavily]
Patrick.
Patrick!
[Mechanical whirring]
[Breathing heavily]
Patrick!
[Theme from "The X-files" plays]
Season 6 Episode 9
"Clap Your Hands If You Believe"
I'm here because I believe
that Elwood, Indiana,
has become a center
of extraterrestrial activity.
There was this light,
and then Patrick just vanished.
It's all happening, you know?
I mean, these entities have come
to help push humanity
to the next stage.
My name is Wayne Whitaker, Jr.,
and I have personally recorded
dozens of eyewitness accounts.
Strange lights in the sky,
mysterious presences
attempting contact.
Since this whole damn circus
has blown into town,
no one seems to realize we've
got four missing-persons cases,
wide open.
My friends lost loved ones.
What happened to him?
Something took him.
I know it!
We are right in the middle
of what we in the field
like to call a "U.F.O. flap",
and I am as happy
as a pig in shoes.
[Chuckles]
I can guarantee you this has
nothing to do with U.F.O.s
or little green men or anything
extraterrestrial whatsoever.
Of course it's not U.F.O.s.
It's fairies.
Fairies?
Okay, well, thank you
for your input.
What, flying saucers
not insane enough for you?
What newspaper did you say
you work for?
Look, if you want to add glitter
to that glue you're sniffing,
that's fine, but don't dump
your wackadoo all over us.
We'd rather not step in it.
Okay, we... we... we're done.
The only thing you're missing
is a couple dozen cats, sister.
Yeah. It's... it's a
blood-sugar thing. Oh.
My apologies.
- What?
- "What?" You gotta ask?
Right, yes.
You do have to ask.
Look, I'm sorry, but this is
all a big joke, right?
I mean, we're not actually taking this
U.F.O. crap seriously?
No, man. E.T. is made of rubber.
Everybody knows that.
But there are four legitimate
vanishings in this town.
Something's going on.
And, Sam, by the way,
it's not the lady's fault
she took the brown acid.
Yeah. So?
Empathy, man. Empathy.
I mean, the old Sam
would've given her
some... some wussified,
dew-eyed crap.
Old Sam had a soul.
Was a soul. Whatever.
Right. Yes. And... and...
and... but you don't...
or aren't. Whatever.
- Right.
- You don't care.
- Well...
You have to care!
About what, exactly?
About everything, man!
[Sighs]
A... about being human, at least!
Look, Dean, you obviously care.
A lot. And that's great.
But... but I can't
care about what...
what I can't care about, you know?
[Sighs]
What do you want me to do, fake it?
Yes. Absolutely. Fake it.
Fake it till you make it.
What happened to you
wanting me to be all honest?
Hey, you want to be
a real boy, Pinocchio,
you got to act the part.
I was faking it, Dean!
Ever since we got back
on the road together,
I... I was picking
every frickin' word!
- It's exhausting!
- Okay, all right.
But until we get you
back on the soul train,
I'll be your conscience, okay?
[Chuckles]
So you're saying
you'll be my... Jiminy Cricket.
Shut up.
But, yeah, you freakin' puppet.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
[Car door closes]
[Engine turns over, revs]
[Sighs]
Mr. Brennan?
Hmm?
We're with The Mirror.
- DEAN: We'd just like to ask you...
- What?
Is this about Patrick?
Patrick's gone.
Missing. Right, yes.
That's... that's what
we want to talk to you about.
Now, your son was the first
to disappear.
First to be taken.
Taken?
Get out.
Out!
Mr. Brennan, who do you believe
took your son?
You people can't help me.
My boy is never coming back.
You sound awfully sure.
Excuse me?
Like you know something
you're not talking about.
Okay, all right.
You know what they say...
72 hours.
After that, the odds
of finding a missing person
drop to nothing, right?
Well, every case is different.
It's been weeks.
Right.
Listen, uh...
Call us...
If anything comes to mind.
Okay.
[Sighs]
[Door closes]
Is that all right?
[Exhales sharply]
What do you think?
I think he's hiding something.
Why don't you stay
and watch watchmaker,
see what happens
when the sun goes down.
- I'll go check out the crop circles.
- Okeydokey.
But do not engage with, maim,
or in any way kill Brennan.
In fact, I don't want you making
any judgment calls whatsoever.
Anything happens, call me.
You know, Jiminy, I was
on my own for a whole year.
[Scoffs]
I did fine without you.
- [Chuckling]
- Yeah.
I don't want to know
your definition of "fine".
[Sighs]
[Cellphone plays rock music]
[Beep]
[Exhales sharply]
What?
Only thing this guy's up to
is alcoholism.
Good.
You know, maybe I should
go talk to him again.
I mean, you're the one
who said he's hiding something.
Shh, shh, shh!
[Corn rustles]
What? You see something?
Dean, what's up?
Hang on a second.
[Electronic pulsing]
Holy...
U.F.O.! U.F.O.!
Whoa. Dude, stop yelling.
You're breaking up.
I didn't catch that last part.
Close encounter!
[Grunts]
Close encounter?
What kind? First, second?
They're after me!
Third kind already?
You better run, man.
I think the fourth
kind is a butt thing.
Empathy, Sam! Empathy!
# Won't you please
take me along for a drive? #
They still after you?
[Grunting]
Come on!
[Corn rustling]
SAM: Dean? Are you there?
What happened?
Dean?
# Won't you please
take me along for a drive? #
[Sighs]
# Oh, won't you please
take me along... #
Thanks.
[Insects buzzing]
[Cellphone plays rock music]
[Beep]
[Theme from "Close Encounters
of the Third Kind" plays]
[Radio tuning]
[Theme from "Close Encounters
of the Third Kind" plays]
[Radio buzzes]
# Years went by #
[indistinct conversations]
So, they're real. U.F.O.s.
Like I said before, son...
the truth is out there.
Okay. You're the expert.
How do I get 'em?
Come again?
Well, you hunt E.T.s, right?
I need to know how to get them.
[Chuckles]
Uh, you and me both.
This is it?
Well, I'd say that 30 years
of eyewitness accounts
speak for themselves,
as incontrovertible proof.
Yeah, right.
My brother was abducted, so I'm
pretty good on the whole proof part.
Your brother was abducted?
Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- It's fine.
I mean, I've had time to adjust.
Did it... did it happen
when you were kids?
No.
Like half an hour ago.
So, you've been hunting U.F.O.s
for over three decades,
and you basically
have no concrete data
and zero workable leads.
- Well, I...
- Have you considered the possibility
that you suck at hunting U.F.O.s?
I'd like to help.
If I can.
[Theme from "Close Encounters
of the Third Kind" plays]
[Corn rustling]
[Shouting]
[Breathing heavily]
Dean!
What the hell?
Oh, that's Dean?
Sam!
They brought your brother back.
Okay.
It's all right, Sam.
I so totally understand
you need time as a family.
But it's just...
What were they like?
They were grabby,
incandescent douchebags.
Good night.
- Too soon.
- Okay.
[Sighs]
Y... you're upset.
I was abducted.
And you were banging Patchouli.
I didn't think
she smelled that bad.
- I was abducted by aliens!
- I was looking into it!
Looking into it?!
I was gone for like an hour!
- SAM: An hour?
- And most of that was walking back to town!
Dean, I think your watch is off.
You've been gone all night.
What are you talking about?
No, I haven't.
4:00 a.m.?
Yeah.
U.F.O. time-slip.
[Chuckles]
That actually falls in line
with a lot of abduction stories.
"Falls in line"?!
Nothing's falling in line!
Here. Drink.
- Good.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
Now... come on...
Talk to me.
What happened?
[Exhales sharply]
Well, uh...
There was this, uh...
God help me, Sam,
there was this bright white light.
It's okay.
Safe room.
And then... and suddenly,
I was, uh...
I w... I was in a different place.
And there were these... beings.
And they... they were...
they were too bright to look at,
but I... I could feel them...
Pulling me towards
this sort of... table.
- Probing table!
- God, don't say that out loud!
Right.
Uh, so what did you do?
I went... crazy.
I started hacking and...
and slashing and firing.
[Chuckles]
They... they actually
seemed surprised.
I... I... I don't think
anybody's ever done that before.
Yeah.
I had a close encounter, Sam...
and I won.
You should take a shower.
I should take a shower.
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna take a shower now.
So, on top of all the demons
and the angels
and the ghosts
and the skin-walkers,
it turns out that there's...
So, if aliens are actually real,
what's next, huh?
Hobbits?
Seriously.
You just gave her
the silent "how you doin'".
What?
Our reality's collapsing around us,
and you're trying to pick up
our waitress?!
Yeah.
Okay, look...
[Clears throat]
That brings up a question.
So, say you got a soul,
and you're on a case,
and your brother
gets abducted by aliens.
Yeah, then you do everything
you can to get him back.
Right. You do.
But what about when there are
no more leads for the night?
I mean, are you supposed to
just sit there in
the dark and suffer,
even when there's nothing
that can be done at that moment?
- Yes!
- What?
Yes.
You sit in the dark,
and you... you feel the loss.
A... absolutely.
But... but couldn't I
just do all that
and have sex with the hippie chick?
No!
It would be in the dark.
No, you couldn't,
because you would be suffering.
And you can't just
turn that off for the night.
- Thanks, guys.
- Thanks...
Why not?
Because if you had a soul,
your soul wouldn't let you.
So, you're saying...
Having a soul equals suffering.
Yes, that's exactly what I'm saying.
Like...
The million times
you almost called Lisa.
So, you're saying
suffering is a good thing.
I'm saying it's
the only game in town.
Okay.
[Sighs]
So, how do we deal
with the little green men?
Research.
We got about a century
of U.F.O. lore to catch up on,
and there's no time for...
What's up with that guy?
Who?
The guy by the window
giving me the stink eye.
You mean the cop?
No, not the cop.
The guy! He's right...
well, now he's gone.
Who's gone?
- Can we please just get out of here?
- What's wrong with you?
- Before I hit you.
- Okay.
Geez.
SAM: Library's closing up soon.
I'm almost done.
You find anything?
Yeah, way too much.
Everyone on the planet
believes in U.F.O.s,
[David Bowie's "Space Oddity" plays]
And they will not stop
writing books about it.
Yeah, well, at least books
have punctuation.
All right, keep digging.
We'll see what you got
when you get back.
[Beep]
# Take your protein pills #
# and put your helmet on #
[electricity crackles]
# ground control to major Tom #
Oh, no.
[Electronic pulsing]
Not again.
# Commencing countdown, engines on #
# check ignition #
[chimes tinkle]
# and may God's love
be with you #
Nipples?
# This is ground control
to major Tom #
Oh, you bitch!
# You've really made the grade #
# and the papers want to know
whose shirts you wear #
[chimes tinkling]
Ha ha!
# Now it's time to leave
the capsule if you dare #
[chimes tinkling rapidly]
[Liquid splatters]
Aah!
[Sizzling]
Ha ha!
See what?
S... se... see what? See... see the...
the b... the blood!
See all the... the... the blech!
Sorry, man. I'm not seeing it.
You don't see the... the echh?!
It's right there!
Okay, let's go with
you see it and I don't.
What the hell was it?
[Sighs]
It was a little...
naked lady, okay?
It was a... a what?!
It was... it was a little glowing,
hot, naked lady
with nipples,
and...
and she hit me.
I'm not supposed to laugh, right?
Right. Okay, sure.
Um... So, shot in the dark here,
but did this...
little lady have wings?
[Keyboard clicks]
What the hell
made you say that?
She did, didn't she?
Yeah, but how... how did you...
One of the fringier theories
I came across.
I... it's actually what crazy crystal
lady was yammering about.
What if these abductions
have nothing to do with U.F.O.s?
- What?
- Okay, say these encounters
have been going on
for centuries...
not with extraterrestrials
but with ultra-terrestrials.
I mean, people nowadays
say space aliens or whatever,
but they used to call them...
- Smurfs?
- Fairies.
Fairies? Come on!
Dean, there's a straight line
between E.T.s and fairies.
Glowing lights, abductions.
I... it's all the same U.F.O. stuff,
just under a different skin.
You seriously think the secret
with the U.F.O.s is...
Hey, you're the one
who pizza-rolled Tinker Bell.
I'm just doing the math.
But this is good.
This is a lead.
A lead where?!
Fairies!
Sprites and spriggans,
boggarts and brownies.
The little people
have many names.
Well, that's, uh...
- That's her.
- Mm.
That's... that's...
that's the little...
[Chimes tinkling]
Anyway, I, uh, I... I get
that Tinker Bells are fairies.
But, uh, what about
the tiny Santa Claus
and the troll and the...
Oh, oh, that's a garden gnome,
and that's a large goblin,
- and that...
- But they're all fairies?
Yes.
Fairy comes in many
shapes and sizes...
Magical, mischievous beings
from the realm next door.
- The fairy realm?
- Mm-hmm.
So, it's like another dimension?
Another reality, yes.
Only people who have been there
and returned to our world
can see the fairy here.
Right. Um...
Why are the fairies
abducting people?
Mm.
Well, there is much theory
and little fact.
We know they only take
first-born sons.
Just like Rumpelstiltskin did!
Personally, I think
they're taken to Avalon
to service Oberon,
King of the fairy.
Dean...
Did you...
service Oberon, King of the fairies?
- Marion...
- Hmm?
Um...
- Let's say fairies are real, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- What can we do about them?
- Sorry?
I mean, how can we...
Interact with them?
Yes, yes.
Forcefully interact.
Well, if you want to win
a fairy's favor,
leave a bowl of fresh cream.
They love cream.
Okay.
Uh, and... and more forcefully?
Hmm.
Well, all fairy hate iron.
And the dark fairy burn
when touched with silver.
What else?
Oh!
You could spill sugar or salt
in front of them.
No matter how powerful,
the fairy must stoop
to count each grain.
Well, all righty.
That's... wow.
[Chuckles]
Lot to absorb.
Um, thank you.
Oh! Oh, stay!
Finish your tea.
I got to say,
I... I... I love the feel.
Uh...
It's, uh, it's... it's...
It's like Sedona, Arizona,
crapped in here.
Pewter-iffic is what it is.
[Laughs]
Pewter-iffic.
Do you have bigger cups?
God, is it on me?
- I feel like I've got the crazy on me.
- No, you...
You did sit in some glitter, though.
Just makes me want to believe
in U.F.O.s again.
Doesn't really give us a next
move. I'll grant you that.
We can always
put the call out to Bobby.
Hey.
I'll be damned.
Isn't that the watch guy?
Huh.
They love cream.
All right, you stick
with half and half.
I'm gonna go check out his store.
And no hippie chicks.
[Lock disengages]
[Machines grinding, sawing]
[Drill whirring]
[Machines squeaking, rattling]
[Clears throat]
[Cellphone rings]
# ...For U.F.O.s #
[Beep]
Yeah.
Friggin' full of Keeblers
over here, man.
Just full of 'em.
- What?
- It's like... it's like the story
with the... with the shoe guy
and all the elves.
Hey, you... you think
Brennan made a deal
with a bunch of fairies?
Let me get back to you.
# I know they're coming #
# they're coming tonight #
# oh, oh, oh #
So, Mr. Brennan.
Hello again.
Leave me alone.
Did I ever mention
how beautiful your work is?
What?
The watches...
just stunning.
But what I can't figure out
is how one man can put out
that much product.
I mean, hell,
if I didn't know better,
I'd say you have a bunch
of elves working for ya.
Except I do know better.
And you have a bunch of elves
working for you.
You're insane.
So, tell me... how does a father
decide to trade his son
for a bunch of watches?
I mean, I'm assuming
you have a soul,
so what's your excuse?
You don't understand.
It wasn't like that.
[Scoffs]
Then how was it?
I supported my family for
30 years making those watches.
It's the only thing
I know how to do.
But the Parkinson's...
I was losing my hands.
I was losing everything.
My grandmother, she always
used to say that they were real,
told me all these stories
when I was a kid
about how to summon them.
[Sighs]
How to get favors from them.
So you learned
how to work a spell.
I mean...
Honestly, I doubted
it would even work.
[Scoffs]
I was just desperate.
She left me this book.
So I did the ceremony
in my back office
two months ago.
[Inhales deeply]
And this... man appeared.
Said he was a Leprechaun.
A Leprechaun?
I asked him just
to cure my hands,
but he said he would
do even better.
He'd make me more successful
than I'd ever been.
He told me he'd bring
a crew of workers,
that I could save my business,
save my name.
In exchange for...?
He just wanted a place
for them to rest,
"to take of the fruit
and fat of the land".
I...
I said yes.
I... I wasn't thinking.
And the "fruit and the fat" was...
My first-born.
But not just mine.
There's been others.
They're not stopping.
They're not going to stop.
There's got to be a way
to reverse the spell.
There is.
But the book is...
it's in the safe in my shop.
They won't let me near it.
It's been a nightmare.
So you can see the fairies?
Yes.
[Sighs]
- Help!
- I got you!
I got you, you little fairy!
What do you want, you fairy?
- I'll kill you, you fairy!
- Help!
[Grunting]
Talk, fairy!
GIRL: Daddy!
- What the...
- Oh, God, no.
[Laughing]
I'm just kidding.
All right, now,
don't worry, Brennan.
We can do this.
Just, uh, my brother and I
are gonna cover you
while you reverse the ritual,
all right?
Dean! Hey, dude!
What happened?!
Sam!
Sam! Hey!
What am I supposed to do?!
Fight the fairies!
You fight those fairies!
[Grunts]
[Police radio chatter]
Fight the fairies!
I'm just trying to understand...
exactly what kind of hate crime
this even was.
It wasn't a hate crime.
I mean, if this gentlemen
were a full-sized homosexual,
would that, uh,
would that be okay with you?
I don't hate any-size person
or... or... or any-size gay guy.
Well, he's not gay, as it happens.
But he is the District Attorney
for Tipton County.
Runs a tight ship, tell you what.
Well, it's nice to hear
he's done so well for himself,
considering his, uh
[Clicks tongue]
Considering
the tough economic times.
Good for him.
Son...
You are all kinds of messed up.
[Door rattles]
[Door creaks]
Are they here?
Yeah, but it's all right.
Cream hits them like tequila.
[Book clatters]
Leig seachad an ceangal sin
agus smal an solus sin,
agus fuadaich an sidhe
air ais gu'n aite breith.
[Groans]
You.
You're the Leprechaun?
Indeed I am.
Sorry about the mess,
but your friend here, uh...
went back on his deal.
Well, you weren't very clear
with him on the terms.
I told him there was a price.
Once we come,
we come to stay.
So you take first-borns,
and then what?
You just sit back and watch
while they cover up
the abductions for you
with all that crazy U.F.O. crap?
Which you help encourage,
naturally.
Nice con.
But your cover's blown now, Wayne.
"Blown"? To whom?
Brennan's dead.
Your brother?
[Chuckles]
He's marked.
Been to the ranch.
He's ours now.
Yeah, well...
Then there's me.
You?
But you can only see me...
if I let you.
True.
But you'll have to
get near me eventually.
And I have very good reflexes.
You're not like
the rest of them, are you?
Nope.
No. I could see that right off.
You're missing a certain piece,
right in the center, ain't ya?
Says who?
Oh, we fairy folk
are all about energy.
And the human soul
gives off a certain... [Sniffs]
perfume.
Your soul is far away,
but not completely out of reach.
That so?
Sam...
I can get it back for you.
- [Chuckles]
- For a price.
That's adorable.
It's locked in a box with the Devil.
Your Devil, not mine.
There's no freakin' way
a Leprechaun can do
what angels cannot.
Angels.
[Laughing] Oh, please.
I'm talking about
real magic, Sonny,
from my side of the fence.
Got a way of gettin' in back doors.
So you're my blue fairy?
You can make me
a real boy again?
When you wish upon a star.
Yeah.
I got a wish.
Aah!
Iron.
Painful...
but not a deal breaker.
[Footsteps approach]
[Giggles]
[Sizzling]
[Grunts]
Come on, lad.
You've already taken
your best shot.
[Breathing heavily]
You're right.
[Gun clatters]
I'm done shooting.
So do me a favor...
and count this.
[Salt rattles]
Oh, no.
[Cane thumps]
[Cartridge clatters]
[Breathless]
Why didn't I do that earlier?
1...
- Cum sabhailt...
- 3...
- Ar naoidhein...
- You ass!
- Gun am breith.
- 4... 5.
- Agus cum duinte...
- Damn it!
An geata uamhasach seo.
[Sighs]
[Trunk slams]
So...
[Exhales sharply]
Here's to the tiniest D.A.
Thanks for dropping the charges.
Little big man.
I was wondering something.
Yeah?
You think lucky charms
really could have, you know,
returned soul to sender?
[Scoffs]
Come on.
It's crazy to think.
He did talk a good game, though.
Hmm.
You said no.
Why?
It was a deal.
When's a deal
ever been a good thing?
I'm just trying to figure out
how it works in there.
[Scoffs]
Dude, I... I do still have
all my brain cells.
If anything, my brain
works better now.
I'm just making sure
that's where your head's at.
You know, that you're not
having second thoughts
about getting your soul back.
Oh.
You're not, are you?
No.
[Chuckles]
== sync by elderman ==
== corrections by elderman and gloriabg ==
== www.addic7ed.com ==
Edited by Scooby