Yeah, I think these are
John Winchester's boys.
Hey, I'm Ellen.
That's my daughter, Jo.
The can of whup ass
I ought to open on you.
You better put me
on speed dial, kid.
Yes, ma'am.
Those are hell
hounds out there, Dean.
We'll let the dogs in.
You guys make a break
for the building next door
and I can wait here
with my finger on the button.
If I can get us a shot on
the devil, we have to take it.
I will not leave you here alone.
- It's civil war up there!
- I know.
If we can beat Raphael,
we can end this!
You did more than rebel.
You tore up
the whole script
and burned the pages
for all of us.
Do you have any idea
what souls are worth?
What power they hold?
Have you seen this man?
- Rufus Turner?
- No.
I ain't asking for no help.
Never seen that dick.
I'm not asking
for your permission.
Just like old times.
Long as I get to drive.
What are you?
Eve cooked me up herself.
The mother of all of us...
she has a message for you.
It was my fault.
Piece of crap.
Ah, damn it.
Season 6 Episode 17
"My Heart Will Go On"
- Say something.
- You.
No. You.
Uh...
You two just gonna stand there
like the ugly girl at the prom,
or you gonna pitch in?
This so-called Eve,
Mother, whatever...
ain't gonna gank herself.
What's wrong with you two?
Bobby, you haven't slept in days.
I sleep.
What are you, my wife now?
I'm just saying
that, you know,
taking five might be a good thing.
For whom?
Look, Bobby,
it was...
it was tough for all of us,
seeing Rufus go like that.
You think this...
This ain't about Rufus.
Bobby, he wasn't just
a poker buddy.
You know when I knew
Rufus was done for?
The day I met him.
The only question was,
who first... him or me?
Now, you want to stand there
and therapize,
or you want to get me
some coffee?
Make it Irish.
Well, he's doing fantastic.
Yeah. This isn't
about Rufus at all.
Well, what do you
want to do?
I mean,
we can't just sit here
and watch him
poop out his liver.
Well, we could
get him out of the house.
There's a job.
Really?
What do you got?
Look.
Chester, Pennsylvania.
Three people got kicked off
in the last week,
all freaky.
Last guy got karate-chopped
by his garage door.
And these are all
blood relatives.
- What do you think, family curse?
- Could be.
Hey, grumpy...
You, uh...
I don't want to do crap.
Leave me alone.
Just... get out of my house,
both of you.
You're driving me nuts.
Bobby.
Now!
For the love of Pete.
You know, maybe we should wait
till she gets back.
Dude, she just called
from the road,
said she'd be here
in "two shakes."
You really want to sit around
and smell him
stew in his juices?
Yeah, yeah. Drive.
What the...
Tell me you haven't been
drinking this whole time.
You're worse than the boys.
I'm working.
My God.
I'm gone a week, and this place
goes completely to hell.
What is wrong with you,
Bobby Singer?
Get a pen.
It's a long list.
You smell like a bar,
you know that?
You don't exactly
smell like a rose yourself.
Huh. Yeah,
I been hunting with Jo.
What's your excuse?
If I need one,
I got a good one.
I know.
And I'm so sorry.
He meant a lot
to me, too.
Go wash up.
I'll fix us something.
Anybody ever tell you
you're a pain in the ass?
That's why you married me.
Go.
Don't tell me
what to do, Ellen.
Not a bleep.
Well, not a vengeful
spirit, then.
So what is it?
Huh.
Whatch you got?
What is that,
Christmas tinsel?
I don't know.
It's gold.
You mean, like,
gold, gold?
Why would a handyman have gold
just lying around in his garage?
I don't know.
There is definitely a skeleton
in this family's closet.
I mean, accidents
don't just happen accidentally.
You know what I mean.
All right. How about
I'll go check family records,
you go with next of kin?
Yeah.
On the courthouse steps...
for the deposition.
No, I told you,
3:00 p.m.
No, my usual fees.
I got to go, Ma.
I'm sorry.
Uh, what department?
Genealogy.
From the university.
W-w-we're doing a study
on local families,
and, well,
the Russos are a big one...
Yeah, you know what?
I got to tell you, I am
extremely busy right now, so...
Yeah, I-I'm sure you've had
a rough week.
I, uh, read
about the recent tragedies.
Your cousins, right?
Yeah. It's a shame.
But I'm not that close
with my family, so, uh...
Is this gonna take long?
No. Five minutes.
Five minutes.
Uh, can you...
can you tell me
anything noteworthy
about the Russos?
Noteworthy?
No.
I mean, not exactly...
average,
you know,
big, from Italy.
I see.
Uh, was anyone ever
killed or maimed in a war
or... you know,
some other violent thing?
What do you mean?
Like something so dark that it
would Sully future generations.
Uh...
No.
Good. Good stuff.
Anyone own a slave?
What?
Routine question.
Any ties to the Nazi party?
Excuse me?
Did grandma ever
piss off a gypsy?
Okay, you know what?
I don't know
what kind of study you're doing,
but it's over right now,
so, if you don't mind...
Okay, I-I'll just
cut to the chase here.
Um, your life is in danger.
What?
What is that, a-a threat?
Are you threatening me?!
No, no, no. No, no.
I'm not threatening you.
I'm just simply saying that...
If you don't watch your back,
you're gonna die.
Get the hell out of my office.
- Okay.
- Now!
- Hey.
- Sam.
Find anything?
One ass-hat
in a shiny suit. You?
Not much. Great grandparents
born in Calabria.
Emigrated 1912.
Been here ever since.
What,
no severed horse head?
Ha. Four generations
of picket fence.
If these people
are the Waltons,
then why the hell
are they dying?
Well, how about Cuba?
It's beautiful
this time of year.
And the new Trump casino...
amazing.
Don't worry about the kids.
There's a wave pool.
Oh! Sure, yeah!
Look, if you like
cigars, Cher, or the circus,
it's all about Havana.
Yes, I've seen the Shatner ads,
but you know what they don't have?
Personal touch.
Okay, then.
I'll e-mail you some details.
You too.
Aah!
Anne Witting.
We sure
she's not a Russo,
a second cousin
twice removed or something?
No, I checked the records twice.
She's not related.
Oh, if this isn't a family
curse, then what the hell is it?
You got me.
I got nothing.
Hold on.
Not nothing.
So, we found
another piece of this,
I don't know, shiny string.
I was afraid of that.
Why? What's up?
Oh, these so-called accidents...
we're seeing 'em nationwide.
About 75 so far.
I got Jo and her crew working
on a cluster in California.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Blood relatives?
Some yeah, some no.
She's got
about what you do...
pile of bodies and
a whole bunch of gold thread.
- So what's it mean?
- I don't know.
I got Bobby working on it
right now.
How's he doing, by the way?
Oh, don't worry.
I'm kicking his ass
back to health and happiness.
Who asked you to?
To hell with you.
I heard that.
He'll be okay.
Are you okay?
Oh, honey, you're sweet.
You know me.
I just worry about you boys.
Yeah, well...
All right,
so, all these corpses...
anything relate 'em?
Well, actually,
I did dig up one thing.
I just don't know
what to make of it.
Hit me.
Well, it's a weird one,
and it was buried pretty deep,
but Bobby and me
were combing through
the family trees on all the
victims, and we started seeing,
well, the families all came over
to America the same year.
- Hm.
- Yeah. 1912.
But here's
the real weird part...
they all came over
on the same boat.
- Really?
- Yep.
All right, so what's so special
about the boat?
Nothing. It was a boat.
It did what boats do.
What was it called?
The Titanic.
You ever hear of it?
No.
Yeah, me neither.
I'll keep digging.
All right.
Does the name Titanic
ring a bell?
Titanic?
No.
"The RMS Titanic
was the largest passenger
steamship in the world
when it made
its maiden voyage
across the north Atlantic
in 1912."
So what's the big
friggin' deal?
It's a ship.
It sailed.
Yeah, I don't know.
Um...
Oh, looks like
there was a close call.
Ship almost hit an iceberg.
Almost? So?
So, uh,
looks like the first mate
spotted it just in time.
Good for him.
There anything else?
Wait a second.
What?
Uh, this first mate...
Mr. I.P. Freeley.
Well, that's not suspicious.
You got a picture
of old Freeley?
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
Let's see.
Balthazar.
Boys, boys, boys.
Whatever can I do for you?
We need to talk.
Oh, you seem upset, Dean.
The hell with the boat,
Balthazar.
What boat?
The Titanic.
Oh!
Yeah. The Titanic.
Yes, well, uh, it was meant
to sink, and I saved it.
What?
It was meant to bash
into this iceberg thing
and plunge into the briny deep
with all this hoopla,
and I saved it.
Anything else
I can answer for you?
Why?
Why what?
Why did you un-sink the ship?
Oh, because I hated the movie.
- What movie?
- Exactly.
Wait, so you saved
a cruise liner because...
Because that God-awful
Celine Dion song
made me want to smite myself.
Who's Celine Dion?
Oh, she's a destitute Lounge
singer somewhere in Quebec,
and let's keep it that way,
please.
Okay, I didn't think
that was possible.
I thought you couldn't
change history.
Oh, haven't you noticed?
There's no more rules, boys.
Wow.
The nerve on you.
So you just, what,
un-sunk a giant boat?
Oh, come on. I saved people.
I thought you loved
that kind of thing.
Yeah, but now those people
and their kids,
and their kids' kids...
they must have interacted
with so many other people,
changed so much crap.
You totally butterfly-effected
history!
Dude. Dude.
Rule one,
no Kutcher references.
Ah, yes. Unfortunately,
there's still an Ashton Kutcher.
And you still averted
the Apocalypse,
and there are still
archangels.
It's just the small details
that are different,
like you don't drive
an Impala.
Yes, yes.
"What's an Impala?"
Trust me,
it's not important.
And, of course,
Ellen and Jo are alive.
Ellen and Jo? What?
Yes, they're
supposed to be dead.
You see, I save a boat,
one thing leads to another,
which leads
to another thousand things,
and yada, yada, yada.
To cut a long story short,
they don't die
in a massive explosion.
Mm.
Anyway, let's agree
I did a good thing.
One less
Billy Zane movie,
and I saved
two of your closest friends.
But now
somebody is killing
the descendants
of the survivors.
And?
And that's maybe
like 50,000 people.
And?
And we need to save
as many as we can,
but we need to know
who's after 'em.
Oh, oh, sorry.
You have me confused
with the other angel...
you know, the one
in the dirty trench-coat
who's in love with you.
I...
don't care.
Goodbye, boys.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Son of a bitch!
So, Balthazar
un-sank a boat,
and now we got
a boatload of people
who should
never have been born.
Yeah. Like 50,000.
Makes sense.
How does any of this
make sense?
Because I got an idea
who we're up against.
What?
Fate.
You mean...
I mean Fate, like the Fates.
Or one of 'em, at least.
You mean like Greek mythology?
Like the sisters?
Bingo.
Nerd.
These ladies are responsible
for how you go down, literally.
So if you get creamed
by a garage door
or crunched by a copy machine,
they're the ones who hammer out
the details of how you die.
Spin out your fate
on a piece of pure gold.
Gold thread.
And then one of 'em
writes it all down
in her day runner of death.
High-level stuff.
Anyway... fits.
Now we know
what Balthazar did.
It seems to me
that maybe fate is just
trying to clean up the mess.
So, how do we stop it?
How do we stop fate?
Good question.
Well, there's got to be a way.
Or there ain't.
I mean, this is fate
we're talking about here.
You know,
the easiest way would be
to get that angel
to re-sink the boat.
No. No way. Forget it.
Big difference
between dying awful
and never being born, Dean.
We are not
sinking the boat, Bobby.
Okay?
Don't even think about it.
Well, okay. What's got
your panties in a clench?
Nothing.
Try that again?
It...
Look, it... it... it doesn't
even really matter, but...
But?
Apparently, a crap-load
of dominoes get tipped over
if the Titanic goes down.
And, bottom line...
Ellen and Jo die.
Okay, you two listen up.
You make sure...
Keep those angels
from sinking that boat.
You understand me?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Yeah, Bobby, of course.
Oh, he's bad enough
with her.
Think how he'd be
if she was gone.
Yeah.
So, what do we do?
I mean, how do we save
50,000 people?
I got no freakin' clue.
Yeah. We don't even know
who they are.
Well, we know one.
That's him. Let's go.
Hello.
Yeah. What?
Mr. Russo!
I don't care.
Send him a fruitcake.
Shawn!
Who's the judge?
Russo!
All right, send him
a nice bottle of champagne.
Shawn! But nothing more than
$30... ah, no. 20 bucks.
Believe me, this guy...
he owes me a favor.
Russo, stop!
Get off of me.
And you... I told you
to leave me alone, didn't I?!
Look, we're just trying
to help you out, okay?
Help me?! You almost killed me,
you lunatic.
Give me that.
Unbelievable.
Russo! Hey!
Just be glad I'm not suing your ass!
You've got to be kidding me.
Sam, check it out.
What?
Too soon?
Yeah, Dean.
I'm pretty sure
six seconds is too soon.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
I think I saw her.
Right over there.
- Her? Like Fate her?
- Yeah.
What'd she look like?
Kind of like a librarian.
Your kind of librarian
or my kind of librarian?
Well, she was wearing clothes,
if that's what you mean.
- All right.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
We can't just walk over there.
We're not on the hit list.
We have nothing to do
with the boat.
Let's go talk to her.
Talk.
Yeah, you know.
Worth a shot, right?
Hello?
Oh, come on.
You got a lighter?
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, come on.
It's out of juice or something?
It shouldn't be.
Cass!
- Hello, Dean. Sam.
- Hey. Thanks, man!
Where are we?
White Russia.
What?!
Are you aware
of what your frat bro did?
I'm aware.
Balthazar can be impetuous.
Well, riddle me this...
if fate's going after
the boat people,
why'd she try to waste
me and Sam?
Well, I imagine
she harbors
a certain degree of rage
toward you.
What did we do?
Nothing of import...
just the tiny matter
of averting the apocalypse
and rendering her obsolete.
I think maybe she's a little
irritated about that.
And then you go and dangle
yourselves in front of her...
So we've pissed fate off
personally.
If I know her...
and I do...
she won't stop
until you're dead.
Awesome.
So what do we do?
Kill her.
Kill fate?
Do you have
another suggestion?
No, I'm...
I just mean, uh...
Can you even do that?
Balthazar has a weapon
that will work against her.
Of course he does.
Yeah.
Boy, that guy's just
got it covered, doesn't he?
You need
new friends, Cass.
I'm trying to save
the ones I have, Dean.
We'll have to
draw her out.
All right, well, uh,
she's gunning for us.
She's bound to surface
again eventually.
We'll make it easy
for her.
I think you have
an expression for it.
"Tempting Fate."
Yeah, well,
you just be careful.
That was Jo. 30 more dead
on the west coast.
What exactly do those boys
think they're gonna do?
It's the boys.
If anybody can pull this out
of their ass, it's those two.
Yeah, you ever hear the saying
"you can't stop fate"?
You know, cleanest fix
would be just to sink the boat.
Why would you say that?
Well, because, right now
they're all dying bloody.
It's not the same
as never being born.
You're talking about people...
People who are loved...
Who would be missed.
What the hell is up with you?
Nothing.
Oh, please.
You are a neon sign.
So, I can beat it
out of you,
or we could just skip
that part... dealer's choice.
So, not just me, but Jo, too?
They're not gonna sink
the boat. I promise.
The boat stays.
You don't have to worry.
Well...
If it was meant to be,
then...
I guess whatever happens,
happens.
But that's just my point.
Nothing's "meant to be."
Whether we're together is
at the whim of some dick angel.
Oh, Bobby, relax.
I can't.
We need you.
Especially me.
I know.
Okay, so, we're just gonna meet
our fate at any time, right?
Yeah.
Just walk.
Act natural.
Okay.
That's fine.
Oh, you got to be
kidding me.
All right, just... just
Keep walking.
Sam, they're juggling knives.
- And hatchets.
- Yeah, I know.
Can't avoid fate.
Ah.
All right. I don't get it.
I don't either.
Who do you got to kill
to get killed around here?
Maybe Cass was wrong.
Look out!
Castiel.
Atropos.
You look well.
I look like stomped-over crap,
because of you.
All right,
let's talk about this.
Talk? About what?
Maybe about how you
and those two circus clowns
destroyed my work.
You ruined my life.
Let's not get emotional.
Not get emotional?!
I had a job.
God gave me a job.
We all had a script.
I worked hard.
I was really, really good
at what I did...
Until the day
of the big prize fight.
And then what happens?
You throw out the book!
Well, I'm sorry.
But freedom
is more preferable.
Freedom? This is chaos!
How is it better?
You know,
I even went to heaven
just to ask what to do next,
and you know what?
No one
would even talk to me.
There are more pressing
matters at hand.
But I don't know
what happens next.
I need to know.
It's what I do.
I'm sorry.
But your services
are no longer required.
You know what?
I've kept my mouth shut.
I could have complained,
I could have raised a fuss,
but I didn't.
But you know
what the last straw is?
Un-sinking the Titanic.
You changed the future.
You cannot change the past.
That is going too far!
- It's Balthazar. He's erratic...
- Bull crap.
This isn't about
some stupid movie.
He's under your orders.
You sent him back
to save that ship.
No, I didn't.
Why would I?
Oh, maybe because you're
in the middle of a war
and you're desperate?
Come on.
This is about the souls.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
That angel went and created
50,000 new souls
for your war machine.
You're confused.
No.
You can't just mint money, Castiel.
It's wrong...
It's dangerous...
And I won't let you.
You don't have a choice.
Maybe I don't.
So here's
a choice for you.
If you don't go back
and sink that boat,
I'm gonna kill
your two favorite pets.
I won't let you.
Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do?
Do you really want to test me?
Okay. Fine.
But think about this...
I've got
two sisters out there.
They're bigger,
in every sense of the word.
Kill me...
Sam and Dean are target one.
For simple vengeance.
You're not fighting a war
or anything, right?
You can watch them
every millisecond of every day.
Because
maybe you've heard...
fate strikes
when you least expect it.
Balthazar, stop.
Ah.
Awkward.
Set things right
before I flick
your precious boys off a cliff
just on principle.
Uh, sweetie,
before we go, um,
I could remove that stick
from your...
Don't try me.
Oh. We'll leave it
inserted, then.
All right, then.
Let's sink the Titanic.
Dude,
what time is it?
I-I just had
the weirdest dream.
20 bucks says mine was weirder.
I am not kidding.
No, no.
I'm not kidding either.
I-I mean, it was...
Just bizarre.
Mine had
the actual Titanic in it.
What?
There something on my face?
D-did it, uh...
Not sink,
because Balthazar...
had a hate on for Billy Zane?
Why are you
having my dreams, dude?
It wasn't a dream.
Wait, what?
You're saying
this actually happened?
That t-the whole...
whatever... t-that was real?
Yes.
So, what happened?
Well, I insisted
he go back in time
and correct
what he'd done.
What?
Why?
It was the only way
to be sure you were safe.
So...
So, you killed...
50,000 people for us.
No, I didn't.
They were never born.
That's far different from being
killed, wouldn't you say?
Ellen and Jo?
I'm sorry.
Hold on.
Uh...
So, if you guys went
a-and changed everything back,
then that whole time-line
or whatever, it just got erased?
Yeah. More or less.
Well, then, how come
he and I remember it?
Because I wanted you
to remember it.
Why?
I wanted you to know
who fate really is.
She's cruel and capricious.
I'd go so far as "bitch."
Well, yeah.
You're the ones who taught me
that you can make
your own destiny.
You don't have to be ruled
by fate.
You can choose freedom.
I still believe that that's
something worth fighting for.
I just wanted you
to understand that.
So, wait.
Did... Balthazar
really, uh,
unravel the sweater
over a chick flick?
Yes.
Absolutely.
That's what he did.
Wow. Well, might be time to
take away his cable privileges.
Besides, "Titanic"
didn't suck that bad.
Winslet's rack.
I'll tell you
one thing about Cass,
he does not appreciate
the finer things.
I guess things
are back to normal, huh?
"Normal." Awesome.
Poor bastard.
Doesn't even know
how good he had it.
Yeah, well, what he doesn't know
won't hurt him.
I say we keep
our mouths shut.
Yeah. I'm with you.
Should we wake him?
Nah.
That's probably
the best he's felt all week.
Sync by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Edited by Scooby