This thing goes our way
and I... Triple lindy
into that box...
...you know
I'm not coming back.
You got to promise
not to try to bring me back.
You go find Lisa.
You go live
some normal, apple-pie life.
Promise me, Dean.
Promise me.
you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Supernatural Season 6 Episode 1
"Exile on Main Street"
-- sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
And thank God
this is before facebook, right?
Because it'd be me and that goat...
...all over the Internet.
- That's right.
- So...
Don't get me wrong, right?
No complaints.
But if you'd have said
to me,
"Hey, you...
15 years from now?
Suburbia."
- Oh, yeah.
- Right?
Believe me, I know.
So, you've traveled around
a lot, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, my whole life,
pretty much.
And?
I don't know.
Come on.
You... what, you moved in,
what, about a year ago?
Yeah, thereabouts.
So I been buying you beer
for a year.
And I think that means you
owe me a couple of gory details.
Oh, no. There's not much
to tell, you know?
It's, uh...
I lived on the road...
Took, uh, crap jobs
that nobody else wanted.
Like?
Like...
Pest control.
Really?
Yeah.
You get to work
with a partner.
You get to help people.
You have no idea
what's in some people's walls.
It could eat 'em alive.
Yeesh.
'Course, that was then and now...
You're practically respectable.
Yeah. Wow.
I guess so.
That's kind of Scary, actually.
Thanks, guys.
Thank you.
I think she likes you.
You think?
What is it with you?!
Like, every time!
It's like chicks specifically
dig unavailable guys.
Who knew?
Okay.
I will see you
tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks, man.
And no one's called
about a missing person?
No, this would have
been today.
So no reports of anything
around Vineland and Oak street,
near that hotel renovation?
Uh, call it a hunch.
I've been a cop
for a long time.
Okay, yeah.
No, I'll call you tomorrow.
You too, man. Bye.
Hey.
Who was that?
Sid.
I'm just setting up
a poker game.
It's 11:30.
Is it really?
Well, that explains why
he was asleep when I called.
I'll be right up.
Okay.
Dean! Is that a gun?
No, no. Yeah.
Well, it's...
I got a permit for it.
What, to shoot
the Glickmans' dog?
I thought
that was a possum.
Remember when I said
I was in pest control?
Well, possums
carry rabies, so...
I did not know that.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Possums...
possums kill, Sid.
Oh, crap.
What's that?
Sulfur.
- I got to go.
- Hold on, Dean!
What the hell?
Hey.
Just getting a hammer.
So, I just
ran into Sid.
Did you almost
shoot a Yorkie?
Technically.
What's going on?
Nothing.
How come
I don't believe you?
I just... I, uh,
I-I got this...
I don't know,
spidey sense.
Okay.
Are you hunting something?
Honestly?
Uh, at first,
I thought that I was.
But I'm pretty sure that
I got worked up over nothing.
It's, uh, you know...
it happens.
Are you sure?
I'll tell you what...
just because, you know,
I have an OCD thing about this,
why don't, uh, why don't
you and Ben go to the movies,
hit the cheesecake factory...
you know, hang out
with the teeming masses,
and I'll do one last sweep
just to be 100%.
Okay.
Be careful.
Careful's my middle name.
Hiya, Dean.
Look what the apocalypse
shook loose.
You have fun
sniffing that trail?
'Cause I sure had fun
patting you around.
You can't be...
Oh, sure I can!
- No.
- Yeah, kiddo.
The big daddy brought your pal
Cass back, right?
So why not me?
Add a little Spice
to all that... that sugar.
Really?
After all we've been through
together?
You know, you got
a great little life here.
Pretty Lady... real understanding.
Hell of a kid.
And how do you
keep your lawn so green?
I mean, come on, Dean.
You never been
what I'd call brainy,
but did you really think
you were gonna
get to keep all of this?
You had to know that we were
coming for you sometime, pal.
You can't
outrun your past.
Hey, Dean.
I was expecting, uh...
I don't know, a hug,
some Holy water in the face...
something.
So I'm dead?
This is heaven?
Yellow eyes killed me,
and now...
yellow eyes?
That's what you saw?
"Saw"?
You were poisoned.
So whatever kind of crazy crap you
think you been seeing, it's not real.
So, then,
are you still... real?
- Or... or am I still...
- I'm real.
Here, let me
save you the trouble.
All me.
That's nasty.
Sammy?
Yeah.
It's me.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
You... you... you were...
you were gone, man.
I mean, that... that was it.
- How the hell are you...
- I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
I mean, no idea.
I... I'm just back.
Well, was it God,
or... or... or Cass?
I mean, does Cass
know anything about it?
You tell me.
I've been calling.
Cass hasn't answered
my prayers.
I don't even know
where he is.
I mean, I was... down there
and then, next minute,
it's raining
and I'm lying
in that field, alone.
It's kind of hard to go looking
for whatever saved you
when you got no leads.
But I looked.
I mean,
believe me, I looked...
For weeks.
Wait, weeks?
How long you been back?
How long
you been back, Sam?
About a year.
- About a year?
- Dean...
You been back
practically this whole time?!
What, did you lose the ability to
send a friggin' text message?!
You finally had
what you wanted, Dean.
- I wanted my brother, alive.
- You wanted a family.
You have for a long time, maybe
the whole time. I know you.
You only gave it up
because of the way we lived.
But you had something,
and you were building something.
Had I shown up, Dean,
you would have
just run off.
I'm sorry.
But it felt like
after everything,
you deserved
some regular life.
What have you been doing?
Hunting.
You left me alone,
and you were flying solo?
Not solo.
- What?
- I hooked up with some other people.
You?
Working with strangers?
They're more like family.
And they're here.
Hey.
Hi.
My God, you have
delicate features for a hunter.
Excuse me?
Dean, Gwen Campbell.
Good to finally meet you.
Sam's gone on and on.
And this is Christian...
...and Mark.
Campbell.
Hi.
Cam... Campbell?
Like...
Like your mom?
Third cousin.
Something, something
twice removed.
They grew up in the life,
like mom and like us.
I thought all of mom's relatives
were gone.
And I'm sorry.
It's just, you know, why didn't
we know about any of you?
'Cause they didn't
know about you.
Not until
I brought you all together.
Samuel?
I'm your grandfather.
Guys, give me a second
with my grandsons here, please.
Lot of resurrections
in your face today.
It's all right, take a minute.
It's gonna take
a little more than a minute.
I mean, what the hell?
H-how did this happen?
We're guessing whatever
pulled Sam up pulled me down.
So, whatever this is,
we're both a part of it.
But you don't know
what that is.
Bingo.
And you have no leads?
Nothing?
Well, this...
this is, uh...
No more doornail's coming out
of that door, is there?
As far as we know,
it's Samuel, and it's me.
Okay, am I the only one here
that... that... that thinks that
this can't all just be fine?
Believe me, you're not.
I wanted to come get you,
of course.
Sam was adamant about
leaving you out, so we did.
Until this.
Right.
So, then you ended up
in my garage how?
I got hit before you did,
few days ago.
Dosed up with poison.
- By?
- Couple of Djinn.
Djinn?
I thought those were...
were cave-dwelling hermit-type.
That's pretty exotic.
Not anymore, at least.
These... look like regular people.
They can blend in.
And all they got to do
to kill you is touch you.
Their toxins
get in your system,
all of a sudden you're
hallucinating your worst nightmares
and pretty soon you O.D.
Well, then how are you
breathing air?
Samuel had a cure.
You got a cure
for Djinn poison?
Oh,
I know a few things.
Stick around, I'll show you tricks
your daddy never even dreamed of.
Uh...
Okay, why are these things
after us?
Well, you did stake one
a while back.
After
they came after me,
we were pretty certain
that they were gonna
go gunning for you next.
Lisa and Ben...
they're at the house right now.
- If that thing comes back...
- It's all right.
I already sent someone
over there to watch 'em.
You got to
take me home right now.
Lisa?!
Lisa! Ben?!
Ben!
Come on! Come on!
Hey, there you are.
Where the hell
have you been?
We... we were at the movies.
You knew that.
Dean, ow.
What happened?
- Go upstairs and pack a bag.
- Where are we going?
I'm taking us
to a friend's house. Go.
It's okay. Go on up.
I'll be there in a sec.
What the hell?
Um...
Oh, my God.
Lisa, Ben, I don't know
if you remember...
Sam.
Damn it.
It's good to see you, too,
Bobby. It's been a while.
If you're here,
something's wrong.
Bobby,
this is Lisa and Ben.
Hi.
Well, it's nice to finally
meet you two.
Mi casa es su casa.
Maybe you want to
just go upstairs.
TV's broken, but there's plenty
of reader's digest.
Just don't touch the decor,
okay?
Assume it's all loaded.
So...
Hey, Bobby.
Sam.
You knew?
You knew Sam was alive.
Yeah.
How long?
- Look...
- How long?!
All year.
Oh, you got to be
kidding me.
- And I'd do it again.
- Why?!
Because you got out,
Dean!
You walked away
from the life.
And I was
so damn grateful,
you got no idea.
Do you have any clue
what walking away meant for me?
Yeah...
a woman and a kid
and not getting your guts
ripped out at age 30.
That's what it meant.
That woman and that kid... I went to
them because you asked me to.
- Good.
- Good for who?
I showed up
on their doorstep
half out of my head
with grief.
God knows why
they even let me in.
I drank too much.
I had nightmares.
I looked everywhere.
I collected
hundreds of books,
trying to find anything
to bust you out.
You promised
you'd leave it alone.
Of course
I didn't leave it alone!
Sue me!
A damn year?
You couldn't put me
out of my misery?
Look,
I get it wasn't easy.
But that's life!
And it's as close
to happiness
as I've ever seen
a hunter get.
It ain't like
I wanted to lie to you, son.
But you were out, Dean.
Do I look out to you?
How's he doing?
- He's okay.
- How are you?
Look, I know Bobby's a little
crotchety, but he's great.
He's gonna look after
you guys.
Me and Sam,
we're gonna head out.
For how long?
I'm so sorry, Lisa.
For what?
Those things
were coming for me
and I should've known.
How could you know
a monster was gonna show up?
I should've known.
I should've known,
that if I stayed with you,
that something would come,
because something always does.
But I was stupid
and reckless and...
...you can't outrun
your past.
You're saying goodbye.
I'm saying I'm sorry...
for everything.
Everything.
You're an idiot.
I mean, I know it wasn't
greeting-card perfect,
but we were in it together.
I was a wreck
half the time.
Yeah, well, the guy that
basically just saved the world
shows up at your door,
you expect him
to have a couple of issues.
And you're always
so amazing with Ben.
You know what I wanted,
more than anything...
was...
...a guy that Ben
could look up to...
like...
like a dad.
So, you're saying
it's all bad, Dean?
'Cause it was
the best year of my life.
What's the plan?
Well, right now,
we stock up, get set.
So you're saying
there is no plan.
We'll find 'em.
Just got to be patient.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, here's an alt.
Why don't we go kill
the sons of bitches
that broke into my home?
Relax, Dean.
We got it handled.
Djinn are hard to draw out.
Now, you've been
out of the game for a while.
Leave it
to the professionals.
Yeah. Sure.
Tiny suggestion.
You see, Djinn are easier
to draw out when you got bait.
They want Sam and me.
They know where I live.
Now, I haven't been hunting
in a while,
but I'm gonna
stick my neck out
and guess that's a pretty good
place for us to go.
See? It's almost like
I'm a professional.
Huh.
I love this one.
Yours or,
uh, your wife's?
Hey.
Do me a favor...
don't touch that.
Golf?
Really?
It's a... it's a sport.
Nice house.
Oh, yeah. Go ahead, say it...
call me a soccer mom.
Whatever.
"Soccer mom," huh?
Well, I'll have to look that up
on the "intranet."
You know,
believe it or not, I...
I get it, Dean.
You wanted a normal life.
Your mom
wanted a normal life, too.
You remind me of her,
actually.
The attitude,
for one thing.
Your brother tell you what we been
dealing with the past few months?
No, not really.
I've never seen
anything quite like it.
Been working
'round the clock.
- So what's going on?
- We don't know.
But whatever it is,
it goes way past
a couple of Djinn acting off.
Nocturnals attacking in broad daylight,
werewolves out on the half-moon,
creatures that we've never
even seen before.
We don't... we don't even know
what they are.
I'm knee-deep
in half-eaten human hearts
and exsanguinated
10-year-olds,
and it's all making me...
uneasy.
So what's your theory?
You tell me.
All we really know
is it's all hands on deck.
We're counting on each other
right now.
That's how it is
with Campbells'.
We need you, Dean.
Look,
I hear you, but...
You don't know
what you're part of, Dean.
You know, you had ancestors
hacking the heads off vamps
on the Mayflower.
What I'm saying
is that, we're your blood.
And we're out there dying,
trying to get in front of
whatever this is.
Maybe not the best time for golf.
Hey.
You don't really
say much, do you?
Enough.
Any sign of 'em?
Three Djinn
off in the trees.
Here.
Those Djinn are just sitting
out there, watching us.
- Everybody's got to clear out.
- What?
They're not gonna come in here
until me and Sam are alone.
So, what, I'm supposed to
leave you here with no backup?
Dean's right.
They're smart. They'd wait
till they weren't outnumbered.
All right,
we won't be far.
You call when they come,
you hear?
You bet!
All right, pack up.
We're out of here.
You okay?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
No, this is...
this is crazy.
I mean, you, grandpa.
Whoever brought you back...
- They don't want to be found.
- Yeah, I get that.
But who are they, and what do
they... what do they want? Why?
That's a good question.
Do you remember it?
What?
The cage.
Yeah.
You want to...
No.
Well, if anybody
can relate...
Dean, I don't want
to talk about it. I'm back.
I get to breathe fresh air,
h-have a beer,
hunt with my family,
see you again.
So why exactly would I want
to think about hell?
And you really think...
Dean, they're already dead
and you know it.
This is happening
because of me!
Dean!
Sid.
You made it through
that last trip,
so how about
a big, fat double dose?
Bad news... it'll kill you.
The good news?
At least you'll go fast.
That's for our father,
you son of a bitch.
I just... I-I
couldn't sleep at that house.
It's okay.
Don't worry. We'll call Dean.
Ah, don't worry
about them, Dean.
Worry about me.
No!
There, there, kiddo.
You stay away from him!
Lisa!
- Drink it.
- Ben, no!
You'll feel better.
No!
It's all your fault.
Lisa!
This, something else...
we both know that's details.
There's something's
coming for this one
and you can't stop it.
It's all your fault.
- Lisa!
- Drink it.
You'll feel better.
- Ben, don't!
- Your fault.
Can't stop it.
No!
I got her, go get Dean.
Got her.
Relax, hon.
We're not gonna kill you.
Get her in the van. Quick, now,
before the boys get back.
Come on. Come on.
So, Samuel
and the cuzzes?
Don't know.
They left in a hurry.
I'm meeting them
back at their place.
You, uh,
you coming with me?
No.
No, I'm going back
for Lisa and Ben.
I thought you said...
I did.
I changed my mind.
Look, I practically
shoved you at them.
That's a funny way to put it,
but all right.
I'm just saying,
I really wanted that for you.
And when I told you to go,
I-I thought...
You could have it,
you know?
But now
I'm not so sure.
I mean,
you got to consider the fact
that you'll be putting them
in danger if you go back.
So, what, it's better to
leave them alone, unprotected,
and then they're not in danger?
I did this to them.
I made them vulnerable the
moment I knocked on their door,
and I can't undo that.
But what I can do
is go with the best option.
I hear you.
I guess I just, uh...
wish you were coming, that's all.
Why?
- Don't be stupid.
- No, I mean it.
I mean, you know plenty of
good hunters, I'm rusty.
I did something seriously stupid
going out there.
I almost got us both killed.
And that's exactly
why I want you.
What are you
talking about?
You just went.
You didn't hesitate.
Because you care,
and that's who you are.
Me?
I wouldn't even
think to try.
Yes, you would.
No, Dean.
I'm telling you, it's just
better with you around,
that's all.
Listen...
she should be hunting.
Take her.
Thanks. Really.
But I already got my car
set up how I like it.
I should hit the road.
I'll walk you out.
Keep in touch,
you hear?
'Course.
It was really good
to see you again, Dean.
-- sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.Com --
Edited by Scooby