Hey, Dean.
- How long you been back?
- About a year.
- What have you been doing?
- Hunting.
You been back practically this whole time?!
You finally had what you wanted, Dean.
I wanted my brother, alive.
You wanted a family.
You only gave it up because
of the way we lived.
But you had something,
and you were building something.
I need you to go. You're a hunter.
And now you know your brother's out there.
Things are different.
- You don't want to be here, Dean.
- Yes, I do.
Me and Ben will be here and...
you come when you can.
Just come in one piece.
And you really think we could
pull something like that off?
It's worth a shot.
Castiel: Archangels are fierce.
They're absolute.
They're heaven's most terrifying weapon.
Raphael.
Come and get me, you little bastard.
Castiel.
When the oil burns,
no angel can touch or
pass through the flames,
or he dies.
Raphael: Castiel.
I'm warning you.
Do not leave me here.
I will find you.
What are you gonna do now?
- Return to heaven, I suppose.
- Heaven?
With Michael in the cage,
I'm sure it's total anarchy up there.
[Water running]
Oh, come on.
Ohh.
Oh.
[Exhaling sharply]
What the hell?
Come on, man. Let's get going.
[Breathing rapidly]
Jerry?
Ed, I think I'm bleeding.
[Fluid splashes]
Season 6 Episode 3
"The Third Man"
[birds chirping]
Hey, you.
[Grunts lightly]
Hey.
[Rumbling]
[Truck horn blares]
Don't stop on my account.
[Laughs]
I'm done.
Last night was a... [clears throat]
High point, if you don't mind me saying.
Good.
All right.
Well, I see you need to start your day.
When did you say you were heading out?
[Inhales, exhales sharply]
You didn't. Right.
Damn, you know how to play
that mystery card.
[Clears throat]
Right.
I almost forgot.
Next time...
You can call me on my night off.
If you want.
Okay.
[Door opens, closes]
[Cellphone rings]
- Sam: Hey.
- Hey.
I'm about eight hours out
of the Campbell base.
Uh, change of plans.
I need you to meet me. I'm in PA,
town called Easter.
What are you doing in Pennsylvania?
Caught a case.
A case?
When? It's been like a day and a half.
I like to work.
Apparently.
Glad we hashed that out.
Call me when you roll into town.
Who died and made you boss?
[Car door opens]
[Sighs lightly]
[Vehicle approaches rapidly]
Oh, you could do better than that.
[Branch snaps]
[Exhales sharply]
[Cellphone rings]
Why are you calling me?
He's dead, right? That's it.
Now, I don't want to talk about it.
We do what we do...
We go to work, we go to the funeral.
[Sighs]
Calm down.
This is nothing to do with you and me.
You're just working yourself up.
Don't call me.
Idiot.
The hell?
God!
Dispatch, this is... [Chokes]
[Strained] Please, I... I need...
Please.
Ben... I know you're lying.
Because I lie professionally, that's how.
Now tell your mom that
you broke the damn thing
and take it like a man.
Okay? Ok... Okay.
- Wow.
- What?
You... Molding the minds of tomorrow.
Who knew?
Yeah, tell me about it.
- How'd it go?
- With?
You and Lisa.
How'd she take it when you bailed?
Shockingly cool, actually.
Better for everybody.
Yeah, I suppose.
Still driving the plastic
piece of crap, huh?
What's your mileage, again?
Shut up.
Officer Gerald Hatch, 17-year veteran,
found dead in the ready room
three days ago.
Whoa.
Somebody was over-hydrated.
[Laughs] Basically, yeah.
The guy just... liquefied.
Most of the meat, bones, dense tissues...
they just turned to blood.
- Okay, I don't get it.
- Nobody gets it.
No. I mean, I get that.
I'm saying, if the guy was a mop job,
then what are we doing in the morgue?
What's left of him to look at?
Not here to look at him.
Here.
[Door creaks]
Ooh. Bad news.
Officer Toby Gray.
They just brought him in.
Found him dead in his patrol car,
sitting at a speed trap
on the outside of town.
"Extreme allergic reaction."
Yeah. Boils. Covered from head to toe.
Yeah, on the inside, too.
It says his airways
are chock full of them.
This startin' to look
a little witchy to you?
That was my first instinct,
but I found zero signs
of hex-work anywhere.
Far as I can tell,
witchcraft was not involved.
There's got to be some sort of link
between, uh, skid mark
and bubble wrap here.
No question.
- All right, well, can I get a witness?
- Yep.
Uh...
Officer Ed Colfax.
Saw Hatch go from a solid to a liquid.
Another cop?
Hatch's partner.
[Tires squeal]
[Car alarm beeps]
Were you, uh...
[Chuckles]
Were you racing me?
No.
I was kicking your ass.
Very mature.
[Knock on door]
Hello? Officer Colfax?
Whoa.
Lookin' sharp, Kojak.
Who the hell are you?
We're the Fed, Ed.
We're here to ask you a
few follow-up questions
about your partner's death.
Don't worry about it.
It's nobody's business.
- Officer Colfax...
- Don't worry about it!
[Sighs]
Dude!
Officer Colfax?
[Scratching]
Hey, man, you all right?
Don't worry about it.
Right.
Look, Officer Colfax... Ed.
Um...
We think that your partner
died of unnatural causes.
Did he have any
enemies that you know of?
[Groans] You might say that.
Oh, yeah?
Who's that?
They both had it coming. Me too.
I'll be the next to go
and then it'll be over.
And God will be satisfied.
Why does God want you all dead?
'Cause of Christopher Birch.
Oh, damn it.
Who's Christopher Birch?
He has no face.
Ed?
Officer, you all right?
Who is Christopher Birch, Ed?
Ed!
Christopher Birch is
a kid with no face...
and a planted gun.
Uh, you, uh...
You got a little something...
Yeah.
Damn.
My head's been itching like a dirty jock.
Sam: Ed?
Dead.
[Buzzing]
You hear that?
[Buzzing intensifies]
Sweet. Blood, boils, locusts.
Three of your more
popular Egyptian plagues.
Yeah, but these guys...
ate their way out of a cop's melon.
I don't quite remember
that in the King James.
Meanwhile, a kid named Christopher Birch
was shot in the head last month
after a vehicle pursuit.
Hatch, Gray and Colfax were
the three officers involved,
and they all filed the
exact same police report.
"Suspect exited vehicle
brandishing a firearm".
"We were forced to fire."
"Just a kid with no
face and a planted gun."
Bunch of dicks.
So they pop the kid, plant the piece.
Maybe Colfax is right.
You know, maybe Heaven has
a hate-on for bad cops.
So we're listening to the guy
with the bug in his custard?
That's... that's the, uh,
The theory you want to go with?
Dean, angels got to have
something to do, right?
Now that we're post-apocalypse?
[Bottle cap pops]
Yeah, maybe.
We should call Cass.
You're kidding, right?
[Scoffs]
Dean, I tried.
It was the first and second
and third thing I did,
soon as I got topside.
Son of a bitch won't answer the phone.
Well, let's give it a shot.
Now I lay me down to sleep.
I pray to Castiel to get
his feathery ass down here.
- You're an idiot.
- Stay positive.
Oh, I am positive.
Come on, Cass!
Don't be a dick.
We got ourselves a...
Plague-like situation down here.
And...
do you... do you copy?
Like I said... [clears throat]
the son of a bitch doesn't answer.
He's right behind me, isn't he?
Hello.
Hello?
Yes.
[Imitating Castiel] "Hello."
[Normal voice] "Hello"?
Uh, that is still the term?
I spent all that time trying
to get through to you.
Dean calls once,
and now it's [Imitating Castiel] "Hello"?!
Yes.
[Normal voice] So, what, you...
You like him better or something?
[Scoffs]
Dean and I do share
a more profound bond.
I wasn't gonna mention it.
Cass, I think what he's
trying to say is that...
he went to hell for us.
I mean, he really took one for the team.
You remember that?
And then he comes back without a clue
and you can't take five friggin' minutes
to give him some answers?
If I had any answers,
I might have responded.
But I don't know, Sam.
We have no idea who brought
you back from the cage
or why.
So... it wasn't God?
No one's even seen God.
The whole thing remains mysterious.
What the hell does that mean?
What part of "I don't know"
escapes your understanding?
Cass, look, if Sam calls, you answer.
Okay? You wing your ass down here,
and you tell him, "I don't know."
Just because we have some
sort of a... a bond or whatever...
You think I came
because you called?
I came because of this.
Oh, well, it's nice
to know what matters.
It does help one to focus.
Wait, so... so you and the Halo Patrol,
you guys aren't the
cause of these killings?
No.
But they were committed
with one of our weapons.
There's only one thing that could
have brought this into existence.
You call it the Staff of Moses.
The Staff?
It was used in a dominance
display against the Egyptians,
as I recall.
[Scoffs]
Yeah. That one made the papers.
But I thought the staff
turned, like, a... a river into blood
not one dude.
The weapon isn't being
used at full capacity.
I think we can rule
Moses out as a suspect.
Okay, but... what is...
what is Chuck Heston's disco
stick doing down here, anyway?
I mean, don't you
guys put away your toys?
Before the apocalypse,
Heaven may have been corrupt,
but it was stable.
The Staff was safely contained.
[Sighs]
It's been chaos up there
since the war ended.
In that confusion, a number of
powerful weapons were...
stolen.
Wait, you...
you're saying your nukes are loose?
Yeah, I'm afraid so.
But you've stumbled onto one of them.
We must find the weapon that did this.
I need your help.
[Scoffs]
That's rich. Really.
[Grunts]
Sam, Dean,
my "people skills" are "rusty."
Pardon me, but I have
spent the last "year"
as a multidimensional wavelength
of celestial intent.
But believe me,
you do not want
that weapon down here.
Help me find it.
Or more people will die.
All right. Okay.
Well, if the angels didn't pull the trigger,
then that brings us back to motive.
What?
Back to the case.
Right now, we got three dead cops.
Only thing linking them...
is this.
"Father of slain suspect
calls for investigation."
Boy: Come on, dad.
How many times are you
gonna read that thing?
You know what?
We should just throw it away.
Go out back and play.
- Oh, Cass, a little warning next time.
- What the...
How'd you get in here?!
Mr. Birch, settle down.
Federal agents.
But you can't just walk in here!
Quite a collection
you've got there, huh?
What are you trying to...
Look, we know the truth, all right?
Chris didn't have a gun on
him when those cops shot him.
- They set him up.
- Yeah.
They're all getting theirs.
And who's giving it to them, Darryl?
Darryl?
- Did you kill Toby Gray and the others?
- Me?!
I didn't kill anyone!
Look at how they died!
You smote them with the staff of Moses!
The hell kind of fed are you?
We don't have time for this.
- Where is it?
- Boy: Leave my dad alone!
- Is that...?
- Yes.
- Shouldn't it be bigger?
It's... it's been sawed off.
- Leave him alone! It wasn't him!
- Aaron, get out of here!
- What did you do to him?
- It's all right. He's just sleeping.
Cass, take it easy!
Listen, we're not here
to hurt you, okay?
But we need to know...
where did you get this thing?
Please don't kill my dad.
It was me. I did it.
Okay, nobody's killing anybody.
What's your name?
Aaron. Aaron Birch.
Okay, Aaron Birch,
where did you get this?
- You won't believe me.
- Try me.
It was an angel.
An angel?
Those liars, they killed my brother,
and nothing bad even happened to them.
It's not fair.
So I prayed to God every
night he would punish them.
God didn't answer.
But he did.
His name... did he give you a name?
No.
He just said I could have justice,
but I was gonna
have to take it myself.
He... he gave me the stick.
He just... gave it to you?
Ah, come on.
He didn't just give it to you,
did he, Aaron?
Aaron?
I bought it.
You bought it? [chuckles]
With what?
What's your allowance?
What did the angel want for it?
What did you give him for it?
My soul.
You sold your soul to an angel?
Can that even happen?
It's never happened before.
An angel's buying souls.
That could explain why he
cut the staff into pieces.
Why?
More pieces, more product.
More "product"? Who is this guy?
We'll find him.
- What did you do that for?
- Portability.
Cass, you realize you
just kidnapped a kid?
If the angel we seek truly
bought this boy's soul,
when a claim is laid on a living soul,
it leaves a mark, a brand.
What, like a... like a shirt tag at camp?
I have no idea.
But I can read the mark
and find the name of the
angel that bought the soul.
How?
Well, painfully for him.
The reading will be excruciating.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on.
- Dean.
- He's a kid, Cass.
A ki... Sam?
Any permanent damage?
- What?!
- Physically, minimal.
Oh, well, yeah, then by all means,
- stick your arm right in there.
- Dean!
If I get the name, I can work a
ritual to track the angel down.
And I'm all for that, but come on.
- There's got to be another way.
- There is no other way.
You're gonna torture a kid?
I can't care about that, Dean!
I don't have the luxury.
[Screaming]
[Screaming stops]
He'll rest now.
Did you get a name? What is it?
I thought he died in the war.
What, he... he was a...
he was a friend or something?
[Sighs] A good friend.
Yeah, well, your frat buddy
is now moonlighting
as a crossroads demon.
Balthazar. I wonder...
So we can find him now, right?
Balthazar.
Thanks, Castiel.
We'll make good use of the name.
And by the way, Raphael says hello.
[Chuckles]
[Car alarm blares]
My car.
Okay. Silver lining.
Castiel: He's gone.
Alright, Cass. Who was that guy?
A soldier of Raphael.
He must have followed me
when I answered your call.
Raphael? The archangel?
I'm sorry, what's going on here?
I can explain later.
Right now we have to...
No, not later. Now. Stop, all right?
Too many angels, Cass!
I don't know who's on first,
what's on second.
What is "second"?!
Don't start that.
It is simple... Raphael and his followers,
they want him to rule heaven.
I... and many others...
the last thing we want is
to let him take over.
It would be catastrophic.
You're talking civil war.
Technically, yes.
Which is why we have to find
Balthazar and his weapons
before Raphael does.
Whoever has the weapons wins the war.
Help yourself.
And what happens if Raphael wins?
- What... what does he want?
- What he's always wanted...
to end the story the
way it was written.
You mean the apocalypse,
the one that we derailed?
Yes, that one.
Raphael wants to put
it back on the rails.
Why?
I need myrrh.
Myrrh?
Friggin' angels.
[Clatter]
Dean: Why does Raphael want
to bring back all this crap?
He's a traditionalist.
Cass, why didn't you tell us this?
I was ashamed.
I expected more from my brothers.
I'm sorry.
Now I need your blood.
Whoa, whoa! Hey! Ahh!
Why don't you use your own?
It wouldn't work. I'm not human.
[Grunts]
Zamran ils soba
vpaah zixlai grosb.
[Sirens wail in distance]
Uh, Cass,
how long does this spell take?
[Wailing intensifies]
Got him. Let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What about him?
Don't you think the
police will take him home?
[Crickets chirping]
Huh.
I was expecting more
Dr. No, less Liberace.
[Frog croaking]
[Dance music plays]
Cass.
You're here.
Balthazar.
It's so good to see you.
He told me you were floating around.
- He?
- I believe you two have flown together.
[Laughs]
Oh, you know, the old frog in the throat.
[Frog croaks]
Even i know that,
that's a bad joke.
I grieved your death.
Yeah, yeah. I'm sorry
about that, you know.
I wanted them to think, you know,
so... they wouldn't
come looking for me.
What... is all this?
- What are you doing?
- Whatever I want.
This morning I had a m?nage ?...
What's French for 12?
You stole the staff of Moses.
Sure, sure.
I stole a lot of things.
You were a great and honorable soldier.
We fought together.
Yes, too many times to count.
I know you.
You're not some common thief.
Common? No.
Thief? Eh.
I need your help.
I know.
I've been hearing all about you,
and as far as I'm concerned,
you and me, Cass...
Nothing's changed.
We're brothers.
Of course I want to help you.
Thank you.
I need the weapons.
Don't ask that.
Why take them? Why run away?
Because I could!
What?
What? I me... you're the
one who made it possible.
The footsteps I'm following...
they're yours.
What you did, stopping the big plan,
the prize fight?
You did more than rebel.
You tore up the whole
script and burned the pages
for all of us.
[Laughs]
It's a new era.
No rules, no destiny,
just utter and complete freedom.
- And this is what you do with it?
- Hey, screw it, right?
I mean, dad's not coming back.
You might as well blow
coke and jump on the bed.
You proved to me we could do anything,
so I'm trying everything.
What difference does it make?
Of course it makes a diff...
It's civil war up there!
I know.
If we can beat Raphael,
we can end this!
Just give me the weapons.
[laughs]
Do you know what's funny about you?
You actually believe that
you can stop the fighting.
It will never stop.
My advice... grab something valuable
and fake your own death.
You've gone insane.
Your little holiday is over.
Raphael knows you're alive by now.
Oh, Raphael can try me anytime.
I'm armed.
I'm sorry, Cass.
All else aside, I'm really,
really happy to see you.
Even though you still have
that stick up your ass.
[Thunder crashes]
Was that you?
Oh, that's my cue then.
Tell, uh, Raphael to bite me.
[Thunder crashes]
Watch them. They're all snakes.
Sam: Hey, there.
Yeah, I got one of those, too.
You think you can
knife fight an angel?
Who's fighting?
Peace out, douche-wad.
[Thunder crashes]
You're making a mistake.
Please. There is another way.
Brother, please.
I don't want to hurt you.
[Screams]
Why won't any of you listen?
[Grunts] They don't listen, Castiel,
because their hearts are mine.
[Groans]
[Grunting]
[Thunder crashes]
[Breathing heavily]
Somehow, I don't think
God will be bringing
you back this time.
Balthazar: Hey!
Look at my junk.
No.
[Salt clatters]
[Chuckles]
Same thing happened to Lot's wife.
Iodize the poor sucker,
and your kitchen is stocked for life.
[Laughs]
You came back.
Well, now Raphael will have to
go shopping for a new vessel.
Should give me a nice
long head start on him.
Until next time.
Next time.
Dean: No time like the present.
Holy fire.
You hairless ape! Release me!
First you're taking your marker
off of Aaron Birch's soul!
Am I?!
Sam?!
Unless you like your
wings extra crispy,
I'd think about it.
Castiel, I stood for you in heaven.
- Are you gonna let...
- Castiel: I believe...
the hairless ape has the floor.
[Laughs] Very well.
[Inhales sharply]
[Exhales deeply]
The boy's debt is cleared.
His soul is his own.
Why you buying up human souls, anyway?
In this economy?
It's probably the only
thing worth buying.
Do you have any
idea what souls are worth?
What power they hold?
Now... release me.
Suck it, ass clown.
Nobody said anything...
Cass, what the hell?
My debt to you is cleared.
Fair enough.
Cass, are you out of your mind?!
Cass?!
Oh, friggin' angels! Come on!
Yeah, well I didn't realize I
had this much stuff back here.
Sam: Well, I need some space.
Kind of picked up some
stuff along the way.
[Both exhale sharply]
What the hell is that?
Oh, it's, uh, Ben's Halloween costume.
Wendigo?
Yeah.
[Both chuckle] Accurate.
Hey, so, uh...
Are you okay?
Me?
[Chuckling] Yeah, I'm great.
Really? 'Cause there's been a few
times that you got me wondering.
Come again?
Well, like where were you
when Cass was, uh,
giving the Holy taser treatment
to that kid?
I was right there.
Really?
'Cause honestly,
I felt like I was the
only one raising a card.
Right.
Uh, I mean, I was with you,
but... I don't know.
We... we needed the Intel.
Yeah, I know, but we
tortured that kid to get it.
[Sighs]
I just didn't get
the feeling that you...
that you even cared.
You're wrong.
Man, I'm just trying to
figure this out because...
Something's different with you.
You know that.
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
Really?
Yeah.
I mean...
[Chuckles]
I've been hunting nonstop
for the past year,
kind of...
Kind of out in the wild, you know?
So, yeah, I suppose I'm a
little rough around the edges.
Yeah, I get that.
I just don't think I'm
getting the whole scoop.
You went to hell, Sam.
And believe me,
I know what that does to a guy.
To you.
What?
You know what it does to you.
It... it tortured you.
You know?
I think it still does.
But, Dean...
I'm okay.
So you're saying, what,
that... that you're stronger than me?
[Chuckling] No.
Just saying we're different.
[Sighs]
[Car door closes]
Monsters lately.
Is it me or is it weird?
[Machinery rattling]
Woman: Look out!
Vampires? [scoffs]
These aren't vampires, man.
These...
These are douche bags.
Explain to me what's going on out there.
Lis, I can't bring
this crap home to you.
You're talking about your work.
I'm talking about my life.
Anyone in town who asks
aloud for the truth,
invokes Veritas.
And she doesn't just give it to you,
she slams you with it.
- Whoa, why the hell am I telling you this?
- Because I'm cursed.
I'm saying I asked for the truth
and, uh, guess what?
I'm getting it.
So, like I said,
I have a few questions for you.
Dean, you all right?
It's Sam, Bobby.
You got my back.
No matter what happens,
I can always count on you,
right, Sammy?
Yeah.
Of course, Dean.
Sync by elderman, corrected by gloriabg...
...for www.addic7ed.com...
Edited by Scooby