You turned me.
Hate those fangs.
You bit me
in the neck.
The bite
doesn't matter.
You have to actually ingest
the blood to be infected.
That was vampire blood
he dosed you with.
What?
Lights are too bright?
Sunshine hurt your skin?
I get so hungry.
What have you been doing?
Hunting --
with some other people.
You?
Working with strangers?
More like family.
I'm your grandfather.
Stick around,
I'll show you tricks
your daddy
never even dreamed of.
I-I can't just
lose you and Ben.
Me and Ben will be here,
and...You come when you can.
Just come in one piece.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
'Cause there's been a few times
that you've got me wondering.
It's Sam, Bobby.
He's just -- he's different.
Something's not right to me.
? White on white,
translucent black capes ?
? back on the rack ?
? Bela Lugosi's dead ?
? the bats have left
the bell tower ?
? the victims have been bled ?
? red velvet
lines the black box ?
? Bela Lugosi's dead ?
? undead, undead, undead ?
You came.
I told you I would.
? Undead, undead, undead ?
Shall we sit?
I can't tell you that.
Too embarrassing.
Come on.
Nothing you could
ever say would...
I mean,
those poems you posted?
They revealed
who you really are.
I know you, Kristen.
Thanks.
I actually, um...
Wrote one today.
You want to...?
Of course I do.
Ow. Damn it.
Paper cut.
Hi,
clumsiest person ever.
I have to go.
Wait!
Hi.
I shouldn't be here.
So why are you?
I can't stop
thinking about you.
Then...
Don't.
We can't do this.
We can't be together.
- There has to be a way.
- No.
You think you know me...
But you don't.
I've done bad things.
You should run.
Now.
I can make
my own decisions.
I'm 17.
I have to
show you something.
Okay.
I knew it.
- Are you scared?
- No.
You should be.
I'm just scared...
I'm dreaming and I'll wake up
in math class.
Is it gonna hurt?
I could never hurt you.
Come with me.
Where?
Let me show you my world.
So, your place...
Is there gonna be...
Velvet?
Yeah, sure.
This is it?
But...
It smells like pee.
Nice work, Robbie.
Robert,
what's happening?
This is what you wanted,
isn't it?
? Supernatural 6x05 ?
Live Free or Twihard
Original Air Date on October 22, 2010
-- sync by elderman  --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Hey.
So, uh,
I'm actually not far.
I'm about
a night's drive.
Yeah?
So, you think...
Well, there's some stuff
I got to do here first.
Of course.
But I was thinking that,
uh, I'll wrap up here
and, you know, make sure
I'm not followed.
I'll have to
take side streets,
and I'd have to
come at night --
will you just shut up
and get your ass home?
I can't wait to see you.
This phone thing's getting old.
Yeah.
Well,
call us when you're close.
And be careful.
Of course.
Hey.
What are you
so stoked about?
What? Nothing.
What do you got?
Six girls in seven days,
which is more disappearances
than this city has seen
in over a year.
All about the same age.
And cute.
Hey, ice cream
comes in lots of flavors, Sam.
Gotcha.
Yeah, well,
half a dozen girls,
late teens,
a shower away from greatness.
Sounds like a profile.
Wonder what else
they got in common.
Well, six directions
to go, here.
Pick a number.
Seven. Another call
just came in today.
Kristen's a good kid --
a little naive, sure.
You try
and be a good parent.
Girls are hard.
Right. Well, we'd just like
to find your daughter.
Last door on the left.
Thanks.
What do you think
he was talking about?
Drugs?
Oh,
it is so much worse.
Vampires?
These aren't vampires, man.
These --
these are douchebags.
Yeah.
Wow.
Hmm.
Aha!
All right.
Let's see
what we can see.
All right.
That -- that's just...
Uncomfortable.
What is
he so bummed out about?
Look at this.
He's watching her sleep.
How is that not rapey?
I got to concentrate here,
Dean.
"He could hear the blood
rushing inside her,
"almost taste it.
"He tried desperately
to control himself.
Romero knew their love
was impossible."
Romero? Really?
Dean. Shut up.
This is
a national bestseller.
How is that possible?
Hey, try, um...
"Lautner."
Wait. He's a werewolf.
How do you even know
who that is?
What, are you kidding me?
That kid's everywhere.
It's a freaking nightmare.
Hey, how many t's are there
in Pattin--
That's it. We're in.
Ha!
All right.
Well?
Well, her in-box is full
from some guy
claiming to be a vampire.
A real vampire?
Well, uh...
"I can only
meet you at night.
"I don't trust myself
with you.
The call of your blood
is too strong."
Vampires phishing
for victims?
Probably just
a human mouth-breather, right?
On the other hand,
talk about easy prey.
For actual vamps.
Yeah,
I mean, these chicks
are just throwing themselves
at you.
All you got to do is...
I don't know.
Write bad poetry.
Huh.
Well, this guy
wanted to meet her
at a place called
the Black Rose.
Give me a break.
I'm just
reporting the news.
It's probably just
your standard-issue perv, right?
Stop!
Let me go!
Okay. So now you're sure
it's vampires.
100%?
Definitely.
We got a pattern now --
kids go missing,
blood-bank van gets jumped.
This is the fourth town.
Clincher is,
this last hit --
driver was found,
throat ripped out.
Okay, they grab kids --
that's food, right?
But if they already got
a bunch of walking,
talking juice bars,
why bother
with the blood mobile?
It doesn't add up.
Find the nest.
Figure it out.
Well, you wanted emo chicks.
I think we hit ground zero.
Thank you.
Think she wears all that rubber
at the beach?
When's the last time
we had a beer together, anyway?
There.
What do you think?
He's hitting on her
hard enough.
Real?
I don't know,
it's hard to tell.
And we got multiple choice.
Great.
Three of them, two of us.
? Well, he wants you ?
? and she wants him ?
okay,
make that two of them.
One's on the move.
All right, you go with Efron.
I got Bieber.
Are you sure, baby?
Are you ready
to join me in eternity?
Oh, my God, totally.
Go! Get out of here!
- What the hell are you doing?!
- Open your mouth!
Take those out.
Take 'em out!
Ohh.
For the love of...
What are you, 12?
Are you wearing glitter?
I only do it
to get laid, man!
Does it work?
I'll be damned.
All right,
"mmmbop" your way out of here.
Go! Go.
And use a condom.
You're pretty.
I'm sorry?
I said...
"You're pretty."
Yeah.
Sorry again, pal.
I don't
play for your team.
No!
Sammy.
Oh, my God,
what is that sound?
What sound, Dean?
What?
Hey, come on!
Keep it down, damn it!
Please,
please shut that off.
Oh, geez.
Dean,
you should sit down.
You sit down.
Out of
all the ways to die,
I never thought
I'd be going out like this.
Dean, nobody is going out.
Right.
What?
Samuel's gonna kill me
when he gets here.
No, Dean, he's not.
Yes, he is, 'cause
I'm gonna ask him to
because you won't do it.
Okay, just hold on a second.
For what, huh?!
Look at me!
- We can figure this out!
- How?!
Why aren't you
freaked out?
- Of course I am!
- Really?
'Cause I can hear
your heartbeat,
and it's
pretty damn steady.
That's 'cause I'm --
I'm trying to remain calm.
Dean, look,
Samuel will know what to do.
Come on, man.
I'm a monster, okay?
This is not a problem
that you spitball.
We got to deal with this
before I hurt somebody.
This is...
How's it feel?
Now?
Now you want to talk
about my feelings?
I-I mean physically.
How do you think it feels?
Not good!
Where you going?
Bathroom, okay?
News flash, Mr. Wizard --
vampires pee.
Dean?
Dean.
Hey.
I wasn't expecting you
for a couple of days.
Yeah, yeah.
I wanted to see you.
What --
oh, God.
Are you okay?
Listen --
what's going on?
It doesn't matter.
But I need you to know --
you and Ben.
Just, uh...
Thanks. Okay?
For everything.
Dean,
you're scaring me.
Oh, God, I'm Pattinson.
What?
Nothing.
I-I-I got to go.
No. No, you can't just show up
here like this and then --
believe me, I wish it was different.
Just stop!
And explain to me what's
going on out there.
Lis, I can't bring this crap
home to you.
You're talking
about your work.
I'm talking about my life.
It's ugly.
And it's violent.
And I'm gonna die.
Soon.
Just tell me.
Just tell me what the hell
is going on.
Dean?
I got to go.
Ben, just stay there.
I thought
I heard you --
I said stay back!
You can't keep track
of your brother now?
Well...
I mean, I didn't think
he'd just --
he's not himself, Sam!
He's a monster,
and he's hungry.
I've got to prepare to do
the right thing.
I told you he'd kill me
when showed up.
Did you feed?
I went to say goodbye
to Lisa.
Which, for the record,
is a lousy idea.
Dean,
answer the question.
You can relax.
I didn't drink anyone.
Thank God.
But I came close.
All right.
Do it.
Okay. If you insist.
Or I can
just turn you back.
- What?
I didn't drive all this way
to kill you, Dean.
I'm here to save you.
That's my grandfather's
journal.
Cure's an old
Campbell recipe.
Kind of like the soup.
No one's tried it
since God knows.
From what I hear,
the stuff is a bad trip.
Awesome.
Hey, the cure is good.
But a lot of this is on you.
You drink, you're done.
It won't work.
I'm talking
one drop of human blood.
- I got it.
- Do you?
Because you will feed.
It's a matter of time.
What else do we need?
Some stuff we got,
some we got to get.
Trickiest thing
on the list --
blood of the fang
who turned you.
That guy was huge.
There's nothing in the recipe
about easy.
I can get it.
You're gonna walk
right into the nest?
Well, I'm one of them,
aren't I?
So all I got to do
is get in there,
get the guy alone,
and...
Shoot him with so much
dead man's blood
he'll think
he's rushing a fraternity.
I should
come with you.
No. Dude, you reek.
You're like
a walking hamburger.
I got to do this solo.
Yeah, except we haven't
been able to find him yet.
No problem.
I can smell them.
They're two miles
east of town.
You guys get the other crap
and meet me there.
Dean!
It's dead man's blood.
Now, there's enough there to
drop a linebacker and then some.
Good luck, son.
What the hell's
wrong with you, Sam?
What do you mean?
You knew
about the cure.
What?
No I didn't.
Thought we talked about it,
months ago.
Not me. It must have been
Christian or something.
Huh.
That's strange,
'cause if you had known,
it'd be almost like
you let him get turned.
Get a man on the inside,
help us find that Alpha vamp
we've been looking for?
You serious?
You think I'd do something
like that, risk my own brother?
What's wrong with you?
Look, I'm just relieved
we can fix him.
'Sup?
Hey. Uh, I'm --
the guy Boris turned
outside the bar, right?
He said
to look out for you.
Yeah.
Well,
glad you made it, man.
Oh.
Follow me.
So, you must be starving.
Uh...
Here you go.
I'm okay.
I killed so many people
on the way over here,
so...
Yeah, uh, about that.
Company line is we don't just
kill people anymore.
But you got to
tell me what that's like.
Yeah.
Yeah, first chance I get,
I'll -- I'll show you myself.
Sweet.
Don't worry about them.
They're jealous.
The recruiters
get to bang all the chicks.
That's you now, bro.
Recruiters?
Yeah.
Big man will explain.
Be with you
in a minute.
"Your skin is the black velvet
of the night."
Nice. That stupid bitch will
eat that up.
She'll be dying
to meet.
Go get yourself some blood,
sweetheart.
Then march that little ass
right back here, okay?
You.
Thank goodness.
I thought the hunter
chopped your pretty head.
No, I got away.
Sorry,
what's a hunter?
You'll see,
if he finds us.
You'll see him inside out.
You eaten?
Yeah.
Good.
You'll need
your strength.
For?
Robert didn't tell you?
How old do I look?
Uh, 33?
You're off.
By about...Six centuries.
And these are the best days
in the last 600 years
to be a vampire.
Dracula, Anne Rice?
Please.
These stupid little brats
are so horny,
they reinvented us
as prince charming with a Volvo.
They want a promise ring
with fangs.
So I give it to 'em.
You -- you go out,
you get them,
and you bring 'em
home to me.
So what's with
the cages?
Oh, that's just, you know,
till they're compliant.
Eventually,
these girls will go out,
and they'll fetch me
boys like you.
And around and around
we go.
I got to say,
I'm impressed.
This whole system,
that's -- that's all you?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, I just implement,
you know?
Make sure that you all
fall in line.
It's his.
Our father's.
Hmm. Your father's?
Aren't you
the curious one.
Oh, you don't
know the half of it.
Hmm.
In due time.
You, uh...
You want the private tour,
don't you?
Thought you'd never ask.
You playing games
with me, boy?
Father!
Go get him!
This must be the place.
Shh.
So much for undercover.
Let's go.
You've stopped nothing.
You know that?
This is much bigger
than you and me.
Looks like your brother has
some Campbell in him after all.
Dean, you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
If this works,
it's not gonna be a kiddie
ride. You know that.
That's great.
Light her up.
So what did you see
in there?
What?
In the nest.
What did you see?
Sam, I can't hear you.
Your -- your blood
is so freaking loud, okay?
Just -- just back off.
Give me the damn cure.
L'chaim.
I don't think it --
is it working?
Either that
or he's dying.
Hey.
So, what did you see?
What?
In the nest.
What did you see?
Um, well, I'm still
trying to work through it,
but, uh, I'm pretty sure
they're not figuring out
anything on their own.
They're getting their orders
from the top --
where to go next,
everything.
The top as in...
Their Alpha.
At least,
that's what I think it is.
They've got some sort
of psychic thing happening.
And he sends them, uh --
I don't know -- messages.
Saying what?
Honestly?
Recruitment drive.
Their Alpha's
building an army.
Well,
that's comforting.
That's not the worst.
Then what is?
We don't
scare them anymore.
You've reached Lisa.
Leave me a message.
Thanks.
Hey, Lis.
Um...
To continue recording,
press 1.
To erase --
How did it go with Lisa?
It didn't.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
At least, uh...
You got my back.
No matter what happens,
I can always count on you,
right, Sammy?
Yeah.
Of course, Dean.
-- sync by elderman  --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --