I know what I want.
But I can't have it --
not how you live.
I'm trying
to get over you.
Just 'cause
you love someone
doesn't mean you should stick
around and screw up their life.
You know you're walking out
on your family, right?
What do you know
about dragons?
Dr. Visyak.
Medieval studies, S.F.U.
Dr. Visyak:
Bobby Singer.
Tell him something for me
next time you see him.
Actually,
just kick him in the jewels.
- Raphael...
- Tomorrow you kneel, Castiel.
Are you proposing that I start
a civil war in heaven?
Ding! Ding! Ding!
- Balthazar.
- Of course I want to help you.
I mean, the amount of power
that it would take
to mount a war --
But what if I said
I knew how to go nuclear?
Purgatory.
You and Crowley have been
going after Purgatory together?
- Just kill the Winchesters.
- No.
Then I'll do it myself.
If you touch a hair
on their heads,
I will tear it all down --
our arrangement.
Hello, Dean.
You are
like a brother to me.
So, if I'm asking you
not to do something,
you got to trust me,
man.
Or what?
Or I'll have to do
what I have to do to stop you.
I'm sorry, Dean.
Hello?
Please...
We didn't know.
I'm sorry!
? Supernatural 6x21 ?
Let It Bleed
Original Air Date on May 20, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Well, you know what?
At least you tried.
Yeah, a fat lot
of good it did.
Why did he even come,
right?
Well, Samuel's journals
are pointless.
I mean, I'm sorry,
but, uh,
Jebediah Campbell
has squat to tell me
about how to stop Cass
from cracking Purgatory.
Well, actually, it's not about
the journals we have.
It's about
the one we don't.
Meaning what?
Well, that's
the bad news.
Our pal Cass didn't stop in
last night just to mend fences.
What did he do?
- Stole something.
- What?
The journal
of one Moishe Campbell.
"Moishe"?
Of the New York
Campbells.
Uh, so we got to
get it back, right?
Or just read the copy
I had already made.
Hi. Glad to meet you.
Bobby Singer, paranoid bastard.
I think I zeroed in
on something.
What do you got?
"Went to talk
to Howard Phillips
about the events
of March 10th."
That's March 10, 1937.
All right, so,
who's this Phillips guy?
Phillips ain't his last name.
It's Lovecraft.
Wait -- H.P. Lovecraft?
Let me see that.
Am I supposed to know
who that is?
Horror writer?
"At the mountains
of madness,"
"the call of Cthulhu."
Yeah.
No, I'm -- I was too busy
having sex with women.
Well, anyhow,
there's one notion that comes up
over and over again
in his stories --
namely, opening doors
to other dimensions
and letting
scary crap through.
You don't say.
Wait, so you're saying
you think
Lovecraft knew something
about Purgatory?
All I know is,
Moishe paid him a visit.
? You must be livin'
with a four-leaf clover ?
? the number 7 running
all the way through you ?
Mnh!
Oh! No!
Just --
just let her go.
Okay, just --
aah!
No!
Ben?
- There's men in the house.
- What?
They killed Matt.
They got mom.
They're coming.
I hear them.
- What are they?
- I-I don't know.
- Did you see their eyes?
- No.
- Teeth?
This is important, Ben.
I need to know.
Dean, I don't know.
- Ben, where are you now?
- In my room.
Can you get to your mom's closet?
I left a shotgun in there.
No! Dean, what do I do?
Okay, Ben, listen to me.
Go to your window...
And jump.
- What?!
- Any bones you break
won't compare to what
they're gonna do to you, Ben.
- You've got to jump.
- Okay, I'm going.
I'm coming right now.
I'm gonna get you and your mom,
I promise.
You with me, Ben?
Ben?
Ben!
Hello, Dean.
Fancy a chat?
God, how long's it been
since my so-called
demise, yes?
Crowley,
let them go now.
Or I swear --
Right, right.
You'll rip me
a cornucopia of orifices.
Let's get to the bit
where I tell you how this goes.
Your chocolate's been in my
peanut butter for far too long.
I'm going to kill you.
Oh, Dean.
Ever the wit.
I've got your --
what are they? --
Ex-ladyfriend
and not-kid,
and I'm keeping them
until I'm satisfied
that you've backed
the hell off.
I'm telling you --
last chance to let 'em go easy.
You're adorable
when you get all threatening.
Don't worry --
I won't hurt them,
provided you and Jolly Green
stand down.
Got it? Splendid.
Kisses.
What's the story?
He said Lisa and Ben
keep breathing...
As long as we
sit on our thumbs.
You think
Cass knows about this?
We got to assume
he does.
So what are we
gonna do?
I'll tell you
what we're not gonna do --
sit here.
- I'm going after 'em.
- I'm coming with.
No, Sam.
You and Bobby stay
on the Lovecraft thing, okay?
Cass is already
way ahead of us.
You got to be nuts if you think
I'm gonna let you do this alone.
Bobby can
take care of the case.
- No, guys.
- Bobby...
This is a big ball. Okay?
We can't drop it now.
Fine.
Then how are you two
gonna find Lisa and Ben?
I'm sorry, boys.
Do I look like
a manservant to you?
No? No? Then quit
ringing for me. Please.
This is important,
Balthazar.
I was drinking a '75 Dom
out of a soprano's navel
when you called.
That was important.
Crowley's alive.
Well,
you've been scooped.
Cass already told me.
Well, did Cass tell you
that he is Crowley's butt buddy,
you smug little dick?
Excuse me?
Handshake deal.
Go halfsies
on all the souls of Purgatory --
He fill you in
on that?
Well, yes, yes.
Yes, of course he did. Yes.
Oh, yes, of course.
I -- I --
We can read it
all over your face.
Crowley and Cass took two people
who are very important to me.
And I care about this
because...
Because maybe
there is a shred of decency
underneath this --
this snarky crap.
They're innocent people,
and I'm asking
for your help.
Hmm.
I see.
Fair enough.
Son of a bitch!
Look, Dean,
let's just call Cass.
Maybe he doesn't know
anything about --
We are not calling Cass.
- Yeah, but, Dean --
- We're not calling Cass!
So what, then?
You know, uh, horror --
lowbrow.
Put us
in the ghetto, fine.
But H.P. Lovecraft --
this guy is literature.
I mean, he -- he should be
taught in schools.
He's up there with Dickens
and...Dean R. Koontz.
Seriously.
Well, that's --
that's definitely
the angle I'm taking
with my piece.
Oh, okay. Okay.
Sorry. You can --
please, please.
So, I hear you have
a large collection
of Lovecraft's
private letters.
Yeah.
World's largest.
Wow.
You must be
catnip to the ladies.
I'm in a long-term
online relationship, so...
Well, I'd like to ask you
about Lovecraft's last years --
specifically anything
that might have gone down
around March 10, 1937.
Okay.
A-are you working on this
with the other guy?
Other guy?
Yeah, uh, you know,
trenchcoat, looks like Columbo,
talks like Rain Man?
Right.
W-we're...
Competitors.
Rival magazines.
Okay.
Okay, well, um,
I'll tell you what I told him.
Howard had a dinner party
on March 10th.
Party?
How many friends
at this party?
Well, six --
if by "friends" you mean
co-worshippers
in a black-magic cult.
They were getting together
that night to perform a ritual.
Something big.
Define "big."
Not much. Just open a door
into another dimension.
Why would they do that?!
To see what's out there --
you know, maybe it's friendly.
It's never friendly!
I mean...I imagine.
So, did it work --
the spell?
Well, uh, there was
no mention of Cthulhu
in the morning
papers, so...
Actually,
I do happen to have
several letters
detailing the dinner.
Worst thing that was reported
was a hangover,
so it's, uh...
- Got it --
- I've got them right here.
Some -- it's actually
pretty interesting.
Um, and --
and they were...
They were --
they were right th--
they were right here.
Well, it's not like
an invisible guy
could just pop in
and steal 'em, right?
Right. Right.
- Oh, uh,
- I'll leave you to it,
and, uh, you call me
if you find 'em, huh?
Okay, hey...
Thanks.
Thanks again
for dropping by, huh?
Lovecraft tried to Jimmy
a damn dimensional door.
Idjit.
So, what happened?
Oh, nothing much...
Except I dug.
And every guest
invited to the hoedown --
dead or disappeared
inside a year.
Wow. Um, so,
where are you off to now?
Have a chat
with one of the guests.
Wait, didn't you just say
that everyone there died?
Yeah, everybody
Lovecraft invited died.
Seems the maid
had a 9-year-old boy.
He was there.
So he'd be, what,
83 years old now? Where is he?
Same place he's been
ever since the big night --
locked in a mental ward.
I see.
Um...Well,
keep me posted, huh?
Okay. Stay in touch.
How's things
going there?
You got a lead
on Lisa and Ben?
Well, we're making
a few inquiries.
Slow going.
How's Dean?
About how you'd expect.
Next customer.
Look, I don't know
anything.
Yeah, we'll see.
Dean?
Yeah?
Look, man, y-you're
running on, what, uh,
whiskey and coffee and whatever
else you're taking.
Yeah, and?
And we're grasping
at straws here, man.
Look, I kill enough
of these demons,
eventually one of them's
gonna tell me where Crowley is.
So, we good?
Well, look, you've been at it
for a while.
Why don't you at least
let me take over?
- You deserve a break.
- No, thanks.
- Dean --
- Sam, back off.
Lisa and Ben --
wherever they are,
that is 100% on me.
And if they are hurt...
I'll yell
if I need you.
Castiel, it's Sam.
Um...
So, look, I don't know if you're
in on this whole Ben/Lisa thing,
but if you have
any heart whatsoever,
bring them back to us, man.
Come on.
Please.
I'm begging you.
I am begging you.
Do you understand?
? Smiling faces sometimes ?
Sweetie...
You look tense.
You took Ben and Lisa.
Oh. That.
I told you --
Not to touch
Sam and Dean.
I've respected that.
I'm merely exploiting
the obvious loophole.
As long as I have
the woman and the boy,
your fop-coiffed
little heroes
will be scouring
the Earth for them --
therefore,
not you and not me.
Everybody wins.
You should have
talked to me first.
I'd rather ask forgiveness
than permission.
Where are they, Crowley?
You are not to harm them.
Do you understand me?
You know what?
You're maxed out
on putting humans out of bounds.
I'll do with them
as I please.
You want to stop me?
Go find
friggin' Purgatory!
Call on the bat phone?
Never call during
business hours, do they?
I'll be back.
Cass, Cass, Cass.
So good of you to come.
Balthazar,
why'd you summon me here?
Can I ask you
a direct question?
Of course.
Are you in flagrante
with the King of Hades?
Of course not.
Always were
such a terrible liar.
So it's true.
All right, then.
Why?
It's a means to an end.
Balthazar,
you understand that.
Oh, absolutely.
What's the end here,
exactly?
You know, raid Purgatory, snatch
up all the souls? Win the war.
And I can only assume that
you'd be the vessel, correct?
Suck up all those souls
into yourself -- all that power.
It's the only way.
Or too much juice for you,
in which case you explode,
taking a substantial chunk
of the planet along with you.
- That won't happen.
- Sure, sure.
Of course.
Just...
Just tell me
that it's entirely risk-free.
I'm sorry that I didn't
tell you, but I need to know.
Are you with me or not?
You know, you may be
certifiable, but...
Fine.
In for a penny...
In for a pound.
How'd you hear
about this, anyway?
Oh, your howler monkeys,
of course.
See, they're
just a touch worked up
about that kidnapping
business, you know.
Woman on P.A. System:
Paging Dr. Bender.
You're sure you're not
with that other reporter?
In the coat?
Liar, that one --
not who he says.
No, sir.
Uh, I'm not...
Affiliated
with his paper.
I just have
a couple of questions
about a dinner party
you were at in 1937.
Everyone's so fascinated.
Want to know
about my night
at the home
of the great H.P. Lovecraft?
If you don't mind.
Well, you know the story.
They did their spell,
and they all said it failed.
Do you believe in
monsters?
Yup.
You know,
you go saying that,
they'll lock you in here
rest of your life.
Whatever you saw...
you tell me,
and I'll buy it straight.
The spell worked.
A door opened,
and something came through.
B-but it was invisible,
so no one knew.
Except me.
How did you know, then?
Because it took my mother!
It went into her.
She wasn't the same.
She even smelled different.
And then
she disappeared.
And --
surprise, surprise --
one by one,
they all start dying.
I'm sorry...
About your mom.
You're the first person
ever said that.
Hey. You want to see
a picture?
Hmm?
I'll be damned.
I promise you, pal...
You start talking...
...or I swear
I will rip your skin off,
strip by strip.
And then I'm gonna kill you.
And then I'm gonna
do it to the next demon.
You hear me?
Yeah.
I hear you.
So you can stop talking,
you miserable sack.
Agh!
I didn't
ask for your help.
Well, regardless,
you're welcome.
Why are you here?
I had no idea Crowley
would take Lisa and Ben.
Yeah, right.
You don't believe me.
I don't believe a word
that's coming out of your mouth.
I thought you said
that we were like family.
Well, I think that, too.
Shouldn't trust run both ways?
Cass, I just can't.
Dean, I do
everything that you ask.
I always
come when you call.
And I am your friend.
Still, despite
your lack of faith in me
and now your threats...
...I just saved you,
yet again.
Has anyone but your closest kin
has ever done more for you?
All I ask
is this one thing.
- Trust your plan to pop Purgatory?
- I've earned that, Dean.
I came to tell you
that I will find Lisa and Ben.
And I will
bring them back.
Stand behind me...
The one time I ask.
You're asking me
to stand down?
Dean --
That's the same
damn ransom note
that Crowley handed me.
You know that, right?
Well, no, thanks.
I'll find them myself.
In fact, why don't you
go back to Crowley
and tell him that I said
you can both kiss my ass?
Bobby?
Ellie.
It's been a while.
Come in.
So, how did you find me?
Well, we weren't together long,
Ellie, but, uh,
I know a thing or two
about you.
I know your safehouses.
And let me tell you --
this one ain't all that safe.
So, did you come here
just to, um, chat?
I know what you are,
Ellie.
You're not exactly
from Milwaukee, are you?
Not exactly.
And -- not that
I'd have minded,
but you kind of fibbed
about your age, too.
Just slightly.
900 years.
Okay, so,
what's your game, then?
Game?
Yeah.
Why are you here?
Eve came through and raised
all kinds of hell quickly.
You been here how long?
What's with the slow burn?
- Well, you know, we're not all alike.
- Monsters?
Okay, if it makes you feel
better to call me that, fine.
You're from
freakin' Purgatory.
You never
thought to mention that
the whole time
you slept with me?
I am what I am, Bobby.
And I happen to be
a friend.
You want to explain
that to me?
I didn't ask those idiots
to crack the door.
I just happened to be
the thing that fell through.
And let me tell you something --
you are lucky it was me.
You're saying
you're on our side?
I'm on my side.
I happen to like it here.
I don't want to see
this place
turned into
some bloody wasteland.
So you killed
H.P. Lovecraft.
Please. That guy
couldn't even write "hello."
I have spent 75 years
trying to keep Purgatory closed.
Why do you think
I gave Dean the sword?
To stop Eve.
Hell, you guys were supposed
to kill the damn dragons!
Look.
This all comes down
to one Angel.
He wants Purgatory,
and he's looking for you.
Well, thanks
for the heads up.
I know him, El.
He's gonna figure it out
one way or another.
Now, the only way I can stop him
is to get ahead of him.
So I need to know
how you open the door.
No.
No, Bobby. It's too dangerous
for anyone to know.
If I found you...
He ain't far behind.
At least
let me take you somewhere,
protect you.
No.
Thanks.
I have a couple other places
lined up. Don't worry.
Bobby.
You're just a man.
I'm better off
protecting myself.
Drinking
your feelings, Sam?
I thought that was
your brother's bag.
Stressful times.
Well, we need to talk.
Why?
Because --
I know I'm gonna live
to regret this, but...
I'm officially
on your team.
You bastards.
And we should
believe you why?
Would you believe I had
a shred of decency?
No.
Oh, that hurts.
Okay, you're right.
It's survival.
You see,
I asked Cass some questions,
and I disliked
his answers.
He seems
awfully sure of himself
for a man who wants to swallow
a million nuclear reactors.
I mean, these things can get
a bit Chernobyl, you know.
So, voil?.
Consider me
your double agent.
Oh, and I took the liberty
of searching for your friends.
Took a while --
Crowley's a clever one.
You found them?
The upside is yes.
The downside is,
no, I can't get them for you.
Why not?
Because Crowley's
Angel-proofed
the whole
bloody building.
I guess
he doesn't trust Cass.
Seems that marriage
is going swimmingly.
Okay, well,
get us as close as you can.
Sure.
But then
you're on your own.
All right, boys,
this is where I get off.
God be with you...
Or what have you.
All right, be careful.
Oh, Dean. Thank God.
Still got to
get you out of here.
Okay.
Let's go.
The brat's
not going anywhere.
And neither am I.
Crowley thought
you might come.
So he had me jump
this hot little piece of ass
for insurance.
Can't go losing our leverage,
now, can we?
Ah! Another step...
...Free appendectomy.
You know, she's awake
in here -- your mom.
I can hear her
thinking.
- Don't listen to her, Ben.
- What?
I was just gonna tell him
that you're his real daddy.
Just kidding.
Who knows
who your real dad is, kid?
Your mom's a slut.
You shut your mouth!
Oh, what?
You're her white knight now?
She wishes
she never met you, Dean.
You're the worst mistake
she ever made!
Well, second worst...
After keeping you.
That's not your mom, Ben.
She's lying.
Says the C-minus lay
with 10 miles of mommy issues.
Whatever gets you through
the night, Tiny Tim.
Ah-ah-ah.
Back off, cowboy.
You know,
she's begging me to kill you.
She says
you hold her back.
Never had a lick of fun
since you were born.
Ben, look at me.
Look at me.
You're gonna be
just fine.
Aah!
Ben, knife!
What's the matter, Dean?
Hit me.
Oh, you don't want to hurt
poor Lisa?
Exorcizamus te,
omnis immundus spiritus --
Shut your mouth!
Omnis satanica potestas,
omnis incursio
infernalis adversii,
omnis congregatio
et secta diabolica,
ergo, Draco maledicte --
ecclesiam...
Stop it.
...Tuam...
I'm warning you.
You can go to hell,
you black-eyed bitch.
You sure about that?
Mom!
Exorcise me now...
She's just
a dead meatsuit.
Now, what was it
you wanted to say?
Secura...
Tibi...
Facias libertate...
...Servire...
Te rogamus...
Audi nos.
- Mom!
- Lisa!
Lisa.
Here, put pressure
on that, okay?
I know, honey. I know.
It's all right, it's all right,
it's all right.
It's Sam.
Leave me a message.
Sam, where are you,
damn it?!
All right, Ben. We got to
get her out of here, okay?
Ben.
Ben?
Hey!
Listen, man, I need you
to pull it together, okay?
You got to be strong.
Your mom needs you right now.
Go over in that duffel bag.
Grab the salt gun.
I got to carry
your mom out,
so if anything comes at us,
you shoot it.
But --
go. Now.
Okay. Get the knife.
Get the knife.
All right, Ben.
Keep your elbow in,
gun tight to your shoulder,
and watch for the kick.
Ben!
Ben.
- Ben!
- Dean.
Come on!
Pull it together!
You want your mom to die?!
Let's go.
Come on.
Dean!
Sam?
In here!
Come on. We got to get
to a hospital.
Here.
Give the gun to him.
Sam, we need a ride.
Yeah.
Go, go, go, go.
She's fine, Ben.
She's fine.
She's gonna be just fine.
We're almost there.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Stay with me.
Sam, you got to go
faster, man.
You're gonna be fine.
You're gonna be just fine.
Ben, I'm sorry.
Ben.
What do you want?
Dean, listen.
What do you want
me to say?
She'll be dead
by midnight.
I'm sorry.
I don't care.
It's too little,
too late.
Okay.
Well, regardless,
I didn't come for you.
Meaning?
She's fine now.
She'll wake soon.
Dean, I said I'm sorry,
and I meant it.
Thank you.
I wish this changed
anything.
I know.
So do I.
All else aside, I just wanted
to fix what I could.
There's one more thing
you could do for me.
Hey, mom.
Hey.
What --
You're in the hospital.
- What happened?
- We were in a car crash.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm -- I'm fine.
You hit your head
pretty bad,
but you're okay now.
Hi.
Who are you?
I-I'm Dean.
Um...
I'm the guy who hit you.
Oh.
I just, uh...
I lost control for a minute.
And I just wanted to say
that I'm sorry.
But I'm real happy
you two are both okay.
And, uh...
...I'm just -- I'm glad your
life can get back to normal now.
We're okay, so...
So that's
what's important, right?
Yeah.
Anyway, uh...
I'll leave you two alone.
You take care
of your mom.
Well?
Well, nothing.
Dean, you know, you have pulled
some shady crap before,
but this has got to be
the worst.
Whitewashing
their memories?
Take it from somebody
who knows --
if you ever mention
Lisa or Ben to me again,
I will break your nose.
Dean --
I'm not kidding.
Sam!
? Carry on, my wayward son ?
You got to promise
not to try to bring me back.
? There'll be peace
when you are done ?
? lay your weary head to rest ?
Sammy?
? Don't you cry no more ?
You're a hunter. Now you know
your brother's out there.
I need you to go.
It's Sam.
He's different.
It's his soul.
It's gone.
I'm going to go to hell
to fetch your brother's soul.
I don't remember anything.
? Once I rose
above the noise and confusion ?
? just to get a glimpse
beyond this illusion ?
? I was soaring ever higher ?
Finding Purgatory's
important to me --
an untapped oil well
of every fanged, clawed soul.
Do you have any idea
what souls are worth?
What power they hold?
Raphael
and his followers,
they want him
to rule heaven.
The last thing we want
is to let him take over.
That little limey mook
roasted months ago.
Crowley's alive.
I want to discuss
a simple business transaction.
With me?
You and Crowley have been
going after Purgatory together?
I can stop Raphael.
You have to trust me.
? Don't you cry no more ?
We're closed.
Just, uh --
just give me a second.
Sorry, pal.
We -- we open at noon.
Look,
you don't understand.
Okay, I-I think
I understand...just fine.
Look, I-I don't need
this kind of hassle,
so, seriously,
just get the hell out.
Please. Please, just give me
a minute to think, that's all.
Then I'm out of your hair.
One minute, please.
What's your name?
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
I mean I don't remember.
I don't remember anything.
? Supernatural 6x22 ?
The Man Who Knew Too Much
Original Air Date on May 20, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Come on.
You're dickin' with me.
Nothing?
I'm telling you --
blank slate.
Well, you got
a wallet, I.D.?
I wish I did.
Okay, what's the last thing
you remember?
Um...
I woke up on a park bench,
cops shoving a flashlight in
my face, trying to take me in.
- So you ran.
- No, I, um --
I knocked them out cold,
both of them.
No, look,
I didn't mean to.
It just happened really fast,
you know?
I-I think I-instinct
or something, I guess.
Some instinct.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I mean, who even knows
how to do something like that?
We'll get you to the E.R. the --
the quacks will hash it out.
No.
Try "yeah."
Look, the bats
have flown the belfry.
- You need to see a doctor.
- No, I...
I don't have time.
Time for what?
Look, it's hard to explain.
I just feel like
I-I have to...be somewhere.
There's s-something
I got to stop.
Oh, like a wedding?
A train?
No, something important,
something like...
- Life or death, like --
- Hey, hey, hey.
Just relax.
Y-you can't poop it out.
So, just -- it'll come to you.
What is it?
You a horror fan?
Yeah, um, I think so.
You know,
I really think so.
Something --
something about this.
Phillips ain't
his last name. It's Lovecraft.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Seriously,
we are taking you to a doctor.
Have you got a computer?
What?
That's it. It exists.
Look -- two towns over.
- You think you're staying in this dump?
- Maybe.
Maybe you're a hooker.
I guess I'll find out.
Look, um...
I don't know how to say, uh --
thanks for everything.
Where do you think
you're going?
I'll be fine.
Says the head case that
just slumped over a minute ago.
Look, is there any way I can
convince you to go to a hospital?
No.
Apparently, I'm stubborn.
Well...
So am I.
I'm driving.
Look, that's really nice of you
but not necessary.
Really? Okay, look,
your eggs are scrambled.
But --
But nothing.
No, I mean,
I'm -- I'm just some guy.
I-I could be anybody.
You got to be nuts.
I've been called that.
Look, if I let you
go off alone,
I won't be able to sleep
at night.
And, honestly, I'm dying to know
how it all turns out.
So, uh,
where do we start?
Uh, ground floor,
corner room...
nearest
to the fire escape.
That's the one I'd pick --
quickest getaway.
And why do you know that?
I just do.
Hey, you got
a credit card?
Uh...
Why?
Are we, uh, checking in?
Sort of.
Dude...
Who are you?
Good question.
This all yours?
I don't know.
I guess.
Well, I love what you've done
with the place.
It's very "Beautiful Mind"
meets..."Se7en."
Sorry.
I talk when I'm nervous.
Hey, well,
I guess we know your name.
Nice to meet you,
Jimmy Page.
And, uh, Neil Peart.
And Angus Young.
Okay, listen, no offense,
but I'm...really starting
to freak out.
You and me both.
Where is she?
She said to
meet her here.
I'll try her again.
- Elle?
- Hey.
I guess I could have used
your help after all.
Just be still.
- What happened?
- They took me.
I got away.
Oh, Ellie.
Oh, what have they done
to you?
Everything.
The demon I could have handled,
you know?
But when
the Angel stepped in...
I told him, Bobby.
They have enough
to crack Purgatory wide open.
Tell me.
I need to know.
They need virgin blood.
That's a milk run for them.
And they need the blood
of a Purgatory native.
Well, they've got
plenty of that now.
Have they opened it
yet?
Mnh-mnh. Tomorrow.
The moon
and the eclipse.
I'm sorry, Bobby.
- No, it's okay.
- I'm sorry, really.
Just tell us
where they are.
Elle?
I'm sorry
this had to happen.
Crowley got carried away.
Yeah, I bet it was all Crowley,
you son of a bitch!
You don't even see it,
do you?
How totally off the rails
you are.
Enough!
I don't care
what you think.
I've tried to make you
understand. You won't listen.
So let me make this
simple.
Please go home
and let me stop Raphael.
I won't ask again.
Well, good, 'cause I think
you already know the answer.
I wish
it hadn't come to this.
Well, rest assured,
when this is all over...
I will save Sam,
but only
if you stand down.
Save Sam from what?
Hey, hey.
Are you okay?
Sam.
My name is Sam.
So, uh,
what do you remember?
Well
It might sound pretty strange
if I said it aloud.
Oh, it -- it couldn't get
any stranger.
Yeah?
Don't be so sure.
Look, I-I don't know.
I mean, it's all pretty spotty,
you know?
I just remember I was --
I was with, uh -- with two guys.
One was, like,
a male-model type,
and the other was
an older guy named, uh...
Bobby.
Okay. Well,
what are you looking for?
Here. Bobby Singer.
That has to be it.
Is there a phone number?
No, just an address.
Sioux Falls, South Dakota.
South Dakota.
Okay, uh...
L-listen, Sam --
- Sam, right?
- Yeah.
Look, I'm really sorry,
but this is --
is where I got to get off.
Oh, no. Of course.
No problem.
Okay. Well, how are you
gonna get there?
I guess
I'll take my car.
That's mine.
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah.
Look, Sam,
I don't feel right
about you going off like this.
Oh, look, don't worry.
Y-you've done way too much
for me already.
That's not what I mean.
What I mean is, uh...
I've got a bad feeling,
you know,
with those I.D.s
and that shady-ass hotel room.
Whatever
you're looking for --
you might not like
what you find.
What other choice
do I have?
You could stick around here
a little bit longer,
get your head straight,
instead of going off,
flying blind into --
What the hell was that?!
Stay down.
Sam!
Sammy. Sammy?!
Sammy?
Come on.
Snap out of it.
? Well, you've got
your diamonds ?
? and you've got your... ?
Anything?
I can't just sit here, Bobby.
I've got to help him.
Dean.
You know, "Dreamscape"
his noggin -- something.
You know what Cass did.
The dam inside
your brother's head is gone,
and all hell's
spilling loose.
- We don't know what's going on inside.
- I don't care.
- We have got to do something!
- And we will.
But right now, we got 16 hours
till they pop Purgatory.
I'm down one man.
I can't afford
to be down two.
Yeah, and how's that going, huh?
We've got no line on Crowley.
We got no line on Cass.
Balthazar's M.I.A.
I mean, all we've got
is Sam going through
whatever the hell this is!
You know...
...this is exactly
what Cass wants --
for you
to fall to pieces.
? ...Playing with fire ?
Just try to think
of what Sam would want.
Find Cass, Bobby.
Find him now.
? Old man took her diamonds ?
? and tiaras by the score ?
? now she gets her kicks
in stepney... ?
Do you smell whiskey?
Okay, Sam,
would you focus?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Okay, so, who shot at us?
? ...'Cause you're playing with fire... ?
I-I didn't really get a good look.
Okay, we got to go
to the cops.
No. Look, if we can just get
to my friends,
they can help us --
I know it.
Okay, you don't know
if they're your friends, okay?
You don't know anything
about anything.
- Just turn around.
- No.
- Look, you're safer with me.
- How do you know that?
You're scaring me.
? ...Mother ?
? so don't play with me ?
? 'cause you're playing
with fire ?
? so don't play with me ?
? 'cause you're playing
with fire ?
What? No way.
What was that?
What do you mean?
It's daylight.
Yeah?
It was night,
and now it's day.
It was always day.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, it wasn't. It --
what the hell
is going on here?
Okay, so I am all filled up
on crazy for today.
You know what, Sam?
I'll -- I'll see you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hey, hey, hey.
Get in the car.
Wow.
My God.
Am I
really that gawky?
Howdy.
This is impossible.
Cold. Try again.
I'm, uh --
I'm hallucinating.
Warmer.
But see, normally,
you're awake
when you're tripping balls.
I'm dreaming?
And someone just won a copy
of the home game.
We're inside
your grapefruit, Sam.
Son...
You've been juiced.
I-I-I don't remember
anything.
Well, your B.F.F. Cass brought
the hell wall tumbling down,
and you, pathetic infant
that you are,
shattered into pieces.
Piece...Piece.
I-I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Why would you?
You're jello, pal,
unlike me.
What are you?
I'm not handicapped.
I'm not saddled
with a soul.
In fact, I used to skipper
this meatboat for a while.
It was smooth sailing.
I was sharp, strong.
That is, till they crammed
your soul back in.
Now look at you.
Same misty-eyed milksop
you always were.
That's because
souls are weak.
They're a liability.
Now, nothing personal,
but run the numbers.
Someone's got to take charge
around here
before it's too late.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
You think I'm bad?
Wait till you meet
the other one.
Hey! Sam!
I remember who I am --
everything I did
this past year.
And I remember you.
Walk away,
or the girl dies.
There goes your leverage.
Didn't I tell you
to turn back,
that you wouldn't like
what you found?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Not as sorry
as you're gonna be.
Look what the cat
dragged in.
Well,
at least you mudfish
finally got
the angel-proofing right.
How's sleeping beauty?
You didn't steal any kisses,
I trust?
What the hell
took you so long?
Honestly?
I was having
second thoughts.
About?
About
whether to help you.
I was thinking maybe --
maybe I should rip out
your sticky bits instead.
And what
did you decide?
Well...
...Cass and Crowley
are there.
That's where
the show gets started.
All right, well, give us a minute
to pack up and then zap us there.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I don't think so.
Balthazar.
I'm betraying
a friend here --
a very powerful friend.
We all are.
So I think I've stuck
my neck out far enough already.
Good luck.
Your Purgatory
power shake, monsieur --
half monster,
half virgin.
Thank you.
You seem even more constipated
than usual.
Maybe get you
some colon blow?
I'm renegotiating
our terms.
Is that so?
What terms do you propose?
You get nothing.
Not one single soul.
Can't help notice --
seems a bit...
unfairly weighted.
Castiel...
you wouldn't dare.
I brought you
this deal.
You think I'm handing
all that power...
to the King of Hell?
I'm neither
stupid nor wicked.
Unbelievable.
Have you forgotten that you're
the bottom in this relationship?
Here are your options.
You either flee,
or you die.
We made a pact.
Even I don't break contracts
like this.
Flee...
or die.
Boy, you can't trust anyone
these days.
Hey.
Hey!
Oh.
Hi, Sam.
So?
Which one are you?
Don't you know?
I'm the one
that remembers Hell.
Time's up, Dean.
Just a second.
All right, this is
where we're gonna be, Sam.
So you get your lazy ass
out of bed and come meet us.
Sammy, please.
I wish you hadn't come,
Sam.
I had to.
I'm here, right?
Out there in the real world,
I'm at Bobby's, aren't I?
How do you know?
This whole time,
I smell nothing
but old spice and whiskey.
I figured
if I could get back here,
back to my body,
I could...
I don't know --
I could snap out of it somehow.
First, you have to
go through me.
Why?
Humpty-dumpty has to put himself
back together again
before he can wake up.
And I'm the last piece.
Which means...
...I have to know
what you know...
...What happened in the cage.
Trust me.
You don't
want to know it.
You're right.
But I still have to.
Sam...
you can't imagine.
Stay here, go back,
find that bartender,
go find Jess, but don't do this.
I know you.
You're not strong enough.
We'll just have to see.
Why is this so important
to you?
You know me.
You know why.
I'm not leaving my brother alone
out there.
I'm not gonna fight you.
But this
is your last chance.
Good luck.
You're gonna need it.
You rang, Cass?
Yeah.
We have a problem.
Dean Winchester
is on his way here.
Really? Oh. How'd he even
know where we were?
Apparently...
We have a Judas in our midst.
Ah.
Holy hell.
Who is it?
I bet it's that
bloody little cherub, isn't it?
I don't know.
But I-I need you
to find out.
Of course.
Um, right away, right away.
Uh, but what do you
want me to do about Dean?
Nothing.
I'll handle him myself.
Castiel?
Are you all right?
First Sam and Dean,
and now this.
I'm doing my best
in impossible circumstances.
My friends -- they...
abandon me...
plot against me.
It's difficult
to understand.
Well, you --
you always got little old me.
Yes.
I'll always have you.
Cass...
I count a dozen mooks,
probably more.
Demons?
Angels.
Well, how the hell are we
gonna take out that many Angels?
We don't.
We'll ninja our way in.
Awesome, yeah --
till they hear your knee squeak.
Shut up.
Oh, what,
now you got thin skin?
No, shut up.
You hear that?
What the hell is that?
T. Rex, maybe?
Holy mother of...
Get to the car.
Never underestimate
the King of Hell, darling.
I know
a lot of swell tricks.
Now, I think it's time
to re-renegotiate our terms.
Sweaty hands, mate.
I don't understand.
You can palm me
all you want.
I'm safe and sound under
the wing of my new partner.
Hello, Castiel.
Raphael.
Consorting with Demons.
I thought that was beneath you?
Heard you were doing it.
Sounded like fun.
You know, Castiel,
y-you said all sorts
of shameful,
appalling, scatological
things about Raphael.
I found him -- her --
to be really...
quite reasonable.
You fool.
Raphael will deceive and destroy
you at the speed of thought.
Right, right, 'cause
you're such a straight shooter.
She -- he --
has offered me protection
against all comers.
In exchange for what?
The Purgatory blood.
Castiel, you really think
I would let you open that door?
Take in
that much power?
If anyone is going to be
the new God, it's me.
He's gonna bring
the Apocalypse and worse.
Hey, this is your doing,
mate.
I'm merely grabbing
the best offer on the table.
Now,
you have two options.
Flee or die.
Ianua magna purgatorii,
clausa est ob nos,
lumine eius
ab oculis nostris retento.
Bobby.
Bobby?
Huh?
Come on.
We got to go.
Sed nunc stamus
ad limen huius ianuae magnae
et demisse, fideliter,
perhonorifice,
paramus aperire eam.
Creaturae terrificae,
quarum ungulae et dentes,
nunquam tetigerunt
carnem humanam.
Bit busy, gentlemen.
Be with you in a moment.
Aperit fauces
eius ad mundum nostrum, nunc,
ianua magna aperta tandem!
Mm-hmm.
Maybe I said it wrong.
You said it perfectly.
But what you needed
was this.
I see.
And we've
been working with...
Dog blood.
Naturally.
Enough
of these games, Castiel.
Give us the blood.
You --
game's over.
His jar's empty.
So, Castiel,
how'd your ritual go?
Better than ours,
I'll bet.
You can't imagine
what it's like.
They're all inside me --
millions
upon millions of souls.
Sounds sexy.
Exit stage Crowley.
Now, what's the matter,
Raphael?
Somebody clip your wings?
Castiel, please.
You let the Demon go...
but not your own brother?
The Demon I have plans for.
You, on the other hand...
So, you see...
I saved you.
You sure did, Cass.
Thank you.
You doubted me...
fought against me.
But I was right
all along.
Okay, Cass, you were.
We're sorry.
Let's just defuse you,
okay?
What do you mean?
You're full of nuke.
It's not safe.
So before the eclipse ends,
let's get them souls
back to where they belong.
Oh, no.
They belong with me.
No, Cass, I-it's
scrambling your brain.
No, I'm not finished yet.
Raphael had many followers,
and I must...
Punish them all severely.
Listen to me.
Listen...
I know there's a lot
of bad water under the bridge.
But we were family once.
I'd have died for you.
I almost did a few times.
So if that means anything
to you...
Please.
I've lost Lisa,
I've lost Ben,
and now I've lost Sam.
Don't make me lose you,
too.
You don't need this kind
of juice anymore, Cass.
Get rid of it
before it kills us all.
You're just saying that
because I won...
Because you're afraid.
You're not my family,
Dean.
I have no family.
I'm glad you made it, Sam.
But the Angel blade
won't work,
because I'm not an Angel
anymore.
I'm your new God.
A better one.
So you will bow down
and profess your love unto me,
your Lord...
...or I shall destroy you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==