Death...
he's gonna be there.
I understand you want this.
There are conditions.
You know
you can't cheat death.
I don't think
it's killing people.
I think it's taking them
when their time is just up.
A reaper.
You're much prettier
than the last reaper I met.
So, this is the reaper
that came after you.
- Dean.
- Tessa.
- Balthazar.
- Why you buying up human souls?
Do you have any idea
what souls are worth?
What power they hold?
Just making sure that you're not
having second thoughts
about getting your soul back.
Sam's soul has been
locked in the cage
with Michael and Lucifer.
If we try to force
that mutilated thing
down Sam's gullet,
it could be catastrophic.
He needs his soul.
Look, we get it back.
And if there are complications,
then we will figure out a way
to deal with those, too.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
Hi, I'm, uh, looking for...
Follow all the way back.
All the way back.
Dean Winchester?
You must be Dr. Robert?
Son, I stitched up your daddy
more times than I can count,
let me tell you.
Oh, it's good to see you.
'Course, that was ages ago,
back when, uh, I still
had my medical license.
Right this way.
Well, you know, I'm, uh,
I'm no germ freak, but...
Rent's cheap.
Eva, my assistant.
Hi.
Hop right up.
N... now, you... you have,
uh, done this a lot?
Oh, many, many times.
And your... success rate?
Oh, excellent... almost 75%.
So, should we get the, uh,
preliminaries out of the way?
Yeah. Uh, yeah, right.
Ah. Oh.
Oh.
Uh...
So...
Listen, if, uh, something...
- Goes wrong?
- Yeah. Uh...
Would you mail this for me, please?
Sure.
Would've thought you had
something for your brother, Sam.
If I don't make it back,
nothing I say is gonna mean
a damn thing to him.
Ahh!
Don't be a baby.
You know, a little
bedside manner would be nice.
Are we ready? Hmm?
You've got three minutes.
No pulse, no sinus rhythm.
He's dead.
Good times.
This better work.
Messorum evoco qui me tetigit.
Dean?
What the hell?
What do you know?
It worked.
I was in the Sudan!
What's with yanking me ov...
- Wait, why are you dead?
- Tessa, I need a favor.
Oh, you're kidding.
You died to ask me...
- Tell your boss I need to talk to him.
- No.
- Please?
- Where do you get the nerve?
Desperate times.
He calls us.
We don't call him.
- You make an exception!
- I can't.
- Can't or won't?!
- Both!
All right, Tessa.
Thank you very much.
Hello, Dean.
Season 6 Episode 11
"Appointment in Samarra"
I'm busy, Dean.
Talk fast.
I have something of yours.
You mean my ring?
I recall loaning you that
temporarily.
Well, if you want it back...
I'm sorry,
you assume that I don't know
where you've hidden it.
Now we've established you have
hubris but no leverage.
What is it you want?
Lucifer's cage.
I figure you're one
of the few people
that can actually jailbreak it.
Do you?
Sam's soul is stuck in that box.
- I've heard.
- And our other brother
is trapped in there, too.
Michael rode him in.
Dean, quit shuffling and deal.
I want you to get 'em both out.
Hmm.
Pick one.
What?!
Sam's soul or Adam's.
- But...
- As a rule, I don't bring people back.
I might make an exception once,
not twice.
So... pick.
Sam.
His soul has been in there
for a year,
and I understand
that it's... damaged.
Try flayed to the raw nerve.
Well, is there any way
that you could, uh,
I don't know,
hack the Hell part off?
Four, three, two...
Now.
Again.
Dean, Dean, Dean.
What do you think the soul is?
Some pie you can slice?
The soul can be bludgeoned,
tortured, but never broken.
Not even by me.
Well, there's got to be
something.
Maybe.
Can't erase Sam's hell,
but I can...
Put it behind a wall, if you will.
A "wall".
In his mind...
a dam to hold back the tide.
Nasty, those memories.
You don't want to know
what they'll do to him.
Believe me.
Okay, uh, a wall.
Sounds good.
But it's not permanent.
She's right.
Nothing lasts forever.
Well, I do, but...
Okay, so that's the choice...
Sam with no soul,
or Sam with some drywall
that if or when it collapses,
he's... done?
- Yes.
- Do it.
I never said I'd do it.
Well, then what the hell
have we been talking about?
Your prize.
If you win the wager.
Great.
What's the bet?
Don't roll your eyes, Dean.
It's impolite.
Now, when you fetch my ring,
put it on.
What?
I want you to be me
for one day.
Are you serious?
No, I'm being
incredibly sarcastic.
Eva, adrenaline!
Take the ring off
before the 24 hours are up,
and you lose.
No soul for Sam.
Clear?
Okay. Yes.
But... but why?
Simple, Dean.
Because...
Oh, thank Moses.
You couldn't have given me
five more seconds?
Son, you were gone
for seven minutes.
I was?
Mm-hmm.
I thought for sure
Death had you by the twins.
- You what?!
- Just hear me out.
I heard Cass and Crowley
when they said
it would either kill me
or turn me to jello, Dean!
I heard enough!
- Death said he can put up a wall.
- A wall?
Yes, yes, a wall...
that... that, basically,
- you wouldn't remember Hell.
- Really?
Really.
For good?
Like a cure?
No, it's not a cure.
It...
He said it could last a lifetime.
Great.
So, playing pretty fast
and loose with my life here,
- don't you think, Dean?
- I'm trying to save your life!
Exactly, Dean!
It's my life!
It's my life,
it's my soul.
And it sure as hell ain't
your head that's gonna explode
when this whole scheme of yours
goes sideways!
Just curious.
I presume Death's not doing this
out of the goodness of his heart.
So what's your half of the deal?
I'm sorry. I didn't get that.
I have to wear the ring
for a day.
Why the hell
would he want you to do that?
Get his rocks off. I don't know.
But I'm doing it.
Where you going?
Look, I hear you, all right?
I get it.
I just need a minute to wrap
my head around it, all right?
Looking for this?
Just taking a walk.
Sam.
I'm your brother.
I'm not gonna let you get hurt.
- I know what I'm doing here.
- What if you're wrong?
I won't let it go wrong.
Fine.
Fine? So, you're...
So, I'm trusting you here.
Barely.
You sure?
You're the one
with the compass, right?
Just don't mess it up.
I won't.
Watch him.
So, is this the part
where you pull a gun on me
and lock me in the panic room?
Do I have to?
No.
I guess Dean's got to do
what he's got to do.
Guess we all do, kid.
Well, here goes everything.
Wow.
They'll just let any slack-jawed
haircut be Death these days.
Well, you're all charm today,
aren't you?
Let's be clear
so that we get through this
with a minimum of screw-up.
I don't like this.
And right now,
I'm not crazy about you, either.
This is your boss' idea, not mine.
True.
But you have a long history
of throwing a wrench
in everything,
so let's just stick to the rules.
- Deal?
- And the rules are?
For the next 24 hours,
you kill everyone
whose number's up.
- Well, how am I supposed to know who to...
- Kill?
- Yeah.
- I have a list.
- Let me see.
- No.
You touch them,
they die, I reap them.
Are we clear?
Yeah, I guess.
Remove the ring, you lose.
Slack off, you lose.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Don't mess this up.
It's not my job
to be your damn babysitter.
Sam Winchester.
This had better be good.
Why here's one for
the list of dumbest things ever.
Summon the angel
who wants to kill you.
Desperate times.
I need your help, Balthazar.
Interesting...
Since last time we met,
you wanted to... what was it?
Oh, yes, yes...
fry my wings "extra crispy".
Well, that was
a misunderstanding.
Some misunderstanding!
I need some advice.
- Advice?
- Angel advice.
Well, then go ask your boyfriend.
Cass can't help me.
I need to know if there's
a spell or a weapon,
anything that can keep a soul
out... forever.
Ohh.
What's going on, Sam?
It's for me.
Well...
The plot thickens.
Where's your soul, Sam?
Good God, no.
It's not still...
It is.
My brother found a way
to put it back in me.
I don't want it.
No, you don't.
No, no, 'cause Michael and Lucy
are hate-banging it
as we speak.
- Can you help me?
- Oh, yes.
The question is, will I?
Set your terms.
I'll do it for free.
Free?
Why?
Well, you seem like
a capable young man.
I'd love to have you in my debt.
And I have to say, I'm not a fan
of your brother,
so screwing him would delight me.
Anyway, to business.
The spell, yes.
So, finding the ingredients
should be easy enough,
but, uh, there's one
tricky part, however.
Okay.
You need to scar your vessel.
Meaning what?
Meaning something
that so pollutes it,
it renders it uninhabitable.
Calls for something very specific.
Great. What?
Patricide.
My dad's been dead for years.
To be clear, um, you need
the blood of your father,
but your father
needn't be blood.
Comprende?
Just so you know,
when people die,
they might have questions
for you.
Well, you know,
not you, but Death.
You mean like, "how did
Betty White outlast me?"
"What's it all mean?"
Is popular.
And am I just
gonna magically know?
No.
Then what the hell
am I supposed to say?
Oh, come on,
give me something.
Suck it up.
Comes with the gig.
Come on! Come on!
Let's go!
They can't hear you.
They can't see you.
Just let this play out.
Well, who am I taking?
Wait and see.
Which one?
You want me to shoot the kid?!
Hurry up!
Oh, you think I'm kidding?
And don't forget the drawer
under the register.
Come on, move it!
Let's go!
You idiot.
Hello? Tick-tock.
He's in agonizing pain, right?
Uh, yes.
Give me a minute.
Why?
Mostly because you're a dick.
Enjoy the ride down, pal.
Trust me... sauna gets hot.
That wasn't so hard.
Call me crazy, but this
smells like a heart attack.
Lucky guess.
Why?
You think maybe it was
the extra cheese?
Yeah.
It was good, though.
- Is that a local place?
- Dean.
Right.
Uh, time to go, man.
Sorry.
Wait.
Will you tell me what it all means?
Everything is dust in the wind.
That's it?!
A Kansas song?!
Sorry. He's new.
Woke up and you were gone.
Where you been?
Just driving around.
No biggie.
- Drink?
- Yeah. Sure.
After you, boss.
That's you when we went
to California.
You were 6 then.
God. We should burn that.
You were adorable.
The dad or the kid?
Kid.
Come on.
What is she, 13?
- She's 12.
- And that's...?
That's your mom...
when she was your age.
This guy have any other family?
No, not really.
Oh, I remember that...
Well, this is awesome.
What, you thought it was all
gonna be armed robbers
and heart attacks
waiting to happen?
- She's 12!
- With a serious heart condition.
Who's next on the list?
Dean, you have to take her.
- Says who?
- Death.
- I'm Death.
- You know what I mean.
Well, who tells him?
I don't know.
It just is.
It's destiny.
Give me a break.
I've spent my whole life
fighting that crap.
There's no such thing
as destiny,
just like there was
no apocalypse...
just a bunch of stuck-up mooks
who didn't want us human slaves
asking questions.
Well, I say
the little girl lives.
Do you know what's amazing?
You don't actually
buy a word you're saying.
- Yes, I do.
- Oh, really?
So, all the times that you
messed with life and death,
they just worked out for you?
It was just a beach party
every time, huh?
Well, I know this much...
I'm Death, she's 12,
and she's not dying today.
Yeah. Everything's going to be fine.
Medically, I can't explain it.
So
her heart just healed?
Couple of times in your career,
you see something you
just got to call a miracle.
All I know is
I won't have to operate.
Thank you.
Thank you, doctor.
You did it.
You're gonna be okay.
Hey, hon, guess what?
I'm leaving.
No, surgery was canceled.
Come on.
We have more work here.
Okay. See you soon.
Pair of aces.
- Want another one?
- Yeah, sure.
May have been born at night, boy,
but it wasn't last night.
Not good.
Let's not do anything hasty
here, Sam.
Don't say, "here's Johnny."
I got to do this, Bobby.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have
cornered yourself.
I didn't!
Reinforced steel core,
titanium kick plate.
Get comfy.
You want to explain
what this is about?
I just, uh...
I have to do this, Bobby.
Says who?
If Dean shoves
that soul back in me,
think how bad
that could really be.
I can't let it happen, Bobby.
I mean, it's not like
I want to kill you.
You've been
nothing but good to me.
So... what,
demon deal or something?
Spell.
You're making a mistake, Sam.
I'm trying to survive.
Dean's got a way
to make it safe.
Oh, yeah, what,
some wall inside my head
that maybe stays up?
Come on.
If it works...
Yeah, what if it doesn't?
Dean doesn't care about me.
He... he just cares about
his little brother, Sammy,
burning in Hell.
He'll kill me
to get that other guy back.
Look, I...
I know how scary it is.
But you know what's scarier?
You right now.
You're not
in your right head, Sam.
You're not giving us
much choice here.
Sam?
Balls!
Ain't nobody killing me
in my house but me.
I don't want to blow your legs out,
boy, but I will.
Oh, what, you gonna give me
the silent treatment now?
Really?
Damn it! I knew it!
What?
Code 500, E.R. code 500, E.R.
What's going on?
Fractured spine,
internal bleeding.
Had a heart attack
in the ambulance.
- We need Dr. Owens.
- He just left.
Call Owens.
Tell him to turn around.
- B.P?
- B.P. 60 over 30.
Pupils fixed and dilated.
- Wait, that's...
- You let the girl live.
The nurse goes home early,
gets in a crash
she wouldn't have.
And she needs
the heart surgeon,
and where is he?
You knew this would happen?
No.
Just knew that you
knocked over a domino.
She's in cardiac arrest.
- Take her.
- What?
Clear!
She's not on the list!
Everything you do
has consequences.
Do you want to set off
another chain reaction?
She's got nothing to do with this!
Well, too bad, Dean.
You put on the ring.
Now do your damn job.
- Clear!
- Go!
Fine.
She's crashing again.
We're losing her.
Clear!
Is that...
- Am I...?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
- But I'm...
- So young.
Yeah.
Actually, you were supposed
to live for many decades.
Have kids, grandkids.
Then why?
Because he screwed up.
You did this to me?
Come on, Jolene.
It's time.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
Where is she?
Where's my wife?
Scott, wait!
No!
A real vacation?
Yeah.
I can take you
to this one caf?,
show you where I met your mom.
You saw what happened
to the nurse.
Go and kill that girl, Dean.
I tried to tell you
what you already know.
She's disrupting
the natural order
by being alive.
You of all people
know what that means.
Chaos and sadness will follow
her for the rest of her life.
We tried it your way.
Give me a minute.
What?
Come on, man,
pull the car over.
You're gonna
get yourself killed.
What are you doing?
Pull the damn car over!
Stop the car.
Come on, stop the car.
- Route 10 is still shut down...
- What are you doing?! Stop the car!
From an earlier fatal crash.
- All traffic has to exit...
- Son of a bitch!
- Aah!
- Hit the brakes!
Aah!
Damn it.
Tessa!
You there?! Tessa?!
I lost!
Sam's screwed!
You happy?!
Least you can do
is zap my ass back home!
Hello?!
I lost the bet.
Sorry about your brother.
Let's just go.
Go where, Dean?
We're done.
What are we...
Unfinished business.
It's over.
You took the ring off.
Anyway, I thought you wanted
the girl to skate by.
No one really skates by.
Do they?
You should
say your goodbyes, man.
Hey, honey.
I must have dozed off.
Hilary?
Somebody!
I'm dead?
I'm sorry.
- But what about my dad?
- He'll be fine.
- Really?
- I have no idea.
I... I can't just leave him.
- It's not fair!
- I know.
Well, then why?
Because...
there's sort of a...
a natural order to things.
Natural order is stupid.
Well, I agree with you there.
Listen to me.
You don't want to do this.
Sam.
I've been like a father
to you, boy.
Somewhere inside,
you've got to know that.
Well, that's just it.
Sorry.
Hi, Sam. I'm back.
I can't keep doing this, Bobby.
I mean, what am I,
gonna tie him up every time
he tries to kill someone?
And that's not gonna hold him.
I mean, he's...
Capable of anything.
What am I supposed to do here?
I don't know.
Dean.
Join me.
Brought you one...
from a little stand
in Los Angeles
known for their bacon dogs.
Sit.
Boy, what's with you
and cheap food?
I could ask you the same thing.
Thought I'd have a treat
before I put the ring back on.
Heavier than it looks, isn't it?
Sometimes, you just
want the thing off.
But you know that.
Not hungry?
Look...
I think you know that I flunked.
So there.
Oh, and by the way, I, uh...
I sucked at being you.
Really screwed up
the whole natural order thing.
But I'm sure you knew
about that, too.
So, if you could go back,
would you simply kill
the little girl?
No fuss, no stomping your feet?
Knowing what I know now, yeah.
I'm surprised to hear that.
- Surprised and glad.
- Yeah, well, don't get excited.
I would have
saved the nurse, okay?
That's it.
I think it's a
little more than that.
Today, you got a hard look
behind the curtain.
Wrecking the natural order's
not quite such fun
when you have to
mop up the mess, is it?
This is hard for you, Dean.
You throw away your life
because you've come to assume
that it'll bounce right back
into your lap.
But the human soul
is not a rubber ball.
It's vulnerable, impermanent,
but stronger than you know.
And more valuable
than you can imagine.
So...
I think
you've learned something today.
Want to know what I think?
I think you knew
that I wouldn't last a day.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I lost. Fine.
But at least
I have the balls to admit
that it was rigged from the jump.
Most people speak to me
with more respect.
I didn't mean...
We're done here.
It's been lovely.
But now
I'm going to go to Hell
to get your brother's soul.
Why would you
do that for me?
I wouldn't do it for you.
You and your brother
keep coming back.
You're an affront
to the balance of the universe,
and you cause disruption
on a global scale.
I apologize for that.
But you have use.
Right now,
you're digging at something.
The intrepid Detective.
I want you
to keep digging, Dean.
So you're just
gonna be cryptic, or...
It's about the souls.
You'll understand
when you need to.
Wait...
with Sam...
Is this wall thing
really gonna work?
Call it 75%.
Bobby!
Stay away from me!
Open the door.
- What happened?
- Now!
Get the hell away from me.
Get away from me!
Don't.
Don't!
Now, Sam,
I'm gonna put up a barrier
inside your mind.
No, don't touch me.
It might feel a little... itchy.
But do me a favor...
don't scratch the wall.
Because trust me...
you're not gonna like
what happens.
Please.
Don't do this.
No, no!
You don't know!
You don't know
what'll happen to me!
Dean.
Please!
No. No.
Aah!
== Sync by elderman ==
== corrections by elderman ==
== www.addic7ed.com ==
Edited by Scooby