Bring me creatures.
Aim high on the food chain
Whatever we bag...
ends up there.
That's where he tortures them,
interrogates them...
I don't really know.
- We ain't your employees.
- Of course you are!
What's in the gift bag?
- You are.
- Not possible.
You didn't hide your bones
as well as you should have.
Aah! Aah!
Who is she, this Eve bitch?
The mother of all of us
and the end of all of you.
The ashes of a Phoenix
can burn the mother.
"1861.
"Sunrise, Wyoming.
"Gun killed a Phoenix today.
Left a pile
of smoldering ash."
- Whose gun?
- Colt's.
We hop back in time,
we join up with Samuel Colt,
we hunt the Phoenix,
and then haul its ashes
back home.
- Is that what I think it is?
- Ashes of a Phoenix.
You know what this means?
We take the fight to her.
- I'm serious.
That was way overpriced, dude.
Back where I'm from, okay,
it was like $3 a beer.
Okay.
Then, I'm buying next time.
I'm not even lying.
I'm not even joking at all.
Hey.
Heaven must be
missing an angel.
I think she likes me.
Okay, Fabio.
Let's... let's go.
Are you okay, miss?
I'm perfect.
I mean,
is... is that blood?
Yes, I suppose it is.
You sure you're all right?
Hey, what the hell?!
I gave him a gift.
Come on, man.
Let's get out here.
Aah!
Aaaaaaaaah!
Season 6 Episode 19
"Mommy Dearest"
Hey.How you doing?
Five shells...
that's how I'm doing.
Well, you know,
it's a hell of a lot more
than we had last week.
Maybe.
Meaning?
Meaning I just had myself
a little mishap a few minutes ago,
and, uh...
well, here, look.
Whoa.
Huh.
This stuff is supposed to burn
the bejesus out of Eve.
It doesn't even give me
a sunburn.
The lore says it works.
That's always reliable.
Well, you know what?
M-maybe it's like...
maybe it's like iron or silver,
you know?
Hurts them and not us?
Maybe, but a fat lot of good
it does us
- until we find the bitch.
- I'm looking.
But I'll tell you,
maybe it's time you made a call.
Why's it always got to be me
that makes the call, huh?
It's not like Cass
lives in my ass.
The dude's busy.
Cass, get out of my ass!
I was never in your...
Have you made any progress
in locating Eve?
Well, we were gonna
ask you about that.
I've looked,
but she's hidden from me.
She's hidden from all angels.
Awesome.
You know, what we really need
is an inside man.
What do you mean?
Something with claws
and sympathy.
Like a friendly monster?
Those are in short supply
these days, don't you think?
Sure, but we've met
one or two, right?
Maybe.
So, maybe we can find one.
Lenore.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Hey, hey.
Lenore, stop.
Look, we're happy you're here.
My name's Lenore.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
It's been a long time.
You remember us?
I remember.
Your hunter friend
almost killed me.
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
uh, he turned into a vampire,
and I chopped his head off.
Yeah, with razor wire.
Wicked.
Well, that's something.
What's going on?
Why am I here?
Well, um...
that's Cass.
He's our friend.
And we need to talk to you.
About Eve.
Eve?!
I have nothing to say about Eve.
You sure about that?
I'm trying to stay away
from her. Believe me.
Where's your nest?
Gone.
I couldn't fight it anymore.
It's her voice...
in our heads...
What it does to us.
So they left,
started killing again.
But not you.
Don't look so impressed.
I was hiding in a basement...
not exactly Club Med.
You don't know how hard it is
not to give in.
Everyone gives in.
All right, so, this psychic
two-way you got going...
does that mean you know
where mom's camped out?
You've got to be kidding me.
You want me to tell you
where she is?
You do know she could be
listening to us right now.
I might as well
be a video camera.
What are you thinking?
So, we don't have
the element of surprise.
We're still going in.
You're crazy.
I can't help you.
Can't or won't?
Look, it's clear as day
you still give a crap.
You don't want to kill,
and you don't want
this whole planet dead.
You actually believe
you can stop her?
Just tell us where she is.
Grants Pass, Oregon.
- And now she knows you're coming.
- Well, let's go see.
Hold on.
I didn't tell you this
out of the goodness of my heart.
I need something.
What?
Kill me.
- Lenore...
- Look...
we'll lock you down till
this whole thing is over, okay?
Witness Protection.
You'll be safe.
You don't get it.
It's not about that.
I'm dangerous.
I hear her voice all the time.
You're not like
the rest of them.
I'm exactly like them.
I fed.
I couldn't help it.
The girl couldn't have been
more than 16, Sam.
I'll do it again.
I can't stop.
Not anymore.
You have to.
- Please.
- Lenore...
We needed to move this along.
Well, I was expecting
more "Zombieland",
less "Pleasantville."
Just because it looks
quiet don't mean it is,
especially if she's got a clue
we're coming.
Yeah, well, if she is here,
I'm glad we got Smitey
McSmiterton on our squad.
All right.
Where do we start?
I'm gonna need a computer.
All right.
I finally got the police database,
no thanks to this.
I ask for a computer.
It is a computer.
No, a computer has buttons.
- Can I get you anything else?
- No, we're good. Thanks.
Anything?
Oh, nickel-and-dime stuff,
nothing weird.
Basically, dead end.
You think Vampira was lying?
I'll search the town.
Give me a moment.
Cass, we can still see you.
Yeah, I'm still here.
Okay, well, you don't
have to wait on us.
Well, now it just looks
like you're pooping.
- Something's wrong.
- What, are you stuck?
I'm blocked.
I'm powerless.
You're joking!
Something in this town
is, uh...
it's affecting me.
I assume it's Eve.
So, wait.
Mom's making you limp?
Figuratively, yes.
- How?
- I don't know, but she is.
Oh, well, that's great,
'cause without your power,
you're basically just a baby
in a trench coat.
I think you hurt his feelings.
I got something here, maybe.
Had to go federal to get it.
Call went out from the local office
to the CDC last night.
About what?
A Dr. Silver...
called in an illness
he couldn't identify.
Patient's a 25-year-old
African-American
named Ed Bright.
Well, that's not much to go on.
Well, it's our only lead, so...
So beggars can't be choosers.
Right. I get it.
All right, well,
let's finish up.
Excuse me. Hi.
Uh, I-is Dr. Silver in today?
My friend is very sick.
I have a, uh...
painful burning sensation.
Oh, well, he's out.
Sorry.
Do you happen to know
where he is?
He hasn't called in.
You might want to find yourself
some ointment.
What kind of doctor calls the CDC
and then goes AWOL
the very next day?
Let's have a look, shall we?
Is this gonna take a long time?
What is it?
Ohh.
It's the patient, Ed Bright.
Well, what kind of doctor
calls the CDC
and then stashes the gooey
corpse in his shed?
I don't understand
what's happening here.
Well, I know one thing
about the body...
we need some kerosene.
Here. Dr. Silver.
Wife, two sons.
Uh-oh.
Hi, there.
Hi.
Who are you?
You casual Friday, agents?
We were on a case
a few miles out.
We got a call to come here.
So, how about you?
What's your business?
Oh, Dr. Silver's
a friend of mine.
Heard he didn't show up
for work today,
so I thought I'd stop by
and see if he's sick.
Not sick. Missing.
Missing? Says who?
Says me... empty house,
no bags packed,
car still in the driveway.
Well, how'd you get on this?
Oh, it's a long story.
Tell you what... why don't
you put out an APB?
We'll compare notes down
at the Station. Sound good?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
- Sure.
- Obliged.
Wow, talk about talking
out of your butt.
Yeah.
Just hurry, you idjit.
Ohh.
So we got a missing doctor
and an oozy patient, huh?
Yeah. Plot thickens.
Well, let's go see what
Ed's roommates have to say.
Does Ed Bright have a brother?
No. Why?
Then that's not his twin.
So, what... shifter?
I don't know
what we're looking at.
All right, Dean and me
are gonna go in.
You two stay here
and watch the door.
Something comes out, shoot it.
Yeah, best guess...
silver bullets.
I'm fairly unpracticed
with firearms.
You know who whines?
Babies.
Okay.
Don't touch anything.
Hey, hey, back here.
Come here.
Hey, hey, hey.
Talk to us.
What is this?
Ed?
- Ed, what's going on?
- What?
I'm not Ed.
What's wrong with me?
Uh, nothing.
You're okay.
You're okay, all right?
We're gonna get you help.
Let me ask you something.
Do I...
do all of us...
do we look like Ed?
What? No.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
of course not.
You, uh... you have a fever.
You're hallucinating.
Marshall, Marshall,
hey, what happened here?
Am I gonna die?
No. You're not gonna die, okay?
Now, you need to talk to us.
It's important.
Ed was feeling bad,
so I took him to the doctor.
I think
now we're all sick.
You think?
And before you got sick
and before Ed got sick,
did you do anything?
Did you go anywhere?
Hey, I need you
to focus for me.
I don't know.
Some bar.
A bar? What bar?
Eighth street, I guess.
Eighth street.
Um, and did anything happen
at the bar?
D-did you see anything?
Did you meet anyone?
Look, an ambulance is on the way.
A girl.
A girl? Okay. And?
A girl in white.
Good. Okay.
What did the girl in white do,
Marshall?
What...
what did she do to Ed?
Marshall!
I don't get it.
What, a bunch of regular Joes
wake up shifters?
What the hell?
Shifters usually
run in families.
This looks like an infection.
Nobody touched nothing?
Well, I'm bathing
in Purell tonight.
So, he said they met a girl.
It's got to be Eve.
But why would she do this?
Mommy monster.
Make more.
No, no, no, no,
Cass has got a good point.
I mean, if she's gonna
make a shifter army,
why make one that's
this sick, gooey and dying?
Add that to the pile of crap
that don't make sense.
So, should we hit the bar?
Well, the sheriff's
a mook, but still...
you'd think he'd notice
this many missing folks.
We got a vamp over here.
Nope. Scratch that.
We got a wraith.
What the hell...?
What has teeth and a spike?
Never seen that in my life.
Oh, great.
So Eve's making hybrids now?
- Looks like.
- The question is, why?
I mean, what does she want
with a...
what do you call these?
Well, congrats. You discovered it.
You get to name it.
Jefferson Starships.
Huh?
Because they're horrible...
and hard to kill.
Looks like the whole bar
has been turned into the...
Jefferson Starships.
Fine. But why are all
the... starships dead?
I can't say, but...
It looks like
they all burned up.
Burned up? Like...
Like a high fever,
like the flu.
What the hell's going on here?
Does every monster in this town
have the Motaba virus?
Hands where I can see them!
Now, this is not
what it looks like.
Look, we're the feds.
Yeah? Well, feds are not allowed
to do this.
- Cuff 'em.
- Turn around.
Oof!
Listen, if we can
make a phone call,
we can straighten this all out.
Straighten out a massacre?
I'd like to see you try.
J-Jefferson starships!
Dean, wait!
Well, I'll say this...
you're the healthiest-looking
specimen I've seen all day.
I take my vitamins.
So, you want to tell us
what's going on here?
Hmm?
So, you boys are, uh,
Eve's cleaning crew?
Is that it? You, uh...
you come around
to clean up the bodies,
make sure the word
doesn't get out, huh?
Is that why you snatched up
the doctor?
You're so wasting your time.
You stupid head of cattle.
More starships.
Stay here.
You're Dr. Silver's boys.
All right, don't worry.
We're gonna get you out of here, OK?
- Uh, uh, keys...
- Yeah.
Look...
We're not gonna hurt you.
My name is Sam.
And that's my brother, Dean.
Those cops... they're not
coming back, ever.
What are your names?
Joe. This is Ryan.
Hiya, Ryan.
How you doing?
He won't talk...
Not since they came for us.
All right, listen, Joe,
we're gonna get you
out of those handcuffs.
But you understand what's going on
around here, don't you?
So first we got to make sure
you're you.
How you gonna do that?
Well, there's a few,
uh, dozen tests.
Okay, let's get started.
Ugh!
Y-you really think that's
gonna make me talk?
Something will.
Got a couple of hungry
human boys here.
Come on, guys.
So, you two never
heard them talk...
about a mother or...
someone named Eve?
It was just me and Ryan
in there.
And your folks?
Cops said we were next.
They said we were food.
You have any other family?
An uncle in Meritt.
Meritt. What's that, like
15 miles outside of town?
Okay, we'll get you there.
Dean.
Can I have a word?
We need to find Eve now.
Yeah. Go.
Me and Sam just
got to make a milk run.
No, we need your help here.
Hold your water.
We'll be back in a few.
Dean, Dean.
Millions of lives
are at stake here, not just two.
- Stay focused.
- Are you kidding?
There's a greater purpose here.
You know what?
I-I'm getting
a little sick and tired
of the greater purposes, okay?
I think what I'd like to do
right now
is save a couple of kids,
if you don't mind.
We'll catch up.
Okay, guys, let's go.
Come on.
Hey.
You should get some rest.
They won't take long.
You don't know that.
They may find more
wayward orphans along the way.
Oh, don't get cute.
Right.
Pardon me for highlighting
their crippling and dangerous
empathetic response
with "sarcasm."
It was a bad idea,
letting them go.
Come on.
You don't let Sam and
Dean Winchester do squat.
They do what they got to.
You know that.
Anyway, we want Eve,
we need coordinates.
So, we can stand here
bellyaching,
or we can go poke that pig
till he squeals.
Thoughts?
You know,
she can see you right now.
And you're just making her mad.
Then tell the bitch
to come get me.
I need five minutes alone
with him.
What for?
Cass...
your batteries are dead.
Give me five minutes.
All right. Fine.
Aaaaaah!
Eve's at 25 Buckley Street.
You can call Sam and Dean.
Rigorous interrogation, huh?
Well, we got a location.
Now we just got to get
close enough to take a shot.
All right. Well...
Let's all take one.
Load 'em up. Make 'em count.
You got to be kidding me.
She's been in there
the whole time?
Why'd she ever let us in?
Or out.
Well, there's one way
to find out.
What, just stroll in?
We don't know who's human
or who's her.
Well, there's one way
to draw her out.
- Me and Sam will go in.
- Dean...
Look, we don't get a shot off,
you two better.
That's the plan?
Yeah. Pretty much.
Well, at least
it ain't complicated.
Now what?
Crap. Crap.
Crap.
Starships?
Yeah.
Is there anybody in this diner
that is not
a flesh-eating monster?
Uh, me and you.
Okay, well, let's get
the hell out of here.
- Shall we?
- Two specials, right?
Uh, no, that's not for us.
We were just heading out.
Now, that would be rude, Sam.
Let me guess.
Eve.
Pleasure.
Why don't we step outside,
chat?
Why? This is private.
Phoenix ash.
I'm impressed.
I bet you had to go
a long way for that.
You have no idea.
Destroy these.
Thank you.
Relax.
I'm not here to fight.
No, just to rally every freak
on the planet,
bring in Khan worms and...
and half-assed spider-men
and dragons.
Really, sister? Dragons?
So, I dusted off some of the old classics.
I needed help.
With what?
Tearing apart the planet?
You misunderstand me.
I never wanted that,
not at first.
I liked our arrangement.
What arrangement?
The natural order.
My children turn
a few of you...
You hunted a few of them.
I was happy.
Okay, so what changed?
My children, no thanks to you,
started getting kidnapped
and tortured...
even my firstborns.
I was pushed into this.
After all, a mother
defends her children.
Really?
You're gonna use the
"mother of the year" defense?
You?
It happens to be true.
Know what?
Maybe you'll believe it
if I look a little more like this.
Oh, you bitch.
She died to protect you,
didn't she?
See?
You understand a mother's love.
- I'm no different.
- All right, you know what?
This conversation's over.
If you're gonna kill us, kill us.
You?
No.
It's Crowley I want dead.
Well, you're too late there.
That little limey mook
roasted months ago.
Crowley's alive.
That's impossible.
I see his face through the eyes
of every child
he strings up and skins.
Any idea why he's hurting
my babies?
He wants Purgatory, right?
Location, location, location.
Is that what he told you?
It's about the souls.
Well, what about them?
They're power,
you simple little monkey.
Fuel.
Each soul a beautiful,
little nuclear reactor.
Put them together,
you have the Sun.
Now think what
the king of Hell could do
with that vast,
untapped oil well...
How powerful he'd be.
Now Crowley wants
to siphon off my supply
and torture my children to do it?
Okay, fine.
I'll quit playing nice.
I'll turn you all.
Every soul... mine.
Let's see how hard his Hell burns
when everyone comes to me.
He asked for it.
You know, last I checked
there were a few billion of us.
That plan might take a while.
What exactly do you think
I'm doing here?
I'm building the perfect beast.
Wait a second.
All those...
all those things
we've been finding.
Call it Beta testing.
Well, I think your formula
might be a little off.
They're imploding
all over town.
Ohh, there were a few
unfortunate failures.
But I eventually got it right.
Quiet... smart... inconspicuous.
It can spread through
a whole town in under a day.
Oh, and the best part...
you've been with it the whole time.
What?
Yes, you were the final test.
I had to see
if it could slip past hunters
undetected, of course.
Little Ryan.
Joe?
Ryan?
Aah!
You look upset.
If it makes you feel
any better,
Ryan was bound to work on you...
little wayward orphan...
like yourselves.
There's nothing you can do
about it now.
So let's talk.
Nothing to say.
Well, that's where
you're wrong.
I have an offer to propose.
Crowley...
as you know,
not so easy to find.
So, here's the deal...
you find him...
bring him to me...
I let you live.
Pass.
- Dean...
- Sam, no.
The answer is no.
You say that like
you have another option.
Maybe I do, maybe I don't.
You think?
Well, so much
for your plan "B."
And you, wondering,
"why so flaccid?"
I'm older than you, Castiel.
I know what makes angels tick.
As long as I'm around,
consider yourself...
unplugged.
Work for me.
It's a good deal.
Bonus...
I won't kill your friends.
All right, look,
the last few months,
we've been working
for an evil dick.
We're not about to sign up
for an evil bitch.
We don't work with demons.
We don't work with monsters.
And if that means you got to
kill us, then kill us!
Or...
I turn you.
And you do what I want anyway.
Beat me with a wire hanger,
answer's still no.
Don't...
test me.
Bite me.
- No!
- Dean!
Phoenix ash.
One shell...
one ounce of whiskey...
down the hatch.
Little musty on the afterburn.
Call you later, mom.
Shut your eyes!
We gotta take you on more
monster hunts.
Hey, Cass, um...
Dean's bleeding pretty good.
I think she turned me
into a Jefferson Starship.
Could you clear that up, too?
All right, we're good.
We got to go. Now.
Where?
The kid.
The little kid...
he's one of them.
Unbelievable.
Yeah, I know, Cass.
You told me, all right?
Let's just go.
So, we kill the wicked witch,
and she still wins.
I mean, they could have turned
half the town by now.
Don't say it.
Found them.
Well, who ganked them?
Demons.
So, what do you think?
I think that demons
don't give a crap
about monster twins
unless they're told to.
So, you think she was
telling the truth?
The truth about what?
She said that Crowley's still kicking.
But I burned his bones...
how ca...
Was she certain?
Sounded pretty sure.
According to her,
Crowley's still waterboarding
her kids somewhere.
I don't understand.
Well, he's a crafty
son of a bitch.
I'm an angel.
I'll look into it immediately.
Cass!
Let us know what you find out!
What? What?
How did Crowley get away?
I mean, it's not like Cass
to make mistakes like that,
unless...
Unless what?
Unless he meant to.
Bobby, this is Cass
we're talking about.
Do you believe this?
Sam?
Look, it's probably nothing.
It's just...
You know what? You're right.
It's... it's probably nothing.
Really, Cass...
this is getting ridiculous.
How many times
am I gonna have
to clean up your messes?
Sync by Alice | Corrected by
gloriabg www.addic7ed.com
Edited by Scooby