Hello, Dean.
What is it you want?
Lucifer's cage.
Sam's soul
is stuck in that box.
I can't erase Sam's Hell,
but I can put it behind a wall.
Nasty, those memories.
You don't want to know
what they will do to him
Death said he can put up a wall.
But you wouldn't remember Hell.
- Don't do this.
- Don't scratch the wall.
You should have told me, Dean.
- You weren't supposed to know.
- What I did?
To Bobby? To you?
Of course I should know.
Sam, Death didn't just shove
your soul back in, okay?
He put up the great wall of Sam
between you and the things
that you don't remember.
And trust me when I say
that the things you don't know
could kill you.
- That's not a joke.
- But I have to set things right.
So I need to know what I did.
But you don't know how dangerous
that could be.
I warned you not to put
that thing back inside him.
What was I supposed to do?
Let me tell you what his soul
felt like when I touched it.
Like it had been
skinned alive, Dean.
If you wanted to kill
your brother,
you should have done it
outright.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
How's the arm?
It'll hold
till we get out of town.
Just don't bleed out,
all right?
Yeah, well, that's the plan.
Cop.
Evening, Deputy.
Agent Roark, Agent Wynand,
mind stepping out of the van
a moment?
We're just on our way
to the office.
Everything okay?
No. I can't get
Sheriff Dobbs on the phone.
I can't get anyone!
We spoke to Dobbs earlier.
Maybe he's just, uh...
is that blood?
Hey, look, there's no need
to get riled.
You're coming with me.
All right.
We'll follow you back.
I don't think so.
Get in my car,
or you're under arrest.
You're gonna arrest
two federal agents?
Really?
Have a good night.
If you think...
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, just hold...
You think there were
maybe calmer ways
- we could have done all that?
- Do we care?
Let's go.
Season 6 Episode 12
"Unforgiven"
Sources said
prosecutors were getting closer
to a decision
on whether to charge the actor.
But they adamantly denied that
any prosecution was in any...
What are you watching?
Just trying to catch up.
So...
Mel Gibson really took
a turn this past year, huh?
Or he's possessed.
Seriously, think about it.
So, I just got off the blower
with Bobby.
Oh, yeah?
You got anything else on this,
uh, "mother of all" thing?
Uh, no, nothing solid.
He says it's quiet.
Quiet like quiet
or quiet like too quiet?
When is it ever just quiet?
Right.
- Hmm.
- What?
What are these, coordinates?
Who's it from?
I have no idea.
Well?
Uh, Bristol, Rhode island,
where three women disappeared
in the last week.
Apparently, the, uh, victims
seemed to vanish into thin air.
Could be something.
Who's the text from?
I don't know.
It just kept ringing.
- What's that about?
- Could be another hunter
looking for backup,
throwing us a case?
Who knows how many hunters
I even met,
working with the Campbells,
you know?
But I think we should go.
Whoa, wait. We're just
gonna drop everything?
Dude, two minutes ago,
you weren't doing anything.
You got mysterious coordinates
from a mysterious Mr. "X,"
leading to a mysterious town?
That doesn't throw up
red flags to you?
I don't know. Maybe.
But that doesn't mean we can just ignore
a bunch of missing girls.
Right?
Okay.
We'll check it out.
But if things get squirrelly,
we dump out, okay?
Yeah.
What?
Nothing.
Well, freak's got a type...
brunettes.
Whoa.
This one's got a little bit
of a wild side.
It's all in the eyes, Sam.
See it?
All right, well, aside from
your little deep insight there,
these women actually
have nothing in common...
Different jobs, different friends,
different everything.
So, what's the connection?
I don't know.
Why don't you figure that out?
I'm gonna go hit the poop deck.
Agent Roark?
- It's good to see you again.
- It is.
Oh, you remember my husband?
Right.
- Don.
- Of course, right. Um, hi.
So...
you're back 'cause it started again,
right... the disappearances?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, right.
Um... so, if either of you two
hear anything,
please let me know.
Where's your partner?
The big bald guy?
Agent Wynand, right?
- Agent Wynand, of course. Well...
- Sex rehab.
Yeah, you've heard
of plushies, right?
This is, uh...
this is my new partner.
Hi. Pleasure.
How you doing? Hi.
Uh, so, agent,
we should, uh
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Of course. Uh, nice chatting
with you, Agent Roark.
You too.
Cuff me.
What was that?
She just cougar-eyed you.
I think Samuel and I
have worked a case in this town.
You think?
Come on. Let's get the hell
out of here.
Hey, come on.
Hop to, would you?
We can't go, Dean.
Uh, yeah, we can.
No, listen... five guys
went missing a year ago.
They never found the bodies.
I mean, that's got to be the job
me and Samuel worked, right?
Great. What difference
does it make?
A year ago,
five guys go missing,
and... and now suddenly
all these women go missing.
Something's here.
So either we just didn't stop it,
or we only thought we did.
Okay, but why
the gender bend, huh?
First it's dudes.
Now it's chicks?
That's a totally different M.O.
I don't know.
Who knows?
The point is,
something's still here.
Great. Well, call Bobby.
He can deal with it.
Why? We can deal with it.
Are you serious?
Sam, there is a reason
that hunters don't hit
the same town over again...
'cause we have a habit
of leaving messes behind.
- Right. I agree.
- One of dad's rules...
you never use
the same crapper twice.
- Everyone uses the same crapper twice.
- Not us.
You know what I mean.
Okay, look...
this creature is still walking
around 'cause of me, right?
I mean, I let it go.
Dad also said,
"you finish what you start."
Okay, I get it.
- Do you?
- Yes.
You're afraid
I'll stroll down memory lane
and I'll kick this wall
in my head so hard,
hell comes flooding through,
right?
And then all of a sudden,
I'm some drooling mess on the floor.
It's not a joke.
Okay. I know.
But listen... what's happening
here right now...
it's because I messed up somehow,
in some big way.
So every person who gets taken,
every person who dies...
that's on me.
I have to stop it.
And you'd do the same thing.
All right.
I'll follow up
with the brunettes.
You see what you get
from the cops.
So, you and Nicole were
roommates for a long time.
Since college, but we've been
best friends forever.
Hmm.
This whole thing's
really surreal.
Are you any closer
to finding her, or...?
We're doing everything we can.
Now, you were with Nicole
the night she went missing.
Did she say anything?
Nothing.
It's like I told the cops...
I wish there was something.
Where'd you get this?
Oh, Nicole got that
from that FBI guy.
Agent Roark.
About... about yea high?
Yeah, that was him.
One of the men
that disappeared last year
lived in our building.
Right.
So Agent Roark was asking us
all questions about it, I guess.
You guess?
So he... he came by here?
Oh, he came by a few times.
Did he?
To, uh...
speak to Nicole.
Right.
And how would you...
characterize
their relationship?
Relationship?
No, they weren't having a...
Just the... the... the tone
or the nature
of their conversation.
Well... loud...
and...
athletic.
Hold it right there!
Stop right there!
Hands where I can see them!
Get in my car,
or you're under arrest.
Look... no, sir.
Please just hold on
for a second.
There's been
a misunderstanding here.
Man, you are dumb
as a sack of hair...
coming back here
after what you did?
Look, there's been
a misunderstanding here.
You are not a damn agent, okay?
- The FBI never heard of you.
- Just listen.
Where are the bodies?
Mothers want to bury
their loved ones.
I don't know.
Where's Sheriff Dobbs?
You run out of town
soaked in blood...
Oh, and you bash my brains in
to do it...
and you really expect me
to buy that?
Look, would you believe that
I don't remember anything?
No.
But good luck
selling it to the judge.
What happened to my husband?
Look, I... I don't know.
Don't lie to me.
I know who you are, Sam.
I know what you do.
What?
You do?
Let me get this straight...
you're not feds.
You actually hunt things.
- We know how it sounds.
- I'm not sure you do.
You saw
those crime scenes, Roy.
You really think something human
could have taken those guys?
What you're saying...
it's impossible.
You know, I'm sorry,
I... I don't understand
what she's got to do
with any of this.
She's my wife.
She works with me
at the sheriff's station.
You tell something like this to me,
you tell it to her, too.
All right,
what do you need us to do?
Your husband...
he's the sheriff.
Was the sheriff,
until he vanished...
And you vanished.
What was I supposed to think?
T... that thing got him,
or that you killed him?
I just want to know
what happened.
So do I. Believe me.
Something happened to me.
I have no memory
of being here, ever.
What is this,
"Days of Our Lives?"
You're telling me you have
some sort of amnesia?
If I knew any of this,
would I have stepped foot
into this station?
I'm sorry.
I... I don't even
know your name.
If this is some sort of a game,
you're either incredibly clever
or incredibly stupid.
I'm telling the truth.
Look...
I don't know
what happened to your husband.
But I can find out.
How?
If you really know me,
then you know that's my job.
You really don't remember?
No. I really don't.
I'm Brenna Dobbs.
Brenna...
I'm sorry about what happened
to your husband.
But I can find answers...
just not from in here.
Come on.
Help me find some rope.
If it's gonna look
like a break-out,
you're gonna need to tie me up.
What?
The boxed stuff doesn't
get better with age, Don.
Ahh!
Aah!
Hey, Sam.
So, how does it feel
to be a fugitive again?
Hate to say
"I told you so."
You love
to say "I told you so."
Actually, you're right...
I do love to say "I told you so."
So, I found something on,
uh, "crazy eyes McGee."
Turns out you two
knew each other.
What?
Biblically. I just
spoke to her roommate.
I got to say, man...
you really got around.
I mean, soulless or not
I'm actually kind of impressed.
Eight Sierra Papa.
Got a 1057, 1100 block
of Hope Street. Over.
Missing person...
another one.
Okay, all right.
I'll go. You stay.
Yeah. Fine.
- Sam?
- What?
Stay here.
Fine! Go!
Listen, thank you
for your time.
We're on it.
Yeah. Thanks.
This is Sam.
Leave a message.
Sam, answer the phone, damn it.
I found the connection
between the missing chicks.
They all banged the same dude...
you.
It's you, Sam.
The texts, the victims,
all of it...
it's a trap for you.
Call me back.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- You can't be here!
Okay, p... please just listen.
- What happened to Debbie Harris?
- Debbie?
I let you out,
and she's just gone.
And y... you think
I did something to her?
I don't know what to think.
Look, um, I need your help.
Are you kidding?
I need the case files
that your husband made
about the disappearances
last year.
So go to the station
and find it.
It's not there.
I broke in and I looked,
and it's gone.
And I have a theory
about who might have it.
Look, we both want
the same thing here, Brenna.
I promise.
We want to find out
what happened last year,
and we want to stop
what's happening right now.
The file's upstairs.
I'll be right back.
Let's go!
So, you guys just travel
all the time?
I mean,
you just pick up and go?
Doesn't that get hard?
Not when you're young...
it's great.
Once you got a family,
it's a little tougher.
Deanna got pregnant,
and we didn't know
what we were gonna do.
But Mary was...
she was a blessing.
There's more in the garage.
Ah, listen, you sit.
I'll get it.
He misses her.
You know, at least you two
have each other.
Well, Samuel wasn't really
around when I was a kid.
We have more of a, uh,
business relationship.
Uh, do you have
any other family?
- Family just slows you down.
- Sam?
Sam?!
You all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Um... All right,
let's see what you have.
Best guess...
it came from an Arachne.
- You ever seen one?
- No one has...
not outside of Crete,
not for about 2,000 years.
- Then what do we even know about them?
- Zip.
Just a bunch of guesses
and a blurry picture
on the side of a Greek vase.
Yeah!
Ohh!
Yo, ho, sea Captain.
So, I gather we got no clue
how to kill this thing, huh?
I guess we just go at it
till something sticks.
Well, great. I got an idea of where
it might be, at least.
So far, all the vics have been
men in their 30s,
and they've all gone missing
within a 2-mile radius.
So we just get out
and kick bushes.
No, that'd be a waste of time.
I mean,
it's all suburban sprawl...
hundreds of houses, at least.
It could be anywhere.
- Lonely Pines Park.
- Yeah.
I say we make this thing
come to us.
How do we do that?
Hey, um, Brenna,
do you mind if I...
if I, um, borrow all this stuff
for a couple of hours?
Um, okay, I guess.
You really don't remember Roy,
do you?
He was a good man.
I've made peace that he's dead.
I have.
But I just want to know
what happened.
I'm sure he died a hero.
Sam, answer the phone,
damn it.
I found the connection
between the missing chicks.
They all banged
the same dude...
you.
It's you, Sam.
The texts, the victims, all of it...
it's a trap for you.
Call me back.
Whoa. Whoa.
I almost shot you...
again.
What the hell?
I figured you'd come
and talk to her.
I told you to stay home, man.
Did you get my message?
Come on. We got to get you
out of here. Let's go.
Well we know that this is a monster
with opposable thumbs
and unlimited text messaging,
and we know that it wants
to kill you specifically.
Does that about cover it?
It's an Arachne.
A what?
I remembered.
You remembered?
Y... I'm sorry.
Uh, what else
have you remembered?
Don't worry, all right?
I... it's nothing to do with Hell.
- Uh-huh. Not yet, anyway.
- What can I do, Dean?
The stuff is just starting
to come back, all right?
Maybe it's natural.
- We're leaving.
- No, we can't.
We are not the only hunters
on the planet, okay?
We can call Bobby.
- He and Rufus could come and wrap up.
- How?
Like you said,
it could be anybody.
- We got jack for leads.
- We know that it hates you.
I know who did this.
I just... I can't remember.
I don't think
you get the risk here, Sam.
- Yes, I do.
- Really?
You get that every time
you scratch that wall,
that you are playing
Russian roulette?
Dean, I get you're worried,
okay?
And I know what you think
is gonna happen.
- But you know what? It will or it won't.
- Sam...
Look, I'm starting to think
that... that I might have done
some bad stuff here, Dean.
And so I don't care
if it's dangerous.
I have to set things right,
'cause I got
a frigging soul now,
and... and it won't let me
just walk away.
I'm staying here.
And I need you to back me up.
All right.
Why not?
Well, let's "memento"
this thing, shall we?
So, you're back 'cause it
started again, right... the disappearances?
You're not feds.
You actually hunt things.
You really don't remember?
I, uh, found something
on "crazy eyes McGee."
Turns out you two
knew each other.
You okay?
That's right.
Yeah, Lonely Pines Park,
one hour. Thanks, Roy.
All right.
Are you sure about this?
The Arachne's been snacking
on mid-30s guys.
We need bait
that fits the demo.
I'm too young.
You're too old.
89 and counting.
I still think that we should
have looped Roy in on the plan.
Do we want a credible
performance, or don't we?
But what if something
goes wrong?
Roy's a big boy.
He'll be fine.
Trust me.
It's just... not the way
I'm used to doing things.
Got it.
Welcome to the future.
Let's go.
Let's hope this thing's hungry.
Ugh! Aah!
Let's split up, look for him.
No, no, wait.
It's too late.
- Let's go!
- They're gone, Samuel!
Look... it's okay. I turned on
the G.P.S. on Roy's cell.
In English, please.
We can track them back
to wherever she goes.
So, what, Roy's just
some red-shirt to you?
Just spider bait?
No, no, of course not.
This is my back-up plan.
My God, son. You're about
as cold as they come,
you know that?
Let's go.
Poor bastard.
Help me.
I can't... feel...
Roy, hey, where is she?
Ugh!
Unh!
Aah!
Ow.
Ahh.
Well, I guess
decapitation works.
Roy.
You're gonna be okay.
Just hang in.
We're gonna get you some help.
Listen, if we can get him
to the hospital quick...
- He can't be helped.
- What?
I don't know about Arachne,
but I do know about spiders.
One brown recluse bite
can kill you. This thing?
Look at these guys...
that poison's eating them alive.
- They're just dead men walking.
- So, what are you saying?
I'm saying we put him
out of his misery.
Sam... please.
Killing this thing
saved a lot of lives.
- We couldn't have done it without you.
- No.
You're a hero.
We can't just
leave the bodies here.
Get the gasoline.
I know what happened.
Roy?
I love you.
What are you gonna say
to Brenna?
Relax, Dean.
Hey, Brenna, it's... it's Sam.
I'm just checking in.
Yeah, of course I can swing by.
Okay. Yeah. Bye.
What was that about?
She wants me to swing by.
For?
She said it's no big deal.
But I can tell
she's in deep trouble.
Dean, back door.
Sam.
Light's on in the shed.
My spidey senses are tingling.
Shh.
Sam?
Brenna?
Hey.
What you did to Roy...
is it true?
Answer the question, Sam.
You got to admit
I look good, Sam.
Well, except for
your little souvenir.
You win. I'm here.
Let Brenna go.
This has nothing
to do with her.
You come back around,
start hanging out
with my wife,
and you think this has
nothing to do with her?
But then... you thought
I was out of the way, right?
I got to say, you get
a hell of a lot wrong, Sam,
like that thing
you threw me to.
You thought
it was here to feed.
- She was here to breed.
- Yeah.
That thing was playing
the mating game,
and I guess
I fit her profile...
Me and all those other
poor bastards.
She bit us to turn us
into what she was.
By the time
you pulled that trigger,
I wasn't human.
Not anymore.
So bullets didn't hurt me much.
Oh, and neither did fire.
So after you left,
well, we ran.
Me... I hid for months,
nearly starved.
But you know
what kept me going?
Every night, I dreamed about
ripping your throat out.
I thought I was sending you
a neon sign.
The text?
Taking all those girls
you screwed?
I was kicking so much sand
in your eye,
I couldn't figure out
why you weren't getting it!
Then Bren tells me
you've got brain damage.
It's just too good.
Where are they, Roy...
the women?
Scattered... in the wind.
They're like me now.
You killed one monster,
you made so many more.
Congratulations.
The only question is,
do I kill you...
or turn you?
Ugh!
No! Roy, stop!
Brenna...
Look, I am so sorry.
Brenna, I... I mean, I...
You okay?
You were right.
We shouldn't have
come back here.
Well, you did
kill the spider man.
So, you're suggesting what I did
back there was a good thing?
- I'm just saying...
- What?
Sam, y... y... you got to understand
that all that crap last year...
all of it...
none of it was you.
Let's be crystal clear, okay?
It was me.
Well, can I get you anything?
What are you now, my waitress?
I'm just trying to make you feel better.
Don't be a bitch.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Yeah, you look fine.
All I'm saying is
everything's gonna be okay.
I don't know, Dean.
If I did this here,
then who knows how many oth...
Sammy?
Sammy?!
Sammy, talk to me!
== Sync by elderman ==
== corrections by elderman & gloriabg ==
== www.addic7ed.com ==
Edited by Scooby