Name's Crowley.
You're Crowley?
I see
you have heard of me.
I can give you
anything you want, mate.
- All I need is...
- My soul.
You sold your soul?
Oh, more like pawned it.
- I fully intend to give it back.
- Well, then give it back!
- I can't.
- Can't or won't?
I won't, all right?
It's insurance.
- Rufus Turner. He's a hunter.
- One of your old friends?
Friend? He's not
the Christmas-card type.
Gentlemen.
I'm Sheriff Jody Mills.
I don't believe
we've had the pleasure.
Agent Willis speaking.
- Bobby?
- Oh...
So you know Bobby Singer?
Bobby, I thought
the Sheriff hated you?
She did
till five days ago.
What happened
five days ago?
The dead started rising
all over town.
Bobby, you just
gonna sit there?
No, I'm gonna Riverdance.
Really wasted
that crossroads deal.
Son of a bitch.
Hello...
king of the crossroads.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
'Cause there's been a few times
that you got me wondering.
- Something's different with you.
- I'm okay.
You went to hell, Sam.
Yesterday, this Galveston
shoreline was being pounded
by 10-foot swells and winds
up to 150 miles per hour.
But today, well,
there's not a cloud in sight.
Hurricane Tiffany has broken up
over the Gulf,
and our 5-day forecast
calls for nothing...
...But sun and clear skies.
I guess somebody up there
likes us.
Thank you, Phil...
Et ad congregandum...
Eos coram me.
Been making merry,
have we?
Bite me.
If that's your thing.
That swan dive of Sam's
was a thing of beauty.
Tens all the way 'round,
standing "O"
from the Romanian judge.
You should be proud, Bobby.
As deaths go,
it wasn't too shabby.
Cheer up, mate!
We just saved the sodding world
together.
Me?
I've been celebrating.
I hate to see what you call
"celebrating."
Yes, you would.
Drink?
No.
Let me get this straight.
We just "Saved
the sodding world together,"
and you're
too good to drink with me?
Obviously.
And I doubt
that you have my brand.
What's your poison,
your highness?
Craig, aged 30 years, at least.
Been drinking it
since grade school.
Well...
I got old rotgut...
Aged six days.
Swill like that is gonna
burn a hole in your soul.
Oh, sorry.My soul.
But that's why you called...
our little... deal?
Yeah, well...
it's about time
you hold up your end
and give it back.
Give it back?
Our deal was...
We ice Lucifer,
you rip up the lease.
Oh.
You didn't read your contract.
The hell you talking about, contract?
Paragraph 18, subsection "B."
Which is
on your naughty bits...
I only have to make
"best efforts"
to give you back your soul.
Meaning what?
Meaning...
I'd like to...
but I can't.
You lying sack of...
10 years...
you come to daddy.
Till then, I suggest you start
drinking the good stuff.
I figured you'd say that.
So you can rot here
until you change your mind.
- Why? 'Cause you asked nicely?
- No.
'Cause I'm going "Dateline"
on your ass.
I hope that's paint.
Really?
What am I going to do?
Doggy breath.
Bracing, isn't it?
Ball's in your court, Robert.
10 years of living...
or 10 years as Alpo.
This ain't over.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
Happy hunting.
Season 6 Episode 4
"Weekend at Bobby's"
No EMF.
Find anything in there?
Yeah, I got some kind of a... claw
What in the hell
has a claw like that?
That is a good question.
Maybe he's in the can.
Yeah?
- What happened, you fall and can't get back up?
- Hilarious.
- What's up?
- We're in Wisconsin.
Six bodies,
chests cracked wide open.
No EMF, no sulfur,
no hex bags.
We did find this, though.
Hang on.
All right, check your wang.
That's a new one.
Yeah, we need an I.D. ASAP.
This thing's on a rampage.
Call as soon
as you dig something up.
Dean, I'm a little busy.
Well, then kick Bo Derek
out of your bathtub.
We got a case here.
I'll call you back.
Balls.
Balls!
Come on!
You're hunting a Lamia.
Come again?
It's a monster.
Juices hearts, chugs the blood.
Never heard of one popping up
outside of Greece, though.
Yeah, well, looks like
this freak has immigrated.
It's snacking
on cheese-heads.
How do we gank it?
There's a couple of ways.
Easiest is a silver knife
blessed by a padre.
Gotcha.
You're welcome.
Hey! I'm still here!
Hey, there, cranky.
You were gone so long,
I just assumed alcoholic coma.
- Where were we?
- Your soul.
Right.
Talk.
Look at you... all in a rush.
Foreplay...
gets you more play.
I want Crowley's name.
His real name,
back when he was flesh
and blood.
Does tying demons up
in your basement
make you feel better
about that time
you killed your wife?
What's that?
You don't recognize them?
They're yours.
It won't work.
It's a myth.
Then you got nothing
to worry about.
I can't!
You don't know
what he'll do to me.
- Right now, you better worry about me.
- You don't get it.
He's the king.
King of the crossroads,
I've heard the speech.
No.
King of hell.
You gonna get that
or what?
Marcy.
- Bobby Singer, how long have we been neighbors?
- Six months.
Well, don't you think
it's time
you welcomed me
to the neighborhood?
My famous
ginger-peach cobbler.
Take a whiff.
Seriously, I'm a genius.
Help me!
Somebody help me!
It's, um...
stupid horror flicks.
Guilty pleasure.
I love scary movies.
Hey, have you seen
"Drag Me to Hell"?
Trying to avoid it.
But it's fantastic.
Saturday, 7:00, my house.
I'll fix you dinner,
and I'll whip up a batch of my
famous white-chocolate popcorn,
and we'll watch it.
Deal?
That sounds super, Marcy,
but, uh...
Okay, no worries.
Um, hey, one other thing...
uh, my wood chipper...
it's a piece of crap.
You know, it just
broke down on me,
and... and I hear
that you're quite handy.
Maybe you could come over
and... take a look.
You know, just whenever.
Yeah, I'll see
what I can do.
Okay.
Okay, see you soon.
Aw! She sounds nice.
Are you gonna
make sweet love to her
before you stab
her to death, Bobby?
That is your usual thing, right?
I want Crowley's name, now!
- Crowley's name!
- Okay!
Okay.
Macleod.
Fergus Macleod.
I swear.
We call him lucky the leprechaun
behind his back.
Macleod's Scottish, Einstein.
You got what you want.
Now send me back.
No.
We had a deal!
Gave it my best effort.
No!
Yeah, Garth. What do you got?
I've never heard of a vamp doing that.
Doesn't sound
like our kind of thing.
Better drop a dime to the FBI.
Willis. FBI.
No, Garth. Not me, the FBI.
The real FBI.
How are you still alive?
You got Castle.
Yeah.
Willis.
Uh-huh.
Of course she's one of ours.
And if she says
she's got to dig that grave up,
you better damn well let her.
Mm.
Oh, good, you're home.
Listen, you got to
help me bury a body.
Why'd you bring it here?
The law is on my tail.
What was your guess?
What? What? What?
They got lucky.
Yeah,
or you're getting slow.
I'm getting slow.
Yeah, says Mr. "sits on his ass
all day taking calls."
Vamp? Shifter? What?
None of the above.
Okami?
Where'd you shiv it?
Get this... billings.
Only time I ever saw
one of these was in Japan.
Duh! No one's ever seen
one of these except in Japan.
For what it's worth,
Sam and Dean are tracking
a Lamia in Wisconsin.
Get out. I thought
they never leave Greece.
Monsters lately...
is it me, or is it weird?
Yeah, well, it's...
definitely something.
So, you got a shovel?
Man! I know what I want
for Hanukkah.
So, the son of a bitch's name
is Fergus Macleod?
That's the son of a bitch's name.
Where you gonna look?
Scotland.
Crowley let slip
that he likes Craig.
It's, um...
It's Scotch.
Only made and sold
in a tiny area
on the north tip
of Caithness County.
It's peaty and sharp
with a long finish
of citrus and tobacco notes.
Hey, what?
What am I, a heathen?
I know what Craig is.
Well, I got a hunch that, that's
where Crowley lived and died,
back when he was a human...
a few hundred years before
he got the big squeeze in hell
and came out a demon.
You know, I got contacts
over there.
I can make a few calls.
I ain't asking
for no help.
I'm not asking
for your permission.
Yeah.
What's another way
to kill a Lamia?
Well, what happened
to the silver knife
- blessed by a priest?
- That didn't pan out.
What's plan "B"?
Police!
- Balls!
- Come on, Bobby, get the lead out.
- Where are you?
- The church... in a rectory.
- Is there a kitchen?
- Yeah.
Find salt and rosemary.
Open up, Singer!
Mr. Singer, I'm Agent Adams.
I believe you know Sheriff Mills.
Come on.
My mom. Just a second.
- Rosemary! I got it!
- Great, great.
Now blend the herbs,
saut? over a high heat.
Cook well.
Sammy! Fire in the hole!
Okay, great, great.
Enjoy the roast, mom.
Have you seen this man?
Rufus Turner,
aka Luther Vandross,
aka Ruben Studdard?
- No. Never seen that dick.
- How you know he's a dick?
- Lucky guess.
- Funny.
'Cause I got a couple guys
working the highway,
said they saw him pull in here,
carrying a body.
Well, that's ridiculous.
Look, it's a work day.
I got to...
We just want
to take a look around.
You got a warrant, Sonny?
Well, do I need one... Sir?
Okay, fellas,
put the rulers away. Zip up.
Look, Bobby here's
kind of a...
Crank.
And he ain't what you call
a fan of Big Brother.
But me and him...
how long I been
arresting you now, 10 years?
- Thereabouts.
- Yeah, we got a history.
So, what do you say you just
let me scope the place out?
That okay?
You can just wait outside.
Five minutes.
Great.
Why'd you send him
outside?
'Cause I didn't think
you'd want him in here.
- I don't. I've got a body in the basement.
- My point.
Yeah, but I've got another body
buried in the yard.
Damn it.
He's not there.
Balls.
Mr. Singer,
come with me please.
You mind explaining this?
What, you never had
a septic tank explode on you?
I got it pretty well cleaned up,
but watch where you step.
Get back here.
Get back... I'm two states
over, Bobby. I can't...
The okami ain't dead.
Of course it is.
- Did you use a bamboo dagger?
- Yeah.
Blessed by a Shinto priest?
I'm not an imbecile, Bobby.
Did you stab it seven times?
Five times.
It's seven.
No, I'm pretty sure
it's five.
Well, clearly
it's seven times.
The damn hole is empty.
What was it feeding on
when you found it?
Single, white females...
While they slept.
Aah!
Bobby? Where's your bedroom?
Bobby, I am trying
to keep my cool here.
What are you doing in my house
with a shotgun?
Have you see anything... weird?
You mean besides you?
Bobby! No!
Look out!
I, uh...
I thought
your chipper was broke.
I just said that
to get you over here.
Oh.
Well...
I guess I could come over
for dinner some night.
Might be fun.
I don't think so.
Story of my life.
Your still alive, huh?
Don't act so surprised.
- How about Godzilla?
- Put her down.
So, you just happened
to have a bamboo dagger
blessed by a Shinto priest
laying around?
Wood chipper.
Oh, okeydokey.
That... that pretty much
trumps... everything.
Listen, uh, Bobby, um...
Thank you.
I screwed up.
Forget it.
I figure I still owe you
more than you owe me.
All righty. Then add
one more thing to the list.
I got a lead
on your boy Crowley...
aka Fergus Rodric Macleod.
Born in Canisbay, Scotland,
1661.
Great. I don't know
what that's gonna get me.
All right. Well, then, behind
door number two, Bob...
Crowley had a son.
Did he, now?
Yeah, name of Gavin.
Moved across the pond
after his parents bit it
and captained
a trading ship
that went down
in Massachusetts in 1723.
A couple of Cousteau
wannabes found the wreck
about 30 years ago.
- They fish out his bones?
- No, no.
They did find his
signet ring, though.
It's part of the "Treasures
From the Deep" exhibit
at the Maritime Museum
in Andover.
I need that ring.
Ooh!
Oh, are you, um...
you asking for my help, Bob?
Bobby?
I'm asking for a ring.
And... I'd appreciate your...
help getting it.
I'm way ahead of you, brother.
I'm headed for Andover now.
I should be there
around midnight.
You're, um...
you're thinking
hostage exchange, aren't you?
I mean, get the ring,
you can summon junior's ghost.
Get the ghost, you can swap
Crowley his son for your soul.
Something like that.
Let's hope that works out.
Dean, you all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, the Lamia grilled up fine.
I sense a "but" coming on.
It's Sam, Bobby.
He's just... he's different.
You know, and I get it.
You go through something like that,
and... and you change.
But...
Something's not right to me.
- Dean...
- I've got a few questions about that year.
- When you saw him and I didn't.
- Dean, I got another call.
- You what?
- Just hang on.
I got to take this.
It's important.
More important than Sam?
Bobby?
Rufus?
The good news is I snagged
the ring, Bobby. However...
- Tell me that ain't...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Three guesses, and one of 'em...
it ain't the paramedics.
- Listen, Bobby, I-I got to stash this ring.
- But don't swallow it.
Right. I'm swallowing it, Bobby.
Don't swallow it.
Ahh!
Damn it.
Aw, hell!
Get on
the ground! Out of the car!
I know my rights, damn it!
That is unnecessary force.
You still there, Dean?
Bobby, what the hell?
I-I'm sorry.
You know, you are the one person
that I can talk to
about this stuff...
about... about Sam,
about leaving Lisa and Ben.
I mean, I don't... I don't even
know which way is up right now.
Bobby?
Hello?
I-I hear you, son.
I-it just ain't a good time.
Yeah, okay.
You know what?
Forget it.
I mean, I'm baring my soul
like a freaking girl here,
and, uh...
and you've got stuff to do.
Well, that is... that's fine.
That's fine, but seriously,
though... a little selfish.
Not all about you.
Where's your brother?
Outside.
Get him.
You're on speaker, Bobby.
Sam? Dean?
I love you like my own.
I do.
But sometimes...
sometimes,
you two are the whiniest,
most self-absorbed
sons of bitches I ever met.
I'm selfish?
Me?
I do everything for you... everything!
You need some lore scrounged up?
You need your asses
pulled out of the fire?
You need someone to bitch to
about each other?
You call me,
and I come through...
every... damn... time.
And what do I get for it?
Jack with a side of squat!
- Bobby...
- Do I sound like I'm done?
Now, look, I know
you've got issues.
God knows I know.
But I got a news flash for you.
You ain't the center
of the universe.
Now, it may have
slipped your mind
that Crowley owns my soul
and the meter is running!
And I will be damned
if I am gonna sit around
and... and be damned!
So, how about you two sack up
and help me for once?!
Bobby, all...
all you got to do is ask.
Anything you need, we're there.
Hey!
Got a call
from Marcy Ward.
Seems she had
a little home invasion.
Told her I'd look into it.
Didn't bother filing a report.
Thanks.
Need a favor.
Luther Vandross turn up?
Tell him I'm a fan.
His real name's
Rufus Turner.
He's being held
in Andover, Mass.,
on a burglary charge.
Need you to get him
extradited here.
Extradited for what?
Murder.
You're not joking.
Do you have any idea what it
takes to extradite a prisoner?
I'd need a court order,
permission from the D.A.
I-I would have to call in
every marker I got
and hand out a few to boot.
So, you're saying
there's a chance.
And if by some miracle we can
get him here, then what?
Then your pal's here
on a murder charge.
How you gonna to get him out
from under that one?
Let me handle
the "B" side.
I like you, Bobby,
but this could nuke my career.
Look, I've done a lot
for this town...
some you know about,
some you don't.
And I'm not real good at this
whole "asking for help" thing,
but...
I'm sorry, Bobby. I can't.
Miss me?
- How did you...
- Don't ask.
You got one hour,
and then I call the Feds
and tell them he busted out.
Thanks.
I lose my job over this,
I am taking it out of your ass.
Tell me the ring is still
in your stomach.
I'll go boil some water.
What?
Amate spiritus obscure...
Te quaerimus.
Oramus nobiscum colloquere...
Apud nos circita.
Gavin Macleod?
Is...
is this hell?
That's gonna depend on you.
Are you
Fergus Macleod's boy?
You and me...
are gonna have
a nice, long chat.
Well, you look like hammered crap.
And you're a vision, as always.
Don't we both know
how this game ends?
Really, Bobby...
you got to know
when to fold 'em.
Word on the street is,
that ever since Lucifer
went to the pokey,
you're the big kahuna downstairs.
- I see you've been reading The Trades.
- Trouble in paradise?
Mate, you have no idea.
I thought...
That when I got
the corner office...
I thought
it was all gonna be...
rainbows and two headed puppies.
But if I'm being honest...
it's been hell.
Thought that was the point.
You know what the problem
with demons is?
- They're demons?
- Exactly.
Evil, lying prats,
the whole lot of them.
And stupid.
Try to show them a-a new way...
a better way...
and what do you get?
Bugger all!
You know, there's days that I think
Lucifer's whole "spike anything
with black eyes" plan
wasn't half bad.
Feels good to get that
off my chest.
We should make this
a thing.
Do I look like Dr. Phil
to you?
A little.
Anyhoo...
Obviously not here
for a social call,
so on with it.
I want...
Ah.
I'll save you the recap.
In fact, I'll do
the shorthand for you.
I want my soul back, idjit!
Afraid not.
But
I'm surly, and I got a beard!
Gimme!
Blah, blah, blah,
homespun, cornpone insult,
witty retort from yours truly.
The bottom line is...
you get bubkes.
Are we done?
Just getting started.
Gavin?
Is that you?
I-it's... it's been so long.
I love you so...
Sorry.
Your soul for my boy...
that's it, right?
I got to give you credit
for thinking outside the box
on that one,
but problem is,
I loathe the little bastard.
You want to torture him?
Just let me pull up a chair,
and I'll watch.
Hell, burn his bones,
send him down to me.
We can have
a family reunion.
That's right, son?
You picked the wrong bargaining
chip this time, my friend.
He ain't a chip.
I was just using him
to dig up dirt on you.
And since Gavin hates you
maybe even more
than you hate him,
he was more than happy
to squawk.
What did you
tell him, son?
Everything.
I know it all now...
Fergus.
Now, you may be
king of the dirt-bags here,
but in life, you were nothing
but a two-bit tailor
who sold his soul
in exchange for an extra
3 inches below the belt.
Just trying
to hit double digits.
So...
you got a glimpse
behind the curtain.
And?
And...
Now I know
where you're planted.
Hiya, Crowley.
Dean.
It's been a long time.
- We should get together.
- Sure.
We'll have to do that
when I get back.
- Back?
- Yeah.
Me and Sam...
we've gone international.
In fact, we're in
your neck of the woods.
Did you really
used to wear a skirt?
A kilt.
I had very athletic calves.
- What's the game?
- Dominoes.
In fact,
we just dug yours up.
This is ridiculous.
The whole burning-bones thing...
I-it's a myth.
I know an employee
of yours who'd disagree.
What's that?
You don't recognize 'em?
They're yours.
That's where she got to.
You demons.
You think
you're something special,
but you're just spirits.
Twisted, perverted,
evil spirits,
but end of the day,
you're nothing but ghosts
with an ego.
We torch your bones,
you go up in flames.
You hear that, Crowley?
That's me flicking my bic
for you.
Your bones for my soul.
Going once.
Going twice.
Bollocks!
You can go ahead and leave in
the part about my legs.
Pleasure doing business with you.
Now, if you don't mind...
I believe those are mine.
You know, now that
I think about it,
maybe I'll just...
...napalm your ass anyhow.
Dean...
he's a Dick...
but a deal's a deal.
I don't need you to fight
my battles for me, moose.
Get bent.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
I have a little hell to raise.
I appreciate you
boys lending a hand
Hey, anytime we get
to punk Crowley works for us.
Yeah.
Still, knowing how much you love
flying the friendly skies.
I guess a 9-hour plane trip
was no picnic.
What'd you do,
drink your way through it?
I was fine.
No, he white-knuckled his way
through four puke bags.
Well, at least I was sober.
Some nut-job decided to try
something, I was ready.
I had a fork.
Listen, um...
About the things
I said earlier...
- I was in a tough spot, and I-I guess I was...
- You were right, Bobby.
We take you for granted.
You've been cleaning up
our messes for years, Bobby.
Without you, I don't even want to think about
where me and Sam would have ended up.
Okay, then. Let's roll credits
on this chick flick.
You boys have a safe flight.
And, uh, try some
of the local grub.
I hear it's... exotic.
Oh, yeah, no, definitely,
we are.
I hear they have
an olive garden.
Willis.
Yeah, he is.
One of our best agents, in fact.
-- sync by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Edited by Scooby