People are talking about what we're doing out here every day.
We're gonna have to tell 'em.
They're not ready. I saw a beach craft.
What is inside of it, John?
You're gonna have to climb up there for us and find out.
Anybody out there? Mayday. Mayday.
Help!
What happened?
There was an accident. Boone fell off a cliff.
Tell me exactly what happened.
John? Locke!
Come on, out of the way.
I need room.
Keep him steady.
Boone, can you hear me? It's okay. We got you.
- What happened?
- Fell down a cliff.
- But he was with Locke.
- Keep him steady now.
He's bleeding a lot.
I know he's bleeding. Keep him steady, damn it.
You gotta press harder than that, Kate.
I'm trying.
All right, slow now. Slow and gentle.
Easy.
Sun, a pair of scissors in the second drawer of the cart.
Second drawer!
Diapers in the first drawer.
Sun's gonna switch places with you.
- Sun, I need --
- Yes, I understand.
Hurley, grab me that first-class seat from up there.
I need that mesh. We need to create some sort of sterile --
Hurley, I swear to god, if you faint!
No. First-class, mesh. I'm cool.
Get to the beach. Ransack Sawyer's stuff.
I want his alcohol -- rubbing, scotch.
Jack, what's going on?
His lung just collapsed.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Good, Boone.
Good, Boone. That's good. Good job.
All right, I'm gonna put a tube in that, and you're gonna be just fine.
What are you still doing here?
The alcohol, Kate! If you want him to live, get to the beach now!
Damn it, just get the stupid clip-on, huh?
You know why they call it a tie? 'Cause you gotta tie it.
You know why they call ita clip-on? 'Cause you clip it... on.
You nervous, silverman?
What the hell do I have to be nervous about?
- It's a big responsibility.
- I can handle responsibility.
Maybe. But I know that you don't like to get up in front of crowds.
I'll be fine.
After about eight beers, I'll be fine.
- She'll bust you, man.
- I'll brush my teeth.
She'll bust ya.
You can still back out, Marty.
Nah.
It's just a stupid speech. I'll make you proud.
Okay, groom's turn.
You can still back out, Jack.
Oh, it hurts.
It's a closed fracture, but I think I can set it.
His chest -- the wound -- can you, uh, sew him?
He's lost a lot of blood.
I don't know how far Locke had to carry him.
Boone, listen to me -- listen!
You are not gonna die.
I'm gonna fix this, okay?
I am gonna save you.
Got to flip them, or they'll burn, Walt.
Hey, mamacita.
Want some fish?
No, thanks. I'm not really hungry.
How long, do you think, till it's ready?
Maybe a week. Maybe less.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
She likes me.
Hey, Jin!
Jin, want some fish?
Take a break. Eat some fish.
Man's got what I call an overzealous work ethic.
Try obsession.
He wants off this island bad, man.
Can't say I blame poor cato.
His lady speaks english all this time, and he didn't have a clue?
I'm surprised he didn't try to swim out of here.
- Hell, I would--
- Sawyer!
I need all your alcohol. Now!
How'd it happen?
Locke said that he fell off a cliff while they were hunting boar.
The boar they never seem to get.
- Is that it?
- I'm afraid so.
Do you need anything else?
- I can come with you.
- Too many cooks already.
But thanks.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- He needs blood.
- What?
B lood.
Transfusion.
- How will you --
- I don't know.
I'll figure it out...
after I set the leg.
Let me.
No, it's okay.
Get some air.
How is he?
Don't  know yet.
Well, what happened out there? Where's Locke?
I don't know.
What, he just took off?
Yeah, Charlie, he just took off.
- Where's Shannon?
- I don't know.
- Well, she's his sister --
- I don't know where she is!
And here she is, the future mrs. Jack Shepard.
Thank you.
Wow, can I get another microphone?
I think this one's been drinking.
A little over two years ago, I blew a tire out,
flipped over the center divider into oncoming traffic
and was hit head-on by an S.U.V.
My back was broken.
They all said it was irreparable.
And then there was Jack.
And he promised that he would fix me
because that's the kind of guy he is.
Because you are the most committed man I have ever known.
Because you fixed me,
I will dance at our wedding.
To Jack.
My hero, Jack.
Give him this for the pain.
I think we're a little beyond herbal remedies here.
It is not a remedy.
Will you hold his shoulders?
Here we go.
Oh!
Oh, no.
Come on.
Claire?
What are you doing out here?
Nothing. Just leave me alone, please.
Oh, god.
You're having a baby.
Claire, we need to get you back to camp.
No, I'm fine. I just need to catch my breath.
It's not okay. You're having your baby.
No, I'm not, okay? It's just gas pains. It's fine.
You're having contractions, Claire.
No, I'm bloody not. Can you just leave me alone?
I gotta get you to Jack. Please try to stand. Please.
Look, I can't!
Help!
Somebody help!
Somebody please help!
Help!
Please help! Somebody!
Jin, I need you to go to the caves and get Jack, okay? You understand?
We need Jack.
Jack. Doctor.
Yes. Yes, the doctor. Please come here.
Don't leave me.
Oh, no, no, honey. I won't.
I'm not going anywhere, okay? I promise.
Jack. Hurry.
- Ask him again.
- He's in shock.
That's why you need to ask him again.
Boone, can you hear me?
What is your blood type?
Boone, please listen.
- Damn it.
- Maybe a smaller piece.
Veins are like a wet noodle.
First you have to find one,
then you have to have a hollow needle sharp enough to actually pierce it.
I've got bamboo.
None of it actually even matters because I don't know his blood type.
- Not to mention that his injuries --
- A-negative.
Boone, what'd you say?
Shannon...
Did you hear "a-negative"?
Get Charlie, ask everyone you can find -- everyone -- what their blood type is.
A-negative, okay?
And find his sister. Find Shannon.
Where are we going?
This way.
Oh, okay.
Are you lost?
No. Absolutely not.
Those trees look really familiar.
It's this way, I think.
Did you just say, "I think"?
Surprise.
Damn  it!
I found an "A."
- Positive or negative?
- She doesn't know.
I also found two B-positives and one AB-negative.
At least, he thinks so.
Did you find any O-negative?
- Sun said A-negative.
- Where is she?
We split up. I thought she'd be back here.
So you only asked four people?
I asked the whole sodding camp. No one knows their blood type.
I don't know my bloody blood type.
Did you find Shannon?
No, I was getting you this.
A hollow needle sharp enough to pierce a noodle.
It's perfect.
Not to rain on your proverbial parade,
but I thought you said we needed someone who was A-negative?
Or o-negative.
Right, which judging by your tantrum, no one is.
Someone is.
You? Why'd you make us --
O-neg is the universal donor.
It's in the ballpark, it's not a match.
My blood could put himin to anaphylactic shock --
stop his heart.
You mean he'll die?
He's not gonna die.
Those girls are checking you out.
- You're in your PJs.
- Indeed, I am.
- Are they cute?
- Who?
The girls that are checking me out.
Mm, one of them's kinda cute,
the other one's just trashy.
- "Heart and soul"?
- You got it.
- I'm taking the easy part.
- Of course.
You know, you really don't have to do this if you don't want to.
How do you know I haven't?
Because you haven't.
Oops, sorry.
It was a silly idea.
I just -- I read too many bridal magazines. I think it rotted my brain.
Sarah, I want to. I'm going to.
I just have to figure out the right way to say it.
They're just vows.
Just vows?
Hey,
he's gonna come.
Yeah, I know.
So, you stay down here as long as you need to.
And when you're ready, I'll be upstairs.
I cannot wait to marry you, Jack Shepard.
Jack.
- Jack. Doctor. Jack.
- Jack.
Claire.
Claire? What about Claire?
He says Claire's with Kate. She's in labor.
Claire's having the baby? Where? Where?
He says he thinks she's okay, but she's in pain.
Does he know how fast the contractions are coming?
Every two minutes.
Is she nauseous?
Can she stand?
Is there any bleeding? Did her water break?
No, none of that.
But she can't move.
We should go.
What do we need? Towels, bandages, hot water.
How do we take hot water?
I'm sure you'll figure all that out.
You tell Jin to take Charlie with him and go back to Claire.
I can do that. That dilating thing, how do I look out for that?
Listen to me. Tell Kate -- Charlie, look at me.
Tell Kate
to wait until the contractions are 60 seconds apart. You got that?
Now, she's gonna need to make sure that Claire pushes,
but not too hard, not too fast --
just until the head is clear, and then as hard as she can.
When the baby is out, you make sure she clears its nose
and its mouth.
Okay, but you'll be there by then, right?
No, I won't. I'm not going anywhere.
I need to stay here.
Now you tell Kate she's gonna have to deliver this baby.
They've stopped.
That happens, I think.
No, no. They're not coming anymore.
I'm fine. I'm okay. I'm okay, really.
Claire --
No, no, no. I'm okay, really.
Claire, I don't thinkthat you should be doing --
What is that?
I think your water just broke.
No, no, no. I can't have the baby!
- Just hold on.
- I can't have the baby now!
Just hold on. Jack's coming. Claire, he's coming.
Screwed myself up pretty bad, huh?
Hey.
My leg hurts.
Don't try to move it.
Can  you breathe okay?
It fell on me.
What fell?
The plane. I was in the plane.
Boone, Boone, Locke said you fell from a cliff.
No.
No. It fell.
The plane.
It's 'cause of the hatch.
We found a hatch.
Boone, Boone, stay with me, man.
Hey, stay with me.
Locke said --
John --
John said...
not to tell about the hatch.
What did Locke do? What hatch?
My leg hurts.
Boone. Boone!
Hey.
Shannon.
I need to tell you something.
All right.
My brother -- Boone -- he's not really my brother.
He's my stepbrother.
Our parents got married when we were, like, 8 and 10.
He's kind of in love with me.
In love with you?
And how do you feel towards him?
I'll always feel something for him,
but am I in love with him in that way?
No.
Not at all.
We're here for god knows how long, and so is Boone.
Maybe we should go back.
I don't wanna go back.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
I just...
need to take it a little slow.
Are you okay with that?
I had no expectations.
Right.
Hopes, not expectations.
Oh, god, that hurts.
Hello?
Hey. Kate.
Claire. Is she okay?
- Where's Jack?
- He couldn't come.
What do you mean he couldn't come? He has to come.
Yeah, he's pouring his own blood into Boone's arm right now.
Okay. Okay.
We'll just have to pick her up and bring her to him.
No, Kate.
No, we have to get her to him before it's too late.
Look...
Jack said you have to deliver the baby.
What?
Now he talked me through it, and it's relatively simple.
- Charlie, I can't do this.
- Yes, you can. I have water --
You're not listening to me. I can't deliver this baby.
Well, somebody bloody has to.
You know, I was out there for over a week.
There are days I can't remember.
I mean, what if --
what if they did something to the baby?
God, I'm not ready for this.
I'm not --
I'm so scared.
I'm scared.
Hey...
I'm -- I'm scared, too.
But we're gonna get through this together.
Okay?
Come on, Boone.
It's not working.
Blood's not the problem. It's the leg.
All the blood's pooling there.
Compartment syndrome.
He didn't get this injury from a fall.
Something crushed his leg.
What are you doing?
You've given him enough.
Hurley.
Whoa, dude. You all right, man? You're looking kinda goth.
- Look, where's Michael?
- Beach, I think.
I need you to go get him for me, okay?
What for?
Just get him.
Hey, kiddo.
Hey.
How's the water?
Ah... it's fantastic.
Screaming kid next to me in first class.
How does that happen, huh?
What you got there?
Oh. Sarah wants us to write our own vows.
"My heart skips beats at the sound of your voice.
My skin... warms to the touch of your fingers.
Where you go, I will go," et cetera, et cetera.
This is -- this is very nice.
Ha ha. Those aren't my vows.
Those are hers. I stole them out of the room.
I can't write mine.
Yeah, well, you're a doctor. You're not a writer.
- Right.
Sarah is a beautiful girl.
Hell yeah, she is.
You love her?
Absolutely.
Then why are you sitting out here?
What if I can't be the husband or the --
or the father that I want to be?
What if I asked her because --
because I saved her life?
Should I marry her, dad?
Commitment is what makes you tick, Jack.
The problem is
you're just not good at letting go.
So you're saying Locke lied?
He didn't fall.
His leg was pinned under something -- something heavy.
Okay, Jack, wait. The cargo container.
We got to do this. What about the axe?
Can't use the axe.
What are you doing?
His right leg is filling with blood.
If I don't stop it, I won't be able to save him.
- You don't mean --
- The leg is dead.
There's no other choice.
Claire...
I think this is about the time you're supposed to start pushing, okay?
So, uh, push.
And...
don't hold your breath, honey.
You're not gonna be able to push if you hold --
Claire?
Claire, what are you doing?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Claire, you need to push right now.
Don't do this, Claire, okay?
You can't stop this. This is happening.
Your baby is coming, and I need your help.
It's not going to want me.
What?
It knows I don't want it and I was gonna give it away.
Babies know that stuff.
Do you want this baby now? Hmm?
Do you want it to be healthy and safe?
Okay.
Because your baby knows that, too.
You're not alone in this. We are all here for you.
This baby is all of ours.
But I need you to push, okay?
Okay? Okay.
On the count of 3.
Ready?
1...2...3, push.
Go ahead.
Good. Push.
Good, good.
Yeah, that's good.
- Yeah. Right.
- Push. Push.
Okay.
Jack.
Let's go.
Jack --
On 3. 1...
- Jack!
- 2...
Why are you doing this?
He's bleeding inside.
You're not helping him!
You can't save him, Jack! You just can't.
Don't tell me what I can't do!
Okay. 1, 2, 3, go. All right.
You don't need to see this.
If you need me, shout.
In sickness, in health,
in good times and bad...
I risk it all because I love you.
Thank you, Sarah.
Jack has also prepared his vows.
Jack, if you would, please.
Jack?
I didn't write any vows.
I've been trying to for a month, but...
I couldn't, and...
so I started to wonder why that was.
And as time went on, it only got worse,
because I'm --
because I'm not good at letting go.
Or maybe I'm afraid of what'll happen if I fail.
But I know one thing.
I would have never been able to write anything
as beautiful as what you just said.
And last night, Sarah, when you were talking about the accident,
you got it all wrong.
I didn't fix you.
You fixed me.
I love you, Sarah,
and I always will.
Wait.
I have to.
If I don't --
I'm all messed up inside.
You know it.
This is out best chance.
There is no chance.
Really.
I mean...
look where we are.
I'm not gonna let you give up.
I know you made...
a promise.
I'm letting you off the hook.
Let me go, Jack.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Relax, relax, relax. Breathe.
Come on, breathe.
Breathe. Okay.
Okay. Ready? You got to do another one.
I can see it's close. Go, go, go, go.
Push. It's really -- I think it's close.
Come on. That's it! Okay.
I can see. I can see the top of its head.
It's almost clear. Come on.
I can see, I can see it. Okay.
You're almost there.
You're so close. You're so close.
Ready? Ready? Come on. One more.
Go, push! Push, push, push, push, push!
Yeah, come on!
You have a little boy.
It's your baby.
I have a son. I have a son.
Shh, shh, shh.
Tell Shannon...
tell...I --
A beautiful, healthy baby.
Want to talk about it?
Talk about what?
Boone died, Jack.
He didn't die.
He was murdered.
What?
Jack?
Where are you going?
To find John Locke.
Synchro: Amariss
Transcript : RaceMan
www.forom.com