Previously on Lost:
Jack is on his way
to blow up a hydrogen bomb.
We have to stop him.
Jack, we need to be there
at the moment of the incident.
- Why the hell are we stopping?
- That's why.
- What's going on, Kate?
- Doc, we gotta talk.
- You wanna talk, get in the van...
- I ain't gettin' in the van!
I need five minutes. Say what I gotta
say, then you can do whatever you want.
But you're gonna listen.
You owe me that much.
Five minutes.
Dr Shephard? You all right?
The dural sac. I cut it.
- Give me some suction.
- Calm down. It's all right.
- Fluid's leaking.
- Look at me.
- Give me some suction.
- Jack.
Look at me.
Count to five.
- What are you talking about?
- Stitching up the sac
so this girl isn't paralyzed
for the rest of her life.
The only way you're gonna do that
is not to be afraid.
So close your eyes and count to five.
And then fix her, Jack.
Or I'll have to fix her for you.
One, two,
three, four...
...five.
Sutures.
Hey, kiddo.
Girl's in recovery, responsive
to stimulus below the waist,
so no paralysis.
Good.
Something wrong, Jack?
You embarrassed me.
- Did I?
- It was bad enough
that everybody thinks
the reason I got this residency
is because you're my father.
But then you...
You put me in a timeout
during my first major procedure!
In front of my entire team.
Dad, I know you don't believe in me,
but I need them to.
Are you sure I'm the one
who doesn't believe in you, Jack?
One of these yours?
- Machine got stuck.
- Guess it just needed a little push.
- Take a load off, doc.
- No, thanks.
Sit down, Jack.
My folks died when I was eight.
I ever tell you that?
No.
Con man took my dad
for everything he had.
He didn't handle it too well, so...
Shot my mom.
Then he blew his own head off.
I was hiding under the bed
when it happened. Heard the whole thing.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
That was a year ago.
- What?
- Right now it's July, 1977.
Which means that happened last year.
So I could have hopped on the sub,
gone back to the States,
walked right into my house and
stopped my daddy from killing anybody.
Why didn't you?
Because, Jack...
...what's done is done.
It doesn't have to be that way.
What did you screw up so bad the
first time, you'll blow up a damn nuke
- for a second chance?
- Not what this is about.
Then what is it about?
Three years ago, Locke told me that
all this was happening for a reason.
- That us being here was our destiny.
- I don't speak destiny.
What I do understand
is a man does what he does
'cause he wants something for himself.
What do you want, Jack?
I had her.
I had her, and I lost her.
Kate?
Damn, doc, she's standing
on the other side of those trees.
- You want her back, just ask her.
- No, it's too late for that.
Your five minutes is up.
Jack! If what you're doing even works,
you and Kate will be strangers.
And she'll be in damn handcuffs.
What's meant to be is meant to be.
I guess there's nothing I can say
that'll change your mind.
I guess there's not.
Who the hell do you think you are?!
Think you can come here
and do whatever the hell you want?
I had a life here!
Sawyer, listen...
You don't get it.
Will you stop?
- Will you stop?!
- No.
James!
- Let him go.
- He wouldn't listen.
- I had to. He won't stop!
- That's because he's right.
- What?
- He's right.
James, we have to do this.
What are you talking about?
You're the one that told me
to come back here and stop him!
What happened?!
I changed my mind.
Girls, your dad and I have something
we need to talk to you both about.
- Are we moving again?
- No, stupid.
- They're getting a divorce.
- Rachel.
Well, aren't you?
- Yes.
- But we need you both to understand
that your father and I,
we still love each other.
Because people love each other doesn't
mean they're supposed to be together.
- What if you are supposed to be?
- We're not, honey.
- But how can you know for sure?
- We just know.
And, when you're a grownup,
you'll understand.
I don't wanna understand!
- Juliet, wait!
- I don't wanna understand!
- Stop! We gotta talk about this!
- There's nothing to talk about.
- Let Jack do what he came here to do.
- Maybe you should have told me
you had a change of heart before
I brought him out to kick his ass!
- Would that have stopped you?
- No!
- Glad you got it out of your system.
- Hey!
Don't!
I need you to tell me
where all this is coming from.
One minute, you're leading the
great sub escape, now you're onboard
with blowing up the damn island?
I got a right to know
why you changed your mind.
I changed my mind
when I saw you look at her.
Don't... Don't.
I don't care who I looked at.
I'm with you.
And you would stay
with me forever if I let you.
And that is why I will always love you.
What we had was just for a while.
Just because we love each other
doesn't mean we're meant to be together.
Maybe we were never supposed to be.
So if Jack can make it that none of you
ever come here, then he should.
Why are you doing this, Juliet?
I...
If I never meet you,
then I never have to lose you.
Slow down that drill.
This has got to be...
It can't be like that.
Radzinsky!
- What is it now?
- Gauss readings jumped off the charts.
Let me see.
- This is it. On top of the pocket.
- If we drill and hit that pocket,
- all hell is gonna break loose.
- Radzinsky, are you there? Over.
- Stuart, come in.
- What do you want, Phil?
That Hostile
that shot the kid came back.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- Here at the barracks.
He attacked us and got rescued
by some other recruits.
- They stole a van and took off.
- Took off where?
I don't know.
Roger said one of them had a bomb.
That Hostile knows about the Swan.
Get some men and some guns,
get your asses out here right now!
If they're coming here, we'll be ready.
Come on!
Jack?
What happened?
My talk with Sawyer didn't go so good.
- Does it hurt?
- It's OK.
OK.
Do you remember when I sewed you up
when we first got here?
Yeah.
Seems like a million years ago.
Or 30 years from now.
Kate, why did you make me promise
to never ask about Aaron?
Because I was...
...so angry with you
for making me come back here.
Is he why you came back?
I came back so he
could be where he belongs.
- With his mother.
- If this works,
Claire'll never come to the island.
They'll always be together,
- the way they're meant to be.
- She was gonna give him up.
You don't know what she'd do.
And, whatever it is,
it would be her choice.
If you wanna save Claire,
this is the only way to do it.
But nothing... Nothing in my life
has ever felt so right.
And...
...I just need you to believe that.
Keep cooling it! Don't let it get hot!
- Keep the drill going!
- It's about to happen.
Are you with me on this?
- Yes.
- Then let's go.
- ...two, three, four.
- Copy that.
One wallet.
Two hundred and 27 dollars cash.
One ballpoint pen.
One Fruit Roll-Up.
- Sign here.
- You don't understand. It's a mistake.
I killed a bunch of people.
You see this?
This is a discharge form.
You've been cleared.
So take your stuff and go.
Look, dude, there are men
with tranquiliser guns
hunting me down. They want to
bring me somewhere against my will.
There's a cab stand right out front.
- Sorry. I didn't see it was taken.
- I'm only going a few blocks.
- You want to share?
- Cool! You sure?
Come on in.
- You want some? It's cherry.
- No, thanks.
- What were you in for?
- Excuse me?
Jail. I was there
'cause I killed three people.
I didn't really.
Guess they figured it out.
- What about you?
- I wasn't in jail.
Then what were you doing
sitting outside a prison in a cab?
I was waiting for you, Hugo.
- Then you must be dead.
- I'm definitely not dead.
What do you want from me?
I wanna know why
you won't go back to the island.
- 'Cause I'm cursed.
- Is that so?
That's why the plane crashed,
my friends died, Libby, Charlie.
Now they visit me,
and I can't make it stop.
What if you weren't cursed?
- What if you were blessed?
- How do you mean, blessed?
Well, you get to talk to
the people you've lost.
- Seems like a wonderful thing to me.
- Sure, it's wonderful
- except for the part where I'm crazy.
- I've got some news for you, Hugo.
You're just gonna have to
take my word on this.
You are not crazy.
- Who are you, dude?
- I'm just up here on the corner.
Ajira Airways, flight 316 out of LAX.
Leaves in 24 hours.
All you have to do is be on that plane.
It's your choice, Hugo.
You don't have to do anything
you don't want to.
- Wait! You forgot your guitar.
- It's not my guitar.
Don't worry, dude. Everything'll be fine
when Jack changes the future.
Or the past. One of those.
I don't think
your buddy's gonna make it.
He'll make it.
- Dude, what happened to your face?
- Nothing.
We were just up on a ridge where
we could look down into the Swan site.
Something just happened down there.
They hit something.
- It's time for me to go.
- It's all set to go.
Remember, be careful.
It's rigged to explode on impact.
According to Faraday's plan, you must
get the bomb as close as you can
to the source of electromagnetism.
Sayid, this is gonna work.
And it'll save you.
Nothing can save me.
See you in Los Angeles.
What is it? Why are we stopping?
You'll see.
Well, it's a wonderful foot, Richard,
but what's it have to do with Jacob?
It's where he lives.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Call 911!
Don't worry,
everything's gonna be all right.
I'm sorry this happened to you.
Are you sure you need to do this?
If you waited,
Jacob would come to you, John.
I'm tired of waiting.
Where is he, Richard?
What happened to the rest of the statue?
I don't know.
It was like that when I got here.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Not really.
All right, Ben. Let's go.
What are you doing?
- John wants me to join him.
- You can't bring him in.
- Why not?
- Only our leader can request
an audience with Jacob.
There can only be one leader at a time.
I'm beginning to think you just
make these rules up as you go along.
Ben is coming in with me. If that's
a problem, Jacob and I can work it out.
Tell him I said hello.
Will you be able to do this, Ben?
I know it won't be easy,
but things will change once he's gone.
I promise.
- Can I ask you something, LaFleur?
- There ain't no more LaFleur.
- Go ahead, shoot.
- Has it occurred to any of you
that your buddy's actually gonna
cause the thing he's trying to prevent?
Perhaps that little nuke
is the incident.
So maybe the best thing to do
is nothing.
I'm glad you all thought this through.
- What's going on?
- It's Phil.
That's the road to the Swan.
If they see Jack, they'll kill him.
What do you think, blondie?
Live together and die alone.
Still running pretty hot.
- Good for you. You got here fast.
- Any sign of them?
Not yet. You got time
to set up a perimeter.
- Did you call these men to the site?
- You, rear. You, top.
- We need to get people away from here!
- Top of the scaffolding. Go, now!
There!
Go, go, over there!
Get him!
Flank him! Get him now!
Who's this?!
Drop it, Phil, or you're a dead man.
Tell 'em to put the guns down!
Drop the guns! Drop the guns!
You can come out now, doc!
Hurry up and do your business.
Turn that damn thing off!
What's the matter?
- It won't shut down!
- Why not?
- Something's pulling the drill down!
- We hit the pocket!
Hurry up, doc!
What are you waiting for? Drop it!
This don't look like LAX.
Dad!
Jack!
Get away from here!
Get as far away from here as you can!
- Get in! What the hell's going on?
- Let's get out of here!
Go, go, go!
Hey, LaFleur!
- Help!
- Juliet!
Come on! Sawyer, help!
Juliet!
Where do you think you're going?
Kate! Help me get those chains off!
Hold on. You hold on!
- I can't! I can't get it off!
- I got you.
I can't!
- I can't reach her!
- You hold on!
I got you.
Sawyer!
- Don't you leave me.
- It's OK.
Don't you leave me!
- I love you!
- No, you don't let go!
- I love you, James.
- No!
- I love you so much!
- No! No, don't let go!
Juliet! No!
- Water?
- Do you have any alcohol?
No. Sure wish I did.
Don't shoot.
It's OK.
It's all right.
Which one of you is Ricardos?
It's Richard, actually.
What lies in the shadow of the statue?
Richard. I'm Ilana.
I have something you need to see.
Open it up.
It's OK. It's OK. Let them.
- Where did you find him?
- In the cargo hold of the plane
we came here on.
In a coffin.
I don't understand.
If this is Locke, who's in there?
You like it?
I did it myself.
Takes a very long time
when you're making the thread,
but I suppose that's the point,
isn't it?
Hello, Jacob.
You found your loophole.
Indeed I did.
And you have no idea
what I've gone through
to be here.
- Have you met before?
- In a manner of speaking.
Do what I asked you to, Ben.
Benjamin, whatever he's told you,
I want you to understand one thing.
You have a choice.
What choice?
You can do what he asks, or you can go.
Leave us to discuss our... issues.
So now, after all this time,
you've decided to stop ignoring me.
Thirty-five years
I lived on this island.
And all I ever heard was your name,
over and over.
Richard would bring me your
instructions, all those slips of paper.
All those lists.
And I never questioned anything.
I did as I was told.
But when I dared to ask
to see you myself,
I was told, "You have to wait.
You have to be patient."
But when he asked to see you,
he gets marched straight up here
as if he was Moses.
So why him?
What was it that was so wrong with me?
What about me?
What about you?
Well...
- They're coming.
- What?
I can't hear you.
They're coming.
- Juliet!
- Sawyer, get off of there!
You have to come out!
It's going down! This thing is gonna go!
You have to go,
this thing is gonna go at any second.
Jack! Jack, help me get him off of here.
Come on!
Come on! Come on, you son of a bitch!