Previously on Lost:
Are you one of them?
- One of who?
- A hostile.
- What's your name?
- Ben.
Take me with you.
If that's what you really want, Ben.
If that's what you want.
I want you to think about that.
And you're gonna have to be
very, very patient.
You wanna protect your friends
or not, Sayid?
I'm Sayid Jarrah,
one of the Oceanic Six.
Stop right there!
Sayid?
Jin.
Shut up! Get down.
Say another word,
and you're dead.
I brought you a sandwich.
Are you a hostile?
- Do you think I am?
- What's your name?
Sayid.
I'm Ben.
It's nice to meet you, Ben.
Hey, Phil.
Hey.
I brought another sandwich for him.
Chicken salad this time.
Yeah, I don't think
it's the menu.
He's not eating.
Save yourself the trouble, kid.
But Horace told me to.
Why does he care so much?
The guy's a hostile.
- That doesn't mean he's not hungry.
- Whatever.
I brought you a sandwich.
And a book.
I read it twice.
It's good.
Thank you.
Did Richard send you?
Richard.
He's your leader, right?
It's just a camera.
They can see,
but they can't hear.
Four years ago,
I ran away into the jungle,
and Richard found me.
I said I wanted to leave,
that I wanted to join you.
So I've been patient.
And if you're patient, too,
I think I can help you.
Lost SO5E10:
"He's Our You"
How'd it go?
He tried to bribe me.
- It didn't work.
- Of course it didn't.
Where to now?
Nowhere.
- You're done.
- What do you mean, I'm done?
We're done.
Andropov was the last one.
You've taken care of everyone
who posed a threat to your friends.
It's been a pleasure
working with you, Sayid.
So that's it?
I killed all those people for you,
and now you're just...
w- walking away?
You didn't kill them
for me, Sayid.
You're the one
that asked for their names.
There's no one else
in Widmore's organization
that we need to go after.
Congratulations.
Mission accomplished.
What do I do now?
I suppose you should
go live your life.
You're free, Sayid.
Put out your hands.
Come on.
Thank you.
It's nice to finally
hear your voice.
I'm Horace.
Now's the part
where you tell me your name.
I need you to tell me what you
were doing out in that jungle.
- Ask him about the model. I-
- Radzinsky. I got this.
Those handcuffs-
Are you having some kind
of problem with your people?
Because either you were
in some kind of disagreement,
which makes me wanna help you,
or you're a spy
trying to infiltrate us.
So which is it?
Okay.
I'm gonna give you
an hour to decide
whether you wanna talk to me.
But if you decide
you don't want to...
then I'm gonna have to take this
to the next level.
I think your bacon's ready.
Oh.
I forgot.
What's on the TV?
It's over, isn't it?
What's over?
This.
Us... playing house.
All of it.
I never actually thought
they'd come back.
So they're back.
Nothing's changed.
What if Sayid tells them
who he is?
Sayid ain't sayin' nothin'.
Hey.
I got this under control.
Morning, H.
- Jim.
- What's up?
- Juliet.
- Horace.
I just spoke to the prisoner.
We have a problem.
- Why? What'd he say?
- Nothing, which is what worries me.
We need to find out
why he violated the truce,
why the hell he would
come into our territory.
I'm just gonna have to have
Oldham do his thing on him.
That psychopath? No way!
What choice do I have?
Just let me
have go at him alone.
Be my guest,
but I'm telling you, man,
he is not gonna talk.
Oh, he'll talk to me.
- Mr. LaFleur.
- Take your lunch, Phil.
You going back there alone?
Take your lunch, Phil.
Yes, sir.
How you doing?
A 12-year-old Ben Linus
brought me
a chicken salad sandwich.
- How do you think I'm doing?
- Sweet kid, huh?
How can you live with him here?
'cause I ain't got a choice.
Is that so?
Let's see how you feel after
3 years of living in the '70s.
Lucky for you...
I spent that time getting myself
in a position to save your ass.
I'm sorry, Sayid.
- What are you doing?
- When I tell them I got your confession,
I need them to believe that
you didn't give it up easy.
What confession?
We're gonna say
you were trying to defect.
You were gonna offer
some intel on the others
In exchange for living with us.
And why in God's name
would I want to do that?
What the hell else
am I supposed to do with you?
Let me go.
And then what?
I can't just let you go.
Why not?
Because these people
trust me.
I've built a life here,
and a pretty good one.
I let you go,
all that goes away.
So you got yourself
a choice, chief.
Either you cooperate and join
the party in Dharmaville,
or you're on your own.
Then I guess I'm on my own.
Fresh off the griddle.
And don't forget
to try the dipping sauces.
They really
bring out the ham.
Thanks, Hurley.
So...
What's going on with Sayid?
Don't know anything yet.
What do you mean,
you don't know anything?
I thought you were
at Sawyer's last night.
What did he tell you?
He told me to leave him
alone and let him do his job.
And you're going to?
I'll talk to Juliet,
see what she can tell me.
Well, if Sawyer didn't tell you
anything, why would Juliet?
- Well, why wouldn't she?
- 'Cause they're together.
- What do you mean, they're together?
- "Together" as...
They live together.
Like, not as roommates.
You know, "together"
like you guys were.
I thought
it was kind of obvious.
- I mean, who couldn't see that comin'?
- Hurley.
Well, I guess I better...
Go make some more waffles.
Did you know?
Yeah.
Hmm.
You know what I can't figure out?
Is how the hell you got caught.
You hostiles are supposed
to be the kings of the jungle.
And how dumb are you that you
got captured by these idiots?
And yet you're the one
who mops up after them.
Yeah, well...
We'll see how cute you are once
Oldham gets done with you, pal.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I was bringing you a sandwich.
A sandwich?
You never made me a sandwich
in your life.
Yeah, well...
I- I made one for myself...
Uh-huh.
So... So I just thought
that I'd bring you-
Oh, yeah? You just...
- Dad, don't!
- Don't you lie to me.
What are you doin' down here?
You made this sandwich for him,
didn't you?
- Hmm?
- Yes.
- Who told you to do that?
- Nobody.
- Nobody?
- I just thought that-
You "just thought," huh?
Go home.
Go on. I'll tell you
what to think.
How did you find me?
I looked.
What do you want, Ben?
John Locke is dead.
I think he was murdered.
Why would anyone kill him?
I'd say it was retribution
for the work
you and I have been doing.
So you're in danger, Sayid.
If I can find you, so can
the people that found Locke.
The same people who,
even as we speak,
are sitting outside
Hugo's mental institution.
They're watching him?
A man in a sedan
has been there all week,
just waiting...
presumably for you or me
to show our faces.
And that's why you're here?
You actually came all this way
to suggest that I kill this man?
You don't want to?
What makes you think I want to?
Because, Sayid...
to put it simply,
you're capable of things
that most other men aren't.
Every choice
you've made in your life,
whether it was
to murder or to torture,
it hasn't really
been a choice at all, has it?
It's in your nature.
It's what you are.
You're a killer, Sayid.
I'm not what you think I am.
I don't like killing.
Well, then I apologize.
I was mistaken about you.
All right, last chance.
Take him to Oldham.
WOMAN: # I can't give you #
# anything #
# but love #
# baby #
# that's the only thing #
# I've plenty of #
Oldham.
# baby #
Hey, man.
Are we ready?
# dream a while,
scheme a while #
# you're sure to find #
# happiness #
# and I guess- #
Who is that man?
He's our you.
Better put him
in the restraints.
They're for your protection.
There are side effects
to what I'm giving you.
Open his mouth.
Open up.
Don't be afraid.
Just turn your mind off.
Let it take effect.
It's beyond your control,
so fighting it is
a poor use of your energies.
You see,
whether you struggle or not,
one thing's for sure, friend.
You will tell us the truth.
There's somebody-
somebody here in Los Angeles.
- Let me take you to them.
- Who?
The same person
that's gonna show us
- how to get back to the island.
- Is that what this is about?
This is insane.
You are all crazy.
Sayid, where are you going?
I don't want any part of this.
And if I see you again,
it'll be extremely unpleasant
for us both.
Do you have a menu?
There you go.
Sir? Another MacCutcheon?
Please.
What's that run you?
Excuse me?
That scotch.
What's a glass of that run you?
Whatever it is, it's worth it.
I don't understand
why someone would pay 120 bucks
for a glass of anything.
If you knew what my drink cost,
why did you ask me?
Same reason I'm eating my dinner
here instead of a table.
I'll have the rib eye,
bloody.
Yes, ma'am.
Rib eye, bloody.
Are you a professional?
A professional what?
You think I'm a prostitute?
Mm.
I'm not a professional anything.
I just...
Thought you looked sad.
I like sad men.
I'm sorry to hear that.
So...
Other than drinking alone at bars...
what do you do?
For a living.
I'm between jobs
at the moment.
So what did you do?
The only thing
I was ever good at.
Then why did you quit?
I'm trying to change.
I know why you're sad now.
Do you?
When you are that good
at something,
there are always going to be people
who tempt you into staying the same.
And how do you know so much
about temptation?
Buy me a glass of that scotch,
and I'll tell you.
Hello there.
Hello?
I'm going to ask you
a few questions.
I want you to relax
and answer them truthfully...
Not that you'll have
any choice about it.
What is your name?
Sayid.
Sayid Jarrah.
All right, Sayid.
Why were you in handcuffs
when we found you?
Because...
because I am a bad man.
Were you running away
from your people?
What people?
The hostiles.
I am not a hostile.
Then where did you
come from, Sayid?
I came on a plane.
What plane?
Ajira flight 3-1-6.
And that's how
I returned to the island.
"Returned"?
You've been here before?
Oh, yes.
The first time,
I was
on Oceanic flight 8-1-5.
It crashed.
I was here
for a hundred days.
Then I left.
Ask Sawyer.
- Who's "Sawyer"?
- Who cares?!
None of this matters.
Ask him about the Flame.
Quiet.
What do you know
about our stations here?
I know the Flame was
a communication station.
The Pearl was to observe
other stations.
The Swan was to study
electromagnetism.
But, of course, that was
before the incident-
The swan?!
How could he know what
we were gonna name it?
We haven't even built it yet!
I told you! He saw the model!
- You see?! He is a spy!
- Hey!
I knew it!
Radzinsky!
I'm not gonna tell you again.
Cool it.
You're all going to die,
you know.
What?
You're going to be killed.
How exactly
would you know this, Sayid?
Because I am
from the future.
Maybe I should've used
half a dropper.
Oops.
You...
You used exactly enough.
Bench grinder, lube equipment,
drill press over here.
Plugs, bearings,
sockets, ratchets here.
How are you
with a flat four engine?
You have no idea what
I'm talking about, do you?
No, not really.
It's okay.
Jack told you about us...
No. Hurley, actually.
It's kind of a relief, actually.
I wasn't quite sure
how to do it
without it sounding like
I was telling you to stay away.
It's fine.
All right...
What do we do with him?
We kill him.
Hold on a second.
We're not killing anyone, right?
He violated the truce.
What do you think they would do
if they caught one of us?
Since when did we start
acting like them?
- We're civilized.
- Yes, we are.
We have a rule of law.
And we've given him every
opportunity to defend himself.
Blah, blah, blah. Need I remind
you, this man's seen things?
He knows things.
There's nothing to talk about.
- He's a spy.
- You sure about that, Stu?
He was trying to escape
from the hostiles.
He obviously has problems
with his people.
Yeah, and sharing our secrets
are the quickest way for him
to solve those problems.
Okay, I'm gonna need
a little more time to consider.
Consider?
I mean, the longer
he's among us,
the-the more danger we're in.
I can talk to him, Horace.
I just need more time.
No, you had your chance, LaFleur!
Why are we on your clock, Radzinsky?
Horace, you've got to call
for a vote.
Either we make a decision,
or I call Ann Arbor...
and they make it for us.
Radzinsky's right.
Horace, please...
I can't...
I can't sleep
with one eye open.
We have a baby now.
We have to think about Ethan.
We have to think
about all the children here.
How are we going to feel safe
with this man around?
I don't know what he's up to,
but we can't keep him here.
We have no choice.
Okay.
Let's put it to a vote.
All in favor
of Radzinsky's solution,
raise your hand.
LaFleur?
I would really like to say
it's unanimous.
Mmm.
Just for the record,
I really was
just there for dinner.
Are you afraid I'll get the wrong idea?
Mmm.
I think
it's too late for that.
Take it off.
You so much as flinch,
and you're dead.
So who are you?
You asked me earlier
if I was a professional.
I am a professional.
I was hired to bring you to Guam.
Who hired you?
The family of Peter Avellino-
the man you killed
in cold blood last year
on a golf course
in the Seychelles.
- You're a bounty hunter?
- Doesn't matter what I am.
You're going to answer
for what you've done.
Hit me in the face.
What?
Go on. You owe me one anyway,
so make it a good one.
Then I want you to take
these keys out of my pocket
and let yourself out.
The guard outside is Phil.
He's a dimwit, so I reckon
you can get his gun before
he even realizes you're out.
Just promise me
you won't shoot him.
I appreciate the offer,
but I'm fine right here.
They're gonna kill you.
They just took a vote.
Even the new mom wants you dead.
I'm going to stay here, James.
This morning, you were
begging me to let you go.
- Why would you change your-
- Because...
when I woke up in the jungle
and I realized I was
back on this island...
I felt there was
no purpose to it.
But now I know
exactly why I'm here.
To get shot? Then what?
You're out of your mind.
Hey.
Hi.
Why'd you come back?
What?
Sayid just filled my ear
full of some crap
about his damn purpose,
and I wanna know...
Why'd y'all come back?
Uh...
Why, Kate?
I don't know why
everyone else came back.
I just know why I did.
What?
What the hell?!
Are you ok?
Craig! Grab a wrench, open those
valves. Get the hoses going.
Okay.
Erin, grab the fire gear!
Bill, go help Craig.
What the hell happened?
Three years-no burning buses.
Y'all are back for one day...
Get on that hose.
Man this hose!
Push it out!
All security! All security!
This is LaFleur! We have a fire!
Everyone get to building 15 now!
Roger that. I'm on my way.
What happened
to your glasses?
My dad.
For bringing me
the sandwich?
I know.
My father was a
hard man as well.
I really hate it here.
If I let you out...
will you take me with you,
to your people?
Yes, Ben, I will.
That's why I'm here.
Attention, passengers.
Ajira Airways flight 3-1-6
to Honolulu and Guam...
Are you sure
we're going to Guam?
Where else would we be going?
Can I ask you a favor?
Can we get the next plane?
Why?
I'm very superstitious
when it comes to flying.
I'll buy you a rabbit's foot
at the gift shop.
This is
the plane we're taking.
Sorry about the handcuffs,
but at least we're in business.
Hold up! Wait, please!
Thank you for not closing it.
What's he doing here?!
No, no, he can't come!
Hurley, hey,
if you want to get back,
- this is how it's gonna have to be.
- Are you working for Benjamin Linus?
- What?
- Are you working for him?
Who's Benjamin Linus?
He's a liar, a manipulator...
a man who allowed
his own daughter to be murdered
to save himself...
A monster responsible
for nothing short of genocide.
Why would I work
for somebody like that?
I did.
Hide!
Jin?
Sayid.
What are you doing here?
How did you get out?
Sawyer let me go.
They were going to kill me.
What?
Attention. The prisoner escaped.
The hostile is no longer
in custody. Be on the lookout.
He could be armed.
They don't know he released me.
Please, Jin,
I need to keep moving.
Okay.
Let me talk to him first.
- LaFleur, it's Jin here.
- Come in.
Whoa!
Where'd you learn to do that?
Come on.
We better go.
He called LaFleur.
You were right about me.
What?
I am a killer.
subtitle made by rogard and LeapinLar