Previously on "Lost"...
This is your daughter.
Her name's Clementine.
Those are fake necklaces.
I'll take
the one on the end.
Why'd you help me?
Just one girl watching
another girl's back, I guess.
Why are you
telling me this?
Just do it, freckles.
I think we should say he's mine.
There's other ways to do this.
After everyone we've lost,
I can't lose him, too.
My client insists that we...
handle the exchange of custody quietly.
You are going to lose the boy.
That's Claire's mother.
Everything that Kate and I
have done, it was for Aaron.
Who's... Aaron?
I'm Ben.
It's nice to meet you, Ben.
if I let you out,
will you take me with
you to your people?
That's why I'm here.
Jin?
What are you doing here?
Hello, Jin? Are you there?
Jin? Can you hear me?
Hello?
Jin? It's-it's Phil, man.
Where have you been?
The hostile escaped.
We're searching the east grid.
He's headed north.
How the hell do you know that?
Because he attacked me.
What? Where are you?
Jin?! You still there?
Jin? Jin!
Please, help.
Okay, everybody, listen up.
We don't know yet if
another attack is coming,
so everybody needs to be ready for
your security assignments, okay?
Make sure you're in contact
with your team leaders.
LaFleur's got search parties out, but
the hostile's got a good jump on us.
We're pretty sure he used this fire
as a diversion in order to escape.
Is he talking about Sayid?
If he was locked up,
how could he start the fire?
Who are you?
Jack Shephard. I'm... I'm new.
Well, Jack, the way he started
the fire is he had help, okay?
Somebody torched that van, and then
that somebody let him out of his cell.
And since the security cameras didn't pick
up any hostiles crossing the perimeter,
that means it was one of us.
Baxter, I want a full
report on cleanup ASAP.
You got it, Horace.
Hey, you.
Yeah, you.
You're in the motor pool, right?
- Uh, yeah.
- Do you mind running that winch for me?
You have no idea what
I'm talking about, do you?
Okay, no worries.
Just throw this lever.
When I tell you to
stop... just pull it up.
- All right.
- See? Simple.
- Don't do it till I'm ready.
- Okay.
All right, crank her up.
So they just stuck you in the
motor pool when you got here?
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, same thing happened to me.
Wait, hold. Hold it there.
That's good right there. That's good.
I guess they couldn't sucker
anybody into getting on that sub
if they told us we were gonna
be grease monkeys and janitors.
- Well, you gotta start somewhere, right?
- Yeah.
- What's your name?
- I'm Kate.
Welcome aboard, Kate.
I'm Roger. Roger Linus.
It's nice to meet you, Roger.
That's my kid.
That's my kid!
Hi, handsome.
Did you have a good sleep?
Yeah, that's my boy.
# Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket
# Never let it fade away
# Catch a falling star
and put it in your pocket
# Save it for a rainy day #
Oh, my God!
Hi, Cassidy.
Oh, my God! I saw you on the news!
I told all my friends,
"I know that woman!"
- This is Aaron.
- Hi, Aaron.
Say hi.
You survived a plane crash.
It's amazing.
I never thought I'd see you again.
What are you doing here?
Sawyer sent me.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- proudly presents
sync:??????, edited by rogard
Lost Season 05 Episode 11
"Whatever Happened, Happened"
Sawyer.
So that son of a bitch is still alive?
He was when I left.
And he asked you to come here and
give me an envelope full of money?
Well, he-he told me
where to find you, and...
said to take care of Clementine...
his daughter?
Well, she's asleep
in her crib right now.
Want me to wake her up?
I, uh, shouldn't have bothered you.
I could've sent it,
and I probably should have.
Why did you tell me all this?
Why'd you trust me?
Because I thought your daughter had
a right to know that her father cared.
Why didn't he come back
with the rest of you?
The helicopter that we were
on was running out of gas,
so he jumped so that we
could make it to the boat.
What a coward.
He was trying to do the right thing.
He was trying to get away from you.
I told him he had a daughter.
He never so much as lifted
a finger to try to call her.
So now I'm supposed
to think he's a hero
because he told you to
come here and help us?
Hell, I bet this money's
not even his, is it?
They gave us a settlement after the
crash, and I didn't need it all--
You don't have to explain it, Kate.
You got the same look on your
face I did when he ditched me.
All I have for you is sympathy.
Is it his?
- What?
- Your son.
Is it Sawyer's?
No. No, I was...
pregnant before I met him.
That's not your baby, is it?
Kate, you just told me that you and your
friends cooked a story for the whole world
about what happened on that island.
So you tell me the truth about that?
Why are you lying to me about him?
Because I have to.
What happened?
What the hell are you doing here?
That was Ben.
That kid who was shot was Ben.
Was it Sayid? Did he shoot him?
Here's what you need to do, Kate:
Keep your mouth shut and
stop asking questions.
'Cause putting any attention on yourself
is the last thing I need right now.
Now scram.
I don't want you around here.
- I just wanna know what's going on.
- LaFleur.
What... what, uh...
what's she doing here?
- This is, uh...
- I'm Kate.
Kate. She's new over at the motor pool.
I was seeing if she saw anything
suspicious, but she didn't, so...
You can run along, thanks.
Have you checked out
the hostile's cell yet?
I was a little busy trying to keep
the town from burnin' down, Horace.
Okay. Well, then let's do it.
He didn't break out.
Somebody let him out.
These are janitor's keys.
We've only got three janitors.
There's Roger, Willie
and, uh, that new guy.
I just met him. His name's Jack.
Yeah. I just brought him in
from the sub.
I'll go talk to him.
Miles, you wanna come with me?
Yeah, sure, boss.
All right, I want you to find Jack and
Hurley and Kate as quick as you can.
Put 'em in a house and sit on 'em.
What for?
'Cause I don't want 'em
talking to anybody else.
Things are starting to
spin out of control here.
- All right, I got it.
- All right, go.
Who did this? Do you know
who did this to my son?
Not yet, but we're working on it.
How's he doing?
I don't know.
Juliet told me to wait out here.
Let me see if I can
get an update for ya.
Thanks, Jim.
- Roger?
- Yeah?
You happen to have your keys with you?
Yeah. Why? What do you need?
I must've left them at-at the house.
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
More gauze.
- Here's some gauze.
- Yeah, right here, yeah.
If we can't stop the hemorrhaging,
we're just gonna have
to pack the whole tract.
- Okay.
- Where's the doctor?
At the Looking Glass
station till Friday.
- How is he doing?
- Not well. Hook him.
He's still bleeding in there
somewhere, and I can't fix it.
- It's all right.
- No, it's not all right.
Someone needs to get in there who can
find the damage that bullet did and fix it.
He needs a real surgeon.
You're telling us we're
under house arrest?
No, you're all free to
leave whenever you want...
but I'll shoot you in the leg.
And whose idea was this?
Who do you think?
Sawyer's just doing his job, Jack.
What the hell are you doing, tubby?
Checking to see if I'm disappearing.
- What?
- "Back to the future," man.
We came back in time to the
island and changed stuff.
So if little Ben dies,
he'll never grow up to be big Ben,
who's the one who made us come
back here in the first place.
Which means we can't be here.
And therefore, dude,
we don't exist.
You're an idiot.
- Am I?
- Yeah. It doesn't work like that.
You can't change anything.
You're maniac Iraqi buddy shot Linus.
That is what always happened.
It's just... we never experienced
how it all turns out.
This is really confusing.
Yeah, well, get used to it.
But the good news is
that Linus didn't die,
so that means the kid can't either.
He'll be fine.
Didn't look like he was gonna be fine.
What if you're wrong?
Well, if I'm wrong, then I
guess we all stop existing,
and none of it matters
anyway then, does it?
Doc, I need you to come with me.
Come with you where?
Juliet said the kid's losing blood, and
we ain't got none to put back in him.
So we need you to show
us where he sprung a leak.
No.
What?
No, I'm not coming with you.
If you don't come with me,
Jack, that kid's gonna die.
Then he dies.
What are you doing?
Making some sandwiches.
I figured everybody'd
be getting hungry by now.
He's just a boy, Jack.
You can'just let him die.
You heard Miles.
We can't change what's
already happened.
This has nothing to do with me.
Unless you're the one
who's supposed to save him.
30 years from now,
that boy's gonna be a man that locks
me in a cage because he needs surgery.
And then you're gonna come in and
you're gonna beg me to operate on him
because he's threatening
to murder Sawyer.
I've already done this once.
I've already saved Benjamin Linus,
and I did it for you, Kate.
I don't need to do it again.
This is our fault.
We brought Sayid back.
We caused this.
You know, when we were here before,
I spent all of my time trying to fix things.
But... did you ever think that maybe the
island just wants to fix things itself?
And maybe I was just...
gettin' in the way?
You know, I don't like the new you.
I liked the old you, who wouldn't just
sit around and wait for things to happen.
You didn't like the old me, Kate.
Where are you going?
Just relax. You're okay.
I'm sorry. Juliet?
One of the new people is here.
She heard Ben needed blood,
says she's a universal donor.
This might hurt for a second.
Good. Very brave.
So James told me that Jack wouldn't
help, but he didn't say why.
If I understood why
Jack does what he does,
I sure as hell wouldn't
be sitting here.
Off island, did something
happen with you two?
We were engaged.
Does that count?
What's going on?
Roger, I asked you to wait outside.
No, what's going on with my kid?
Kate is giving us some fresh
blood so we can transfuse Ben.
Well, I'm not waitin' outside.
You know, he could stay with me,
and you could check on Ben,
and-and Roger here could keep me
company, make sure I don't pass out.
Okay. Roger, have a seat.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
- He stole my keys.
- Sorry?
LaFleur asked me where my keys were.
That bastard doesn't ask any questions
he doesn't know the answers to...
which means my son stole my keys so
he could bust that animal out of jail.
Why-why would he do that?
Because of me.
You got kids?
No.
I thought I was gonna be the
greatest father ever, you know?
I guess it didn't work out that way.
What about his mother?
Is she still around?
No, she's dead.
She died the day he was born.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
I tried to do what I thought
she'd want me to do, but...
I guess a boy just needs his mother.
- What's going on?
- He's going into hypoxic shock.
What does that mean?
What's the matter with him?
He needs more oxygen.
Roger, get out of here!
What?
- Get him out of here!
- Wait! What--what is--
- Please, Roger, just wait outside.
- Wait a minute.
Let me get this straight.
- All this already happened.
- Yes.
So this conversation
we're having right now...
- We already had it.
- Yes!
Then what am I gonna say next?
I don't know.
Then your theory is wrong!
For the thousandth time, you dingbat,
the conversation already happened,
but not for you and me.
For you and me,
it's happening right now.
Okay, answer me this.
If all this already
happened to me, then...
why don't I remember any of it?
Because once Ben turned that wheel,
time isn't a straight
line for us anymore.
Our experiences in the
past and the future occurred
before these experiences right now.
Say that again.
Shoot me. Please. Please?
I can't shoot you.
Because if you die in 1977,
then you'll never come back
to the island on the freighter
30 years from now.
I can die because I've already
come to the island on the freighter.
Any of us can die
because this is our present.
But you said Ben couldn't die
because he still has to grow up
and become the leader of the others.
Because this is his past.
But when we first captured Ben,
and Sayid, like, tortured him,
then why wouldn't he remember getting
shot by that same guy when he was a kid?
I hadn't thought of that.
How is he?
He's stable.
Is he gonna be okay?
He's got some fresh blood running
through him, which is a good thing.
Roger, I need you to go out
to the medical station.
There are some supplies there
that we don't have here.
Hey, I just wanna say, I-I...
I wanna say thanks.
I know that you're doing
everything you can...
to save him, and--
All right,I'm-I'm gonna go,okay?
Is he any better?
He is stable now.
But I can't, um...
I can't fix it.
What about the sub?
I mean, can we take him somewhere?
No. It's gone.
It won't be back for a couple of months.
But he can't die, right?
He is going to die.
He is in a medical situation
that is not resolvable.
Okay, well, we can't just
sit here and do nothing.
I mean, there's got to be
someone who can help him.
We have an entire k--
What?
Maybe there's something they can do.
"They"?
The Others.
You got him?
Yeah. Ready?
One, two, three, go.
Okay, let's go.
I'm coming with you.
No, no, no, no.
If something goes wrong
or we get caught,
it doesn't matter for me,
but you've got a whole life here.
And besides, if Sawyer knew that I got
you involved in this, he'd kill me.
How are you gonna manage?
I'll manage, don't worry.
Kate, Sawyer's gonna find out
Ben's gone, and when he does,
I have to tell him what happened.
But I'll give you as much
of a head start as I can.
Good luck.
There's someone...
someone here in Los Angeles.
Let me take you to them.
Who?
The same person that's gonna show us
how to get back the island.
Is that what this is about?
You knew about this.
No, I was o--
And that is why you were
pretending to care about Aaron,
to convince me to go back there?
I wasn't pretending anything.
This is insane. You guys are crazy.
- Kate--
- Jack,don't!
Mommy, I'm thirsty.
I need some milk.
Do you want chocolate milk
or regular milk?
Juice box.
You don't want milk anymore?
Excuse me.
Where are you juice boxes?
Aisle 5.
Thank you very much.
Aaron?
Um, excuse me.
Have you seen my son?
- I'm sorry?
- A little 3-year-old blond?
Aaron?
Aaron!
Excuse me. I've lost my son.
He's 3. He's a little blond boy.
Don't worry, ma'am.
I'll make an announcement.
No, no, no.
You have to seal
off the store. You...
Aaron?
Hey, is this your mommy?
Honey, is this your mommy?
I found him in the fruit section.
I--he looked lost.
I was getting ready to
make an announcement.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
It's okay, honey.
Mommy's got you.
Tell--
Tell my--
Try not to talk,okay?
Tell my dad I'm sorry I stole his keys.
I know you gotta stop me...
but I can't just let that kid die.
Damn it, freckles.
I ain't here to stop you.
I'm here to help you.
Hi, Auntie Kate!
Hi, Clementine.
Is your mommy home?
Sure. I'll go get her.
They're going back?
To the island?
Why in God's name would
they wanna do that?
I don't know.
Jack says that we weren't
supposed to leave.
Well, Jack sounds like a piece of work.
You look exhausted. Drink this.
Curl up on my bed.
Take a nap.
I'll watch your fella.
I lost him.
What?
I don't know what happened.
We were in the supermarket,
and I turned around for one second,
and he was gone.
And, you know,
the crazy thing is, is that...
as scared as I was...
I wasn't surprised.
All I could think was, it's about time.
Why would I feel that way?
I mean, why would I
expect him to be taken?
Because you took him, Kate.
No, I...
Claire was gone.
I mean, she left him.
I had to take him.
He needed me.
You needed him.
Sawyer broke your heart.
How else were you supposed to fix it?
Figure out how you were gonna
carry him out there by yourself?
Well, the line's just
right over there, right?
The Others are on the other side.
Well, they ain't right on the other side.
We better get movin'.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you helping me?
When I found out Ben was gone,
and Juliet told me
what you were up to,
I asked that exact damn question:
Why are you helping Ben?
And she said,
no matter what he's
gonna grow up to be,
it's wrong to let a kid die.
So...
that's why I'm doing this.
I'm doing it for her.
Where's Jack?
Uh, he-he's in the shower. I think.
Is he in trouble?
I just need to talk to him.
You two mind giving us some privacy?
Hey, ask me more questions
about time travel.
I needed you.
I'm sorry?
That kid was bleeding out.
You're a surgeon, and I needed you.
- That kid is Ben.
- That's not Ben yet.
He's just a kid.
Juliet, I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
I'm not asking for your help, Jack.
You made it pretty clear
you weren't interested.
It's up to Sawyer and Kate now.
What?
She's trying to save him,
and I sent James after her to help
because they actually care.
I came back here because I care, Juliet.
I came back here
because I was trying to save you.
We didn't need saving!
We've been fine for three years.
You came back here for you.
At least do me the courtesy
of telling me why.
I came back...
because I was supposed to.
Supposed to do what?
I don't know yet.
Well, you'd better figure it out.
You know, I can take him for a while.
Sure you can.
You know, his father said
that you think Ben broke Sayid out.
Kid'll do almost anything
if he's pissed off enough at his folks.
Is that why you asked me
to take care of your daughter?
Did you?
Of course I did.
Go ahead and tip his head back.
What's she like?
Clementine?
Yeah.
Clementine.
Oh, she's beautiful.
Looks just like you when she smiles.
She's growing up fast.
Already has a little attitude.
I bet you and Cassidy
had a lot to talk about.
She had an interesting theory
on why you jumped off the chopper.
Yeah? What's that?
She thought you were worried
about what would happen if you didn't.
You and me would've
never worked out, Kate.
I wasn't any more fit
to be your boyfriend
than I am to be that little girl's father.
You seem to be doing
all right with Juliet.
Yeah.
I've done a lot of growing up
the past three years.
Hands up!
Do not move.
I said, don't move.
This is a violation of the truce.
- You're over the line.
- We know.
This kid's been shot.
That's both of our problems.
So unless you want to go to war,
you're gonna take us to Richard Alpert,
and you're gonna do it now.
Mrs. Littleton, um, I'm Kate Austen.
I know who you are.
Come in.
Thank you.
Your friend Dr.Shephard
came here last night,
going on and on about
some person named Aaron.
When I asked him who that was,
he ran out of here like
the room was on fire.
He's your grandson.
And your daughter Claire...
is alive.
What are you talking about?
Claire died in the plane crash.
No, she survived.
When we crashed, your daughter was
eight months pregnant, and...
she's the one who gave birth
on the island, not me.
We lied.
There were other survivors, too.
We just left them behind.
Why?
Why would you leave her there?
Because she disappeared,
and she left the baby behind.
We looked everywhere, but--
That's when I started
taking care of Aaron.
And when we were
rescued, we didn't--
We had to decide
what to do with him.
And I knew that she had wanted him
to be adopted, but I couldn't.
I had to protect him,
so I said he was mine.
Why did you lie?
Why didn't you come to me
in the first place?
Because I needed him.
I'm sorry.
You're gonna see that he's so
sweet and kind and good.
Where is he?
Um, I checked in two doors down.
He's asleep.
I know that this is
a lot for you to handle.
But...
When you're ready,
he's waiting for you.
I told him that you're his grandmother,
that you'll take care of him while
I'm gone and that I'll be back soon.
Where are you going?
I'm going back to find your daughter.
Bye-bye, baby.
Don't worry. We got 'em
right where we want 'em.
Shut up and keep movin'.
What's it look like I'm doing?
Hello there, James.
Where the hell did you come from?
You asked my people to bring you to me.
Here I am.
Is that Benjamin Linus?
You two know each other?
What happened to him?
He was shot.
And who might you be?
She's with me.
And why are you here?
'Cause we need you to save his life.
Can you?
If I take him,he's not ever
gonna be the same again.
What do you mean by that?
What I mean is that...
he'll forget this
ever happened, and that...
his innocence will be gone.
He will always be one of us.
You still want me to take him?
Yes.
Richard...
you shouldn't do this
without asking Ellie.
- And if Charles finds out--
- Let him find out.
I don't answer to either of them.
Wh-where are you taking him?
Come on.
Hello, Ben.
Welcome back to the land of the living.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-?????? ????·?
edited by rogard