Previously on "Lost":
- Is that Benjamin Linus?
- We need you to save his life.
If I take him, he's not
ever gonna be the same again.
He will always be
one of us.
Get your ass out here right now,
or I'm gonna kill your daughter.
I stole her as a baby
from an insane woman.
She means nothing to me.
So if you want to kill her,
go ahead
and do it--
This guy is dangerous.
Sun, that boat I came here
on was filled with commandos
whose only mission
was to get him.
And how'd that work out
for everyone?
- You know him?
- Yeah.
He's the man who killed me.
- What have you done, Richard?
- Calm down!
Calm down. This has
nothing to do with you.
So it's true?
You actually brought one
of them to our temple?
He's just a boy,
and he was dying.
Then you should've
let him die.
Jacob wanted it done.
The island chooses is
the island's chooses.
You know that.
Yes.
Yes, of course.
What's his name?
Hello, Benjamin.
What happened?
You were injured.
How?
You don't remember?
Where am I?
You're among friends.
We're going to
take care of you.
My dad.
Is he here?
You'll be back to him
soon enough.
No. No,
I don't want to go back.
- Okay, easy. Easy.
- Oh!
I don't want to go back.
I wanna stay.
I wanna be
one of you.
Just because you're
living with them,
doesn't mean
you can't be one of us.
You should be dead,
Benjamin.
But this island...
It saved your life.
Who are you?
I'm Charles.
Charles Widmore.
Ben.
Hello, Ben.
Welcome back to the
Land of the Living.
My God!
You're alive!
Yes, I am.
I knew it.
I knew that this
would happen.
Then why are you so
surprised to see me?
Because it's one thing
to believe it, John.
It's another thing
to see it.
Then why were you trying to
run away to the main island?
I broke the rules,
John.
I came back to the island.
I was going to answer
for what I'd done.
I was going back...
To be judged.
Judged?
By whom?
Well, J-John...
We don't even
have a word for it.
But I believe you call it
'The Monster'.
S05E12:
Dead Is Dead
Transcript:
Yyets.net
Final Edits By: VeRdiKT
[Subscene.com]
Morning.
Hello.
What's in the crate?
Just some stuff
we need to get moved.
Need a hand?
Oh, thanks.
We got it.
Okay.
Have a great day.
How you feeling,
my friend?
Like someone hit me with an oar,
but I'll live.
- What do you make of him?
- I'm not sure.
What has he told you?
When you were out cold,
he was watching over you.
And he said
you killed him.
I killed him?
Really?
'Cause he looks fine to me.
You know, I don't really
remember him from the plane.
- Do you?
- No, I don't.
What if...
he was already here,
before we crashed?
If he thinks I killed him,
then he's insane.
We may be dealing with a man
who's dangerously deranged.
Then the question is:
What are we gonna do about it?
Don't worry,
my friend.
I have your back.
Caesar.
Pleasure to meet you, Caesar.
I'm Ben.
You want me to do it?
Shh.
I can do it if
you want me to, Ben.
Shut up!
And stay here, Ethan.
Don't!
Don't do it.
You're the one who infected us,
aren't you?!
You're the one
who infected us!
No! Shh.
It's okay.
It's okay, baby.
Please,
don't take my Alex!
Do you want
your baby to live?
Why are you taking her?!
Be grateful
you're still alive.
Now you listen to me.
If you try to follow me or if
you ever come looking for me,
I'll kill you.
And if you want
your child to live,
every time you hear whispers,
you run the other way.
What's that?
Just something sentimental.
So this is
your old office, huh?
I never pictured you
leading your people
from behind a desk.
It seems a little...
Corporate.
Was there something
that you needed, John?
Well, Ben,
I was hoping
that you and I could talk
about the elephant in the room.
I assume you're referring to
the fact that I killed you.
Yeah.
It was the only way to
get you back to the island.
Along with as many of
those who left as possible.
You do remember, John--
That's why you left in the first place,
to convince 'em
to come back?
But you failed.
And the only way
to bring them together
was by your death,
and you understood that.
It's why you were about to kill
yourself when I stopped you.
If all I had to do was die, Ben,
then why did you stop me?
You had critical information
that would've died with you.
And once
you'd given it to me...
Well, I just didn't have time
to talk you back
into hanging yourself.
So I took a shortcut.
And look at you, John.
I was right.
You're here. You're back.
So are the rest of them.
I don't know where yet exactly,
but they came. It worked.
And that's why
I did it.
Because it was in the best
interests of the island.
I was just hoping
for an apology.
I've decided
to help you, Ben.
Help me do what?
Do what you say you
are on your way to do.
Be judged.
That's not something
you want to see, John.
If everything you've done
has been in the best
interests of the island...
Then I'm sure
the Monster will understand.
Let's go.
Hey!
- What are you doing?
- We're taking a boat.
Where?
Over to the main island.
I don't think so,
my friend.
Are these your boats?
Are they yours?
Caesar, right?
I was under the impression
these were found here
so I'm just
gonna borrow one.
I'm happy to leave
the other boat for you
- in case you want to follow us.
- "Us"?
Are you
going with him?
He didn't really
give me a choice.
I'm sorry,
but I'm calling the shots here.
And I said
you are not taking anything.
What you are going to do
is to sit down
and tell us how you know
so much
about this island,
my friend.
You're in the habit of
calling people, "Friend."
But I don't think
you mean it.
- Step away from the boat.
- No.
I'm not gonna step
away from the boat.
I'm gonna take it,
and you're gonna let me,
my friend.
You're not taking anything.
You looking for this?
This gentleman and I
are taking a boat.
Does anyone else have
a problem with that?
Consider that
my apology.
Home,
sweet home.
Looks like
we're not the first ones
who decided to
tie up here.
That would be
Sun and Lapidus.
I showed 'em
where the boats were,
and Sun thanked me by smashing
me on the head with a paddle.
Oh. Is she the one
that hurt your arm?
I noticed you were
favoring it on the way over.
No.
Someone else hurt my arm.
You just make friends
everywhere you go, don't ya?
Well, I've found sometimes
that friends can be
significantly more
dangerous than enemies, John.
Is that why you shot an
unarmed man in the chest?
The man was unarmed
because I'd stolen his gun--
The gun he was going
to use to kill you.
I couldn't let that happen.
No sense in me
dying twice, right?
You're welcome.
We're going to your old house,
aren't we?
Yes.
It's the only place
I can summon it...
The "Monster."
Once it arrives,
I'll either be forgiven...
Or I won't.
I think you're lying.
Lying about what?
That you want to be judged
for leaving the island
and coming back because
it's against the rules.
I don't think
you care about rules.
Then what do I want to be
judged for, John?
For killing your daughter.
Well...
Did you do it?
We had a...
complication.
I'm sorry.
Is that a... baby?
Your orders were to
exterminate that woman.
Why? She's no threat to us.
She's insane, Charles.
Besides, you didn't
tell me she had a child.
What was it
I was supposed to do?
Kill it.
It's not an "it."
This is a child.
You might find this difficult
to understand, Benjamin...
Every decision I've made
has been about
protecting this island.
Is killing this baby
what Jacob wants?
Then here she is.
You do it.
So whose idea was it
to move into these houses?
Excuse me?
Well, your people were living
in the jungle.
And then after you
murdered the Dharma folk,
you relocated here.
I just wondered if it
was your idea.
Do you disapprove,
John?
It just doesn't seem like
something the island would want.
You don't have the first
idea what this island wants.
Are you sure about that?
That was your house,
wasn't it?
Yes, and that's Alex's room.
Well, I suppose you better go over
there and check it out.
Sun?
What are you doing here?
This used to be my house.
I saw a light turned on.
What are the two of you
doing in here?
- That was taken in 1977.
- Are you trying to tell me
that your friends were
in the Dharma Initiative?
You don't know about this?
Of course not.
Where did you get this?
Who gave this to you?
We met some
crazy old man outside.
He said
his name was Christian.
- He told us to come in here and wait.
- Wait for what?
He said if I ever wanted
to see my husband again,
I had to wait here
for John Locke.
But considering he's dead,
we ain't holding our breath.
Well, you might
want to look outside.
What you're saying,
it's...
Impossible.
But here I am.
I don't know how,
I don't know why, but...
I'm sure there's a
very good reason for it.
As long as the dead guy
says there's a reason,
well, then I guess everything's
gonna be just peachy.
And forget about the fact
that the rest of your people
are supposedly
30 years ago...
Now the only ones who
are here to help us...
are a murderer and a guy
who can't seem to remember
how the hell
he got out of a coffin.
Sun, please,
let's just go back to the plane,
see if I can
fix the radio,
and maybe we can
get some help.
If you leave with him,
you'll never find
your husband again.
I'm all the
help you need.
Are you saying you
know how to find them?
How to find Jin?
I have some ideas.
I'm sorry to say,
but--
I'm leaving with
or without you.
If there's any chance
of finding my husband,
then I have to stay.
All right.
Well, for God's sake,
watch your back.
All right.
How do we find Jin?
Ben has something to do first.
Isn't that right, Ben?
Yes, John.
That's right.
Better get to it then.
I'll be outside.
Again, daddy!
Again!
Okay. Okay.
Wow, Alex!
Any higher, and you're gonna
fly right off the island.
The sub's
about to leave.
Higher, daddy!
Higher!
All right.
You don't have
to see him off, Ben.
Yes, Richard, I do.
Higher!
Higher, daddy!
Charles!
I came to say good-bye.
No, you didn't.
You came to gloat.
No, don't act
as if I wanted this.
You brought this on yourself.
Are you quite certain you want
to do this, Benjamin?
You left the island regularly.
You had a daughter
with an outsider.
You broke the rules,
Charles.
And what makes you think you
deserve to take what's mine?
Because I won't be selfish.
Because I'll sacrifice
anything to protect this island.
You wouldn't sacrifice Alex.
You're the one who
wanted her dead, Charles.
Not the island.
I hope you're right,
Benjamin.
Because if you aren't,
and it is the island
that wants her dead...
She'll be dead.
And one day...
You'll be standing
where I'm standing now.
You'll be the
one being banished.
And then
you'll finally realize
that you cannot
fight the inevitable.
I'll be seeing you, boy.
Where did John go?
He said he had
something to do.
Did he say
what it was?
No, I didn't ask.
Jack must have lied.
- Excuse me?
- About Locke being dead?
I don't know why he would,
but that's the only explanation.
Jack didn't lie.
John was dead.
Just because
he was in a coffin
doesn't mean that he
couldn't have faked his dea--
Trust me.
I'm sure.
So you knew
this would happen to Locke
if we brought him
back here?
Sun, I had no idea it
would happen.
I've seen this island
do miraculous things.
I've seen it
heal the sick,
but never once has it
done anything like this.
Dead is dead.
You don't get to
come back from that.
Not even here.
So the fact that John Locke
is walking around this island...
Scares the living hell
out of me.
You may want
to go inside.
Why?
Because what's about to
come out of that jungle...
is something
I can't control.
Any luck?
It hasn't shown up yet.
Last time we didn't
have to wait this long.
It's not a train, John.
It doesn't run on a schedule.
Well, if it's not gonna
come to us, then...
I suppose
we'll have to go to it.
It doesn't work that way.
I only know how to summon it.
I don't know
where it actually is.
I do.
It's weird for me, too.
Excuse me?
I realize how
strange this all is--
Me, here.
But I assure you,
Sun,
I'm the same man
I've always been.
Are you ready?
Lead the way.
Hello?
Charles?
It's Benjamin.
How did you get
this number?
Doesn't matter.
What matters is...
I'm going back
to the island today.
The island won't let
you come back, trust me.
I've spent almost 20 years
trying to return.
Well, Charles, where you failed,
I'm going to succeed...
Just as soon
as I do one thing.
And what's that,
Benjamin?
Kill your daughter.
In fact, I'm looking at
"our mutual friend" right now.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
It's the name of the
boat that Penny's on.
Don't you dare.
Good-bye, Charles.
May I ask you
a question, John?
Shoot.
How is it that you
know where you're going?
I just know.
I mean,
how does that work, exactly?
How does what work?
The knowing. I mean,
did it come upon you gradually,
or did you wake up
one morning
suddenly understanding the
mysteries of the Universe?
- You don't like this, do you?
- What?
Having to ask questions
that you don't know
the answers to.
Blindly following
someone in the hopes that
they'll lead you to whatever it is
you're looking for.
No, John,
I don't like it at all.
Well, now you know what
it was like to be me.
We should keep moving.
Yes, we should.
I think I know where
we're going now, John.
Do you?
It's the same place they
brought me as a child.
It's where
the island healed me.
Well...
Let's hope it's as generous
this time around.
What is it?
It's the wall
around our temple.
What temple?
About a half mile
from here.
We built this wall to keep
people like the two of you
from ever seeing it.
We're not going
into your temple, Ben.
We're going under it.
After you.
I need to ask
a favor of you, Sun.
If you can ever
get off this island,
find Desmond Hume for me.
Tell him I said I was sorry.
Sorry for what?
He'll know.
Hey!
What are you
doing here?
Desmond!
Des?!
Don't move.
Not another word.
Hello, Penelope.
My name is
Benjamin Linus.
I'm sorry that you're caught
up in the middle of this thing,
- but your father--
- My father and I
have absolutely no relationship
whatsoever, so whatever--
Your father is a
really terrible human being.
He's responsible for the
killing of my daughter.
That's why I'm here.
Mommy!
Charlie,
go back inside, babe.
Go back inside. Please.
Please, whatever you do,
don't hurt my son.
- Please don't hurt my son.
- Mommy?
Mommy?
Charlie, go inside!
Captain Lapidus!
You're back.
Thank God!
They found guns.
What are you talking about?
Who found guns?
Ilana and
three of the others.
They said
they were in charge now.
Where are they?
Ilana!
What's going on?
What lies in the
shadow of the statue?
What?
Answer the question!
What lies in the
shadow of the statue?
I have no idea
what the--
Get everyone else.
Tell them it's time.
And tie him up.
He's coming with us.
You know,
you were right.
About what?
Why I need
to be judged.
When Charles Widmore's
men came,
they gave me a choice.
Either leave the island
or let my daughter die.
All I had to do was
walk out of the house
and go with them.
But I didn't do it.
So you were right.
John, I did kill Alex.
And now I have to
answer for that.
I appreciate you
showing me the way,
but I think I can
take it from here.
You got it.
I'll meet you outside.
If I live--
Ben!
Are you all right?
Never better.
Hang on. I'll find something
to get you out of there.
John, wait!
You didn't tell me that
she had a child.
What was it
I was supposed to do?
- Kill it.
- It's not an "it." This is a child.
Higher!
Again, daddy! Again!
Higher, daddy!
I hate you!
I hate your guts!
I wish you were dead.
These people--
You said they're dangerous.
More dangerous than you?
Dad, they're serious.
They killed
Karl and my mother.
Please, Dad.
Help me!
She's not my daughter.
She means
nothing to me.
So if you wanna kill her,
go ahead and--
Daddy?
Alex.
Hi, dad.
Ohh, Alex.
I'm so, so sorry.
It was all my fault.
I know.
Listen to me,
you bastard!
I know that you're already
planning to kill John again,
and I want you to know that
if you so much as touch him,
I will hunt you down
and destroy you.
You will listen to every word
John Locke says,
and you will follow
his every order.
Do you understand?
Say it!
Say you'll follow him.
Yes, I will.
I'll follow him. I swear.
Ben?
Ben!
What happened?
It let me live.
Transcript By:
Yyets.net
Final Edits By: VeRdiKT
[Subscene.com]