wanna hear something crazy?
What's that?
did you see the big guy
when we got on in L.A.?
Sitting in first class,
curly hair, guitar case?
What about him?
He's one of the oceanic six.
Guy's got nerves of steel, man.
He survives a full-on
mmercial airliner crash.
Now he's back flying over
the same south pacific?
Yeah, well...
maybe he doesn't believe that lightning
will strike twice in the same place.
you all right there, frank?
I'm just fine.
dude... you might wanna
fasten your seat belt.
oh, no.
What?
autopilot off!
I got the controls.
Autopilot off. You have the controls.
pull that rudder!
what? What?
- stall. Stall.
- We've lost power!
- Stall.
- Restarting one.
Restarting two.
Altimeter reads 650.
oh, my god.
Give me more power! I
can pull us out of this!
- You're gonna rip us apart!
- Do it!
Come on. Come on.
is that a runway?
massive instrument failure!
We're puttin' her down!
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
This is ajira 3-1-6!
- 50... 60...
- full flaps!
Gear down! Airspeed 190!
we're coming in too steep!
reverse thruers!
Come on!
We're runnin' out! We're runnin' out!
Hold on!
Brace for impact!
Hey, lady. Are you okay?
- Jarrah?
- No. My name is caesar.
We had an accident. But we're okay now.
- frank?
- Sun.
you all right?
Oh, my god. What happened?
I don't know.
Where's everyo else?
Jack and... kate and
hurley-- where'd they go?
they're gone.
gone? Gone where?
How would I know?
********
you're alive.
Dude! I can't believe it!
- easy on the ribs there, kong.
- "Kong."
- I actually missed that.
- I missed you, too, hugo.
Sawyer.
Doc.
Good to see you, kate.
You, too, james.
you're really here.
Son of a bitch actually did it!
Locke said he was gonna
bring you back, but...
where is he?
John's dead.
Dead? How?
Doesn't matter. He's gone.
So what's up with you guys
and the old dharma jumpsuits?
You didn't tell 'em?
No. I was waiting for you.
Tell us what?
We're in the dharma initiative.
They came back to the island?
No. We came back.
And so did you.
It's 1977.
what?
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:??????
720p re-sync : tw612
Lost
Season05 Episode09
so you're telling me
that you've been here,
living with the dharma initiative
for the past three years?
That's right.
How long's it been for
you since the chopper?
Three years.
hey, jin, this is miles.
Where are you? Over.
if I don't report in soon,
they'll send out a patrol.
What should we do with them?
Dude, your english is awesome.
What we do is we bring 'em in.
Bring us in where?
Back to the barracks at dharmaville.
You can't be wandering around
in the jungle with the hostiles.
"The hostiles"?
The others.
What about everyone else from the
plane? They could still be out there.
What do you mean, everyone else?
We didn't come back alone.
Sayid was on the plane, too. Lapidus...
and sun.
Jin! Hold up! Where you goin'?
The flame.
If a plane landed on the
island, radzinsky will know.
hold on! We gotta think about this!
all righ that's it.
Listen, you guys gotta stay put.
Don't go nowhere, don't do nothing till I can figure
out how the hell to explain where you came from.
Sawyer, wait.
Other than you and jin,
who else is still here?
Miles, have you seen james?
Nope.
He's not answering his walkie, either.
Jin called him this morning, then he just
ran off without telling me what was going on.
Well, let's see what we've got.
hang on. There he is.
You seen my baggy sweatshirt,
the one with the bulldog on it?
It's in the laundry. James...
- what's going on?
- They're back.
I'm sorry. Who's back?
Jack, hurley, kate.
What?
I know.
They came back, juliet.
Are they here now?
They're out at the north point,
waitin' for me to tell 'em what to do.
how did they get...
I'm not sure. They said
they were on a plane.
I don't understand it
any more than you do.
But they're here, and I gotta find a way to
bring 'em in before somebody else finds 'em
and they screw up
everything we got here.
There's, um, a sub
coming in this afternoon.
hey, you understand
the concept of knocking?
oh, get your hands off that!
I thought you learned
english. I said, hands off!
Nobody handles any of the gear in
this station except me. Understand?
I need to check the radar logs.
- For what?
- Please.
I need to know if a plane
landed on the island.
If a plane landed? Here?
Yes.
What, so you think if a plane landed on our
island, I'd be over there just building my model?
That I wouldn't have called anyone?
That I wouldn't have put out an alert?
Maybe you missed it.
Can you check with the other stations?
I just told you
I would not be--
check with the other stations.
attention all stations, this is a system-wide
broadcast from radzinsky at the flame.
I'm checking in to see if anyone's
seen an airplane over the island.
no one else has seen an airplane, but if you
have, could you call in to me, please? Over.
so what are you all hot
and bothered about, kwon?
Why is this plane so damn important?
It just is.
did you lose someone?
Excuse me?
I just saw you looking around.
I thought maybe you lost
someone on the plane.
No. I was traveling alone.
can I get everybody's attention?
Everybody, please!
Listen up, folks!
Here's where we're at.
The radio's dead, so I haven't
been able to call in our situation.
But that's all right.
Soon as they figure out we're not where we're
supposed to be, they'll come looking for us.
So best thing to do right
now is just stick together.
Stick together, hunker down and
just wait till help gets here.
- And where is here?
- What's that?
Where is here? What is this place?
I don't know where "here" is because
this island's not on my charts.
- Really
- really.
Because there are some buildings
over there... and animal cages.
Down the beach, you can see a
bigger island across the water.
So maybe you should get some new charts.
right now, I'm just trying
to keep everyone here safe.
So let's gather up some firewood.
if he wants to wait, let him!
I say we search these buildings!
Maybe they have a radio or some food!
Who wants to help me?
Why are you following me?
Where are you going?
Back to our island.
You wanna come?
Juliet?
Hey, amy. I'm sorry. I
didn't mean to wake you.
Oh, no, it's fine.
I just came to get the sub manifest.
- obviously, I don't want you working today.
- Thank you.
- Full load?
- Almost.
Two of the recruits dropped
out in the eleventh hour.
They didn't want to take
the sedative for the trip.
Can you tell pierre for me?
Oh, hello, little one.
Have you and horace decided on a name?
Yeah, we have.
We're gonna name him ethan.
oh, hey, buddy.
So... when are you and jim
gonna have one of these?
I don't know.
Timing's gotta be right.
so the woman who told
you how to come back...
did she mention that it
would be 30 years ago?
No. No, she left that part out.
So what are we supposed to do now?
I'm not sure yet.
sawyer's back!
all right, listen.
Y'all are gonna be thcond batch of recruits comin'
in off the sub pullin' into port right about now,
so we ain't got much
time. Nice suit, doc.
Not exactly island wear. Try this.
You want us to say we came in on
the sub. How's that gonna work?
Everyone gets knocked out before the trip, so
no one meets each other until we process 'em.
Look, we need to find the rest
of the people from the plane.
If there was a plane, jin will find it.
So we got about ten minutes to make intake, or y'all
are gonna be camping in the jungle for a long time.
There ain't another batch of
recruits due in for six months.
What do you think?
I think we should listeno sawyer.
I vote for not camping.
Trust me. Do what I say.
Everything will be fine.
Let's move.
I just heard from the looking glass.
They were the last station to check in.
They got nothing but an incoming sub.
Why don't you go home, and I'll
call you if something happens?
move. Move. Out of my way.
those bastards.
What do you see?
Grid 325. Motion sensor
alarm was tripped.
We got a hostile inside the perimeter.
Where you going?
Stop right there!
Sayid?
Jin?
where's sun?
- I don't know.
- shut up!
Get down!
Say another word, and you're dead.
Okay, so it's 1977.
Yep.
And... you guys are all members
of the dharma initiative.
Yep.
Well, you do realize
thosdudes get wiped out, right?
I mean, I saw the pit where
all the bodies got dumped.
- What about it?
- Well, aren't you gonna warn 'em?
Aren't you gonna stop it from happening?
I ain't here to play
nostradamus to these people.
Besides, faraday's got some interesting
theories on what we can and can't do here.
Did you say faraday? He's here?
Not anymore.
recruits will be going
inside for processing,
where you'll be given your
work assignment and lodging.
put these on and listen up.
Juliet's got it worked out so your
name's gonna be on the list, all right?
So when you get in there, just watch
the little meet and greet video,
wait for 'em to call your name.
When they do, just smile, step up, take
your jumpsuits and work assignments.
- Work assignments?
- Yeah, don't worry. I got it covered.
Just remembeto act a little doped up,
'cause you just woke up from the sub.
What if they start asking us questions we
can't answer, like, uh, who's president in 1977?
It's not a damn game show, hugo.
Besides, I'm gonna be in there
to get your backs, all right?
Let's move.
lafleur! Where have you been?
I've been trying to
reach you on the walkie.
what--what the hell
are they doing here?
They're our new inductees.
I'll explain everything later.
stop staring and tell me
what your damn problem is.
'S, uh... it's jin.
There's a fourteen-j at the flame.
What? jin, you there?
james, we have a problem.
We found a hostile.
what? What do you mean
you found a hostile? Where?
he was wandering in the jungle.
Radzinksy's taking care of him now.
What's he doing in our territory?
It's a violation of the truce.
- it's sayid.
- what?
Son of a bitch!
was anyone else with him?
No. He was alone.
wait!
I'm sorry, sun, but waiting
doesn't interest me much right now.
There are three outriggers
near here. I'm gonna take one.
So you can come along and help me row...
or you can stay here.
Frankly, it make no difference to me.
- Why are you leaving?
- Why are you staying?
The main island...
is that where jin is?
Honestly, I don't know.
But that's where I'd start looking.
- sun!
- Over here!
Hello, frank.
you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
I got worried when I couldn't find ya.
I saw him leaving.
What are you doing out here?
Ben knows where there's a boat.
I'm going back to the
main island with him.
You don't think you can
really trust this guy, do ya?
I have to trust him.
- you ready?
- Yes.
Sun. I want you to think about is, okay?
This guy is dangerous.
Sun, that boat I came here on-- it was filled
with commandos whose only mission was to get him.
And how'd that work out for everyone?
Don't do it.
Why don't you come with us?
I can'T. I got a group of
people I gotta look after.
That's right, frank.
A captain's first responsibility
is to his passengers.
T I have people I have
to take care of, too.
There's a small dock about a half
mile due south across the water.
It leads directly to a town where I
used to live. There are resources there.
So if anyone can help you and the rest
of the plane get out of here safely, it--
I thought you trusted this guy.
I lied.
Welcome to the island.
For your own comfort and safety, we ask that you
stay within the confines of your new living quarters.
Our barracks are surrounded
by a high frequency sonar fence
to protect us from the island's
abundant and diverse wildlife.
How are we gonna do this?
Shephard? Jack shephard?
Here we go.
Hey, jack. Have a seat.
Of course it isn't here.
- what's that?
- Your file.
Could they be any more
disorganized on the other side?
Sorry. Namaste. I'm pierre chang.
Welcome to the dharma initiative.
How was your ride in?
- It was fine.
- Good.
Who was your shuttle driver?
I'm sorry?
the shuttle from the
sub. Who was your driver?
Oh, that was, uh... mr. Lafleur.
Ah, yes. Good man, lafleur.
Runs a very tight operation.
I'm sorry for the disorganization.
The woman who was supposed to be
processing you in had a baby last night.
I got pulled out of my lab. I...
ah, here it is... your job assignment.
you've been assigned to the shed.
"Work man." What does--
what does that mean?
Based on your aptitude test,
you'll be doing janitorial work.
hey there, ma'am. They
haven't called you yet?
No. Not yet.
What's your name?
Kate... austen.
Austen. austen...
You're not on my list, and you're
not on the sub manifest either.
Who's your recruiter?
hold on, phil. I just
got the new list from amy.
Some, uh, last-minute additions,
includinG... miss austen?
All righty then. She's all yours.
I'm sorry for the mix-up. I'm juliet.
Kate.
Hi, kate. Welcome to the island.
what the hell happened?
Sayid just came walking out of
the jungle in handcuffs alone.
What? Did he say anything
about the plane they were on?
No, I couldn't talk to him. Radzinsky thinks
he's a hostile. He won't leave us alone.
I got this.
- Where is he?
- Locked in the storage room.
Give me the key.
You need to
know, lafleur--
he saw the model of the swan, and he could've
seen the survey of where we're building it.
- Your point is?
- He's a spy.
This whole thing is an act, and
we either play into it or we don'T.
We can end this right now.
What theell are you
talking about, radzinsky?
We shoot him.
Well, I appreciate your
input there, quick draw.
But I wanna talk to him
first. Give me the damn keys.
my name's lafleur. I'm head of security.
I want you to listen real
carefully to what I got to say.
And if you do that,
you'll be fine. Understand?
All right, let's start simple.
Identify yourself as a hostile.
The terms of the truce say you
gotta identify yourself as a hostile,
or we got the right to shoot you.
We do not refer to ourselves as
"hostile," but yes, I-I am one of them.
all right. Good. Now we can
proceed like a couple of gtlemen.
All right, let's go. Just
taking him back to the barracks.
Oh, if you're taking him
in, then I'm coming with you.
this is a horrible mistake.
I'm gonna talk directly
to horace about this.
Fine. Talk away.
You wanna remind me why
the hell we're doing this?
Ben said if my husband is on the isla, the
best place to start looking for him is here.
Oh, I see, that's some advice you took
before you whacked him in the head.
tell me you saw that.
Probably just an animal.
Animal. Right.
I'm sorry to say, sun, but...
I don't think we're gonna
find your husband here.
Maybe we oughta just head back.
hello.
Who the hell are you?
My name's christian.
I'm looking for my husband.
His name is jin kwon.
Do you know where he is?
Follow me.
What is this place?
'72... '76, '78...
where is my husband?
Here we go. '77.
He's, uh... he's with your friends.
What are you talking
about? What friends?
I'm sorry, but you have a
bit of a journey ahead of you.
okay, ready? Everybody say, "namaste!"
namastE.
- Nama-what?
- okay.
right on.
So you guys have the rest
of the day to get acquainted
with your security protocol
handbooks waitin' in your new digs.
Now some of it may seem a little scary, but I
promise you all, we are perfectly safe here, okay?
So make yourselves at home. Come
on. We got hamburgers. We got punch.
you there, phil? We're
coming in with a fourteen-J.
Roger that, mr. Lafleur.
okay, if I could get everyone to hold back,
please, we have a minor security situation.
move.
I guess we found sayid.
All right, you can hang out here until
we can figure out what to do with you.
What are we gonna do with him?
bring the man some damn
food. We're not savages.
ah, excuse me.
could you tell me where
james lafleur lives?
Uh, that's his house right there.
thanks.
But I wouldn't call him "james."
He hates it.
hey, jack.
I saw you earlier today
when you were helping kate,
and I wanted to say
something to you then, but...
we're not supposed to know each other.
Yeah.
I was looking for sawyer. I
guess I came to the wrong house.
No. Come in.
Evening, doc.
well, I'm sure you two
have a lot to talk about.
Take a load off. You want a beer?
No. no, I'm fine.
What can I do for you, jack?
I don't even know where to start.
how about with sayid?
I had no choice.
He was running around in the
jungle, got caught by my people.
And seein' as how he can't tell the truth
about how he got here, I had to improvise.
Improvise?
And for now, sayid is safe,
which is all that matters.
So where do we go from here?
I'm working on it.
Really? Because it looked to
me like you were reading a book.
I heard once winston churchill read a
book every night, even during the blitz.
He said it made him think better.
It's how I like to run things. I think.
I'm sure that doesn't mean that much to you,
'cause back when you were calling the shots,
you pretty much just reacted.
See, you didn't think, jack, and as I
recall, a lot of people ended up dead.
I gous off the island.
But here you are... right
back where you started.
So I'm gonna go back to reading
my book, and I'm gonna think,
'cause that's how I
saved your ass today.
And that's how I'm gonna
save sayid's tomorrow.
All you gotta do is go home,
get a good night's rest.
Let me do what I do.
now ain't that a relief?
Yeah.
Hey, phil. I'm just gonna go in
there and deliver him a sandwich.
All right.
hello.
I brought you a sandwich.
I didn't put mustard on it, but if
you'd like some, I could get some.
This will be fine. Thank you.
are you a hostile?
Do you think I am?
What's your name?
Sayid.
What's yours?
I'm ben.
It's nice to meet you, ben.