Previously on "Lost"...
How did you know my father?
He came to see his daughter.
My daughter was on your plane.
Her name was Claire.
We're here to get
a blood sample from you...
and one
from your son Aaron.
Why?
To determine your
relationship to the child.
Where are you going, mommy?
We're going on vacation, baby.
Wait, you're in L.A.?
Of course we can meet, yeah.
Hello, Kate.
You okay?
Get me to the car.
- Sayid, you've been attacked.
- Where's Hurley?
The only way to save the island, John,
is to get your people back here.
How? How am I supposed to do that?
What? You've...
Do you know what's happening to me?
Charlotte? Charlotte?
Hey.
Oh, you don't have to whisper.
- When he's out, he's out.
- Yeah.
At least one of us can sleep.
It's gonna take more than two nights...
for me to get used to
sleeping in a normal bed.
What are we gonna do about him?
About Aaron.
I don't know.
I've been thinking a lot about him.
Did you know that Claire was flying
to L.A. to give him up for adoption?
No. No, I didn't.
I think we should say he's mine.
What?
We could say that I was six months
pregnant when I was arrested
and that I gave birth
to him on the island.
- No one would ever know.
- Kate.
No. You don't have to...
There's other ways to do this.
After everyone we've lost...
Michael, Jin, Sawyer...
I can't lose him, too.
Sawyer's not dead.
I know.
But he's gone.
Good night, Jack.
Kate.
If we're gonna be safe,
if we're gonna protect the
people that we left behind,
tomorrow morning, I'm gonna
have to convince everyone to lie.
If it's just me, they're
never gonna go for it.
So I'm gonna turn to you first.
Are you with me?
I have always been with you.
How does it fit?
It's perfect. Thank you for the loaner.
Looks great on you.
Are you sure you want to do this?
It was your idea.
Mommy!
Aaron, honey, mommy's gonna
run out and do an errand.
I'll be right back. Okay?
And then we can go home.
Don't worry about us, Kate.
There's candy in the minibar
and a hundred channels on tv.
We're going to be just fine here.
Sun...
I don't know what I would've
done if you weren't here.
Thank you.
It's what any friend would do.
Okay, well, I will be back soon.
Okay, you be good for Sun.
Okay, honey?
Good luck.
Delivery for you, Ms. Kwon.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I'll be right back, honey.
Lost SO5EO4
"The Little Prince"
subtitle by ydy. com
edited and synced by rogard
Charlotte? Charlotte.
What the hell is wrong with her?
She's been out for ten minutes.
Stop shouting, James.
Hey, man.
Thank you.
If there's something that you want to
tell me, Daniel, now would be a good time.
I'm not sure what you mean exactly.
She's asking if you know why
your girlfriend had a seizure.
Give us some space, would you?
She's like this 'cause
the sky keeps lighting up.
He knew this would happen and he
didn't say squat about it.
James.
Go away.
Did you know that this would happen?
I thought...
I thought it might.
I think it's neurological.
Our brains have an internal clock,
a sense of time.
The flashes... throw the clock off.
It's like really bad jet lag.
Really bad jet lag doesn't
make you hemorrhage, Daniel.
You wanna tell me why it isn't
happening to the rest of us?
I don't know.
But thank God it's not.
Thank you for waiting.
Did my assistant offer
you something to drink?
Um, yes. I'm fine, thank you.
Good. Please, Ms. Austen, sit.
So...
How can I help you?
Mr. Norton,
when you came to my house
looking for blood samples
from me and my son,
I asked you who your client was.
- And I said I couldn't tell you.
- Yeah.
I'm here to offer you a deal.
I'll give you the blood samples,
but first, I wanna talk to your client.
Considering what you're asking for,
that's more than reasonable.
Well, I am, uh, seeing
my client later today,
and I will be sure to
pass along your offer.
But I am pretty sure of
what the answer's gonna be:
No.
And the reason, of course,
is that you're in no position
to be making any kind of deals,
and we both know it.
I have a signed court
order compelling you
to let us confirm that
you're the child's mother.
I could send the sheriff over
there today and make you do it,
but my client insists that we...
handle the exchange of custody quietly.
What do you mean "exchange of custody"?
You know exactly what I mean.
No, I...
Mr. Norton,
I just wanna know who
is doing this to me.
You did this to yourself.
Now it is time you
prepare yourself, Ms. Austen.
You are going to lose the boy.
We have to go back to The Orchid.
Excuse me?
The Orchid.
That's where all this started.
Maybe it's where it'll all stop.
That greenhouse is a long ways away.
You said you had a
zodiac raft back at the beach.
We could take that,
cut around the horn of the island,
be at The Orchid in half the time.
And let me guess. You know exactly
what to do when we get there.
No, not exactly at all,
but I know that Ben used
it to leave the island.
And if I can do the same thing,
I believe I can save us.
And how you gonna do that?
This is all happening because they left.
I think it'll stop if
I can bring them back.
- Bring who back?
- Jack, Sun, Sayid, Hugo, Kate.
The boat blew up,
and that chopper was probably on it.
They're not dead, James.
- Says who?
- That doesn't matter.
All that matters is
they've gotta come back.
I have to make them come back...
even if it kills me.
Don't you want 'em to come back, James?
Don't you want her to come back?
It doesn't matter what I want.
Hey!
She's waking up!
Are you okay?
Who are you?
It's me.
It's Daniel.
Daniel.
Oww..
Oh, my head.
What happened?
There was another flash. You passed out.
How do you feel?
A bit dizzy, but...
I'm fine.
Good.
Hooray. Everything's back to normal.
Now what?
I'll tell you "now what. "
We're going to The Orchid.
Oncologist on call to the I.C.U.
Dilation's almost back to normal.
Good. Now take this I.V.
out of my arm, and let's go.
Sayid, you were
unconscious for over 42 hours.
You had the equivalent of three doses
of horse tranquilizer in your system.
If you sent that man to
Hurley's house, we have to leave...
- You need to relax.
- ... now.
Ben is not gonna hurt Hurley.
Ben is on our side.
The only side he's on is his own.
Dr. Shephard?
I'm Dr. Ariza, director
of clinical services.
A word with you, please?
I'll be right back.
What do you think you are doing here?
I was treating a patient.
I apologize. It was an emergency.
I know that-
You were suspended
on charges of substance abuse.
Emergency or not, Dr. Shephard,
you have no business being here.
I understand, and I take
full responsibility for my actions.
No, doctor.
The hospital takes full
responsibility for your actions,
and that makes us liable for them.
Excuse me.
- Hello?
- Jack? It's me.
- Hurley.
- Hey, did Sayid get to you?
Did my dad drop him off?
- Yes, he did. Hurley, where are-?
- Is he okay?
- He's fine.
- Awesome.
Hurley, where are you?
Dude, I'm totally cool.
I'm in L.A. County lockup.
Oh, and tell Sayid I did
exactly what he said.
I'm totally safe. Ben's
never gonna get me now. Thank you.
What are you talking about,
Hurley? Wait! Wait-
Good. You're here. How's Sayid?
How are you doing today, sir?
Got your meds for you.
Sorry, I think you have the wrong room.
Nope. Room 133, right?
Got the orders right
here. Don't worry.
I won't have to give you an injection.
Put this right in your I.V. line.
Who are you? Who are you working for?
Okay, talk, talk.
Address... it's in my pocket.
Hello, Sayid.
What happened?
Do we know anyone who
lives at 42 Panorama Crest?
That's Kate's address.
Hello?
Kate? It's Jack. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Where are you right
now? Are you at home?
Uh... What?
Listen, I'll explain
everything once you're out,
- but you've gotta get Aaron-
- Look, I'm not at home, okay? I'm...
Aaron is at a hotel with Sun.
Sun? Sun's in L.A.?
Yeah, she's here on business.
Listen, Jack, this is
really not a good time.
I'm so sorry that I even
picked up the phone. I'm not-
Kate, do not hang up on me.
Please listen. Listen, uh...
Will you tell me where you are?
I need to see you.
Kate, please.
I'm downtown.
Wilshire and Olive.
Okay. All right. I'm on my way.
She's not at home,
but I'm gonna go to her right now.
- Good. I'll go deal with Hugo.
- Sorry, Ben.
I'm not letting
you get anywhere near him.
You have friends in trouble.
Let's get them to safety
and save the dirty linen for later.
I'll drive.
After you get Kate,
meet us at the Long
Beach Marina, slip 23.
And, Jack... Hurry.
We're running out of time.
Hey, Locke.
What are you gonna say to her?
Sorry?
Kate.
What are you gonna say to her
to get her to come back?
I haven't figured that out yet.
Well, let me tell you something.
She was pretty excited
to hop on that chopper
and get the hell out of here.
What the hell is that?
Whatever it is, we
better stay clear of it.
Beach is this way.
Now you wanna take the scenic route?
John...
Do you know when we are?
We need to keep moving.
Hey. How's your headache?
Better.
Nothing like sore feet to take
your mind off your head, eh?
Well, don't worry.
Once we get to the beach,
we're gonna take the zodiac
around the other side
of the island and rest.
You're sweet, but you don't
need to baby me. I'm fine.
You okay?
I'm peachy.
Now what?
Nobody move.
James!
I got this.
... you con't stop now.
It knows I don't want it,
and I was gonna give it away.
Babies know that stuff.
Okay, no, no, hang on. Listen, listen.
Do you want this baby?
Do you want it to be safe and healthy?
You're not alone in this.
We are all here for you.
This baby is all of ours.
But I need you to push.
Okay?
One, two, three...
Push! Push!
Come on, Claire! Push!
Okay! He's coming!
Push! Push! Push! Push!
James?
What happened?
Did you see something out here, James?
It don't matter.
It's gone now.
You shaved your beard.
Yeah.
I just needed a change.
Look, Jack, uh...
I don't know why you called,
but I can't be dealing
with this right now.
What's going on?
Nothing. Just...
- Can you just go?
- Why don't you just tell me?
Jack, please, just go.
Kate, please, tell me.
Somebody wants Aaron.
What?
There's a lawyer in there.
His clients... they know we're lying.
They know I'm not his mom,
and they're gonna take him away.
Who's gonna take him away?
What- what are you doing?
Look, I gotta go, all right?
Get in or don't.
Hey.
You ready to tell me
who you saw back there?
Already told you. It was nothin'.
You and I both know when
we were before the flash, James.
So who was it you saw?
Charlie? Shannon? Yourself?
And how is it that you
knew when we were, Johnny boy?
That light in the sky...
it was from the hatch, wasn't it?
The night that Boone died...
I went out there and started
pounding on it as hard as I could.
I was... confused. Scared.
Babbling like an idiot,
asking, why was all
this happening to me?
Did you get an answer?
Light came on, shot up into the sky.
At the time, I thought
it meant something.
Did it?
No. It was just a light.
So why'd you turn us around then?
Don't you wanna go back there?
Why would I wanna do that?
So you could tell yourself
to do things different,
save yourself a world of pain.
No, I needed that pain
to get to where I am now.
Hey.
I just got a nosebleed.
What? When?
Let's just not freak
out the others, okay?
Just tell me...
Why-why her? Why me?
I don't know.
Uh, I think it might have something
to do with duration of exposure.
You know, the amount of time
you've spent on the island.
Doesn't make any sense.
Those yahoos have been here for months.
I've never been here
before two weeks ago.
Are you sure about that?
Hello?!
The camp's back.
Finally.
Anybody for a Dharma beer?
Hello? Anybody here?
Rose? Bernard?
I wonder how long ago this happened.
Son of a bitch!
What is it?
It's Vincent's.
Yeah? Well, where's the rest of the dog?
Where's the rest of our people?
The zodiac's gone, too.
Maybe your people took the boat.
Why the hell would they do that?
To get away from whoever came in those.
Where did these come from?
That's a good question.
They're pretty old.
Not that old.
Let me see that.
"adg-uh-ruh"?
Ajira. It's an airline.
It's based out of India,
but they fly everywhere.
Great. Maybe they got a flight
out of here to Vegas tonight.
Who came in these?
Other Others?
Don't look at me.
My question is, when
are they coming back?
Let's not wait to find out.
This plan sounded a hell of a lot better
when we were going by motorboat.
How far is this place?
It's around that point.
Not more than a couple hours.
Oh, joy.
You all right?
I saw Kate.
What?
Last night, in the jungle.
Before the last flash.
She was delivering Claire's baby.
But that was two months ago.
Time travel's a bitch.
Get down!
Paddle!
I think they want their boat back!
Move!
Are these your people?!
No! Are they yours?!
Shut up and keeping paddling!
Little help! Little help!
Paddle harder! They're getting closer!
Thank you, lord!
I take that back!
Everybody, paddle! Head for the shore!
Kate, just because the guy
told you that he was meeting his client
doesn't mean that they're here in L.A.
He could've just told
you that to-to throw you off.
Or they're in
that hotel right now.
Okay. And what if they are?
What if the person who
wants to take Aaron
is sitting in that hotel room right now?
Then what?
Come on. Come with me.
We'll- we'll go get Aaron,
we'll put our heads together,
and we'll figure something out.
All right.
Oh, my God.
It's Claire's mother.
Wait.
- What am I waiting for, Jack?
- Wait. I just...
Let's just think about this for a minute.
- She knows.
- Maybe she doesn't know.
No, but she knows about Aaron,
and that's all that matters.
Let me go talk to her.
What?
If I can just explain
to her why we did it,
maybe if I can get her
to understand why...
She'll listen to me.
I can fix this, Kate. I can fix it.
Aaron is my family, too.
Dr. Shephard?
Hello, Ms. Littleton. Um...
May I come in?
Of course.
You look drenched.
No, no. No, I'm fine.
God, I haven't seen you
since your father's funeral.
How did you even know I was here?
I knew you were here, Ms. Littleton,
because I followed your lawyer.
Why would you do that?
I'm- I did it because, um...
I understand that you
feel the need to do this.
But I need you to know
that everything that Kate
and I have done... it was for Aaron.
Who's... Aaron?
I- I'm afraid I'm not following you.
Ms. Littleton, um...
What are you doing here in Los Angeles?
Let's go. Drive.
Then call Sun and tell her to bring
Aaron to the Long Beach Marina.
- We'll meet her there.
- What-wh-what are you talking about?
- What happened?
- Kate, we have to go now.
I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me what just happened.
She doesn't know anything.
What?
She doesn't know.
She still thinks that Claire is dead.
She doesn't even know that Aaron exists.
But the lawyer...?
She sued Oceanic, and she's in
town to pick up her settlement.
What, and it's just a
coincidence that her lawyer
happens to be the same one
that's trying to take my son?
I don't know.
But whoever's trying to take Aaron...
It's not her.
Then who is it?
Can I ask you something?
Why'd you take it upon
yourself to rescue Hugo?
I had to make sure Hurley was safe.
You can pull in over here.
Mr. Linus.
Mr. Norton.
I looked into it,
and they don't have any kind
of solid case against Reyes.
The M.E. said that the man found outside
Santa Rosa was killed
before Reyes escaped.
That's very good news.
We have a prelim hearing in the morning.
The judge will never
let it get past that,
and Reyes will be a free man.
Thank you, Dan.
Anytime.
Who was that?
That's my lawyer.
Okay.
Remind me never to do that again.
Where are we?
It's hard to say till it gets light.
We didn't get a chance to
finish our conversation.
What conversation was that?
The one before they
started shooting at us,
where you were about to tell me
how it felt to see Kate again.
I wasn't about to tell you anything.
Why don't you tell me now?
I was close enough to touch her.
If I'd wanted to, I could've...
stood right up and talked to her.
Why didn't you?
What's done is done.
Juliet?
What's wrong?
Come and look at this!
It's wreckage.
Looks like it just happened.
Anybody speak French?
Jack, why did you call me today?
I told you. I was...
I was worried.
But why? Why were you
worried? Why today?
I don't...
Right before I called you,
Sayid was attacked.
And the guy that did it...
your address was in his pocket.
Sayid? What's he doing here?
That's not important right now.
What matters is that we
get you and Aaron someplace safe.
Safe from who?
Hello, Kate.
It's okay. He's with me.
He's with you?
I know this is gonna
be hard to understand,
but he's here to help us.
To help everyone that we left behind.
We all need to be together again.
It's him.
What?
It's him. He's the one
who's trying to take Aaron.
- No. No. You- you don't understand.
- No, Jack. She's right.
It was me.
Sorry.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Why don't you just stay away?!
Why don't you leave
me and my son alone?!
Because he's not your son, Kate.
You all right?
No understand.
You speak English?
A little.
Are you okay?
Yes.
How did you get here?
Boat.
Who is he? What does he say
He said he came on a boat.
What boat?
It's gone.
Sink.
It must've been caught in
the same storm as ours.
Who are you? How long you in the water?
I don't know.
How do you not know how you wound
up in the middle of the ocean, huh?
Leave him alone. He's in shock.
Can you get me him some water?
Merci, Robert.
Thank you.
What is your name?
Kwon Jin.
Jin.
Hello, Jin.
I'm Danielle.
Danielle Rousseau.
subtitle by team ydy. com
edited and synced by rogard