Previously on "Lost":
The only way to save the island, John,
is to get your people back here.
The chopper was headed
for the boat. The boat--
No, they're fine, John,
and they're already home.
So you have convince them
to come back.
How? How am I supposed to do that?
You're gonna have to die, John.
You're going down there?
What exactly are you hoping to find?
A way off the island.
Once you get all of
your friends together,
and it must be all of
them, everyone who left,
once you've persuaded them to join you,
Eloise Hawking will tell
you exactly how to come back.
Richard said I was going to die.
That's why they call it sacrifice.
Caesar.
Ilana. What's up?
Find anything?
No. Nothing useful.
Then what'd you just put in your bag?
If you want it, it's yours.
We found someone. A man.
What?
Roxanne was scouting just south of here,
and he was just standing in the water.
He's wearing a suit.
- Nobody recognizes him?
- No. Whoever he is, he didn't come with us.
Then how do we know he isn't
one of the ones who disappeared?
He's not.
And how do you know?
Because he wasn't on the plane.
What did this man have to say?
You can ask him yourself.
Hello.
My name is Caesar. What's yours?
My name is John Locke.
- =http: //sfile.ydy.com=- proudly presents
sync: ??????,
edited by rogard
Lost Season 05 Episode 07
"The Life and Death of Jeremy Bentham"
Morning.
Hello.
Breakfast? We found a tree.
They're pretty good.
Much obliged.
- I'm Ilana.
- John.
Are those your boats?
No. They were already here.
There used to be three, but the
pilot and some woman took one.
Didn't tell anyone, just ran
off in the middle of the night.
The pilot of the plane
that brought you here?
Yes. That's right.
Do you have a passenger list?
You'll have to talk to Caesar.
I think this is the best
mango I've ever eaten.
Nobody remembers you being on the plane.
Well, I don't remember
being on it either.
- What do you remember?
- I remember a lot.
Like why you're dressed up so nice?
No, but I can guess.
Please. Guess.
I think this suit is what
they were gonna bury me in.
- Sorry?
- You asked what I remembered.
I remember dying.
Good luck, John.
Say hello to my son.
Who's your son?
Is anybody in there? Can you help me?
God!
where is this? Where am I?
Where am I? Where is this?
Sir, where am I? Who are you?
Where am I? Do you speak English?
You swallow. Swallow.
Where are we?
Oh--what? What?
What? What--
You bite. Bite!
John?
John, wake up.
You had a compound fracture.
The doctors here did their best, but I had a
specialist flown in to reset your leg properly.
It's nice to see you again, John.
- Do I know you?
- Yes.
I understand your being confused.
Imagine how I feel.
I met you when I was 17.
And now, all these years later,
here we are.
You look exactly the same.
Who are you?
My name is Charles Widmore.
Tell me, John. How long
has it been for you since...
we first met, since you walked into
our camp and you spoke to Richard?
Four days.
That's incredible.
The camera in the desert -
that was yours?
Yeah.
How did you know I'd be there?
Because that's the exit.
I was afraid Benjamin might fool you into
leaving the island, like he did with me.
I was their leader.
The Others?
They're not the "Others"
to me. They're my people.
We protected the island peacefully
for more than three decades.
But then I was exiled by him...
just as you were.
No. Ben wasn't even there when
I left. He was already gone.
I-I... I wasn't exiled.
I... chose to leave.
Why would you do that, John?
You've come to bring them back,
the ones who left.
No.
I understand you lying to me. I do.
But there's something you should know.
All your friends who left the island?
They've been back three years.
Three years?
And they've gone back
to their normal lives.
and none of them has spoken a word
of truth about where they were.
I have to bring them back.
And I'm gonna do everything in
my power to help you do that.
Why?
"Why"?
Why would you help me?
Because there's a war coming, John.
And if you're not back on
the island when that happens,
the wrong side is going to win.
"Jeremy Bentham"?
He was a British philosopher.
Your parents had a sense of humor
when they named you, so why can't I?
This should be money enough for now.
The phone's international.
If you need to reach me,
for anything, just press 2-3.
The folder contains
your people's whereabouts,
everyone that was on
the island that left.
You've been watching them?
I'm deeply invested in the
future of the island, John.
So, yes, I've been watching them.
I wouldn't mention I'm involved in this.
I can't imagine what they think of
me, having listened to Benjamin's lies.
How do I know that you're
not the one who's lying?
I haven't tried to kill you.
Would you say the same for him?
You still don't trust me.
You sent a team of killers and
a boatload of C4 to the island.
That... doesn't exactly scream "trust."
I needed Linus removed,
so it could be your time.
Right.
The island needs you, John.
It has for a long time.
What makes you think I'm so special?
Because you are.
Your chariot has arrived.
He said I would die.
I beg your pardon?
Richard Alpert. He said the only way
to get them to come back was if I died.
I don't know why he said that,
but I'm not gonna let that happen.
This is Matthew Abaddon.
He'll take you anywhere you need to go,
protect you from whomever
intends to do you harm.
Mr. Locke.
Good luck, John, and godspeed.
Anything you need, Mr. Locke,
you just let me know.
Anything.
Anybody from your past you
want me to look up for you?
The whole world thinks
you're dead, Mr. Locke.
There must be somebody
who'd be happy to see you.
Please don't talk to me.
You got it.
But we're almost at the airport,
so you're gonna at least have to
tell me where we're going first.
Santo Domingo.
Finally. I need it for the roof.
Pass me another beam.
Hey, Sayid!
Look! You have a visitor.
I don't believe this.
You actually want me to go back?
I-I know how it sounds, Sayid,
but you have to trust me.
This is the only way to save them.
I'm not going back.
For two years, I was manipulated into thinking
I was protecting everyone on the island.
Who was manipulating you?
Ben.
So who is manipulating you, John?
This is coming from me, nobody else.
I know you, Sayid.
And deep down in your heart, you know
we never should've left the island.
It's only because I left the island that I
was finally able to marry the woman I loved.
We spent nine months together,
the best nine months of my life, John.
That's what I know in my heart.
Where is she now?
She was murdered.
I'm sorry.
Why do you really need to go back?
Is it just because you
have nowhere else to go?
If you change your mind, I'll be staying
under the name "Jeremy Bentham" in L.A.
at the Westerfield Hotel.
And if you change your mind, you're welcome
to come back here and do some real good.
Good-bye, John.
You asked if there was someone
you could look up for me.
Yes, I did.
Her name is Helen, Helen Norwood,
and she was living in Los Angeles.
She an old girlfriend of yours?
Help me get out of the car.
So that's Michael Dawson's son, huh?
Yeah. Boy's gotten big.
Um, I'm-- I'll be right back. Gotta go.
I'll give you two some privacy.
- Hey, John.
- Hi, Walt.
- What happened?
- I hurt my leg.
You don't seem surprised to see me.
I've been having dreams about you.
You were on the island, wearing a suit,
and there are people all around you.
They wanted to hurt you, John.
Good thing they're just dreams.
Is my dad... is he back on the island?
I haven't talked to him in three years.
I figured he must've gone back.
Um, last I heard, your dad was
on a freighter near the island.
So why'd you come to see me?
I just wanted to make
sure you were okay.
Yeah. I'm doing pretty good.
Well, I gotta go.
It was good seeing you, John.
Yeah. Take care.
I take it you didn't invite him along.
Boy's been through enough.
That's 0-for-2,
Mr. Locke.
Maybe I misunderstood, but I thought
you had to bring everyone back.
I only need to convince one. And if
I can do that, the rest will come.
And maybe I was mistaken, but
I thought you we my driver.
Hello, Hugo.
So you didn't make it, huh?
Pardon me?
You didn't make it.
It's cool. No biggie.
You're not the first person
to visit me, you know.
But what's up with the wheelchair?
Uh, I broke my leg falling down a hole.
Is that how you died?
Hugo, I'm not dead.
Sure you're not.
No, I-I promise you,
I'm very much alive.
Hey, Susie, am I talking to a
dude in a wheelchair right now?
Yep.
Whoa, dude. What are you doing here?
I need you to come back
to the island with me.
Wait. What?
And not just you
but everybody who left.
- You mean Jack and Kate--
- Everybody.
I'm sorry, dude. I don't
think that's gonna happen.
Jack's a doctor now, and--and Sun's,
like, got her baby, and Kate's got Aaron.
Dude, be cool. Don't look,
but we're being watched.
Dude!
- Oh, don't worry. He's with me.
- What?
He's just driving me around. He's okay.
That dude is far from okay.
When I first got locked up in here, he showed
up, claiming that he worked for Oceanic Air.
He's evil!
You should not be trusting that guy.
- Please, just listen to me.
- No, no, no! I'm not listening to you!
- Hugo, please, listen.
- La, la, la, la, la. I wanna go back in.
- I wanna go back in.
- Hugo.
No, I'm not going anywhere
with you! Go away! Bye!
- Get out of here!
- You're safe.
That's three visits now.
You may wanna step up
your game, Mr. Locke,
or we're all in serious trouble.
What exactly is it that you
do for Mr. Widmore, Matthew?
You're ready to talk about it now, huh?
John...
you're not really gonna
pretend you don't remember
that I was an orderly in the
hospital right after your accident?
That I was the one who told
you to go on your walkabout?
The same walkabout that put you on
the plane that crashed on that island?
No. I remember.
I help people get to where
they need to get to, John.
That's what I do for Mr. Widmore.
The answer is no.
Kate, I don't think you understand--
No, you made yourself perfectly clear.
Everyone on the island is
gonna die if I don't go back.
And the answer is no.
Why? Don't you care about them?
- Have you ever been in love, John?
- What?
I think about you sometimes.
I think about how desperate
you were to stay on that island.
And then I realized...
it was all because you
didn't love anybody.
That's not true.
I loved someone...
once.
Her name was Helen.
What happened?
Well... it--it...
it just didn't work out.
Why not, John?
I was angry. I was...
obs- obsessed.
And look how far you've come.
Let me help you, Mr. Locke.
- Did you find her?
- Find who?
Helen Norwood.
The woman I asked you about.
No, I didn't. I'm sorry.
Three years is a long time.
It's possible she got
married, changed her name.
- Maybe she moved out of state.
- You found everyone else! All of them.
Sayid was in the middle of nowhere,
but you can't find Helen
because she moved?
Your job is to get people
to where they need to get to?
Well, I need to get to her.
What happened to her?
She died of a brain aneurysm.
I'm very sorry, Mr. Locke.
She loved me.
If I had just...
We could've been together.
Maybe you could have.
That wouldn't change anything.
She'd still be gone.
Would she?
Helen is where she's supposed to be.
As sad as it is, her path led here.
And your path, no matter
what you did or what you do,
your path leads back to the island.
You say that like it's
all det--inevitable.
Mr. Widmore told me Richard Alpert
said that you were going to die.
So you tell me, John.
Is that inevitable, or is it a choice?
What, you think I wanna die?
How is that...
how could you possibly
think that's a choice?
I'm just your driver.
Matthew!
What are you doing here?
Jack, how did you find me?
You were in a car accident and
you were brought into my hospital.
What are you doing here?
We have to go back.
Of course. Of course we do.
Jack, the people I
left behind need our help.
- We're supposed to go back--
- ...because it's our destiny.
How many times are you
gonna say that to me, John?
How can you not see it?
Of all the hospitals they could've
brought me to, I end up here.
You don't think that's fate?
Your car accident was on
the west side of Los Angeles.
You being brought into my
hospital isn't fate, John.
It's probability.
You don't understand.
It wasn't an accident.
- Someone is trying to kill me.
- Why? Why would someone try to kill you?
Because they don't want me to succeed.
They wanna stop me.
They don't want me to get
back because I'm important.
Have you ever stopped to
think that these delusions
that you're special aren't real?
That maybe there's nothing
important about you at all?
Maybe you are just a lonely old
man that crashed on an island.
That's it.
Good-bye, John.
Your father says hello.
What?
A man, the man who told
me to move the island,
the man who told me
how to bring you all back,
he said to tell his son hello.
It couldn't have been Sayid's father,
and it wasn't Hurley's.
That leaves you.
He said his name was Christian.
My... my father is dead.
Well, he didn't look dead to me.
He died in Australia three years ago.
I put him in the coffin!
He's dead.
Jack, please, you have to come back!
You're the only one who can
convince the rest of 'em.
You have to help me!
You're supposed to help me!
John, it's over! It's done.
We left, and we were
never important. So you...
you leave me alone.
And you leave the rest of 'em alone!
(Jack, I wish you had believed me.)
John?
John, what are you doing?
Wait, please. John, stop!
How did you find me?
I have a man watching Sayid.
I'm watching all of them,
keeping them safe.
When you turned up, he called me.
Who-- who--?
W-what are you doing here?
- John, just calm down.
- What do you want from me?
- Please, let me help--
- Answer the question!
I'm trying to protect you.
Protect me?
You shot him.
You killed Abaddon.
Yes.
Yes, I did.
But it was only a matter of
time before he'd try to kill you.
I was just trying to get to you,
but you drove off and crashed.
- Why? Why would--?
- He was working for Charles Widmore.
- He's extremely dangerous.
- No!
Widmore came to me. He saved me.
No, John, he used you.
He waited till you showed up so that
you could help him get to the island.
Charles Widmore is the
reason I moved the island!
So that he could never find it again,
to keep him away so that you could lead.
You can't do this.
If anything happens to you...
John, you have no idea
how important you are.
Let me help you.
There is no helping me.
I'm...
- I'm a failure.
- No, John, you're not.
I am!
I couldn't get any of them.
I couldn't get a single one
of them to come back with me.
I can't lead anyone.
Jack booked a ticket.
W-what?
A plane ticket from Los
Angeles to Sydney, tonight.
Return trip first thing in the morning.
Whatever you said to
him, John. It worked.
And if you got Jack,
you gonna get the rest of them.
John...
You can't die.
You've got too much work to do.
We've gotta get you back to that
island so that you can do it.
Please, John.
Come on.
Come down.
I know we can do this, John.
You haven't even been to Sun yet.
- Let's start with her.
- No.
I...
I promised Jin that I
wouldn't bring her back.
- Jin is alive?
- Yeah.
Yeah. But he didn't want her to know.
He--he wanted me to tell her that his...
that his body washed up on the beach.
And, uh, he gave me his
wedding ring to prove it.
All right.
A promise is a promise.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Come on.
Let's go.
I know we can do this.
Once we can get them
all in the same place...
I don't know where we go from there,
but we'll figure something out.
I know where we go.
There's a woman here in Los Angeles.
- A woman?
- Yeah.
I don't know exactly where,
but she shouldn't be that hard to find.
Her name is--is, uh...
Eloise Hawking.
Eloise Hawking? You sure?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, why?
Do you know her?
Yes. John. I know her.
I'll miss you, John.
I really will.
That symbol, it belongs to an
organization called the Dharma Initiative.
They were conducting some
experiments here a while back.
How do you know that?
I spent more than a hundred days
on this island. I know a lot.
A hundred days?
So when we crashed,
you were already here.
No. No, I, uh...
I left.
How long ago did you leave?
The timing would just confuse you.
Well... how did you get back?
To be honest, that part's
a bit of a mystery to me.
Okay, John Locke...
I have a mystery, too.
Maybe you can help me with it.
I'm happy to try.
On the plane, I was sitting across the aisle
from that really big guy with curly hair.
When the plane started
shaking, really shaking...
there was a big noise
and a bright light.
And this really big
guy with curly hair...
...was gone, man.
I mean, literally gone.
And it wasn't only him.
Some of us saw it happen
to other people, too.
So, Mr. John Locke,
do you have an idea about what happened?
I think...
I might know how I came to be here.
But that would involve
me finding my friends.
- Do you have a passenger list?
- No.
The pilot took it when he ran off.
And everyone's accounted for?
All the people,
O-other than the--the
ones who disappeared?
Yeah, yeah, except for
the people who got hurt.
"The people who got hurt"?
You know him?
Yeah.
He's the man who killed me.
subtitle by sfile.ydy.com,
sync: ??????, edited by rogard