Previously on "Lost"
I'm here to tell you
That the island won't
Let you come alone.
All of you have to go back.
Is that what this is about?
This is insane.
You guys are crazy.
- Kate
- Jack, don't!
- Sayid, where are you going?
- I don't want any part of this.
It's Jin!
- How do you know he's alive?!
- There's someone...
Someone here in Los Angeles.
Someone? Who?
The same person that's gonna show us
how to get back to the island.
Help!
Anyone!
Help, Jack!
Help! Anyone!
Help!
It's okay. You're okay.
Relax. Aah! Oh, God!
Oh, God!
Okay.
- Oh, my God!
- We can stand.
- What?
Oh, my God.
It really happened.
Kate.
Kate, can you hear me?
Jack?
Are you okay?
Are we...?
Yeah.
We're back.
What happened?
46 hours earlier
I thought I said all of them.
This is all I could get
on such a short notice.
Guess it'll have to do for now.
All right. Let's get started.
Shall we?
What is this place?
The Dharma Initiative
called it the Lamp Post.
This is how they found the island.
Did you know about this place?
No.
No, I didn't.
Is he telling the truth?
Probably not.
Here we go.
All right.
I apologize if this is confusing, but...
Let's pay attention, yes?
The room we're standing in
was constructed years ago
over a unique pocket of
electromagnetic energy.
That energy connects to similar
pockets all over the world.
The people who built this room, however,
- were only interested in one.
- The island.
Yes. the island.
They'd gathered proof that it existed.
They knew it was out there somewhere,
but they just couldn't find it.
Then a very clever
fellow built this pendulum
on the theoretical notion
that they should stop looking
for where the island was supposed to be
and start looking for
where it was going to be.
What do you mean, "where
it was going to be"?
Well, this fellow
presumed, and correctly,
as it turned out,
that the island was always moving.
Why do you think you were never rescued?
Now while the movements
of the island seem random,
this man and his team
created a series of equations
which tell us, with a
high degree of probability,
Where it is going to be
at a certain point in time.
Windows, as it were, that while
open, provide a route back.
Unfortunately, these windows
don't stay open for very long.
Yours closes in 36 hours.
Um, I'm sorry. excuse me.
Am I really hearing this?
That's what this is about?
You're all going back
to the island willingly?
Yes. Why are you here, Desmond?
I came here to deliver a message.
Daniel Faraday,
your son, sent me here.
He wanted me to tell you
that he and all the people
on the island need your help.
He said that only you could help them.
He didn't say Jack. He didn't
say Sun. He didn't say Ben.
- He said you.
- But I am helping, dear.
Consider the message delivered.
I'm sorry to have to
tell you this, Desmond,
but the island isn't done with you yet.
This woman cost me
four years of my life,
four years that I'll never
get back because you told me
that I was supposed to go to the island!
That it was my bloody purpose!
You listen to me, brother,
and you listen carefully.
These people
- they're just usin' us.
They're playing some kind of game,
and we are just the pieces.
Whatever she tells you to do,
ignore it.
You say the island's not done with me?
Well, I'm done with the island.
Jack...
The binder in your hands
shows all the air routes
that fly over the coordinates
where I believe the island will be
in little more than a day from now.
There's a commercial airliner
flying from L.A. to Guam.
It's going to go right
through your window.
Ajira Airways, flight 316.
If you have any hope of the
island bringing you back,
it must be that plane.
You all need to be on it.
It must be that flight.
If you want to return,
You need to recreate as best you can
the circumstances that brought
you there in the first place
That means as many of the same people
as you are able to bring with you.
And what if we can't get
anyone else to come with us?
What if we're it?
All I can tell you is the
result would be unpredictable.
So that's it?
We just get on that flight,
and we just hope that it works?
That's all?
No, that's not all, Jack...
At least, not for you.
Come on in.
Ben and Sun heard what
they needed to hear,
and this does not concern them.
Oh. here we are.
What's this?
It's John Locke's suicide note.
Uh... I, uh...
I didn't know.
Well, why would you?
Obituaries don't see fit to mention
when people hang themselves, Jack.
Why would he kill himself?
There are many reasons, I'm sure,
But the only one that matters is this:
He is going to help you get back.
John is going to be a proxy.
A substitute.
A substitute for who?
Jack...
Who do you think?
You need to, as best you can,
Recreate the conditions
of the original flight...
Which is why you need to give
John something of your father's.
You have to get something
that belonged to your father,
And you need to give it to John.
What?
That's what you have to do.
My father... is gone.
My father has been dead for three years.
You want me to...
A-and to give it to
Locke?! He's in a coffin!
This is ridiculous.
Oh, stop thinking how ridiculous
it is and start asking yourself
whether or not you
believe it's going to work.
That's why it's called
a leap of faith, Jack.
Where's Sun?
She left.
And Locke?
I mean... his body? The coffin?
I have a friend looking after it.
I'll pick it up on
my way to the airport.
- What did she say to you, Jack?
- Nothing that matters.
Who is she?
Why is she... helping us?
How does she know all this?
Thomas the apostle.
When Jesus wanted to return to Judea,
knowing that he would probably be
murdered there, Thomas said to the others,
"Let us also go, that
we might die with him."
But Thomas was not
remembered for this bravery.
His claim to fame came later...
when he refused to
acknowledge the resurrection.
He just couldn't wrap
his mind around it.
The story goes...
that he needed to touch
Jesus' wounds to be convinced.
So was he?
Of course he was.
We're all convinced
sooner or later, Jack.
Where are you going?
Oh, I made a promise to
an old friend of mine.
Just a loose end that needs tying up.
See you at the airport, Jack.
Hello?
Yeah, this is him.
He did what?
This is the fourth time he's left.
He's gotta follow the rules, or he'll have
to move to our fully assisted facility.
Yeah, I understand.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
here is my fraidy-cat rabbit!
Hey, Ray.
Hey, Jack.
As for my next trick, I
need someone to pick a card.
- Wanna get out of here?
- The sooner the better.
Would you please pick
one? Look at it. Hm-hmm.
You wanna tell me why you
took off this time, Ray?
Do I really need to answer that?
Will you at least tell me
where the bus was headed?
Doesn't matter.
Anywhere I go is
somewhere better than here.
- You packed a bag?
- Of course I did.
One of these times, I'm
actually gonna get away.
They won't ever find me either.
Take off again, they're gonna
throw you outta here, Ray.
But what would I do
without my magic shows?
Let me help you unpack, granddad.
So how are you, kiddo?
You seeing anyone special?
Whatever happened to the girl that
you brought by with you that time?
The pretty one with all the freckles?
What was her name?
Kate.
We're not together anymore.
Well, look at the bright side:
More time to come visit me.
I'd love to, granddad.
I really would, but...
I think I might be... might
be going away for a while.
Where's "away" exactly?
Somewhere better than here.
Are these yours, granddad?
No.
Those were your father's.
Your mom sent me a box of
his stuff after he died.
Must've got mixed in when I
packed for a quick getaway.
These shoes...
can I take them?
Be my guest.
Kate?
What are you doing here?
Are you still going back to the island?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I am.
Then I'm going with you.
Kate...
- What happened? Where's Aaron?
Where--? - No, don't ask questions.
If you want me to go with you, you'll
never ask me that question again.
You will never ask me about Aaron.
Do you understand, Jack?
Yes.
Thank you.
Morning.
Uh, I made you some coffee,
and there's orange juice.
You still like milk and two sugars?
Yeah, sure.
Those don't make much
sense for the island.
You might want to consider hiking boots.
Those were my father's.
When I went to pick up his body in
Sydney, my dad didn't have any nice shoes.
My mother wanted to have the funeral
as soon as I landed back in L.A.
but I thought, who the
hell's gonna see his feet?
And so I
- I had these old white tennis shoes, and I just said, "Use these.  Put these on him."
'Cause he wasn't worth a
nice pair of shoes to me.
Or the time it would take
to go out and get 'em.
So why don't you get rid of 'em?
Why hold on to something
that makes you feel sad?
Go ahead.
I...
I'll see you at the airport, okay?
- Hello?
- Hello, Jack. Are you there?
Yeah. Yeah, what's u,
is everything all right?
Listen, we don't have much time.
I've been, uh... sidetracked,
and I need you to pick up Locke's
body and take it to the airport.
The coffin is at Simon's butcher
shop, corner of Grand and Hayes.
Why? Wh
- what's happened to you?
Just do it. please.
Are you Jill? Ben sent me.
I know who you are, Dr.
Shephard. Come on in.
What's in the bag?
Sorry.
Ben said to give you the van.
I gotta pull it around back.
Give me about five minutes.
Wherever you are, John...
You must be laughing your ass
off that I'm actually doing this.
Because this... This is
even crazier than you are.
And here.
You can have that back.
I've already heard everything
you had to say, John.
You wanted me to go
back. I'm going back.
Rest in peace.
Mr. Shephard, if you'll
just bear with me.
The reason for transporting
Mr. Bentham to Guam?
Uh, it was his--
these were his wishes.
He wanted to be buried there.
Who will be the recipient
of the deceased upon arrival?
Is there a
funeral home or--?
No, it's me. me. I'll
be escorting the body.
And your relation to the deceased?
He was, uh, a friend.
Now, Mr. Shephard,
I have to inform you that
due to the increased security
measures, we are required
to open the casket and
perform a screening.
I assure you
it's all done with care.
Do you understand, Mr. Shephard?
Mr. Shephard?
Yes. Yes, I understand.
Then please sign here.
Thank you for flying Ajira Air.
My condolences.
I'm sorry you lost your friend.
Thank you.
Please remove all jackets,
sweaters, jewelry and footwear.
Remove all laptops and electronic
devices from their cases and place them...
Jack.
Sun. Hey.
You're surprised to see me?
I just...
I thought maybe you
might change your mind.
If there's even a chance that Jin
is alive, I have to be on that plane.
All passengers, please have your tickets
and identification available for security.
Please remove all Jackets, sweaters...
...all laptops and electronic devices
from their cases and place them in a bin.
This is the preliminary boarding
announcement for Ajira Airways flight 316,
with service to Honolulu and
Guam, departing from gate 15.
For those of you on the standby list,
we'll have plenty of seats available.
We would like to invite
our pre-board, first class
and skyclub passengers to
board the aircraft at this time.
What do you mean, "standby"?
There's no standbys.
Oh, no, sir. You don't need to
worry. There are... 78 seats open.
No. I bought those seats, all 78 of 'em.
I'm Hugo Reyes. They're
not open. They're mine.
Check and see.
Yes, I see that.
Sir, these people just want
to get to their destination.
Why would you not want
them to be able to travel?
You know, it doesn't matter why.
They can take the next plane.
Hurley.
What are you doing here?
How did you know about the--?
All that matters is
that I'm here, right?
I'm glad that you're here, man.
Okay, then.
Let's do this.
After you.
Welcome to Ajira Air.
Thank you, sir. Row 8, on your left.
Welcome aboard.
Yes, ma'am. You may. Thank you.
Yes, make sure you put your...
I will.
Absolutely.
You made it.
Yeah.
I made it.
- That should be everybody.
- Hold up! Wait, please!
Thank you for not closing it.
- Oh, that's okay. Go right on in.
- Thanks.
Wait! What's he doing here?!
- Hurley, hey-- -
No, no! He can't come!
If you want to get back, this
is how it's gonna have to be.
No one told me he was gonna be here.
Who told you to be here, Hugo?
Is everything okay?
Yes. Yes, everything's fine.
- Right?
- Yes, Jack. I'll be fine.
Are you Jack Shephard, seat 8c?
Yes.
Security found this while
screening your cargo.
Now if you two don't mind taking your seats,
we are gonna be pushing back for takeoff.
What's that, Jack?
Nothing.
And the other people
on this plane--
What's gonna happen to them?
Who cares?
It's pretty crazy, huh?
Which part?
Hurley, Sayid...
Being... on the same plane.
How did they end up here?
They bought a ticket.
You don't think that it means something?
That somehow...
We're all back together?
We're on the same plane, Jack.
Doesn't make us together.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen,
and welcome to Ajira Air.
This is your captain, Frank J. Lapidus,
and on behalf of the entire
flight crew, welcome aboard.
Currently we're right on schedule,
flying at a very comfortable 30,000 feet.
So sit back, relax and
enjoy the in-flight movie.
- Excuse me, ma'am?
- Mr. Shephard, can I help you?
Um, I need to talk to the pilot.
Frank Lapidus and I are old friends,
and if you could just tell him I'm
onboard, I'd really appreciate it.
All right, but you
just have to go sit down
because you can't be near the
cockpit door when it's open.
Sure.
I understand.
Captain, I have a passenger
named Jack Shephard.
He says he knows you. okay, sir.
Well, hello, doc.
Small world.
What are you doing going to Guam?
What are you doing here, Frank?
Well, I picked this gig
up about eight months ago.
I fly this route all the time.
Sometimes I take the big
birds into New... Delhi.
Is... that Sayid?
And Hurley.
Wait a second.
We're not going to Guam, are we?
How can you read?
My mother taught me.
I can read, Jack, because
it beats what you're doing.
What's that?
Waiting for something to happen.
And what is gonna happen?
You tell me, Jack.
You're the one that got to stay
after school with Ms. Hawking.
Did you know that Locke killed himself?
No. No, I didn't.
They found this stuffed in his pocket.
And I've been trying to get rid of it,
but it's like it's... following me.
I know it sounds crazy, but...
it feels like John needs me to read it.
Why don't you then?
Is it because you're afraid?
Afraid of what?
Afraid that he blames you, that
it's your fault he killed himself.
Was it my fault?
No, Jack, it wasn't your fault.
Let me give you some privacy.
Dude...
You might wanna fasten your seat belt.
Fasten your seat belt, ma'am. Sir?
Please put on your seat
belts. Seat belt, please.
Help!
Anyone!
Kate.
What happened?
- Can you get up?
- Yeah.
The plane...
Where's the plane?
I don't know.
After that light, I...
I woke up in the jungle.
So this is it? It's just us?
I'm not sure.
Do either of you remember crashing?
Crashing? No.
One second, I'm being tossed around.
The next thing I know, I'm in the lagoon.
Where's Sun and Sayid?
Where's Ben?
All right. Let's spread out,
search the jungle.
We come across anybody
from the plane, we'll--
Dude...
Jin?