Previously on Lost...
The Dharma folks at the Swan work site...
They're gonna drill into the ground and
accidentally tap into a massive pocket of energy.
And that will cause your plane...
Oceanic 815... to crash on this island.
And just how exactly do you
plan on destroying this energy?
I'm gonna detonate a hydrogen bomb.
- Morning.
- Mornin'.
- Mind if I join you?
- Please.
Want some fish?
Thank you. I just ate.
I take it you're here 'cause of the ship.
I am.
How did they find the island?
You'll have to ask 'em when they get here.
I don't have to ask.
You brought them here.
Still trying to prove me wrong, aren't you?
- You are wrong.
- Am I?
They come. They fight. They destroy. They corrupt.
It always ends the same.
It only ends once.
Anything that happens before that is just progress.
Do you have any idea how badly I wanna kill you?
Yes.
One of these days, sooner or later...
I'm going to find a loophole, my friend.
When you do, I'll be right here.
Always nice talking to you, Jacob.
Nice talking to you, too.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
Lost
Season 5 Episodes 16 & 17
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition:
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition: a
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition: af
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition: afr
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition: afre
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition: afrei
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition: afreit
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition: afreita
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
subtitle sync: ?????? °?µ??? ????·?
subtitle edition: afreitas
Are you gonna do it?
- You do it.
- Fine. I'll do it.
But you're gonna be lookout, okay?
Okay.
The crops came in pretty good this year.
Hey you hear? Frank bought the old...
Yeah, I hear he's gonna farm the
land all the way out to Ames road.
Yeah, I hear that, too.
There's nothing he would like less.
What you kids got there? Open your bag.
- Where'd you get this?
- Got it over there.
I know you. You're Diane Austen's girl.
- What's your name?
- Katie.
Well, Katie, I'm calling your mom, then the cops,
because I don't tolerate stealing here. You understand?
No need to do that. I'll pay for it.
I hope this is enough.
Well, long as somebody pays for
it, guess there's no harm done.
But I don't wanna see you in here ever again
without your parents. You understand me?
- Thanks, mister.
- You're welcome.
You're not gonna steal anymore, are you?
Be good, Katie.
Welcome aboard, everyone.
We will be doing some system checks offshore here
before heading out into the open ocean and
submerging to our operational running depth.
You should be receiving your sedatives, and
then we will escort you to your sleeping berths.
Have a nice rest. See you on the other side.
We have to get out of here.
"Out of here"? We're underwater.
What the hell are you doing here?
How'd you get caught?
I came back to get you.
- Came back to get me for what?
- Where's Jack?
Jack is on his way to blow up a hydrogen bomb.
- Why the hell would he do that?
- Does it matter?
We have to stop him.
Sorry, I'm gonna pass.
- Did you hear what I just said?
- Yeah, I heard you.
You just don't get it, Kate.
We were happy in Dharmaville till y'all showed up.
But now that's all over.
So we're gonna drink our O.J. and
take our chances in the real world.
Jack wants to blow up the island?
Good for Jack.
Is there anything in there about how we're
supposed to move a 10-ton bomb across the island?
Actually, it's 20 tons.
Fortunately, it seems that Faraday never
intended to freight the device in its entirety.
What?
He left detailed instructions on
how to remove the plutonium core...
And how to detonate it.
Faraday told me that we need to wipe
out some kind of pocket of energy.
Is only part of the bomb
gonna be enough to do that?
The core itself is a
thermonuclear weapon.
It'll be more than enough.
Wait.
We sealed that thing up 20 years ago,
and we put it underground
because it was emitting radiation.
Does this sound like a good idea to you, Eloise?
- Richard...
- You're pregnant.
Which is exactly why we have
to help them see this through.
Once the core is removed, then what?
Then we have approximately two
hours to take it to the Swan site.
Two hours?
When Faraday returned to the island,
he was very explicit about his timetable.
Well then... we'd better get movin'.
Who stopped the damn drill?
I did.
Why?
Because when we passed 70 meters,
the drill temp went up 60 degrees,
and I didn't want it to melt.
Pierre, that's why we have a truck full of water.
So cool it down and turn it on.
Stuart, we've just evacuated the
island of all nonessential personnel.
We're in the midst of a possible insurrection.
Do you really think this is the
ideal time for your experiments?
I've been working on this
project for six years...
designing a station that'll be able to manipulate
electromagnetism in ways we only dreamed of.
Have you thought about the consequences
of drilling into that pocket?
We have no idea what we are going to...
If Edison was only worried about the consequences,
we'd all still be sitting in the dark.
I came to this island to change the world, Pierre.
That's exactly what I intend to to.
Let's get it started!
Take five, everybody. We still got
a ways to go to get to Jacob's.
Who's Jacob?
He's in charge of this island.
- You said John was in charge.
- No, I said he was the leader...
A title that I've discovered
is incredibly temporary.
But everyone answers to someone,
and the leader answers to Jacob.
What's he like?
I don't know, Sun. I've never met him.
You've been staring for the
last ten minutes, Richard.
Is there something you would like to ask me?
Ben told me that... he strangled you.
That is my recollection, yes.
He said he was sure you were dead.
He saw your coffin loaded onto
that plane that you came back on.
How are you alive?
Well, you've been on this island
much longer than I have, Richard.
If anyone should have an explanation,
I'd think it would be you.
Yeah, I-I have been here a long time, John,
and I've seen things on this island
that I can barely describe. But...
I've never seen someone come back to life.
And I've never seen anyone who doesn't age.
It doesn't mean it can't happen.
I'm this way because of Jacob.
And if I had to guess, he's the reason
you're not in that coffin anymore.
I agree completely, Richard. That's
why I'm doing this... so I can thank him.
And once I've done that, we're gonna need
to deal with the rest of the passengers
from the Ajira flight that brought me here.
- What do you mean, "deal with"?
- You know what I mean.
Let's go!
Untie the crates.
Why'd we even bring this yahoo?
- Because we might need him.
- For what?
He didn't know the answer to the question.
That doesn't mean he's not important.
What, you think he's a candidate?
He's awake.
How long you been listening to us?
Long enough to wonder what
the hell I'm a candidate for.
Who the hell are you people?
We're friends.
So you smack all your friends in the face with
a rifle, shove 'em in a boat and kidnap 'em?
Only the ones we like.
Let's go.
What's in the box?
Your call.
Open it.
Terrific.
Need a pen, son?
Yeah. Thanks.
There you go. You can keep it.
I'm very sorry about your mother and father, James.
Come on, Jimmy. We gotta get to the cemetery, okay?
- What you writin'?
- Nothin'.
"Dear Mr. Sawyer,"
"You don't know who I am, but I know
who you are, and I know what you done."
Listen to me, Jimmy.
I know you're angry at the man
that did this to your mama and daddy.
And hell, you got every right to be.
But you gotta move on, boy.
They're gone, and there ain't
nothin' you can do to change that.
What's done is done.
Now promise me you're not gonna finish that letter.
I promise.
Good.
Come on. Let's go say good-bye.
Let me get this straight.
Jack sets off a nuke, which
somehow resets everything.
So Flight 815 never crashes. It just...
lands in L.A. safe and sound,
and none of this never happens.
Sawyer, if Jack does this,
he could kill everyone on the island.
- Yeah, I heard that part.
- And you're okay with that?
You ain't hearing me, Kate.
I made a choice, and I'm sticking to it.
I decided to leave, and I'm leavin'.
All right, here's your sedatives.
What the hell did you just do?
We decided to leave this island, James. We did.
And now we're going back.
- You serious?
- We can't just let those people die.
You want out? You wanna
stay here and whine about it?
Unlock the damn cuffs.
"Galaga" to base. The system check is complete.
We're locked on departure bearing
and ready to leave the island.
Roger that, "Galaga". Have a
safe trip. See you on the return.
Give me your gun.
Appreciate that, captain.
Now we need you to surface the sub.
What? I can't take this sub...
- Oh, I think you can.
- Once we're gone, proceed on course.
Whatever you do, do not take those
people back to the island. Understand?
And what if Horace tries to contact me?
What am I supposed to say?
You ain't home.
Go.
Sayid... is this big enough?
That'll do.
- Are you done with Faraday's journal?
- Take it.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Over, uh, 20 years ago, a man named John Locke...
He walked right into our camp, and he
told me that he was gonna be our leader.
Now I've gone off the island three
times since then to visit him.
But he never seemed, uh,
particularly special to me.
You said you had a question.
You know him? Locke?
Yeah. Yeah, I know him.
And if I were you, I wouldn't give up on him.
Why haven't you told him yet?
- Told who what?
- Richard.
Why haven't you told him about my plans for Jacob?
If by "plans" you mean murdering him, John,
I assume you'd want to keep that a secret.
When did that ever stop you?
Well, I started thinking differently about things
when my dead daughter threatened to destroy me
if I didn't do everything you said.
W-wait. Wait.
Where did this happen?
In that cavern beneath the temple,
when we went to see the monster.
So... you're willing to do
whatever I say no matter what it is?
Yes.
Well then... I guess I won't
have to convince you after all.
Convince me to do what?
I'm not gonna kill Jacob, Ben.
You are.
- Paris or Rome?
- No.
- Florence?
- It doesn't matter, Sayid...
- Yes, it does.
- As long as we're together.
It's our anniversary.
We have to find the perfect place.
I would settle for finding my sunglasses.
Excuse me, sir? Could you you help me?
I'm sorry. I think I'm lost.
Are you from Los Angeles?
- What are you looking for?
- I found them.
Nadia?
Nadia? Nadia?
Time is short. Let's go.
Mm, stand back.
It's one of the Dharma houses.
I'll go first.
Jack, don't misunderstand who's
in charge here. I'll go first.
Because if someone at that house is a
threat, you might hesitate... but I won't.
All right. Okay, Eloise, go on. After you.
Once we give you the "all clear",
then you bring the bomb.
We don't want any acci... Oh!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm protecting our leader. Get back.
She's gonna be angry when she wakes up,
but that's a lot better than being dead.
She ordered me to help you.
We helped you. Now you're on your own.
And I'm taking her out the way we came in.
After you.
All residents, we are in a code black.
Report with your weapons to your
security assignments immediately.
If you come into contact with a hostile,
you are authorized to use deadly force.
How the hell are we gonna get out of here?
We hide in plain sight.
Set up a perimeter around the barracks first.
You go over there by the gate. You get two...
So you guys go. You go to pylons.
We're gathering over there.
You're the son of a bitch who shot my kid.
Don't fire that weapon!
I'm carrying a nuclear device.
It's the hostile!
Get in!
Drive!
From the looks of the sun, I'd say
that's the north shore over there.
Sun's over there. That's gotta be the west coast.
Really? What, you got a compass?
No. Do you?
- Thank you.
- For what?
For backing me up at the sub.
No problem.
I got no idea where the hell we are.
Vincent! Come here!
How you doing, boy?
I haven't seen you since the
flaming arrows three years ago.
- How you doing?
- How did he survive alone out here?
Oh, hell, no.
Bernard!
They found us.
Son of a bitch.
Is that a bomb?
Try not to move. I need to stop the bleeding.
What's going on back there? Is Sayid okay?
Does he look okay?
Just keep your eyes on the damn road!
Should I pull over?
Yeah, let's pull over and get shot! Just drive!
- I don't know where we're going.
- The Swan site. Head to the Swan.
Why do you want to go there?
If Sayid's shot, shouldn't we...
Hurley, if you want to save
Sayid, take us to the Swan.
- The Swan it is.
- Jack, what's at the Swan?
I think I found a way to
get you back to your wife.
So hold on.
You're telling me you've just been living out here
in the jungle for the past three years, by yourselves?
I'm sorry y'all got left behind.
Didn't you hear me shout out, "meet at the creek"?
You mean with flaming arrows raining down
around us, killing everyone we knew?
Oh, sure, we heard ya.
We spent all sorts of time looking for ya.
I had Jin out searching the island grid by grid.
Yeah, we know.
You know?
Oh, sure, you guys all joined
up with the Dharma Initiative.
Well, damn, I could've brought both y'all in.
Why didn't you find a way
to tell us you were out here?
Because we're retired.
So y'all been scavenging food and
living out in a hut by yourselves.
People try their whole lives
to get themselves a nice,
quiet place near the ocean
where they can live in peace.
And we did it.
That's what we made for ourselves.
Well, I hate to rain on your parade, but...
Your condo's about to go kablooie.
Jack has a bomb.
Who cares?
Excuse me?
It's always something with you people.
Now you say Jack's got a bomb.
And what, you guys are all
gonna try to stop him, right?
Yeah, that's right.
We traveled back 30 years in time, and you're
still trying to find ways to shoot each other?
Rose, we just need to know which way
the Dharma barracks are from here
so we can stop Jack, or you're gonna be dead.
We all will.
So we die.
We just care about being together.
That's all that matters in the end.
The barracks are 5 miles that way.
- Bernard.
- Sawyer.
Rose.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Bye.
You sure don't want some tea?
Maybe another time.
I wish you'd never showed
me what was in this damn box.
What the hell you gonna do with it anyway?
We need to show it to somebody.
What for?
So they'll know who they're up against.
What exactly are they up against?
Something a hell of a lot scarier
than what's in this box, Frank.
Don't worry, though.
As long as you're with us, you're fine.
That would be reassuring if I
knew who you were, "friend".
We are the good guys.
In my experience, the people who go out of their way
to tell you that they're the good guys are the bad guys.
We're here.
Look at the ash!
Wait here.
I'm here because I need your help.
Can you do that?
Will you help me, Ilana?
Yes.
What happened?
He isn't there, hasn't been in a long time.
Someone else has been using it.
Burn it!
I'm no tree hugger or anything, but that's a pretty
good way to torch the whole jungle, don't you think?
So what now?
I guess we know where we're going.
Oh, my God!
Call 911!
Is he all right?
I don't know!
Don't worry. Everything's gonna be all right.
I'm sorry this happened to you.
This is our old camp.
Home sweet home.
All right, everyone, Richard tells me we
should get to where we're going by nightfall.
So why don't you all take this opportunity
to rest up and catch your breath?
Considering what I have planned
for ya, you're gonna need it.
Everything all right?
I was enjoying some alone time.
You see what's behind you?
It's a door.
- How about that?
- It's not just a door, Ben.
It's the door to the hatch
where you and I first met.
- You mind if I ask you a question?
- I'm a Pisces.
What happened that day at the cabin,
when you first took me to meet Jacob?
You clearly already know that I was
talking to an empty chair, John...
That I was pretending.
Which is not to say that I
wasn't as surprised as you were
when things started flying around in the room.
But why would you go to all the
trouble to make something like that up?
I was embarrassed.
I didn't want you to know
that I had never seen Jacob.
So, yes, I lied.
That's what I do.
All right, then.
Why do you want me to kill Jacob, John?
Because...
Despite your loyal service to
this island, you got cancer...
You had to watch your own daughter
gunned down right in front of you.
And your reward for those sacrifices?
You were banished.
And you did all this in the name
of a man you'd never even met.
So the question is, Ben, why the
hell wouldn't you wanna kill Jacob?
How much further?
Uh, we're about five minutes away.
You can't stop the bleeding.
I need fresh dressings.
Jack, so this bomb is supposed
to what, blow us back in time?
We're not going back in time.
Right, because that would be ridiculous.
I need to modify the bomb.
I can rig it so it detonates on impact.
Jack, we need to be there at
the moment of the incident.
Or all of this will be for nothing.
Why the hell are we stopping?
That's why.
What is it?
Why are we stopping?
You'll see.
Well, it's a wonderful foot, Richard,
but what does it have to do with Jacob?
It's where he lives.
- What's going on, Kate?
- Doc, we gotta talk.
You wanna talk? Then get in the van.
- We don't have time...
- I ain't gettin' in the van.
I need five minutes, that's all.
I'll say what I gotta say, and then you
can do whatever the hell you want to.
But you're gonna listen.
You owe me that much, Jack.
Five minutes.
Dr. Shephard? You're all right?
The dural sac... I cut it.
- Give me some suction.
- Calm down. It's alright.
The fluid's leaking everywhere. I can't...
- Look at me.
- Give me some suction.
- Yes, doctor.
- Jack...
Look at me.
Count to five.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about you stitching up the sac so
this girl isn't paralyzed for the rest of her life.
And the only way you're gonna
do that is not to be afraid.
So close your eyes, count to
five, and then fix her, Jack.
Or I'll have to fix her for you.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five.
Sutures.
Hey, kiddo.
Girl's in recovery.
She's responsive to stimulus below the waist, so...
No paralysis.
Good.
Something wrong, Jack?
You embarrassed me.
Did I?
You know, it's bad enough that everybody in this
hospital thinks the only reason I got this residency
is because you're my father.
But then you...
You put me in a time-out during my first
major procedure, in front of my entire team.
Dad, I know you don't believe
in me, but I need them to.
Are you sure I'm the one who
doesn't believe in you, Jack?
One of these yours?
Machine got stuck.
I guess it just needed a little push.
Take a load off, doc.
No, thanks.
Sit down, Jack.
My folks died when I was 8 years old.
I ever tell you that?
No.
Con man took my dad for everything he had.
He didn't handle it too well, so...
He shot my mom, then he blew his own head off.
I was hiding under the bed when it happened.
I heard the whole thing.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
That was a year ago.
What?
Right now it's July 1977, which
means that happened last year.
So I could've hopped on the
sub, gone back to the States,
walked right in my house and stopped
my daddy from killing anybody.
Why didn't you?
Because, Jack...
What's done is done.
It doesn't have to be that way.
What did you screw up so bad the first time around you're
willing to blow up a damn nuke just for a second chance?
- That's not what this is about.
- Then what is it about?
Three years ago, Locke told me that all this was
happening for a reason, that us being here was our destiny.
I don't speak "destiny".
What I do understand is a man does what he
does 'cause he wants something for himself.
What do you want, Jack?
I had her.
I had her, and I lost her.
Kate?
Well, damn, doc, she's standing right
on the other side of those trees.
You want her back, just go and ask her.
Nah, it's too late for that.
Your five minutes is up.
Jack...
If what you're doin' even works, you and Kate
will be strangers, and she'll be in damn handcuffs.
If it's meant to be, it's meant to be.
Well, I guess there's nothing I can
say that's gonna change your mind.
No, I guess there's not.
Who the hell do you think you are?
You think you can come here and
do whatever the hell you want?
I had a life here!
Sawyer, listen...
You don't get it.
Will you stop?
No.
James!
Let him go.
He wouldn't listen.
I had to. He won't stop!
That's because he's right.
What?
He's right, James. We have to do this.
What are you talking about?
You're the one that told me
to come back here and stop him!
What happened?
I changed my mind.
Girls...
Your dad and I have something we
need to talk to you both about.
Are we moving again?
No, stupid. They're getting a divorce.
- Rachel...
- Well, aren't you?
- Yes.
- But...
We need you both to understand
that your father and I...
We still love each other.
Just because two people love each other, doesn't
always mean they're supposed to be together.
But what if you are supposed to be together?
We're not, honey.
- But how can you know for sure?
- We just know.
And when you're a grown-up, you'll understand.
I don't wanna understand!
Juliet, wait!
Stop! We gotta talk about this!
There's nothing to talk about, James.
We have to let Jack do what he came here to do.
Well, maybe you shoulda told
me you had a change of heart
before I brought him out in
the jungle to kick his ass.
- Would that have stopped you?
- No.
Well, then I'm glad you finally
got it out of your system.
Don't.
I need you to tell me where
all this is coming from.
I mean, one minute, you're
leading the great sub escape,
and now you're on board with
blowing up the damn island?
I got a right to know why
you changed your mind.
I changed my mind when I saw you look at her.
Don't.
I don't care who I looked at.
I'm with you.
And you would stay with me forever if I let
you, and that is why I will always love you.
- You don't...
- What we had, it was just for a little while.
And just because we love each other,
it doesn't mean that we're meant to be together.
I mean, maybe we were never
supposed to be together.
So if Jack can make it that... that none
of you ever come here, then he should.
Why you doing this, Juliet?
I...
If I never meet you, then I never have to lose you.
Radzinsky!
What is it now?
The gauss readings has jumped off the charts.
Let me see.
This is it!
We're on top of the pocket!
If we keep drilling and hit that
pocket, all hell is gonna break loose!
Radzinsky, are you there? Over.
Stuart, come in!
What do you want, Phil?
That hostile that shot the kid? He came back.
What the hell are you talking about?
Here at the barracks.
He... he attacked us and then got
rescued by some of the other recruits.
They stole a van and took off.
Took off where?
I don't know, but Roger said
that one of them had a bomb.
That hostile knows about the Swan!
Get some men and some guns, and
get your asses out here right now!
If they're coming here,
we're gonna be ready for 'em.
Come on! Keep it on the ground!
Jack?
What happened?
Yeah, my talk with Sawyer didn't go so good.
- Does it hurt?
- Ah, it's okay.
Okay.
Do you remember when I sewed you up?
When we first got here?
Yeah.
Seems like a million years ago.
Or 30 years from now.
Kate, why'd you make me
promise to never ask about Aaron?
Because I was...
so angry with you for making me come back here.
Is he why you came back?
I came back so he could be where
he belongs... with his mother.
If this works, Claire will
never come to the island,
and they'll always be together,
just the way they're meant to be.
- She was gonna give him up for adoption, Jack.
- Well, you don't know what she would do.
And whatever it is, it would be her choice.
If you wanna save Claire,
this is the only way to do it.
Nothing... nothing in my
life has ever felt so right.
And...
I just need you to believe that.
Go!
Keep going!
Keep the drill going!
It's about to happen.
Are you with me on this?
- Yes.
- Then let's go.
One wallet.
$227 cash.
One ballpoint pen.
One fruit roll-up.
Sign here.
You don't understand. This is a big mistake.
I killed a bunch of people.
You see this? This is a discharge form.
You've been cleared.
So take your stuff and go.
Look, dude...
There are men with tranquilizer
guns hunting me down like an animal.
They wanna bring me somewhere against my will.
There's a cab stand right out front.
Sorry. I didn't see it was taken, dude.
Actually, I'm only going a
few blocks if you wanna share.
Cool. Are you sure?
Come on in.
You want some? It's cherry.
No thanks.
So what were you in for?
- Excuse me?
- Jail.
I was there 'cause I killed three people.
But I didn't really. I guess they figured it out.
What about you?
I wasn't in jail.
Well, then what were you
doing sitting outside a prison?
In a cab?
I was waitin' for you, Hugo.
Then you must be dead.
I'm definitely not dead.
What do you want from me?
I wanna know why you won't go back to the island.
'Cause I'm cursed.
Is that so?
That's why the plane crashed,
my friends died... Libby, Charlie.
Now they visit me, and I can't make it stop.
What if you weren't cursed?
What if you were blessed?
How do you mean "blessed"?
Well, you get to talk to the people you've lost...
seems like a pretty wonderful thing to me.
Oh, sure it's wonderful, except
for the part where I'm crazy.
I've got some news for you, Hugo, and
you're just gonna have to take my word on this.
You are not crazy.
Who are you, dude?
I'm just up here on the corner.
Ajira Airways flight 316 out
of L.A.X. leaves in 24 hours.
All you have to do is be on that plane.
It's your choice, Hugo.
You don't have to do anything you don't want to.
Wait! You forgot your guitar.
It's not my guitar.
Don't worry, dude.
Everything'll be fine when Jack changes the future...
Or the past.
One of those.
I don't think your buddy's gonna make it.
He'll make it.
Dude, what happened to your face?
Nothin'.
We were just up on a ridge where
we could look down into the Swan site.
Something just happened down there.
They hit something.
It's time for me to go.
It's all set to go.
Remember, be careful.
It's rigged to explode on impact.
According to Faraday's plan, you must get the bomb
as close as you can to the source of electromagnetism.
Sayid, this is gonna work.
And it'll save ya.
Nothing can save me.
See ya in Los Angeles.
Are you sure you need to do this?
If you waited, Jacob would
eventually come to you, John.
I'm tired of waiting.
Where is he, Richard?
What happened to the rest of the statue?
I don't know. It was like that when I got here.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Not really.
All right, Ben, let's go.
W-what are you doing?
John wants me to join him.
- You can't bring him in.
- Why not?
Because only our leader can
request an audience with Jacob,
and there can only be one leader
on the island at a time, John.
I'm beginning to think you just make
these rules up as you go along, Richard.
Ben is coming in with me, and if that's a
problem, I'm sure Jacob and I can work it out.
Tell him I said hello.
Will you be able to do this, Ben?
I know it won't be easy, but things will change...
once he's gone.
I promise.
Can I ask you something, LaFleur?
There ain't no more LaFleur, Enos. Go ahead, shoot.
Has it occurred to any of you that
your buddy's actually gonna cause
the thing he says he's trying to prevent?
Perhaps that little nuke is the incident?
So maybe the best thing to do... is nothing?
I'm glad you all thought this through.
What's going on?
It's Phil. That's the road to the Swan.
If they see Jack, they're gonna kill him.
What do you think, blondie?
Live together and die alone.
Good for you. You got here fast.
- Any sign of 'em yet?
- No, not yet. You got time to set up a perimeter.
You called these men to the site?
You, rear ridgeline.
- You, top ridgeline.
- We need to be getting people away from here!
You, top of the scaffolding. Go now!
There!
Get him!
Flank him! Get him now!
Who's this?
Drop it, Phil, or you're a dead man!
Tell 'em to put their guns down.
Drop the guns! Drop the guns!
All right, you can come out now, doc!
Hurry up and do your business.
Turn that damn thing off!
What's the matter?
It won't shut down!
Why not?
Something's pulling the drill down.
We hit the pocket!
Hurry up, doc! What are you waiting for?
Drop it!
This don't look like L.A.X.
Dad!
Jack!
Get away from here!
Get as far away from here as you can!
- Get in!
- What the hell's going on?
Get out of here!
Come on!
Go!
Hey, LaFleur!
- Help!
- Juliet!
- Ah, come on!
- Sawyer! Help!
Juliet!
Sawyer!
Where do you think you're going, blondie?
Kate! Help me get those chains off!
Hold on! You hold on!
I can't. I can't get it off.
I got you.
I can't...
- I can't reach her.
- You hold on!
I got you.
Sawyer!
Don't you leave me.
- It's okay.
- Don't you leave me!
- I love you.
- No, you don't let go!
- I love you, James.
- No.
I love you so much.
No! No, don't let go!
Juliet! No!
Water?
Do you have any alcohol?
No. Sure wish I did.
Don't shoot.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Which one of you is Ricardus?
It's Richard, actually.
What lies in the shadow of the statue?
Ille qui nos omnes servabit.
Richard... I'm Ilana.
I have something you need to see.
Open it up.
It's... it's okay. It's okay. Let them.
Where did you find him?
In the cargo hold of the plane we came here on...
In a coffin.
I don't understand.
If this is Locke...
who's in there?
You like it?
I did it myself.
It takes a very long time when
you're making the thread, but, uh...
I suppose that's the point, isn't it?
Hello, Jacob.
You found your loophole.
Indeed I did.
And you have no idea
what I've gone through to be here.
Have you met before?
In a manner of speaking.
Do what I asked you to, Ben.
Benjamin...
Whatever he's told you, I want
you to understand one thing.
You have a choice.
What "choice"?
You can do what he asked,
or you can go, leave us to discuss our...
issues.
So now, after all this time,
you've decided to stop ignoring me.
35 years I lived on this island, and all
I ever heard was your name over and over.
Richard would bring me your instructions...
all those slips of paper, all those lists...
And I never questioned anything.
I did as I was told.
But when I dared to ask to see you
myself, I was told: "You have to wait".
"You have to be patient".
But when he asked to see you?
He gets marched straight
up here as if he was Moses.
So... why him?
What was it that was so wrong with me?
What about me?
What about you?
Well...
They're coming.
What?
I can't hear you.
They're coming.
Sawyer, get off of there!
We have to go right now. We need to go!
Get off.
It's going down! This thing is
gonna go! You have to let it go.
You have to go. This thing is
going to blow at any second.
Jack!
Jack, help me get him off.
Come on!
Come on, you son of a bitch!