Previously on "Lost"...
Now talk.
Think of the island
like a record spinning on a turntable,
only now,
that record is skipping.
Whatever Ben Linus did
down at the Orchid Station,
It may have... dislodged us.
Dislodged us from what?
Time.
- Come on!
- Aah!
- What's goin' on?
- It's not stopping!
Charlotte!
We have to go back to the Orchid.
That's where all this started.
Maybe it's where it'll all stop.
This is all happening because they left.
I think it'll stop
if I can bring them back.
Bring who back?
Jack, Sun, Sayid, Hugo, Kate.
Don't you want her to come back?
You sure you don't
want us to lower you down?
Where would be the fun in that?
Uh-oh.
John! Damn it, hold on!
Aah!
I think you can let go of that now.
No.
No! No! No! No! No!
James, don't.
Come on! Help me!
James...
Stop.
We can't help him.
Wherever John went, he's gone.
And wherever we are is before
that well was ever built.
Yeah, I'd say way before.
What makes you--?
James!
Can you hear me?!
Can anyone hear me?!
What the hell was that?
That one was different. It was...
That was more like an earthquake.
- Locke!
- James, wait!
Great.
My headache is gone.
Yeah, mine is, too.
And my nose isn't bleeding anymore.
I think it's over.
I think John did it.
Now what?
Now we wait for him to come back.
For how long?
As long as it takes.
Are you kidding me?
I'm gone ten minutes,
and you're having a hootenanny?
Don't be such a bummer, man.
Rosie was just dropping off some brownies.
- You should thank her.
- Yeah.
She shouldn't be here, Jerry.
We're on the clock, man.
Ah, mellow out, Phil.
W... what's gonna happen, huh?
The polar bears are gonna figure
a way out of their cages?
That's not the point.
If Lafleur finds out what you're doing--
- Lafleur's not gonna find out anything.
- It's gonna be my ass, man.
- I'm the one who's gonna have to answer to him.
- Guys?
- Relax, man. Nobody's gonna find out.
- Guys. What...
No.
Is that a hostile?
I don't know.
"Overload"
Is that...
...Horace?
Oh, he's got dynamite.
Get her out of here!
Get her out of here now! Now!
Come on, Rosie.
We gotta get you out of here.
- I told you not to bring her here. I told you!
- Go. go!
Ok. This is bad.
This is bad, man.
We gotta get LaFleur.
3:00 in the morning.
Do you really wanna wake LaFleur up?
- No, of course not, but--
- No.
Maybe we can handle this ourselves, huh?
And maybe Horace blows himself up and
LaFleur kills us for not waking him.
We gotta go now!
Do you wanna knock?
You knock.
Fine.
What?
Mr. LaFleur, sorry to bother you,
but we got a situation
out at the pylons.
What kind of situation?
Uh, it's, uh, Horace.
He's got dynamite,
and he's blowing up trees.
Son of a bitch.
a ydy.com subtitle
edited and synced by rogard
Relax! I'm comin'!
Hey, boss.
Evening, Enos.
You got your zapper with ya?
Yep. You wanna tell me why I need it?
'Cause our fearless leader is out
blowing up trees.
Why's he doing that?
'Cause he's loaded.
Since when does Horace drink?
He doesn't, so we're gonna keep
this on the down low.
Oh, man.
All right. You put out that fire.
Pack up this dynamite.
I'll take him home.
Why don't you put out
the fire, pack up and...
and I'll take him home?
You wanna tell Amy where we found him?
Help me get him up.
Oh, my God. Is he okay?
You tell me.
Bring him inside.
The couch.
The couch is fine.
Oh. Where'd you find him?
By the flame, blowing up
trees with dynamite.
Wanna tell me why?
We had a fight.
Must've been a doozy.
Please, Jim.
- It's personal.
- Personal?
You think this isn't gonna get out?
It'll be on the coconut telegraph
by breakfast.
It was about Paul.
Go on.
Oh...
What's the matter? You okay?
The baby... it's coming.
Oh, hell.
No, no no.
I'm not... gonna tell her.
I don't wanna do it, I don't
wanna tell her. I won't.
- Where's Red?
- I don't know.
No. I won't do it.
I won't tell her.
- I won't do it. Won't...
- Daniel?
You okay?
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not gonna tell her.
Daniel, where's Charlotte?
She's not here.
She...
She's gone.
Where?
She's... dead.
She's dead.
There was another flash, and...
And she was... She was just gone.
Her... body just...
...disappeared.
She moved on, and we stayed.
I'm so sorry.
Hold on. Wait a minute.
We "stayed"?
We're not traveling through time anymore?
You saying it's over?
Of course it's over.
Wherever we are now,
whenever we are now...
we're here for good.
- I won't do it.
- Okay. Okay.
- I won't. I'm not gonna... I'm...
- Okay.
I'm not gonna...I won't...
Okay. Swell.
Until Dan checks back in,
I say we head back to the beach.
When Locke gets back with everybody,
that's where they'll be looking for us.
The beach?
What, you didn't get enough
flaming arrows shot at you?
And your camp is gone.
Why bother?
Sawyer's right, Miles.
We should go back to the beach.
We survived there before.
We can do it again.
Or maybe when we get there,
you'll... you'll wanna go
back to the Orchid again.
And then when that gets boring,
we can head back to the beach.
It's the only two plans you people have.
Hey, zip it. I'm heading back to the beach.
If our stuff's there, great.
If not, we build new stuff.
You don't like the plan, good luck.
Who put him in charge?
Thanks for getting my back
with that whole beach issue.
You should thank me.
It was a stupid idea.
Well, what does that say
about you agreeing with me?
Any plan is better than no plan.
Besides, if I hadn't agreed with you,
we'd still be arguing about where to go next.
I just hope you figure out
something better before we get there.
Well, I'm open to suggestions.
Help! Help!
Help...
Oh, no! No, Paul!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
No, no, no, no!
No, please! We didn't know!
Paul, please,
please do something. No, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
We were just touring this park.
We didn't mean anything.
We were just having... Paul.
Paul, please.
Oh, my God! No!
No, Paul, please. Please.
Who do you think they are?
Who cares who they are?
We don't even know when they are.
Hey.
Dan.
We don't get involved, right?
That's what you said.
It doesn't matter what we do.
Whatever happened, happened.
Yeah, thanks anyway, Plato.
I'm going over there.
You still got my back?
Absolutely.
Paul, Paul. Talk to me!
Talk to me, Paul!
On your feet!
- No, I can't! I can't!
- Come on, get up! Now!
- Aah!
- Up!
All right, drop the gun!
Oh, God...
It's all right.
It's okay. You're safe.
It's over.
Who are you?
Her friend's wearing a Dharma jumpsuit.
That put us '70s, '80s.
The guys with the bags... Others?
Beats me.
What, y'all don't know each other?
Before my time.
Sawyer.
Walkie.
We need to go.
I'm on it.
Listen, sweetheart, we gotta get moving now.
Who are you people?
Our ship wrecked here
on the way to Tahiti,
But that ain't important right now,
'Cause whoever's on the other end of this...
those two might've given 'em
a call before we saved you.
We have to bury them.
Bury them? We ain't got
time to bury nobody.
We have to. The truce.
Oh, God.
We have to bury them.
And... and we have...
we have...
And we have to bring it--
him back home.
We have to bring Paul back with us.
Please.
Please?
I'll carry him.
All right, we'll put these
guys in the ground
and carry your friend back,
but we better do it fast.
He wasn't... my friend.
He was my husband.
All right, listen up.
When we get there,
there's gonna be a lot of questions.
So just keep your mouth shut.
Let me do the talking.
You really think you can convince
them that we were in a boat wreck?
I'm a professional.
I used to lie for a living.
Daniel! Stop!
Turn it off.
Turn what off?
Whatever that is.
It looks like some sort of
sonic fence or something.
Where did you say your ship was going?
Listen, sister, we're the ones
who just saved your life
and hid those bodies.
So how about you trust us and
turn that damn thing off?
Okay.
Okay, fine.
A "sonic fence"? Didn't I say
let me do the talking?
One more step,
Dan would've fried his brain.
His brain's already fried.
Okay, it's off.
You first.
See? It's fine.
All right, let's go.
And going forward, we should all do
a better job of trustin'--Uh!
It hurts! Oh!
You're gonna be okay, Amy.
Just try and relax.
Where's Horace?
Does he know his wife's in labor?
He's unavailable.
Look, Amy's in a very dangerous
situation. The baby's breeched.
What the hell does that mean?
It's upside down. She needs a Caesarean.
Well, don't tell me about it. Just do it.
I'm an internist, not an obstetrician.
Our women always deliver on the mainland.
Amy was supposed to get on the sub on Tuesday.
The baby's two weeks early.
Can you deliver this baby or not?
I don't know.
Hey, man. Where is she?
What's up?
Amy's having her baby.
What?
Did you hear me?
She's in trouble.
Doc says she needs a Caesarean.
- We had an agreement.
- Screw our agreement.
He ain't never done one.
I'm guessing you have.
Don't you understand that every time
I try to help a woman on this island give birth,
It hasn't worked?
Well, maybe whatever made that
happen hasn't happened yet.
You gotta try. You gotta help her.
You're the only one that can.
- The baby's breeched.
- Yes, but...
Did you try an external cephalic version?
- What? No.
- I... It's probably too late.
I'm gonna need a number 12 scalpel,
14-gauge sutures...
half-round if you've got them...
and an epidural anesthetic.
You're gonna need? Where is Horace?
I'm speaking for Horace now,
and I say she's delivering this baby.
I don't think it's a good idea.
I want her. I want her to do it.
You heard the lady.
Listen... You're gonna do great.
I know you are.
Okay.
Okay. Shhh...
Is everything okay?
Amy went into labor.
I know.
Is she okay?
I don't know. There's a problem.
- Juliet's in there.
- Juliet?
I pulled her out of retirement.
Any luck?
We finished grid 1-3-3 today.
No sign of our people.
No one.
Well, 1-3-4 then.
How long do we look, James?
As long as it takes.
What happened?
It's a boy.
He's okay? She's okay?
Everyone's okay.
How's your head?
It hurts.
- Where are my people?
- They're fine.
Amy told me what happened in the jungle,
and I really appreciate what you did.
Well, y'all got a funny way
of showing your appreciation.
Look, we have a certain defense protocol.
There are hostile indigenous
people on this island,
and we don't get along with them.
So... why don't you tell me
who the hell you are?
My name's James LaFleur.
You can call me Jim.
How did you get to the island, Jim?
If my friends are safe, why are you
asking me all the questions?
They told me I need to talk to you,
that you're the boat captain.
We got caught in a storm.
Our ship wrecked.
Must've hit the reef.
Thankfully, we washed up on shore.
What kind of ship?
A salvage vessel.
We were searching for
a famous lost wreck.
It's an old slaver
out of Portsmouth, England,
called "the Black Rock."
You heard of her?
Can't say that I have.
So... once you got washed ashore,
why were you then wandering
around in the jungle?
Some of our crew were missing.
We were looking for them.
That's when we came
upon your girl instead.
Hmm.
Well... I tell you what, Jim.
If your crew shows up,
we'll send them along with you.
Send them where?
There's a submarine
that leaves this island
first thing in the morning.
You and your friends,
you're gonna get on it.
It's gonna drop you off in Tahiti.
You can find your way home from there.
Hold on a minute, Chief.
We just saved that woman's life.
Doesn't that earn us a week or two
to find the rest of our people?
Nope.
The only people that are allowed
to stay on this compound
are members of the Dharma Initiative.
And look, I don't want you to take this
the wrong way, please, Jim,
but you are not Dharma material.
We're screwed.
He's probably trying to
explain time travel by now.
Sawyer's gonna be fine.
What are you lookin' at?
I lived here for over three years.
That was my house over there.
You were in the Dharma Initiative?
No.
The Others took over these barracks
and wiped out most of the
people living in them.
They brought me here on a sub
a long time after that.
Well... Welcome home.
Daniel... No more flash?
No.
No more flash.
The record is spinning again.
We're just not on the song
we wanna be on.
- Where's dad?
- Come on, Luv.
Charlotte.
Hello.
Somebody will be along shortly
to show you to your rooms.
In the meantime,
Mr. LaFleur here can
fill you in on the situation.
"Mr. LaFleur"?
It's creole. I improvised.
What happened in there?
Well, he believed my story.
But we're getting punted.
The bastard's putting us on their sub tomorrow
and shipping us off to Tahiti.
How's that bad news?
You guys, come on! Now!
Let's go! Get in!
Get in! Move!
Let's go! Get out of here!
Come on! Come on!
Come on! Inside! Move! Now!
Heather, keep an eye on them.
Uh-oh.
Hello, Mr. Alpert.
Hello, Mr. Goodspeed.
I wish you would've told me
you were coming.
I would've turned the fence off for you.
That fence may keep other things out,
but not us.
Now, the only thing that
does keep us out, Horace,
Is our truce...
which yove now broken.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Where are my two men?
You know what?
Getting on that sub is starting
to sound like a great idea.
What do you say? Sub anyone?
Hold your horses, bonsai.
No one's getting on a sub.
Okay, LaFleur, how well did you
bury those bodies?
Well, that depends on how hard he looks.
Call the arrow. Tell them we're at condition one.
Take the heavy ordnance,
and make sure the fence is at maximum.
Yes, sir.
- Let me talk to him. - Excuse me?
Your buddy out there with the eyeliner,
Let me talk to him.
We had a truce with these people.
You don't understand.
I understand I'm the one that
killed his men, and I'm the one
that's gonna go out there
and tell him why I did it.
I can't let you do that.
Well, it's a good thing I ain't
asking your permission.
James, are you sure you know
what you're doing?
Not yet. But I'll figure something out.
Hello, Richard.
I'm sorry. Do we know each other?
I'm the guy that killed your men.
Heard some gunshots,
saw two men throwing a bag
over a woman's head.
Gave them a chance to throw
the weapons down and walk away,
but one of them took a shot at me,
and I defended myself.
Is that so?
That's so.
Your people know that you're telling me this?
They ain't my people, Hoss.
So if you got some
kind of a truce with them,
it ain't been broken.
If you're not a member
of the Dharma Initiative,
then what are you?
Did you bury the bomb?
Excuse me?
The hydrogen bomb with
"Jughead" written on the side.
Did you bury it?
Yeah, I know about it.
I also know that 20 years ago,
some bald fella limped into your camp
and fed you some mumbo jumbo
about being your leader.
and then poof...
He went and disappeared right in front of ya.
Any of this ringin' a bell?
That man's name is John Locke,
and I'm waitin' for him to come back.
So...
you still think I'm a member
of the damn Dharma Initiative?
No.
I guess I don't.
But no matter who you are,
two of my men are dead,
and my people need
some kind of justice.
What are we gonna do about that?
How are you doing, Amy?
Is he gone?
Alpert?
No, he's not gone.
We told him where the bodies were.
You told him? Why?
We had to.
It was the only way
to maintain the truce.
Jim here worked it out with him, but...
Well, he's gonna need something from us now.
He needs to take Paul's body back with him.
- Hey.
- Oh...No.
Hey, Ames.
Listen,
we've been friends
for a long time, yeah?
So... this is completely your choice.
If you don't want to give him to them,
then we will suffer the consequences.
They can take him.
He would want to keep us safe.
Can I have a minute, please?
I'm sorry.
You need some help?
Hmm? Oh.
Nah, I've got it. Thanks.
Hey, Jim, the sub leaving tomorrow morning...
It returns in two weeks.
Until then,
you can stay and look
for the rest of your crew.
Thanks.
I bought us two weeks.
Horace said we can
wait for the next sub.
With any luck,
Locke'll be back by then.
And then what?
What do you mean, "then what"?
Locke said he was leaving to save us.
The flashes have stopped.
They're over.
No more bloody noses.
We're already saved.
That sub behind you brought me here.
I've been trying to get off of
this island for more than three years,
and now I've got my chance.
I'm going to leave.
You do realize it's 1974,
that whatever it is you think
you're going back to...
It don't exist yet.
It's not a reason not to go.
Hell, what about me?
You really gonna leave me here
with the mad scientist
and Mr."I speak to dead people"?
And Jin, who's a hell of a nice guy
but not exactly the
greatest conversationalist.
You'll be fine.
Maybe...
But who's gonna get my back?
Come on.
Just give me two weeks,
that's all I'm asking.
Two weeks.
All right. Two weeks.
Mmm, somethin' smells good.
Hey there.
Is that for me?
You were amazing today.
Thank you for believing in me.
Ah.
Mmm.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Mmm.
Wake up, boss.
Ah.
Oh!
How's your head?
It hurts.
I got good news and bad news.
What you want first?
Good news.
You're a daddy.
Bad news is you missed it.
Oh, gosh.
Amy... She had the baby?
It's a boy.
A boy?
Oh...
Now how about you tell me...
why you're too busy drinking
and blowing up trees
to see him be born?
I was, uh...
I was looking for a pair of socks,
and all of mine were dirty,
so I went to grab a pair of Amy's, and...
I found this...
in the back of her drawer.
It was Paul's.
You got in a fight over a necklace?
I know.
But...
It's only been three years, Jim.
Just three years that he's been gone.
Is that really long enough
to get over someone?
I had a thing for a girl once.
And I had a shot at her,
but I didn't take it.
For a little while,
I'd lay in bed every night,
wondering if it was a mistake.
Wondering if...
I'd ever stop thinking about her.
And now I can barely remember
what she looks like.
I mean, her face... it's...
She's just gone,
and she ain't never coming back.
So...
Is three years long enough
to get over someone?
Absolutely.
Oh.
What?
Wait. What?
H... no. No.
Don't bring them in.
Just meet me in the North Valley.
Who was it?
James, what's going on?
It was Jin.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. I just...
I gotta go.
a ydy.com subtitle,
edited and synced by rogard