Previously on "Lost"...
FARADAY: Whatever Ben Linus did down
at the Orchid station,
it may have... dislodged us.
JULIET: The island is
moving through time?
Yeah, either the island is,
or we are.
I need you to go back
to Oxford University.
Go back to where we met!
I need you to go there and
find my mother! Her name is--
Are you all right?
I was on the island.
You've been off the
island for three years.
You're safe now.
It was just a dream.
It wasn't a dream, Pen.
It was a memory.
Efren Salonga?
Ef-efren Salonga!
Efren Salonga!
Efren Salonga?
Who are you?
Are you the doctor?
Yes.
What's the matter with you?
You're sure you know
what you're doing, yeah?
- Yes, yes!
- Because there's a lot of blood, man!
- How much blood?
- I'm coming, Penny!
It's okay, Pen. We've got a doctor.
Where have you been?!
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay. Okay, here you go.
Okay. Just breathe, Penny, okay?
J-just breathe.
Oh! Breathe.
- I can't breathe.
- You're doing great.
You're doing great, okay.
Okay, just be strong, yeah? Okay.
- Make it come out.
- Please be strong.
Hold it. Hold it.
I can't!
Yes, you-- yes, you can, Penny.
Push! Push!
Okay, push now, Penny. Push. Now!
Come on, Penny. That's it. It's coming.
- Come on, Penny.
- Push harder! Push!
I can see the head! I can see the head!
- One more time! Push!
- I can see it. It's just coming.
It's coming! It's coming!
You got it.
You did it.
Oh, my God, Penny. You did it.
It's a boy.
I love you, Penny. I love you.
Oh, oh, he's beautiful. Beautiful.
Oh, my God. He's so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
I love you.
Look.
Right out there.
Beyond where you can see,
there's--there's an island,
and it's a very special island.
I left it a long time ago.
I never thought I'd see it again.
It's called Great Britain.
And the most beautiful part
of the island is Scotland,
and that's where your daddy's from.
There's mountains and glens
and monsters in deep lochs, and...
And it's where your mommy and daddy...
fell in love.
It's also where he broke her heart.
Yeah, well, I...
I thought I'd leave
that wee bit out of it.
You also left out the bit
about his grandfather,
the man who sent a boat to the island
to kill all daddy's friends.
We'll be in and out.
He'll never know we're here, Penny.
Don't underestimate him, Desmond.
If he finds out we're here,
I don't know what he'll do.
But this has nothing to do
with your father, Penny.
We are here because of Daniel Faraday.
What he told me -
that everyone on that
island is in danger,
and I am the only one
that can help them.
I have to do this, Penny.
Are you sure that's what he said?
Yeah, Sawyer said to meet at the creek,
so unless he got torched
by a flaming arrow,
that's where he and
everyone else should be.
Hey, how's your headache?
Worse, actually.
But considering we're
running for our lives,
I'm not gonna complain.
You have any dizziness or double vision?
Both, actually.
Why do you look so worried?
Is it because you know
what's happening to me?
Listen to me. Nothing is
gonna happen to you. Nothing.
I won't let it.
Hey, we're here!
Some rendezvous. It's just us.
Well, we should probably wait,
see if they show up.
They could be right behind us.
- Yeah, or they came and left.
- Or they're dead.
Miles, that right there,
that kind of attitude...
Not exactly what we need right now.
People are scared enough
as it is. Miles...
Miles?
Wait! Don't move!
Who's in charge here?
He is.
You just couldn't stay away, could you?
a ydy. com subtitle,
edited by rogard
Lost S05E03 "Jughead"
Did he finish his breakfast?
Yeah.
Gave me a bit of a fight,
but he listens in the end...
Unlike his father.
Look, honey,
all I have to do is find his mother,
tell her he's still on the island,
and then I'm done with this for good.
Why now?
I mean, if he told you
all this on the island,
why didn't you remember
it until two days ago?
I don't know.
Look, I don't understand
how any of this works
any more than you do it.
Look, I know it happened.
Daniel Faraday knocked on the hatch door
and told me to go to Oxford.
Everyone was in danger,
and I was the only one
that could save them.
I know how insane it sounds.
I'll be back by dark,
and then I'm done...
Forever.
I promise.
If you're gonna promise
me something, Des,
can you promise me you'll never
go back to that island again?
Why in god's name would
I wanna go back there?
There were 20 of you at the beach,
but only five of you here.
Where are the rest of your people?
Maybe they got blown up by
some more of your land mines.
We didn't put them here. You did.
Once we leave here,
I will be out of control
of what happens to you.
But if you cooperate now,
things will go much easier for you.
So where are the rest of your people?
I don't know.
Who are these people?
Well, gee, I didn't have time...
to ask that, with
Frogurt on fire and all.
They attacked us on the beach.
This is a 30-caliber
M1 Garand rifle. It looks new.
Who cares about the rifle?
Where the hell have you been?
If you've been going
through what I have, James,
maybe the more appropriate
question would be:
When the hell have I been?
- What happened to your leg?
- I got shot.
- By who?
- We can swap stories later.
We told the rest of our group
that we would meet them at the creek.
If there's any chance of reconnecting
with them, we'd better get moving.
Fine, seeing as we have no rope
to make sure these two
don't try to kill us again.
- Guess we're gonna have to shoot 'em.
- Quare non sunt vestitus eis?
- Tace!
- What?
(Latin)
- And what language is that?
- They're speaking Latin.
That one asked why we aren't in uniform,
and this one told him to shut up.
And how is it that they know
how to speak Latin, Juliet?
The same reason I do.
Because they're Others.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
- We just walked over a fresh grave.
- What?
Four U.S. soldiers,
dead just under a month.
Three of them were shot.
One died of radiation poisoning.
Miles, hey, hey.
Did any of them happen
to mention what year it is?
We're here.
Richard? We're back.
Caught the three by the creek.
This one's their leader.
What's your name?
My name is Richard Alpert.
I assume you've come back for your bomb.
No, I'm sorry, sir.
I'm not finding a record of any Faraday.
No, that--that's impossible.
'cause I know her son
was a professor here.
His name's Daniel Faraday.
I'm sure he's in your database.
There's no record of any Faraday
ever having been
employed here at Oxford.
I visited him.
I went to his lab. It was in an attic.
It was...
it was above the physics department.
The archives go back quite far.
Perhaps there was a clerical error.
You don't happen to recall the year
it was in which you last visited?
The year?
No. I'm...
I'm not exactly sure.
May I ask why you're
seeking this information?
Sorry I wasted your time.
Yeah, I wouldn't touch that.
I wondered when someone'd figure out
we weren't just fumigating here.
You a professor?
No. Not exactly.
At least you're honest.
So why'd you tell me not to touch it?
Because I'm the one
who had to take the rats
he made run through this
bloody thing down to the incinerator,
so that no one would find
out what he was up to.
You mean Daniel Faraday.
Yeah. You're not the first
one to poke around here,
asking about him and his work.
Rumor had it, he was trying
to send rats' brains back in time.
Ridiculous, innit?
Aye.
Look, I'll forget you broke my lock
if you tell your mates
that all you found
was rubbish left behind by a madman.
Fair enough.
Faraday...
The university says
there's no record of him.
Well, can you blame 'em?
I mean, after what he'd
done to that poor girl?
What girl?
Hey, take it easy.
It's all right, Dan. I'm fine.
We are so dead.
Hey. No, no, no.
We are not so dead.
We're gonna be fine.
We just need to keep it together
until there's another flash.
All right? Then all this disappears.
- And when's that gonna happen?
- Could be five minutes.
Could also be 5,000 years.
That's--that's just awesome.
What is going on, Dan?
- Why are they doing this to us?
- I'm not sure.
But they must think that we're
with the American military.
And if that's the case,
our best chance of staying alive
is to let them keep thinking
it, all right? Let--
Sorry. Am I interrupting?
Ellie tells me that you're
not willing to reveal
where the rest of your squad is.
And why would I do that?
So you can kill them, too?
We didn't start this, friend.
Your people attacked us.
You come to our island
to run your tests,
you fire on us, and what,
- you expect us not to defend ourselves?
- I don't know anything about that.
We are scientists.
So what? So they sent you
here to recover it?
If you mean our hydrogen bomb, then yes.
And I'm guessing from this
man's radiation burns
that the housing has been compromised.
Is that right?
You need to listen to me.
You have an unstable device
that's capable of destroying
this entire island,
and it's broken.
If you don't allow me
to render it inert,
all of us are gonna die.
All of us.
How do I know you weren't sent
here on some suicide mission?
That I'll take you out to the bomb,
and you'll just detonate it?
Because...
I'm in love with the
woman sitting next to me.
And I would never...
I would never do anything to hurt her.
All right.
Take care of your bomb,
but you try anything else,
and you will hurt her.
So who taught you Latin?
Others 101.
Gotta learn Latin -
language of the enlightened.
Enlightened, my ass.
I suggest you talk to us.
Once we get back to the creek
and meet up with the rest of our people,
there's gonna be a lot of anger
directed at you for attacking them.
The rest of your people
are either captured or dead.
What?
What makes you say that?
That idiot shouted out,
"meet at the creek."
We knew exactly where they were headed.
Sent a group after them.
Well, maybe I should've
said it in my secret language.
James, wait.
* We're not your enemy.
* Then let us go.
What the hell were you sayin'?
* Take us to your camp.
* Please.
* Why would I do that?
* Is...
*...Richard there?
* Richard Alpert?
Did you just say "Richard Alpert"?
John, please.
* Bring us to your camp.
* No one else has to die.
* Please.
All right.
Okay, we need to head east
another couple of kilometers
until we hit the ridge--
Shoot him!
Shoot, damn it!
Are you crazy?! What were you thinking?
Why didn't you shoot him?!
Because...
he's one of my people.
And who might you be?
Uh, my name's Desmond Hume.
I'm looking for Theresa Spencer.
I'm Abigail Spencer.
Theresa's my sister.
All right. Um, can I
have a word with her?
You wanna speak to Theresa?
Yeah, I got her name from a-
a gentleman I met at Oxford University.
Um... Daniel Faraday.
Daniel Faraday?
Well, why didn't you say so?
Please, you must come in.
Thanks.
He didn't tell you, did he?
No. No, he didn't.
Can she hear us?
No. Theresa's away right now.
"Away"? What do you mean?
Well, sometimes she
wakes up, thinks she's 3,
wants to know where her dolly is.
Yesterday, she was talking to our dad.
He died five years ago.
I'm sorry.
Um, this was a mistake.
I... I shouldn't have come.
Of course.
Why would you want to stay?
Daniel certainly didn't.
He left her like this?
Went running off to the States,
never to be heard from again.
He abandoned her.
What kind of a man does that?
I seriously don't know
what we would've done
if it hadn't been for Mr. Widmore.
Uh, I'm sorry. Who?
Daniel's benefactor.
He funded his research,
and he took responsibility
for the result of it.
He's been taking care of Theresa
ever since this happened to her.
Everything here is due to Mr. Widmore,
God bless him.
A hydrogen bomb?
Seriously?
Back in the '50s,
the U.S. Government tested
H-bombs in the South Pacific.
Lucky us.
You didn't have to say that.
Say what?
That you loved me.
I mean, there are plenty of other ways
you could've convinced him
you weren't gonna blow
up the entire island.
I said what I said
because I meant it, Charlotte.
Right, then.
Let's go.
Back soon. I promise.
Whatever your, uh, your
superiors told you,
I want you to know the truth.
A month ago, we found
18 members of an Army battalion
right here in our jungle here,
setting up this camp.
We gave them the opportunity
to leave the island peacefully.
They weren't willing to do that,
so I was forced to kill them.
All of 'em.
- Forced?
- Yeah.
By whom?
You answer to someone, don't you?
You follow a chain of command, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well, so do I.
Richard! Richard!
What the hell happened to you?
Cunningham and I--
a group of them surprised us.
We were outnumbered, but I escaped.
- Outnumbered, eh?
- Shut up, Ellie.
Who's this?
He's gonna help us take
care of our problem.
You'd better get going.
Wait. He's one of them.
You can't actually trust him.
Yeah, you heard me, Ellie. Go.
- How did you escape?
- I ran.
And it never occurred to you
that they might follow you?
Follow me?
Their leader is some sodding old man.
What, you think he can track me?
You think he knows this
island better than I do?
How did you know Richard would be here?
Richard's always been here.
How old is he?
Old.
Why are you so interested
in Richard, John?
I'm interested in him
because he was about to
tell me how I could save us.
"Save us"?
Yeah.
But before he could finish,
we were interrupted by
that flash of light
and I'm hoping we can
pick up where we left off.
I hate to bust up the
"I'm an Other, you're an Other" reunion,
but Faraday, the guy that's
actually gonna save us,
is being death marched
into the jungle right now.
Good luck with that.
You're not gonna help me save him?
No. I'm gonna go down
finish my conversation with Richard.
That's gonna get us all killed.
You go rolling in there,
they're gonna know we're here.
Fair enough.
I'll give you ten minutes head start.
What about you?
You wanna stay here in Crazytown
or help me rescue the geek?
Why do you keep looking at me?
No, no, I'm- I'm not. I--
You are.
You know what?
You're right. I'm--I'm sorry.
It's just...
You look so much like...
someone I used to know.
Someone other than the girl
you just professed your love for?
- Well, aren't you the romeo.
- Far from it, believe me.
I don't believe you, by the way.
You may have Richard fooled,
but you can't really
expect me to believe
that you, a British
woman and a Chinese man
are all members of the
United States military.
Who are you,
and what are you doing on our island?
You wanna know who I am?
I'm your best chance
at disarming that bomb.
Right, then,
disarm it.
What are you doing up there?
I'm examining it.
- Back up.
- What?
Get back, get back.
It's unsafe. We need to move.
I swear, if you try anything...
If I try anything...?
What, you're gonna--
You're gonna shoot me?
Is that right?
Yeah, that would be
perfect because, of course,
rifle fire right next to-
What would you call this?
Hydrogen bomb? Yes, fantastic idea.
Really... Inspired.
Okay, listen to me.
Do you people have any
access to lead or concrete?
For what?
There's a crack in the casing.
It needs to be filled with lead.
You need to take it off
this platform carefully and bury it.
You brought me all the way out here
to tell us that we have to bury it?
You told Alpert you
could disarm that thing.
You don't need to worry.
You do what I say, you bury it,
it won't go off.
- How do you know that?
- I need you to trust me.
I don't trust you.
Just bury it. Bury it,
and everything will be fine. Remember,
- your superior ordered
me to take care of this.
How can you be so sure?
You wanna take care of
this bomb? You bury it!
How do you know that?
Because 50 years from now,
this island is still here!
There you...
What did you just say?
Whoa. Take it easy.
I can explain myself a little better.
I know how this sounds.
Believe me, it's...
It's hard to explain.
50 years from now,
me and my...
Me and my friends--
That's where we're from, okay?
And here's the key - everything's fine.
I'm not saying it's perfectly fine,
but there hasn't been any
atomic blasts, all right?
Drop the gun, blondie.
It's okay.
She's okay. You can put your gun down.
She puts hers down first.
Why don't we all put our guns down?
I said, drop it!
Son of a bitch.
Are they from the future, too?
You told her?
Sir! Sir, you can't--
Mr. Widmore.
I'm so sorry. He charged right past me.
That's all right, Melanie.
Mr. Hume is a... colleague of mine.
Please leave us.
I know you have questions for me.
I'm not gonna answer them.
I've come here to ask you something.
And once you've told me
everything I need to know,
you'll never see me again.
Understand?
All right.
I need to know where I can
find Daniel Faraday's mother.
What makes you think I would
even know the answer to that?
Because even before you put
Faraday on your little boat
and sent him off to the island,
you spent ten years
funding his research.
So I figure, you must know something
regarding his next of kin.
Desmond,
I haven't seen or heard
from my daughter for three years.
Just answer me this.
Is she safe?
Where's Faraday's mother?
She's in Los Angeles.
This is an address for her.
I suspect she won't be
pleased to see you.
She's a very private person.
Wait, Desmond.
Deliver your message...
but then get out of this mess.
Don't put Penny's life in danger.
Danger?
You're getting yourself
involved in something
that goes back many, many years.
It has nothing to do
with you or my daughter.
Wherever you were hiding...
Go back there.
Thanks for the advice.
Richard Alpert!
Hey!
- I'm looking for Richard.
- Don't move.
- Richard Alpert!
- On the ground, now.
- Richard, I need to talk to you!
- Shut your mouth!
That's enough!
Who are you?
My name is John Locke.
Is that supposed to
mean something to me?
Jacob sent me.
Put the gun down.
What?
Richard, you can't seriously trust him.
I said... Put the gun down, Widmore.
Your name is Widmore?
Charles Widmore?
What's it to you?
Nothing. Nice to meet you.
...but it saw the bear
so that it ran away again.
Where?
- Hi.
Good day?
Yeah.
He wanted to go fishing in the Thames.
We were unsuccessful.
And you?
Did you find Faraday's mum?
There was no one to find.
She, um...
She died a few years ago.
Why are you lying to me?
What? I'm not.
Where is she?
She's in Los Angeles.
Look, Pen, you've got
nothing to worry about.
You know, this was a mistake.
No, I... I made a promise
that this would be done in a day
and now it's done.
It's not our problem anymore.
And what happens if you wake up
tomorrow and remember something else?
Then I'll forget it.
- And the next day?
- I'll forget it.
It doesn't matter, Pen.
You're my life now, you and Charlie.
I won't leave you again...
Not for this...
Not for anything.
You'll never forget it, Des.
So I guess we're going with you.
I gave you this?
- Yes.
- After you were shot in the leg
and I... wandered out of
the jungle to patch you up?
That's right.
And why don't I remember...
well, any of this?
Because it hasn't happened yet.
I'm not sure what you're
expecting me to say, John Locke.
I expect you to tell me
how to get off the island.
That's very privileged information.
Why would I share it with you?
Because you told me that
I had something very important to do,
once I get there.
And because I'm your leader.
- You're my leader?
- That's what you told me.
Look, I... certainly don't
want to contradict myself,
but... we have a very specific process
for selecting our leadership,
and it starts at a very, very young age.
All right. All right.
What year is it right now?
It's 1954.
All right. May 30, 1956,
two years from now,
that's the day I'm born.
Tustin, California,
and if you don't believe me,
I suggest you come and visit me.
Oh, no.
- What's wrong?
- It's about to happen again.
You need to tell me now, Richard.
How do I get off the island?
Please! Tell me!
You all right?
Yeah...
I think so.
Charlotte.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Yeah, me too.
I'm great too.
Charlotte.
Charlotte...
Charlotte. No, no, no.
Look at me, hey, look at me! It's okay.
It's okay.
Charlotte!
subtitle created by the ydy. com team,
edited and synced by rogard