Previously on "Lost"
Ladies and gentlemen,
the survivors of Oceanic 815.
I just killed a man
who's been perched...
outside this facility
for the last week.
I want you to come with me
somewhere safe.
You and I have common interests.
We're not the only ones
who left the island.
- We... were not supposed to leave.
- Bye, Jack.
We have to go back, Kate.
Hello, Jack. Did he tell you
that I was off the island?
Yes, he did. he said
that I had to come back.
We're gonna have to bring him, too.
Ah. Hm. Baby's awake.
It's your turn.
Morning. Here you go, doc.
I don't need a script.
Let's go. I don't have all day.
- Speed.
- Okay.
Dharma orientation film number two,
take one.
And... action.
Hello. I'm Dr. Marvin Candle,
and this is the orientation
film for station two,
The Arrow.
Given your specific area of expertise,
you should find it no surprise
that this station's primary purpose
is to develop defensive strategies
and gather intelligence
on the island's hostile
indigenous population--
Dr. Chang!
- Dr. Chang?
- Damn it! What the hell?!
- Cut!
Sir, we got a problem
down at The Orchid.
Over here.
We were cutting through the
rock, right on your specs.
That's when the drill melted.
- The drill melted?
- Yeah, yeah.
3 meters from the margin
line on the plans.
We went through six carbon drill bits,
and the last one just
fried. Then my operator--
My operator starts grabbing
his head and freaking out.
We sonar-imaged the wall.
There's an open chamber
about 20 meters in,
behind the rock.
There's something in there.
And the only way to get to it
is to lay charges here and here
- and blast through it and take a look.
- Under no circumstances.
This station is being built
here because of its proximity
to what we believe to be an
almost limitless energy.
And that energy, once we
can harness it correctly,
it's going to allow us
to manipulate time.
Right.
Okay, so what? We're gonna
go back and kill Hitler?
Don't be absurd.
There are rules,
rules that can't be broken.
So what do you want me to do?
You're gonna do nothing.
If you drill even 1 centimeter further,
you risk releasing that energy.
If that's gonna happen,
God help us all.
All right, get him up. Let's go.
Watch yourself!
Sorry, sir. It won't happen again.
All right. I'll grab
the rest of his stuff.
Let's go.
Did you hear that?
Time travel. How stupid
does that guy think we are?
Let's go, guys.
Why don't you close that up now, Jack?
Come on.
Let's get him in the van.
It's out back.
Where are we taking him?
We'll worry about that
once we pick up Hugo.
Hurley...
is locked away in a mental institution.
Which should make recruiting him
considerably easier than
the rest of your friends.
They're not my friends anymore.
Oh, that's the spirit.
How did we get here?
How did all this happen?
It happened because you left, Jack.
Now let's get started, shall we?
So once we get Hurley... then what?
Then we get Sun, Sayid...
and Kate, of course.
I don't see that happening.
When was the last time you saw him?
I mean, Locke.
On the island...
In the Orchid station
below the greenhouse.
I told him I was sorry
for making his life so miserable,
and then he left.
So obviously John's visit
to you made an impression.
What did he say to make
you such a believer?
Sawyer, Juliet,
everyone from the boat...
and everyone we left behind--
John said that they'd die,
too, if I didn't come back.
Did he tell you what happened
to them after the island moved?
No.
No, he didn't.
Then I guess we'll never know.
What the...
Richard...
Richard?
Anyone?
What happened?
What was that light?
We must've been inside the radius.
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
Where's the freighter?
- Maybe it went down.
- Unh-unh. No way.
A minute ago, that boat
was coughing black smoke.
Now there's just nothin'?
What about the helicopter?
It was heading for that boat.
Rose!
- Bernard!
- Rose!
- Have you seen Rose?!
- No.
Oh, my God!
- Bernard!
- Rose!
- Where were you?
- I was over... by the church.
What was that sound?
What was that light?
I don't know.
Just calm down. There's no
need to panic, all right?
- We'll just go back to camp and...
- Calm down?
No need to panic?
We can't go back to the camp.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- There is no camp.
The--the sky lit up, a-and then this.
The--the kitchen? Gone.
And--and all the tents, all
the food and water... gone.
Well, everything but us. All of it.
It's gone.
It's not gone.
Daniel!
Hey.
I thought you were on the freighter.
No, we never made it.
We were on our way out
there when it happened.
What do you mean, the camp's not gone?
- Who the hell are you anyway?
- That's Dan.
- He's our physicist.
- Listen, we have no time.
I need you to take me
to something man-made,
something that was built,
any kind of a landmark.
There's a Dharma station
15 minutes from here.
You mean the hatch? The one we blew up?
That's perfect.
We should get moving before
it happens again, okay?
Before what happens again?
And why is our camp gone?
Your camp isn't gone.
It hasn't been built yet.
Choo choo! Tunnel!
Oh, I think Choo Choo
knows better than that.
He goes into that tunnel,
he's never coming back out.
Watch your cartoons, Goober.
Mommy'll be right back.
- Ms. Austen?
- Yes?
Hi, I'm Dan Norton of the
law firm Agostoni & Norton.
- May we have a moment of your time?
- And who are you?
He's my associate.
If I could just come in,
I'll be glad to explain--
No, you can explain right here.
Okay, you got it.
Ms. Austen, we're here to
get a blood sample from you
and one from your son Aaron.
Excuse me?
Now I have a court
order signed by a judge
for you to relinquish your blood
upon being served these papers
Why?
To determine your
relationship to the child.
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
Um, who's the--
I'm not at liberty to divulge
the identity of my client.
- Your client?
- Please, may we come in?
Get off my property.
If you won't comply,
then I'm going to have to
come back with the sheriff.
Then come back with the sheriff.
Where are you going, mommy?
We're going on vacation, baby.
Say bye-bye, baby.
Why did you jump off that helicopter?
I told you. We were runnin' out of gas.
I wanted to make sure she--
I wanted to make sure they
got back to the boat.
- Don't matter now anyway, does it?
- Excuse me.
I really need the two of you
to pick up the pace. Okay, thanks.
First things first.
Give me your shirt.
- My shirt?
- Yeah.
I really think we have
far more pressing matters
than me giving you a shirt.
- How about we just keep moving, okay?
- How about we call a time-out
so you can tell us
what the hell is going on?
How about you trust me?
Trust you? I don't know you!
We really do not have time
for me to try to explain.
You have no idea
how difficult that would be
for me to try to explain this--
this phenomenon to a quantum physicist.
That would be difficult,
so for me to try to explain
whatever is happening--
Oi!
What in bloody hell do
you think you're doing?
Shut it, Ginger, or you're get one too.
Now talk.
The island...
Think of the island
like a record spinning on a turntable...
only now that record is skipping.
Whatever Ben Linus did down
at the Orchid station...
I think it may have...
dislodged us.
Dislodged us from what?
Time.
So that's why our camp is gone?
Because the island is
moving through time?
Yeah, either the island is, or we are.
What?
And it's just as likely
that we're moving,
your people and us.
And everyone in your group--
you're all accounted for, right?
Not everyone.
Locke.
Is anyone there?!
Hello?!
Hey!
Uhh!
Who are you?
- Well, listen, listen...
- How many others are on board?
You don't understand.
I didn't come on that plane.
Wrong answer.
No, wait! Stop! Stop!
I know you. I know who you are.
Your name...
Your name is Ethan.
- Your name is Ethan.
- Who are you?
My name is John Locke.
I know this is gonna
be hard to understand,
but Ben Linus appointed
me as your leader.
That is the most ridiculous
thing I've ever heard.
Good-bye, John Locke.
Great.
So when are we now, wiz kid?
We're either in the past...
or we're in the future.
Flight 23 to Paris
will begin boarding at gate 15.
Please have your boarding passes ready.
Evening, ma'am.
Where you flying to tonight?
Los Angeles.
Of course. May I see
your passport, please?
Excuse me.
Could you wait here for
just one moment, Ms. Kwon?
Hey! Where are you going?
Open this door.
Open this door!
Save your breath.
They only do what I tell them to do.
You.
You had me brought in here?
Why?
You had the audacity
to approach me in broad daylight
in front of my business
associates... in public.
Why did I have you brought here?
Because you showed me no respect.
I will be respected, Sun.
Fair enough.
Since you seem to be
worried about your plane,
I'll get right down to business.
You mentioned that you and I had...
common interests.
Why don't you tell me
exactly what they might be?
To kill Benjamin Linus.
The victim was found shot in his car
on the grounds of the
Santa Rosa hospital,
a private mental health care
facility outside Los Angeles.
Okay...
Let's go get him.
Police have now identified
their suspect in the shooting
as a patient at the hospital
who escaped earlier this
evening - Hugo Reyes.
Now if that name sounds familiar to you,
that's because Reyes was a member
of the infamous Oceanic Six.
As to why he may have murdered
a visitor to the facility
where Reyes lived for two years,
that remains a complete mystery.
Well...
Looks like we have a change of plan.
Here she comes, right now.
Here's your order, sir.
- Keep the change.
- Thank you.
Awesome.
- You want a fry?
- No, thank you.
You know, maybe if you
ate more comfort food,
you wouldn't have to go
around shooting people.
So that dude you popped
outside Santa Rosa - who was he?
I don't care. He was armed
and he was watching you.
That made him an enemy.
Do you think he was gonna kill me?
I'm not taking any risks
after Bentham died--
- You mean Locke.
- Yes, I mean Locke.
I need a cool code name.
So when'd you become so paranoid?
If you'd spent the last two years
doing the things I was doing,
you'd be paranoid, too.
Oh, yeah?
Paranoid? Like what?
What kind of things?
I was working for Benjamin Linus.
Wait. He's on our side now?
Listen to me, Hurley.
If you ever have the misfortune
of running into him,
whatever he tells you,
just do the opposite.
Wait here.
- Is he all right?
- I don't know.
Is he breathing or what?
Who is that?
Check him out.
Look out! That guy's got a gun! Run!
Get out of here! Call the cops!
Hurry!
Sayid!
You okay?
Get me to the car.
Dude. Dude...
Oh, man.
I thought it was supposed
to be a safe house.
I never should've left that island.
Hey, do you think he's looking for us?
Who?
Widmore.
It took him, like, 20 years to
find this place the first time.
I'll start holding my breath now.
Over here!
- Is this the hatch?
- It was.
Blown up, just like we left it.
Okay.
So when we are now...
It's now after you and your
people crashed on the island.
You sayin' our camp is back
on the beach again?
It's possible, yeah.
- Good. I'm going back.
- Hey. No, no.
It's pointless.
More pointless than staring
at a hole in the ground?
We don't know when the
next flash is coming.
By the time you get back to the beach,
the camp could be gone again.
Yeah, but what if it ain't?
Hell, what if the helicopter
hasn't even taken off yet?
We could warn them,
stop them from ever flying to that boat.
That's not the way it works.
Who says?
You cannot change anything. You can't.
Even if you tried to, it wouldn't work.
Why not?
Time--it's like a street, all right?
We can move forward on that
street, we can move in reverse,
but we cannot ever create a new street.
If we try to do anything different,
we will fail every time.
Whatever happened, happened.
How do you know so much
about this, Danny boy?
I know about this because...
I've spent my entire adult
life studying space-time.
I know all of this because
this journal contains
everything I've ever learned
about the Dharma Initiative.
This is why I'm here.
I know what's happening.
So how can we stop it?
We can't stop it.
Then who can?
Richard?
Hey, John.
Richard...
What is happening?
What's happening is that
you're bleeding to death.
Here.
I need to get the bullet out.
How did you know there was
a bullet in my leg, Richard?
Because you told me there was, John.
No, no. No, I didn't.
Well... you will.
It was Ethan who shot me.
Well...
What comes around, goes around.
When am I?
Well, John, that-- that's all relative.
Wait, wait.
The- the noise, when the sky
lit up... where did you go?
I didn't go anywhere, John. You went.
All right, this- this is gonna hurt.
It'll be a lot worse if
you move, okay? Hold still.
All done.
Jeez.
I don't understand.
How- how did you know that I was here?
- How did you know where to find me?
- I wish I had time to explain it, John.
But you're gonna be moving on soon,
and we need to go over a couple of
things before you do.
"Moving on"? God!
Sorry. The first thing, okay?
You're gonna need to clean out the wound
every couple of hours
and keep as much weight off
the leg as you can, all right?
The island'll do the rest,
John, all right?
But I don't--
Second thing. No, no, pay attention.
Next time we see each other,
I'm not gonna recognize you.
All right? You'll give me this.
- All right?
- What is this?
- It's a compass.
- What does it do?
It points north, John.
Look, I wish I had time to
be more sensitive about this
because it's a lot to swallow,
but you need to know it in
order to do what you gotta do.
So I'm just gonna say it, okay?
The only way to save the island, John,
is to get your people back here -
the ones who left.
Jack, Kate...
The chopper was headed for the boat.
The boat--
No, they're fine, John,
and they're already home,
so you have to convince
them to come back.
How- how am I supposed to do that?
You're gonna have to die, John.
So... what was this thing
before you guys blew it up?
- A Dharma station.
- For what?
There was a man named
Desmond living down in it.
He was pushing a button
every 108 minutes
to save the world.
Really?
Yeah. Really.
Son of a...
...bitch.
The hatch--it's back.
I guess you haven't found it yet.
Hey! Where you goin'?
Back door. I'm gettin' some supplies.
James, wait. Not a good idea.
The sky can flash all it wants,
but I ain't startin' over, Dilbert.
I ain't rubbin' two sticks
together and making a fire,
and I ain't huntin' damn boar!
There's Dharma food, beer
and clothing in there.
And I'm gettin' Desmond to
let me in one way or another.
- That's not gonna work, my friend.
- Why not?
Because Desmond didn't know you
when he first came out of there,
that means you've never met,
which means you can't meet.
This would all be fascinating
if I was listening to you.
So how you do know
Desmond is even in there?
Think about it. It could be anybody.
I don't care who's in there.
Wait...
- Wait.
- Open the damn door!
- It won't work.
- Sure it will.
Yo, open up! It's the
ghost of christmas future!
No one- no one is gonna answer.
Open! Open the damn door! Open the door!
You're wasting your time.
Open up! I know you can hear me.
If it didn't happen, it can't happen.
- Open the damn door!
- You can't change the past, James!
Everybody I care about just
blew up on your damn boat.
I know what I can't change.
We should get back to the beach.
It's been a long day.
Why are we going back to the beach
if there's nothing to go back to?
So stay here.
That chick likes me.
What?
Wh- what? What's the matter?
You...
Ugh. I haven't had a nosebleed
since I was little.
Dan, I'm fine.
Yeah. no, no, no, you're--
um, of course you're fine.
I'm, uh... you know,
the sight of blood is,..
Yeah, well, it's a good thing
you're a physicist then, isn't it?
Shall we?
Yeah, um... my pack.
Of course I left my pack
back at the hatch crater.
I better get it.
Why don't you head back
with everyone else and...
- I'll be right behind you?
- Don't dillydally.
I wouldn't think of it.
Please let this work.
Please, please, please, let this work.
- Don't shoot.
- Then you'd best explain
why you've been bangin' on my door
for the last 20 minutes, brother.
Desmond.
Are you him?
"Him"? Who?
My replacement.
No, I'm not.
I'm not. I'm not. I'm...
Do I know you?
Yeah... in a way.
But listen, that's not important.
What is important, Desmond,
is what I'm about to say to you.
I need you to listen.
You're the only person who can
help us because, Desmond...
The rules...
the rules don't apply to you.
You're special.
You're uniquely and
miraculously special.
What are you talking about?
Okay, listen to me. Listen!
If the helicopter somehow
made it off the island,
if you got home--
What helicopter?
What are you talking about?
Listen, I need you to listen,
or people are gonna die.
My name is Daniel Faraday, and right now,
me and everyone else you left behind -
we're in serious danger.
You're the only person who can help us.
I need you to go back
to Oxford University.
Go back to where we met.
I need you to go there and
find my mother. Her name is--
Are you all right?
I was on the island.
You've been off the island
for three years now.
You're safe now.
It was just a dream.
It wasn't a dream, Pen.
It was a memory.
Desmond, where are you going?
Des?
Desmond?
What are you doing?
We're leaving.
Leaving to go where?
Oxford.
subtitle by www.tvsubtitles.net
synced and edited by rogard