Comes fully equipped.
I'm telling you,
it's a steal at $400.
- Gotta check with your husband?
- It's just me.
Mommy?
- Can I have a quarter for the machine?
- Honey, I said wait for me by the pool.
I thought you said it was "just me."
I meant my husband's out of the picture.
It's just me and my son.
The other tenants don't like noise.
He's very quiet.
I'm gonna need two months up front.
Here, honey.
Hey, no running.
You hear me, Miles?
Mom!
Mommy! Help!
Miles?
- Miles, what happened?
- Mommy!
God.
Mr. Vonner.
- What were you doing in here?
- He was all alone.
He was scared.
His chest hurt.
He kept calling out for Kimberly.
Kimberly?
That's his wife.
She died last year.
Now how would you know that?
- I heard him.
- What are you talking about?
He's still talking right now.
Honey...
He's dead.
I told you! I can hear him!
I can hear him!
Miles, you there? Pick up.
Where are you?
I'll fill you in later.
I need you to take care of something.
- Like what?
- The security tapes
from the pylon camera feeds.
They need to accidentally get erased.
Erased? Why?
I ain't got time for questions.
Just do it.
Which ones?
Look on your monitors.
You see us?
Yeah. You're on number 4.
Is that Kate?
What are you doing out there?
Just erase number 4.
And if anyone asks, I'm off the grid.
- I'm looking for the escaped hostile.
- You mean your pal Sayid?
You gonna help me or not?!
- Yeah, yeah. I got it.
- All right. I owe you one.
You go back and and find Juliet,
see if anyone's noticed yet
if Ben's gone missin'.
What are you gonna do
when they find out?
Do my best to cover it up.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm the head of security.
I'll see you back there.
Where's Lafleur?
He's out looking for
the escaped prisoner.
I tried to get him on his walkie,
but...
He must be out of range.
Damn it.
All right.
Then it's gonna have to be you.
Jim already knows about this,
but I'm gonna bring you
into the circle of trust.
Can I trust you, Miles?
Absolutely.
Okay. Good.
I need you to take this out
to Radzinsky at grid 3-3-4.
He'll give you something in return.
I want you to bring it back to me
with no questions asked.
Understood?
We're not supposed to be in 3-3-4.
Isn't that hostile territory?
Welcome to the circle of trust.
Stop right there!
What are you doing here?
I was expecting Lafleur.
Lafleur's busy.
Horace sent me instead.
- I'm in the circle of trust.
- Get out.
I'm supposed to give you this.
And he said
you had something for me.
What happened to him?
He had an accident.
- What kind of accident?
- He fell into a ditch.
Is that a bullet hole in his head?
- The ditch had a gun?
- It doesn't matter what happened
because knowing that is not your job.
Your job is to do what I tell you to.
Take him back to Horace now, Miles.
Okay...
So what really happened?
Subtitle:
www.sub-way.fr (1.00)
I need to see her.
Ma?
It's me.
Miles.
I'm sorry that...
I couldn't make it by sooner.
It's okay.
You're here now.
Why did you come, Miles?
I need you to tell me
why I'm this way...
How I do the things I do.
And I need to know why
you won't talk to me
about my father.
Because he never cared about us...
Never cared about you.
I need to know where he is.
- It doesn't matter where.
- It does matter.
- I have a right to know!
- He's dead.
Your father...
Kicked us out
when you were just a baby.
He didn't want anything
to do with us.
So the less you knew about him,
the better.
Why didn't you just tell me?
Because it was over.
Your dad has been dead
a long time.
Where's his body?
Somewhere you can never go.
Pierre, if it was caused
by the electromagnetism, we must know.
You wanna see it now?
He just got back.
I'll send him out with it
right away.
Did you bring the package?
"Package"?
You mean the corpse?
Yeah. Now I need you to bring it out
to Dr. Chang at the Orchid.
Listen, man. I'm security.
If you need somebody to drive the van,
can't someone from the motor pool do it?
If I wanted someone from the motor pool,
I would have asked them.
And since Lafleur decided to disappear,
you're all I've got.
So just bring it out to Dr. Chang,
and we'll all call it a day.
What the hell are you doing?!
That's my van!
Nah, I just signed it out.
Doesn't matter. It's mine.
- Well, where you going?
- The Orchid.
Me too. I made lunch
for the crew. Sandwiches.
Want one? Ham and cheese,
and I made my secret garlic mayo.
You'll wait for the next van.
We're going to the same place.
Why don't we carpool?
It'll help with global warming,
which hasn't happened yet,
so maybe we can prevent it.
Wait a sec.
Are you on some kind of secret mission?
Just get in.
How'd it go?
We gave him to the Others.
- Anyone see you?
- I don't think so.
Did James help?
Yes. Thank you so much
for sending him.
Of course.
I got here as soon as I could.
All the vans were out,
so I had to ru...
Where's Ben?
Did he...
- Then where is he?
- Roger, I'm so sorry.
I was gone for ten minutes.
I don't know.
What? You said he was dying.
How could he be gone?
What is she telling me,
that he just got up and walked out?
You're supposed to watch him!
- I know. Roger, if we just calm down-
- Don't tell me to calm down!
Somebody came and took my boy?!
I know. I am so sorry.
I'm going to security.
Well...
Here we go.
How do you spell "bounty hunter"?
What are you doing,
writing your memoirs?
It's personal.
Dude...
Did you just... You know?
What?
You know.
It stinks. Did you...
Well, it wasn't me.
So roll down your window.
Nah, man,
there's something foul in here.
- It's coming from back there.
- Maybe it's your famous garlic mayo.
That's not possible.
Okay, maybe it is possible.
Pull over. I gotta check.
Forget it.
You're imagining things.
I gotta check. If those sandwiches
are bad, people could get sick.
Will you pull over?!
There's a body bag back here.
There's a body in it.
That's traditionally
what you put in a body bag.
Who is he? What happened?
Don't worry about it
and don't tell anybody you saw him.
Dude, what happened to him?
His name's Alvarez.
He was digging a hole and thinking
about some chick named Andr?a.
Then he felt this sharp pain
in his mouth,
which turned out to be
a filling from his tooth
being yanked right out
of its socket and...
Blowing through his brain.
Then he was dead.
How does a filling get blown
through someone's head?
Got me. Can we go now?
How do you know all this?
Because...
- I know.
- How do you know what he was thinking?
I just know.
You can talk to dead people.
Can we please just go?
Don't worry, dude.
Your secret's safe with me.
You wanna know why?
- No.
- 'cause I can talk to 'em, too.
If you don't mind, Mr. Gray,
can you tell me what happened to him?
Last labor day weekend,
drunk driver ran the light.
That was that.
Where is your son buried?
We cremated him, scattered the ashes
on the football field at school.
For what I do,
it's much better if there's a body.
But your ad said you could communicate
with the dead anytime, anywhere.
- I know what my ad says, but...
- Please.
I just want you to ask him...
Did he know that I loved him?
It's gonna cost extra.
Of course.
Thank you.
Okay, now...
Please give me your hands.
I want you to concentrate on Russell.
Just get a picture of him in your head.
Can you do that?
Yeah. Okay.
Did it work?
Your son says
he knew that you loved him.
He always knew.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Excuse me.
Miles Straume?
- Yeah.
- Hi. My name's Naomi Dorrit.
My employer's been following
your work for some time now,
and he's interested in retaining
your rather unique services.
There's a restaurant
not too far from here.
Would you like to hear
what I have to say?
Yeah. Absolutely.
Hi, Roger.
You okay?
Let me see...
Well, my son got shot
and now he's disappeared, so...
I think I'm pretty far from okay.
You know, I'm sure...
Things are gonna work out.
Well,
thanks for the pep talk.
I just have a feeling
he's gonna be okay.
What do you mean, a feeling?
I just don't think
that you should give up hope.
Do you know something?
- Do you know what happened to my son?
- No, I don't.
Wait a minute.
Why are you so interested in my kid?
I'm sorry I came over here,
I was just trying to help.
You're trying to help, huh?
You wanna help, Kate?
Well, why don't you just mind
your own business?
I don't know
why you just won't admit it.
You can trust me.
I talk to lots of dead people.
So you have conversations with them,
like they're your pals?
Sure, all the time.
Sometimes we even play chess.
You actually see them?
- Of course. Why wouldn't I?
- Because that's not how it works.
You wouldn't know ow it works
unless you can do it.
What I can do has nothing to do
with chatting with ghosts, you nitwit.
It's a feeling,
a sense.
When somebody's dead,
their brain stops functioning,
which means there's no more talking.
There's just who they were
and whatever they knew before they died.
That's how it works for me.
Great. I'm happy for you.
You're just jealous
my powers are better than yours.
We're here.
Now shut the hell up
and deliver your damn sandwiches.
What's he doing here?
He came to deliver lunch
to the work crew.
Lunch?
Your instructions were to come alone.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone about the body.
He knows?
I'm sorry, sir. He was rooting around
in the back, and he saw it.
Dude.
- I can keep a secret.
- Well, you'd better...
Hurley, 'cause if you think
working in the kitchen is bad
I like the kitchen.
Well, how do you feel
about polar bear feces?
Because if you breathe one word of this,
I'll have you shipped to Hydra island
so you can weigh turds
for their ridiculous experiments.
Gross.
You two!
Get the package inside.
And you?
Stay here till I get back.
You think you can handle that?
Yes, sir.
Dude, that guy's a total douche.
You are not qualified...
That douche is my dad.
You did say
you were taking me out to dinner.
No, I said
I was taking you to a restaurant.
You wanna tell me what's back here,
sweetheart?
Your audition.
Look,
whatever you got going on here,
this isn't really my thing.
From what I understand, if the price
is right, this is exactly your thing.
So what can you tell me
about this man?
His name's Felix.
He was...
On his way
to deliver something to, uh...
A guy named... Widmore.
Deliver what?
A bunch of papers,
photos, pictures...
of...
Empty graves.
A purchase order...
For an old airplane.
So...
Did I pass?
I'm leading an expedition
to an island,
and on the island is a man
that will be very difficult to find.
That's why I need you.
Need me for what?
This island has a number
of deceased individuals, residing on it,
and as this man is the one
responsible for their being deceased,
we believe they can supply invaluable
information as to his whereabouts.
As much as hunting down
a mass murderer sounds really safe,
uh, I'm... I'm gonna pass.
Thanks for the audition.
My employer is willing
to pay you $1.6 million.
When do we leave?
- So anyway...
- I don't want to talk about it.
Are you kidding me?
How weird is it that your dad is
that dude from all those movies?
Only, he was called Marvin Kandle.
Was that a stage name?
What part of "I don't want to talk
about it" isn't sinking in?
Well, if you didn't want
to talk about it, why'd you tell me?
How long have you known
he was your dad?
The third day we were here,
I was on line at the cafeteria,
and my mother got in line behind me.
That was my first clue.
But all those Dharma dudes end up dead.
Don't you wanna...
- Save him?
- I can't save him.
They're gonna get kill
no matter what I do, so why bother?
I need you to take me to
Radzinsky at the work site immediately.
You... Hurley, you say a word...
Polar bear poop. Got it.
- What happened to the body?
- What body?
This room is on my rounds.
What are you doing here?
I figured I'd cover for ya.
I heard what happened to your son.
Which part?
That he got shot
or that someone
kidnapped him from the infirmary?
- Then what are you doing here at work?
- What else am I gonna do?
Sit around and pray that
those idiots are gonna find my boy?
So you can get outta here.
You came in here a couple days ago
with that woman Kate, right?
- Yeah.
- You know her at all?
Why?
'cause she's got some...
kinda weird thing for my kid.
First, she shows up
at the infirmary and gave him blood.
But then when he goes missing,
she comes to me and she says,
"Don't worry.
He's gonna be okay."
I'm gonna tell you somethin', man.
I'm beginning to think that
she's got something to do with this.
I should go to Horace,
report her.
What do you think?
I think, Roger, that, uh,
that you've had a hell of a day,
and that's...
Given you a very good excuse
to go out and get drunk.
Maybe that's put some...
some crazy ideas into your head.
I know that woman... Kate.
She's my friend, and she would never
do anything to hurt your son.
Sure.
So I'm new here, Dr. Chang.
What is it exactly you do at the Orchid?
It's classified.
Oh, really? You can't tell anyone?
Not even your wife?
No.
What about your kids?
I have a 3-months son,
so, no, I haven't told him.
3 months? Wow! Congrats.
- What's his name?
- Miles.
Small world.
That's your name, too. Right, Miles?
Yeah.
So are you a fan of jazz, Dr. Chang?
Like Miles Davis?
My wife is.
I like country.
So you two have been here for three
years now. Must be pretty tight, huh?
Dr. Chang and I... don't exactly
travel in the same circles.
I wasn't aware there were circles.
Great. We should all...
get together for a beer sometime.
How awesome would that be?
Stop here.
You don't need to wait.
I'll get a ride back with Radzinsky.
Dude, what is this place?
And what's up with all the secrecy?
Don't know. Don't care.
Hey, Glenn!
What's the serial number
that goes on the hatch lid?
4, 8...
15...
16...
23...
- Hold on a minute. It's smudged.
- 42.
42.
- How the hell did you know that?
- 'cause
they're building our hatch.
What hatch?
The one that crashed our plane.
Hey, Miles.
Do I know you?
My name's Bram.
You owe me a fish taco.
Sorry about that,
but your apartment's being watched,
and we had to try our best to talk you
out of working for Charles Widmore.
I have no idea who that is.
He's the man who chartered the boat
you'll be getting on next week.
And, my friend,
you do not wanna get on that boat.
Do you know what lies
in the shadow of the statue?
No, can't say that I do.
Then you're not ready
to go to that island.
But if you come with us,
all those things you've spent your life
trying to find out?
You'll know.
You'll know who you are, Miles,
why it is you have a gift,
and most of all,
you'll know about your father.
I don't know where you've been getting
your intel,
but I stopped caring about my father
a long time ago.
What I do care about is money.
So I'll tell you what.
You want me to pass
on going to the island?
It's gonna cost you double
what they offered: 3.2 million.
We're not paying you anything.
But all the money in the world
isn't gonna fill
that empty hole inside you.
That's sad, isn't it?
Toss him!
- You're playing for the wrong team.
- Yeah? What team are you on?
The one that's gonna win.
That hatch they're building?
There's gonna be an accident.
They'll have to build a computer
with a button you have to push
so the world doesn't end.
So your dad...
Is he around...
You know, when we came from?
The future?
- Then  this is awesome for you, huh?
- How is it awesome?
Because you get to hang out with him,
get to know him better and stuff.
And don't thank me, but he was
totally down for that beer, dude.
And maybe he'll let you hold baby you,
or you can change your own diaper or...
Listen up, 'cause we're only gonna have
this conversation once.
I don't wanna hang out with my dad.
I don't wanna know him better
and "stuff."
Why not? Did he beat you up
when you were little?
He wasn't even around
when I was little, you dimwit!
I never knew him until now.
Why am I telling you this?
You're in pain,
you need to let it out.
I'm not in pain!
It doesn't matter.
My father is dead. He's gone.
He never cared about me,
and nothing I can do
- will ever change that.
- But he's not gone.
We just dropped him off.
You wanna get into my business?
- Let's get into yours!
- Give it back to me.
- Let's read your diary!
- It's personal!
What's going on in that piece
of granite you call a head?
- Give it back!
- "Exterior: Hoth.
"A little spy robot thingy
zips through the atmosphere
"and crashes
into the snowy planet below.
"That's when Chewbacca shows up
"and blasts it away
with his crossbow laser.
"He shakes his fury fist
in the sky in triumph.
"Chewbacca: - Raaar..."
It's "furry."
"Furry fist."
- I need to spell-check it.
- What the hell is this?
I'm writing Empire Strikes Back.
- I'm sorry. What?
- It's 1977, right?
So Stars Wars just came out.
And pretty soon, George Lucas
is gonna be looking for a sequel.
I've seen Empire like, 200 times,
so I figured
I'd make life easier
and send him the script.
With a couple improvements.
That has gotta be
the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
Yeah?
Well, at least I'm not scared
to talk to my own dad.
- James. You're back.
- Barely.
You ever felt like the little Dutch boy
with your finger in the...
What's going on?
Ben's father thinks that Kate
had something to do
with his son going missing.
Why the hell would he think that?
Because she talked to him,
tried to make him feel better.
- Her heart was in the right place.
- Yeah, well, where was her head?
I had a talk with Roger.
He won't say anything to anyone for now.
I just wanted you to know.
Yeah? Well...
Thanks for filling me in, doc.
No problem.
Hey, boss.
We got a development.
You better come to the office.
I've been running around
the jungle all day,
so whatever developments you got
can wait.
I know who took the kid.
Yeah? Who's that?
You.
Got a perfectly good explanation
for what you saw on that tape.
I sure as hell hope so.
- You talk to Horace yet?
- No.
I thought that after 3 years
of working together,
I'd give you
the benefit of the doubt...
Get some rope.
Mr. Gray?
I hope you don't mind.
Your gate was open.
Mr. Straume.
Of course. No problem.
What, what brings you by?
Well, sir...
I'm about to go on a boat trip
for a while,
and...
I wanted to give this back to you.
I lied to you,
Mr. Gray.
I wasn't able to talk to your son.
Why are you telling me this?
You could have just let me
go on believing what you said.
That wouldn't have been fair
to your son.
I'm sorry?
If you needed your son
to know that you loved him,
you should've told him
when he was still alive.
Sorry I said you were afraid
to talk toour dad, dude.
Don't worry about it.
I used to hate my dad, too.
- Yeah?
- He left when I was 10.
But the best thing I ever did
was give him a second chance.
We got to be the best of friends,
and although I may never see him again,
I miss him.
And I know he feels the same.
My dad didn't leave when I was 10.
I was a baby.
I never knew him.
And I don't want to.
It's not happening.
That was Luke's attitude, too.
- What?
- In Empire,
Luke found out Wader was his father,
but instead of putting away
his lightsaber and talking about it,
he overreacted
and got his hand cut off.
I mean, they worked it out eventually,
but at what cost?
Another Death Star was destroyed,
Boba Fett got eaten by the Sarlacc,
and we got the Ewoks.
It all could've been avoided
if they'd just,
you know, communicated.
And let's face it.
The Ewoks sucked, dude.
Miles? I need you.
You do?
Sub's here from H.Q.
I need your help bringing them in.
- Sure. New recruits?
- No, scientists from Ann Arbor.
Get your van
and let's get to the dock.
- Can I get a hand with this?
- Yeah, sure.
Hey, Miles.
Long time no see.