* going out tonight, I'm feeling all right
* going to let it all hang out
* wanna make some
noise, even raise my voice
* yeah, I wanna scream and shout
Morning, Sheldon.  come dance with me.
No.
Why not?
Penny, while I subscribe
to the "many worlds" theory
Which pots the existence of
an infinite number of Sheldons
In an infinite number of universes, I
assure you that in none of them am I dancing.
Are you fun in any of them?
The math would suggest that in a
few I'm a clown made of candy.
But I don't dance.
Alright, want some french toast?
It's oatmeal day.
Tell you what, next french
toast day,I?ll make you oatmeal.
Dear lord, are you still going
to be here on french toast day?
Morning.
Look, Leonard, Penny made french toast.
Sorry, I haven't given
her your schedule yet.
It's an ical download.  she
can put it right in her phone.
And I thought we agreed that you'd have
your conjugal visits in her apartment.
We did, but there were
extenuating circumstances.
I see.  did her abysmal housekeeping
skills filly trump her perkiness?
No, her bed kind of... broke.
That doesn't seem likely.
Her bed's of sturdy construction.
Even the addition of a second normal size
human being wouldn't cause a structural failure,
Much less a homunculus such as yourself.
A homunculus?
Perfectly folded miniature human being.
Oh, you're my little homunculus.
- don't do that.
- sorry.
Okay, who wants syrup and
who wants cinnamon sugar?
I want oatmeal.
Yes, well, I want a boyfriend whose
roommate isn't a giant pain in the ass.
'm sure that will happen soon enough.
But in the meantime, I still want oatmeal.
You know what, I give
up.  he's impossible.
I can't be impossible exist.
I believe what you meant to say
is, "I get up, he's improbable. "
Sheldon, you really need to find a
better way of dealing with Penny.
What am I supposed to do--
eat french toast on a monday?
Now, that would be impossible.
I'm just saying, you can catch more
flies with honey than with vinegar.
You can catch even more flies
with manure.  what's your point?
It's a...
Yes, that does smell good.
Too bad it's monday.
-=http://sfile. ydy. com=-
proudly presents
sync:????????????
the big bang
theory season03 episode03
Okay, Kim the night manager
went on maternity leave,
And her husband's name is Sandy, right?
So get this-- her replacement is a woman
named Sandy whose husband's name is Kim.
I know.  what are the odds?
Easily calculable.  we begin by identifying
a set of married couples with unisex names.
We then eliminate those
unqualified for restaurant work--
The aged, the imprisoned and the
limbless, for example look at...
Sheldon-- it's an amazing
coincidence.  can we leave it at that?
I'm sorry.
Ooh, Penny, it's just if the cheese cake factory
is run by witches.
Sheldon, it's as if you
don't think I'll punch you.
Come on,you guys, let it go.
Fine, whatever.
Are you finished?
Well, thank you.  how thoughtful.
Would you like a chocolate?
Um, yeah, sure.
Thanks.
What was that?
You said be nice to Penny.
I believe offering chocolate to someone
falls within the definition of nice.
It does.  but in my experience, you don't.
There are more things in
heaven and earth, Horatio,
Than are dreamt of in your philosophy
Now that's you obnoxious
and insufferable.
What's going on, day dwellers?
Oh, man, did the kiss army
repeal "don't ask, don't tell"?
No.  Raj and I are going to a goth club in
Hollywood to hang with the night people.
Anybody want to come along?
Oh, wow, you're actually
going out like that?
No, no.  I'm going out like this...
Howard, what did you do?
They're called tattoo sleeves. look.
I got them online.
Raj got a set, too.
Fantastic, right?
Put them on, have hot sex with some
freaky girl with her business pierced,
Take them off, and I can still
be buried in a Jewish cemetery.
You know, I've always wanted
to go to a goth nightclub.
- Really?
- Bazinga!
None of you ever see my
practical jokes coming, do you?
Okay, how about you two? Look, I've
got some extra tat sleeves.
Why are you carrying extras?
In case I snag one on
someone's nipple ring.
Uh, yeah, I think we'll pass.
Oh, is the missus speaking
for the couple now?
In this case, you bet she is.
Yes, she's pushy, and yes, he's
whipped, but that's not the expression.
Come on, I want to stop at Walgreens
and pick up some more eyeliner.
They're gonna get beaten up at that club.
They're gonna get
beaten up at Walgreens.
Oh, sorry, Sheldon.  I
almost sat in your spot.
Did you? I didn't
notice.  have a chocolate.
Thank you.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I think we're fitting in quite nicely.
It'd help if you weren't
drinking light beer.
What's so gothic about
vodka and cranberry juice?
Hello? it looks like blood.
Did you even read the "wiki how"
link I sent you on being goth?
No, I'm behind on my wiki-reading.
I'm kind of on a John
Grisham kick right now.
What?
I finished reading the pelican brief
And loved it so much, I
dived right into the client.
He was a lawyer himself, so his novels
are accurate as well as entertaining.
Just remember we are lost
boys, children of the night.
Great.  lost boys, children
of the night.  got it.
Can you pass the chex mix, please?
Thank you.
We are lost boys.
Good for you.
I'm actually much more lost than he is.
- Nice ink.
- Thanks.
Can we buy you ladies a drink?
Two light beers.
Light beers. Well, wiki-how about that.
- What?s your names?
- I?m Howard.
- Raj.  I?m Bethany.
Nice to meet you, Bethany.
Yes, very nice.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- I?m Sarah.  Not that anyone cares.
Do either of you ladies enjoy
the novels of John Grisham?
What's this cartoon called again?
Demon samurai.
It?s not a cartoon.  It's anime.
Anime.  you know, I knew a girl
in high school named Anna May.
Anna May Fletcher.
She was born with one nostril.
Then she had this bad nose job
and basically wound up with three.
You're here a lot now.
Oh, am I talking too
much? I?m sorry.  zip.
Thank you.  Chocolate?
Yes, please.
Hey, Kim.  Yeah, I...
You know what, hold on.  Let
me take this in the hall.
You'll never guess who they
got to replace you at work.
Okay ,I know what you're doing.
Really?
Yes, you're using chocolates as positive reinforcement
for what you consider correct behavior.
Very good.
- Chocolate?
- No, I don't want any chocolate!
Sheldon, you can't train
my girlfriend like a lab rat.
Actually, it turns out I can.
Well, you shouldn't.
There's just no pleasing
you, is there, Leonard?
You weren't happy with my previous
approach to dealing with her,
So I decided to employ operant
conditioning techniques,
Building on the works of
Thorndike and B.F.Skinner.
By this time next week, I believe I
can have her jumping out of a pool,
Balancing a beach ball on her nose.
No, this has to stop now.
I'm not suggesting we really
make her jump out of a pool.
I thought the "bazinga" was implied.
We're just tweaking her personality.
- Sanding off the rough edges, if you will.
- No.  You?re not sanding Penny.
Are you saying that I am
forbidden from applying a harmless,
Scientifically valid protocol
this will make our lives better?
Yes.  You?re forbidden.
Bad Leonard.
So, what do you guys do?
Oh, you know, goth stuff.
goth magazines, goth music.
Goth food.
What's goth food?
Blackened salmon?
No, I meant what do you do for jobs?
- Oh, we're scientists.
- Yeah, you know, the dark sciences.
What are the dark sciences?
Well, I am an astrophysicist, and a
lot of that takes place at night.
When there are vampires and
miscellaneous under out and about.
Oy vay.
That sounds really cool.
Does it? okay. if you like space stuff,
I design components for the international
space station, which is in space.
Where, as I'm sure you
know, no one can hear you scream.
So, what do you gals do?
- I work at the gap.
- really?
How about that? I've been to the gap.
I've been there, as well.
I like your t-shirts
with the little pocket.
I work there, too.  Not that anyone cares.
You know, this place is boring.
Yeah, why don't we go somewhere
else and have some fun?
- Okay.
- Sure, we like fun.
- We are fun people.
- Dark and fun.
Come on.  I know a
place you'll really dig.
- Did you bring the black condoms?
- In my fanny pack.
Let's go.
Are you happy now?
Not particularly.
My god, she didn't!
What could she possibly be
talking about for so long?
Obviously, waitressing at the cheese cake
factory is a complex socioeconomic activity
That requires a great deal
of analysis and planning.
"bazinga. "
You know, using positive
reinforcement techniques,
I could train that behavior
out of her in a week.
No.
If you let me use negative reinforcement, I
can get it done before we go to bed.
You're not squirting
her in the face with water.
No, of course not.
We're talking very mild electric shocks.
No tissue damage whatsoever.
Forget it.
Oh, come on. You can't tell me
That you're not intrigued out the
possibility of building a better girlfriend.
I'm not.
Well, and Penny's qualities, both good
and bad, are what make her what she is.
You mean, like that
high-pitched, irritating laugh?
Yes.
You wouldn't prefer a throaty chuckle?
You're not changing how Penny laughs.
No, that would be incongruous.
I was going to lower the whole
voice to a more pleasing register.
Sorry, guys.  that girl is freaky.
Come again?
- Freaky.
- Freaky?
Yeah ,freaky.
Have a chocolate.
Thank you.
Are you seriously going to deface your body just
for the possibility you could have cheap sex
With a strange girl you met in a bar?
Yeah!
What is your mother going to say?
She's not going to see it.
She takes my temperature orally now.
What are you going to get, Howard?
Well, I can't really decide
between a screaming devil,
This mean little
skull, or Kermit the frog.
- Kermit the frog?
- You know.  I?m on Howard?s butt.
Get the mean little skull, and
I'll see if I can make him smile.
Yeah, I'd like the mean
little skull, please.
What are you going to get, Raj?
With my luck, hepatitis.
Okay, here we go.
That's just rubbing alcohol.
I know, but it was cold.
I'm putting on the stencil.
What comes after the stencil?
This.
Okay, that's it.  No
needle.  No pain.  No tattoo.
What's the big deal?
You?ve done this before.
No, I haven't.  Look.
I'm sorry.  I?m a fraud.  He?s a fraud.
We're both frauds.
- Yeah, I think I covered that.
- But I was summing up.
We're not goth.
We're just... guys.
Very, very smart guys.
- So you were totally scamming us?
- Yes.
And I wouldn't blame you if you walked out
of here and never wanted to see us again.
Unless, of course, our bold honesty has
suddenly made us attractive, huh? Anything?
I'm leaving.
I'm leaving, too.  Not that anyone cares.
When we tell this story, let's
end it differently.
What are you thinking?
Maybe a big musical number?
Well, I?m going to make some
warm milk and then turn in.
I trust if you two are planning on
engaging in amorous activities,
You'll keep the decibel
level to a minimum.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
These are so good.
Unbelievable.
What?
I-I was just thinking we
should probably turn in, too.
Well, you know, my new bed got delivered.
If you come over and put it
together, you can stay at my place.
Really? That?s a lot of
work, and it's kind of late.
- Yeah, but if we stay there, we won't have to be quiet.
- Let?s go.
Interesting.
Sex works even better than
chocolate to modify behavior.
I wonder if anyone else
has stumbled onto that.
Okay, wait.  How about this?
We say there were four goth girls.
The two girls in the club had two friends.
I like it,I like it.
Did they smell good despite
their go-like nature?
What's that got to do with the story?
Engaging my olfactory sense
helps make it real for me.
Fine, they smelled good.
Oh, they did. Like jasmine and honeysuckle
Whatever.
And then they held hands and did
a sexy, demonic hokey pokey for us.
No, no. Look, let me just say
my story all the way through
And then you can say
yours, and then we'll pick.
- I?m sorry.  Go on.
- Okay.
We got tattoos, and
then the four girls took us to their place.
But we don't have tattoos.  what if
someone asks to see our tattoos?
We say they're in a very intimate area.
Oh, we're bad boys, aren't we?
Right, right.
So, we go back to their place and then
the six of us end up in a hot tub.
But we just got tattoos.  Wouldn?t we be
concerned about bacterial infection?
True.  Okay.  Forget the hot tub.
The point is, we each had a
menage with sexy goth girls.
What a great night.
Yeah.
Hey, want to try a country
bar tomorrow night?
Maybe we'll get lucky
with some sexy cowgirls.
Could happen.
I wonder how they smell.
-=http://sfile. ydy. com=-
proudly presents
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org