Seems like forever,
since the four of us have
been out to eat, you know?
Just the guys.
Oh, God! Yes, we get it.
You have a girlfriend now.
A little jealous, are we?
No, I'm not jealous.
All right, I'd kill a hobo
if it'll get me laid.
Now, can we order?
Oh, dear Lord,
they re-did the menu.
So what?
It's the same food.
Oh, is it?
Look at this.
General Tso's Chicken
is no longer listed
under "specialties."
It's now under "chicken."
So?
Yes, General Tso.
Not "Tso," the chicken,
"so" the question.
So?
So, why is it no longer
a specialty?
Did the chef
lose confidence
in the dish or himself?
And look over here.
"Shrimp in mobster sauce."
What is "mobster sauce"?
It's obviously a typo.
Perhaps. Or perhaps
this restaurant's
now a front for
organized crime.
For all we know,
the mobster sauce
contains actual chunks
of deceased mobsters.
No, no, no, no--
I think it just means
it's the kind of sauce
that mobsters like.
It doesn't mean any of that!
It's a typo.
You know what?
Let's just get a pizza.
Good idea.
We'll go to Corleone's.
Sure, no mobsters there.
You know, the more
I think about it,
the mobster sauce
couldn't possibly contain
chunks of mobster.
And why is that?
It was listed
under "seafood."
What if they were mobsters
who slept with the fishes?
(laughing)
Leonard, are we having a serious
conversation or not?
LEONARD:
What the...?
The TV is gone.
So are our laptops.
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
It's all right.
They didn't take my comic books.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
Big Bang Theory 3x13
The Bozeman Reaction
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com ---
They took our TV,
two laptops,
four external hard-drives,
our PS2, our PS3,
our X-Box,
our X-Box 360,
our classic Nintendo,
our Super Nintendo,
our Nintendo 64 and our Wii.
We like games.
Right, games.
They took Halo 1,
Halo 2, Halo 3,
Call of Duty 1,
Call of Duty 2,
Call of Duty 3,
Rock Band, Rock Band 2,
Final Fantasy 1 thru 9,
The Legend of Zelda,
The Legend
of Zelda: Ocarina of Time,
The Legend of Zelda:
Twilight Princess,
Super Mario Brothers,
Super Mario Galaxy,
Mario and Sonic
at the Winter Olympics...
...and Ms. Pacman.
Assorted video games.
When does the CSI
team get here?
What?
In anticipation
of their arrival,
I've bagged some evidence.
One of the thieves
had the audacity
to quench his thirst
while ransacking our home.
You should be able to pull
some good prints off this.
And now,
here are my prints
so you can rule me out
as a suspect.
What about me?
I'm sorry, Leonard.
It's too early to discount
the possibility of this
being an inside job.
Would I be completely
out of line to ask you
to shoot him?
I'd be happy to put him
under a 72-hour
psychiatric hold.
I'm not crazy.
My mother had me tested.
We're done here.
Call this number, and we'll fax
you a copy of the report
so you can submit it
to your insurance company.
I-I'm sorry.
That's the end
of your inquiry?
Do you have any more information
that might be relevant?
Oh, my goodness.
Where do I begin? For instance--
my laptop contained
four out of the five
gedankenexperiments
necessary for a cogent
restatement
of the quantum
measurement problem.
How is that going to help them?
Well, they could monitor
scientific publications
and see if anyone posts such
a cogent restatement in the next
couple of months. If so,
the authors are most likely
in possession
of my stolen laptop.
Good night, fellas.
Come on, Bochco.
(groans)
What are we
supposed to do now?
The only thing we can do.
Watch TV on our phones
until the criminals return
and bludgeon us
to death in our sleep.
Does that mean you've ruled
me out as a suspect?
Oh, how I wish I could.
(mumbles)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(lock clicks, doorknob rattles)
(sigh of relief)
(grunting)
(sighs)
I do not have to urinate.
I am the master
of my own bladder.
Drat.
I can't believe it.
If I hadn't been
working the dinner shift,
I would've run
right into the robbers.
Hey, there's no reason
for you to be scared.
I'm not scared.
I would've gone all Nebraska
on their asses.
(three knocks)
SHELDON:
Leonard and Penny.
(three knocks)
Leonard
and Penny.
(three knocks)
Leonard and Penny.
Hand me the bat.
We just had a major crime
in the building,
and you open the door
without asking who it is?
It won't happen again.
What's up?
Nothing.
I just wanted to see
if you were both okay.
We're fine, Sheldon.
All right, then.
Good night.
That was weird,
even for him.
Mm-hmm.
(three knocks)
Leonard and Penny.
Leonard
and Penny.
(three knocks)
Leonard and Penny.
Who is it?
Sheldon.
Sheldon Cooper.
Yes?
May I come in?
Yeah.
I see you're drinking wine.
Yes, we are.
And we're about to go to bed.
Uh-huh.
Sheldon, do you want
to sleep here tonight?
Oh, as small as Leonard is,
I don't think the two of you'd
be comfortable on the couch.
What do you want?
It's not what I want,
it's what evolution wants.
Human beings are primates.
Primates have evolved
to live in groups,
both for protection
and support.
But you don't like other people.
I do tonight.
It's scary over there.
It's getting scary here, too.
Um... three little kittens?
Three little pigs?
(groans)
God, I don't know.
Star Wars?
(timer dings)
Did we win?
Can we go to bed?
Good Lord-- I could not
have made this easier.
Hydrogen atom, H,
plus pigs minus pea-- Higgs.
Bow, General Zod trapped
in the Phantom Zone.
Bow-zone.
Pear. Tickle.
Pear-tickle.
Higgs Boson Particle.
How could you not get that?
He's right, Penny.
It's all there.
Sheldon, sweetie, I know
you're feeling insecure,
but we've really
got to go to sleep.
All right.
I'll take the first watch
and wake you at 0400.
Great. Good night.
Wait, wait--
what's 0400?
4:00 a.m.
That's, like,
in 45 minutes.
Just keep walking.
WOMAN (on TV):
It's quiet out there.
MAN (on TV):
Maybe a little too quiet.
Where are you going?
Just gonna take a look
around outside.
Bad idea.
No, Jim,
don't open the door!
Listen to her, Jim.
(door opening)
Don't worry.
There's no one out there.
(door slamming)
(woman screaming)
(three knocks)
SHELDON:
Leonard and Penny!
(three knocks)
Leonard
and Penny!
LEONARD (singsongy):
Who is it?
All right, we've got
a titanium dead bolt
and a reinforced jamb
controlled by a state-of-the-art
electronic access system.
What if they cut the power?
There's a 200-watt
uninterruptible
backup power supply.
What if someone steals my keys?
There are
independent voice
and fingerprint scanners.
What if someone kidnaps me,
forces me to record my voice,
and then cuts off my thumb?
I'll send them a
basket of muffins.
Now, inside, we've got
motion detectors,
infrared sensors, and cameras
connected to a server
running state-of-the-art
facial recognition software.
Where did you get
all this stuff?
Eh, I got a buddy over
at the Department of Defense.
He just gave it to you?
I'm sure he would have
if I had asked.
Ironically, their security
isn't all that good.
Raj, your car is blocking me...
(alarm blaring)
COMPUTER VOICE:
Intruder alert, intruder alert.
(screams)
Intruder alert.
What the hell?
Sorry, let me help you.
Wonderful
security system
if we're attacked
by a school of tuna.
Don't worry, the net's
going to be electrified.
You picture her on the floor,
spasming uncontrollably.
Better.
SHELDON:
Sheldon's journal.
Security system in place.
However, sleep continues
to elude me.
I've seen the underbelly
of Pasadena...
this so-called City of Roses,
and it haunts me.
Ah, the injustice.
I lie here awake, tormented,
while out there evil lurks,
probably playing Donkey Kong
on my classic Nintendo.
(thud)
(whimpers)
Oh, dear.
(gasps)
I am the master
of my own bladder.
(passing car horn honks)
(three knocks)
Leonard and Penny.
Leonard
and Penny.
(three knocks)
Leonard and Penny.
Oh, my...
God, Sheldon.
What the hell are you
doing out there?
I heard a noise.
It was us.
We knocked over a lamp.
Why would you
knock over a lamp?
We were going to have...
He doesn't need
to know what we were doing,
Leonard.
Oh.
No, she's right, I don't need
to know what you were doing.
Carry on.
What are you doing?
Use the door.
Good thinking.
Perhaps I'll check
the perimeter
and make
some warm milk.
Great, you do that.
Would you like me to bring you
some warm milk?
I'm lactose intolerant.
And you don't wish to alarm me
with any more loud noises.
Very thoughtful.
Warm milk, Penny?
No, thanks.
Fine.
Good night to you, sir.
Miss.
(door closes, Leonard groans)
Sorry about that.
Ugh, what can you do?
Here.
Intruder alert, intruder alert.
(alarm blaring)
(electricity arcing,
Sheldon screaming)
(alarm blaring)
(electricity buzzing)
Looks like Wolowitz got
the net electrified.
Sheldon, are
you okay?
I-I'm fine...
although I'm no longer
the master of my own bladder.
My new computer came
with Windows 7.
Windows 7 is much more user-
friendly than Windows Vista.
I don't like that.
Don't you think looking
for a new city to live in
is a bit of an overreaction?
Our apartment
was broken into,
our security system
tried to kill me,
and as a result,
I'm leaving Pasadena forever.
Tell me how that's overreacting.
Come on, Sheldon,
you can't move.
Don't you need
to stay in one place
so the mother ship can find you
when it returns?
(laughing)
Oh, if that were only true.
Unfortunately, as I'm earthbound
for the foreseeable future,
I need to find a location
that's more hospitable
than the mean streets
of Pasadena, like...
Enid, Oklahoma.
Low crime rate
and high-speed
Internet connectivity...
but no model train shops.
Sorry, Enid.
Is he quitting his job
at the university?
Oh, no, he's going
to telecommute.
Everybody's really
excited about it.
All right.
Boone, North Carolina.
"Every summer since 1952,
"Boone has hosted an outdoor
amphitheater portrayal
of the life and times
of its namesake, Dan'l Boone."
Sounds like something that would
attract the wrong crowd.
Penny, you're from Nebraska,
correct?
Born and raised.
It will take me a few
days to get settled.
After I do, I will e-mail
you detailed PDFs
containing diagrams
and instructions
that will guide you through
packing and shipping
the rest of my possessions
to Bozeman, Montana.
In the meantime,
please forward my mail.
Any place specific
or just the Bozeman,
Montana Loony Bin?
I sense you're making a joke,
but Bozeman does have a comedy
club called The Loony Bin,
so do not forward
my mail there.
Oh, come on.
So you were the victim
of a crime.
That's part of life.
When my great-grandfather
first came to this country,
he put all his
hopes and dreams
into this little
butcher shop he ran
on the Lower East Side
of New York.
You know what happened?
Every customer who walked
into that butcher shop
and asked
for a pound of liver,
(fingers snap)
got ripped off.
But...
those people moved on,
and so should you.
I am moving on.
I'm going to be a Bozite.
They call themselves "Bozites"?
They should. It's one
of the first things
I plan to bring up
upon arrival.
Sheldon, I can't
believe I'm saying this,
but I'm going to miss you.
Please,
Penny, as you know,
I'm not comfortable
with prolonged good-byes
and maudlin displays of emotion,
so I prepared
a short video.
SHELDON (on laptop):
Greetings.
As you know, I'm not comfortable
with prolonged good-byes
and maudlin
displays of emotion,
so I prepared
this short video.
The four of you are three
of my closest friends
and one treasured acquaintance.
Though I cannot state
categorically that my life
will be diminished
by not having you in it,
I am comfortable
if you choose to believe that.
Since you intend to remain
in this lawless
metropolitan area,
statistics suggest that
you will succumb to tragic
and gruesome ends
before we meet again.
Live long and prosper.
Sheldon, that's so...
You might want to lock
the door behind me.
This isn't Bozeman.
How the hell do I know
who's the friend
and who's the acquaintance?
(wind whistling outside)
That is a bracing cold,
an invigorating cold.
Lord, is it cold!
Help you with
your bags, sir?
Thank you, fellow Bozite.
And may I say, you are
the living embodiment of all
the promises made by our lovely
town's Chamber of Commerce.
Wait!
Excuse me!
(wind howling)
One ticket to Pasadena,
California, please.
(door unlocking, opening).
Hey, look who's back!
Interesting.
The acquaintance
is the first to greet me.
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com ---
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org