Oh, damn, they canceled my Visa.
(gasps)
Oh, yay, a new MasterCard!
Uh-oh.
What?
I was going to get my mail.
Okay.
Are... are you hoping
to get it telepathically?
I think you mean
telekinetically.
And no.
I just wasn't sure
of the proper protocol
now that you and Leonard
are no longer
having coitus.
God, can we please just say
"no longer seeing each other"?
Well, we could if it were true.
But as you live
in the same building,
you see each other all the time.
The variable which has changed
is the coitus.
Okay, here's the protocol:
you and I are still friends,
and you stop saying "coitus."
Good, good.
I'm glad we're
still friends.
Really?
Oh, yes. It was
a lot of work
to accommodate you
in my life.
I'd hate for that effort
to have been in vain.
Right.
Just to be clear,
do I have to stop
saying "coitus" with
everyone or just you?
Everyone.
Harsh terms.
But all right-- I'll just
substitute "intercourse."
Great.
Or "fornication."
Yeah. But that has
judgmental overtones,
so I'll hold that in reserve.
So, how you been?
Well, my existence
is a continuum,
so I've been what I am at each point
in the implied time period.
You're just coitusing
with me, aren't you?
Bazinga.
Mm-hmm.
How's Leonard doing?
He seems all right.
Although he does spend a
disturbing amount of time
looking at
photographs of you
and smelling the
pillow you slept on.
Oh, but now
that I think of it,
he asked me
not to tell you that.
I'll pretend
I didn't hear it.
I'd rather you pretend
I didn't say it.
I see you bought Mama Italia
marinara spaghetti sauce.
(laughs):
Yep.
That's the sauce
my mother uses.
She likes cooking Italian
because according to her,
that's what the Romans
made Jesus eat.
Interesting.
I'll have to have you over
for spaghetti some night.
I'm hungry now.
Oh. Um, okay.
Why don't you give me an hour
and come over?
Will you cut up hot dogs
into little chunks
and mix them in with the sauce?
I don't have hot dogs.
Oh, it's all right; I do.
Oh! You're in for what my mother
calls "a real Eye-talian treat""
Hey, where you been?
I was talking with Penny.
What's wrong with you?
You can't hang out
with your roommate's ex.
That's totally uncool.
No, it's fine.
I don't care.
I'm over it.
Yeah, he's over it; that's
why he's been whining all day
about trying to invent
that memory-wiper gizmo
from Men in Black.
Is he making any progress?
Because I'd like to erase
Ben Affleck as Daredevil.
So would Ben Affleck.
The point is, in a
situation like this
you got to pick sides.
You're either on Team Leonard
or Team Penny.
Which one picks last?
What?
Well, usually I'm on the team
that picks last.
Unless there's a kid
in a wheelchair.
Sheldon, I got you
your tangerine chicken.
I hope you're hungry.
Well, of course I'm hungry.
And as I have no plans to eat
with any other team,
I will consume
my tangerine chicken
with the appropriate gusto.
Mm, mm, mm!
Okay.
Just out of curiosity,
do we still have hot dogs?
I don't know. Why?
Just making dinner
conversation.
Go, Team Leonard!
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
The Big Bang Theory 3x20
The Spaghetti Catalyste
Original Air Date on May 3, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Oh, God,
this is good.
Let me ask you
a question.
Do you believe
you're going to go to hell
for eating sweet and sour pork?
Jews don't have hell.
We have acid reflux.
Do you want the last
dumpling, Sheldon?
Certainly.
It's not like I have to
moderate my food intake
because I'm planning on
eating again very shortly.
Mm, mm, mm!
So, you guys want
to do something tonight?
Nah, I can't.
I got to pick up my mom
from her water aerobics class.
18 overweight women
flapping their arm fat
in a swimming pool.
Looks like the manatee tank
at Sea World.
What about you, Raj?
Oh, there it is:
now that you don't
have a girlfriend,
you want to hang out
with me again.
I never stopped
hanging out with you.
Oh, please,
we all know
I'm the friend you call
when you have
no other options.
If we were the Justice League,
I'd be Aquaman.
I wish you were Aquaman.
Then I could send you to scoop
my mom out of the old lady tank.
Excuse me, I'm thirsty, so I'm
going to go to the refrigerator
and get myself
a refreshing beverage.
You know what? I'll just
spend the evening alone.
What, suddenly I'm not
good enough for you?
Ah...
I do so love beverages.
Now I think I'll take
my after-dinner walk.
Since when do you take
after-dinner walks?
Yeah, since when
do you take walks?
I read a study online
that walking after a meal
not only aids in digestion,
but increases serotonin,
and you know me,
if there's one thing I like
more than a refreshing beverage,
it's serotonin. Bye-bye.
Hold on.
I'll walk down with you.
Oh...
that's not necessary.
You can go first.
Or we could go together.
I can't think of
a reason why not.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Nope, no reason.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I've missed you.
All right, say hello
to your mother for me.
Okay.
What?
You said you were going
for a walk.
I didn't say outside.
So what, you're just gonna
walk up and down the stairs?
No, of course not.
That would be odd
and suspicious behavior.
WOMAN:
Here, Russell! Here, boy!
Which way are you going?
I parked my scooter
down the block.
I'm going the
other way. Bye.
Bye.
Actually, I'm this way.
Do I smell hot dogs?
No. I mean, I have
no idea what you smell.
I definitely
smell raw hot dog.
Perhaps you're getting
a brain tumor.
All right,
have a nice walk.
I shall.
Have a nice scoot.
You might want to stand back.
I'm sitting
on top of 13 horses here.
(horn beeps)
Oh. Hello, doggie.
(growling)
Nice doggie.
(barks, growls)
I bet you think
you smell hot dogs.
Look, a cat!
(barking)
SHELDON (knocking):
Penny?
(knocking)
Penny.
Here.
I had to trade the others
for my life.
(music playing over TV)
Hey, Leonard?
Yeah?
I haven't had sex in a year.
Where you going with this, Raj?
Don't flatter yourself, dude.
I want to go out
and meet a woman.
So, go.
Well, I need a wingman.
I don't want to come off
like a lonely loser.
And you think my presence
will help with that?
Well, I do.
Next to you,
I'll look like a catch.
I'm not going out
tonight, Raj.
All right.
Would you mind
if I went to your room
and downloaded
some Asian pornography?
Very much.
Doesn't have to be Asian.
Don't worry.
You'll meet a girl someday.
No, I won't.
Yes, you will,
and she'll be beautiful.
And kind and sexy and funny
and everything you ever wanted
in a woman.
You really think so?
I do, and you'll
fall hopelessly in love
and give her your heart.
And she'll take it and grind it
into pathetic, little pieces.
But we'll have sex first, right?
(exhales)
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
That's Eye-talian.
So, um, was Leonard okay
with you coming over?
Oh, yes.
In fact, he said,
"I'm fine. I don't care."
And he in no way
said it in a manner
which would lead one to believe
that he was covering up
feelings of anguish
and betrayal.
Well, good.
I'm also
pleased to report that
he's all cried out over you.
He's been crying?
Oh, I believe that
was something else
I wasn't supposed to mention.
Oh, God, I feel terrible.
Do you have
a stomachache, too?
No. Why, do you?
No.
Why did you ask
if I had one, too?
Just making polite
dinner conversation.
Your turn.
All right.
So, what's new in your life?
Well, my new shoes are
not made for running.
Have you been running?
No.
It's just a suspicion I have.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
I'm so glad you like it.
I do.
Leonard never cooks for me.
Well, maybe that's
'cause Leonard can't cook.
You can't cook
and you made me this.
Whatever.
Ooh, I'm gonna get the
cheesecake out of the fridge.
Oh, Lord, I'm in Jewish hell.
Look at this.
Do you think
she's really doing that
or is it PhotoShop?
I'm pretty sure
Martha Stewart never got naked
with a room full of big,
fat Japanese guys.
You don't know that.
Prison changes people.
Hey, where you been?
I told you, walking.
For an hour and a half?
I got lost.
How could you get lost?
Your phone has GPS.
Satellites are down.
Solar flares.
There are no solar flares
right now.
Yes, there are.
Dude, I'm an astrophysicist.
If there were solar flares,
I'd be all up in it.
I'm sorry. I misspoke.
What I meant to say was
my battery died.
What the hell
was that about?
I don't know.
Do you think this is
really Hillary Clinton
doing it with Oprah?
Oh, we really need
to get you a girl.
SHELDON (knocking):
Leonard.
(knocking)
Oh, just come in!
Thanks for seeing me
on such short notice.
What do you want, Sheldon?
Maybe this isn't a good time.
Tell me why you woke me up or I
swear to God I will kill you.
Do you really think
death threats
are an appropriate way
to begin this conversation?
Sometimes your lack
of social skills astonishes me.
What do you want?
You may want
to sit down.
I'm in bed!
Point taken.
You may want to sit up.
Sheldon!
I've been seeing Penny
behind your back.
Okay...
When you say "seeing Penny,"
what exactly does that mean?
We had dinner last night.
She made me spaghetti with
little hot dogs cut up in it.
Well, little hot dog.
I gave up the other five
hot dogs to a real dog.
A real, big dog.
A hell hound.
Tangential to the primary story.
How about I circle back to it?
Fine.
Why did you have dinner
with Penny?
I told you, she made spaghetti
with little hot dogs.
I like spaghetti
Then why did you have
Chinese food with us?
I didn't want to upset you.
Howard made it very clear
that my allegiance should be
to male comrades before women
who sell their bodies for money.
Is it possible he said,
"Bros before hos"?
Yes, but I rephrased it
to avoid offending the hos.
Sheldon, I don't care if you
want to be friends with Penny.
Oh. Well, so the emotional
turmoil that's been keeping me
from achieving REM sleep
was entirely unjustified?
Yes.
Well... then as my meemaw
would say,
"Looks like we butchered a pig,
but nobody wanted bacon."
I guess not.
And now, as promised,
the tangent.
Sheldon and the Hell Hound.
Or How I Lost My Hot Dogs.
Oh, um...
(clears throat)
I, I can come back.
D-don't be silly.
We're neighbors.
We're going to run
into each other.
May as well get used to it.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
You used to it yet?
Nope.
Me neither.
Oh, Sheldon seemed tthink
that I would be upset
about you hanging out with him.
But I just want you
to know it's fine.
Oh, oh, good, because,
um, his mother called me.
His mother?
Yeah, she wants me
to take him shopping
for sheets and towels.
I was going to do that.
Oh, well, then you...
you do it.
No, I don't want to do it.
You can do it.
Okay, you can take him
for shoes.
I just took him for shoes.
Well, all I know is
he says they hurt his feet.
Fine. I'll take him
for shoes next Saturday.
Oh, no, no, no--
a bunch of us from work
are going to Disneyland
next Saturday
and Sheldon
wants to come.
You're taking him to Disneyland?
Well, he heard me
making plans on the phone.
Was I going to say "no"?
All right.
But let me know if you're going
to stuff him with junk food.
I don't want to bring home
a nice dinner for him
and see it go to waste.
We're going to Disneyland.
He's going to eat junk food.
All I'm saying is
give me a heads-up.
Okay, whatever.
And don't let him go
on Space Mountain after he eats.
He'll say he can handle it,
but I promise
you'll end up with churro puke
on your shoes.
All right, got it.
Is there anything else?
Yeah, don't let
Goofy near him.
He'll have nightmares
and I'll have to deal with it.
What's the problem with Goofy?
Wish I knew.
He's fine with Pluto.
Hey, do you think the elastic
woman in The Incredibles
needs to use
birth control
or can she just
be a diaphra?
Well, that's it.
We're officially out
of things to talk about.
We're home.
It's 10:00.
Where have you been?
SHELDON:
We stayed
for the California
Adventure water show.
It was pure Disney magic.
I was going to see that
with him.
How was I supposed
to know that?
It's all right.
I'll see it again with you.
And I have food here.
You said you were ing to call.
I know, I know.
I can still eat.
No, you already threw up once.
Go put on your PJs
and brush your teeth.
Okay, but just don't fight
Wee not fighting.
Just go.
Aren't you going to thank Penny
for taki you to Disneyland?
Thank you, Penny.
You're welcome, sweetie.
Want a cup of coffee?
Oh, um, I should
probably get going.
Come on. It's just
a cup of coffee.
(whispering)
Uh, yeah, the whole thing seems
a little twisted to me, too.
What am I smelling?
Sheldon's churro
on my shoes.
He's such an angel
when he's asleep.
LEONARD:
Yeah.
Shame he has to wake up.
I think we can do it.
Smother Sheldon
in his sleep?
Wouldn't that be wrong?
No, be friends.
You and me.
Oh. Sure.
Absolutely.
Good. I'm glad.
Here's aidea.
I'm just throwing it out tre:
friends who have sex.
Good night, Leonard.
Kidding.
Just a couple of friends
goofin' around.
No, Goofy, no.
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org