So two years later,
there's a knock on the door.
Guy opens it, and there on his porch
is the snail
who says, "What the heck
was all that about?"
(both laughing)
I don't really get it.
Well, see, it took two
years for the snail ...
Not important.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Where do you think
this is going?
To be honest, I was hoping
at least second base.
You're so funny.
You're like
a stand-up comedian.
A Jewish stand-up comedian,
that'd be new.
Actually, I think a lot
of them are Jewish.
No, I was just...
Never mind.
Look, Howard, this is our third date.
We both know what that means.
We do?
Sex.
You're kidding.
But I need to know
whether you're looking
for a relationship
or a one-night stand.
Okay, just to be clear:
there's only one
correct answer, right?
It's not like "chicken
or fish" on an airplane?
Maybe you need to think
about it a little.
You know,
it's not unheard of
for a one-night stand to turn
into a relationship.
Call me when you figure it out.
Three dates means sex?
Who knew?
Greetings, homies.
Homette.
Why are you back from
your date so early?
In romance,
as in show business,
always leave them wanting more.
What exactly
does that mean?
He struck out.
* Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state *
* Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! *
* The Ear began to cool
* The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools *
* We built the Wall
We built the pyramids *
* Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery *
* That all started
with a big bang *
* Bang! *
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Hey, did either
of you guys know
that three dates
with the same woman
is the threshold for sex?
Actually, I've never had three dates with
the same woman.
With Penny and me,
it took two years.
Now that I think about it,
that was three dates.
Okay, well, before you
and Penny hooked up,
did she ask for any
kind of commitment?
No, she was pretty clear about
wanting to keep
her options open.
I have something to announce,
but out of respect for convention,
I will wait for you
To finish your
current conversation.
What are you
talking about?
The cultural paradigm
in which people have sex
after three dates.
I see.
Now, are we talking "date,"
the social interaction,
or "date,"
the dried fruit?
Never mind,
what's your announcement?
Oh, good, my turn.
Well, this is very exciting
and I wanted you to be
among the first to know...
Hey, Cooper. I hear you’re going
To be on the radio
with Ira Flatow
from Science Friday next week.
Thank you, Kripke, for depriving
me of the opportunity
to share my news
with my friends.
My pleasure.
My "thank you"
was not sincere.
But "my pleasure" is.
Let me ask you
a question:  at what point
did National Public Radio
have to start scraping
the bottom of the barrel
for its guests
Don't answer.
It's rhetorical.
Why are you such a stupid head?
That is also rhetorical.
I'm sorry you had to hear that.
Are you really
going to be on NPR?
Yes, they're interviewing me
by phone from my office,
regarding the recent so-called
"discovery"
of magnetic monopoles
in spin-ices.
It's pledge week and they're
trying to goose the ratings
with a little controversy.
Very cool,
congratulations.
Thank you.
My mother is very excited.
She's convening her Bible study
group to listen in,
and then pray for my soul.
I was on the radio once.
I called in
to Fever 104 FM New Delhi
and was the fourth person
to say the phrase that pays:
"Fever 104, aajke naye
acchha sangeetka ghar."
That means: "Fever 104,
home of the really
good current music."
It's much catchier
in Hindi.
All right. These are
the talking points
for  NPR
interview tomorrow.
I need to make sure
that they're simple enough
for the less educated in
the audience to understand.
Howard, look this over
and tell me what’s unclear to you.
Excuse me, I have a master's degree
in engineering
from the Massachusetts Institute
of Technology.
It required the completion
of 144 units of grad work
and an original thesis.
Yes.
Look this over and tell me what's
unclear to you.
You know, when Sheldon
gives you homework,
you don't have to do it.
In fact, it's better
if you don't,
otherwise it makes
the rest of us look bad.
Hi, guys.
Hey. Hello.
Yo, Raj, talk to me.
I'm sorry,
just screwing with you.
Hey, Howard, why haven't
you called Bernadette?
Did she say something?
Yeah, she said she hasn't
heard from you in a week.
I thought you liked her?
I do, but she wants a commitment
and I'm not sure she's my type.
She agreed to go out
with you for free.
What more do you need?
Look, Bernadette is really nice.
I just always thought
when I finally settle down
into a relationship,
it would be with someone,
you know, different.
Different how?
Well, you know, more like
Men Fox from Transformers.
Or Katee Sackhoff
from Battlestar Galactica.
Are you high?
You'd have a better shot
with the three-breasted
Martian hooker
from Total Recall.
Okay, now you're just
being unrealistic.
Anyway, that movie
was like 20 years ago.
Imagine how saggy
those things would be.
Howard, you're going
to throw ay a great girl like Bernadette
because you're holding out
for some ridiculous fantasy?
Hey, just because you settled
doesn't mean I have to.
Excuse me,
I'm sitting here.
Hey, I did not
settle for Leonard.
I mean, obviously, he isn't the kind of guy
I usually go out with...
You know, physically.
Again, I'm right here.
My point is, I do not
judge a book by its cover.
I am interested
in the person underneath.
I am here, right?
You see me.
Hey, I'm interested
in what's inside people, too,
but why is it wrong to want
those insides wrapped up in,
say, the delicious caramel
that is Halle Berry?
Yes, you're delicious
caramel, too.
All right, you know what,
I will tell you
why it's wrong...
Excuse me, may I interject?
What?
Biologically speaking,
Howard is perfectly justified
in seeking out the optimum mate
for the propagation
of his genetic line.
Thank you, Sheldon.
Now, whether that
propagation is in the interest
of humanity is, of course,
an entirely different question.
This is Ira Flatow
and you're listening
to NPR's Science Friday.
Joining us today by phone
(helium hissing)
from his office
in Pasadena, California
is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Oh, this is going to be a riot.
FLATOW:
Thanks for being
with us today, Dr. Cooper.
My pleasure, Ira.
Now, let's talk about
magnetic monopoles.
Can you explain to our audience
just what a monopole is?
Of course.
First, consider an ordinary
magnet which has,
(pitch raises):
as even the most uneducated
in your audience
must know, two poles.
(clears throat)
(pitch raises):
A north and south pole.
If you cut that in half,
you have two smaller magnets,
each with its own
north and south pole.
Uh, Dr. Cooper,
I think there might be
something wrong
with our connection.
(higher pitch):
No, I hear you fine.
As I was saying, an ordinary
magnet has two poles.
The primary characteristic
of a monopole
is that it has only one pole,
hence, monopole.
SHELDON (over radio):
A requirement for string theory,
or M-they, if you will,
is the existence
of such monopoles.
I, myself, led an expedition
to the Arctic Circle
in search of said particles.
Kripke, I found the nozzle!
I'm going to kill you!
So nice you could
join me this evening.
You're looking lovely as always.
Thanks, Howard.
Always nice to be part
of your masturbatory fantasies.
Come on, Katee
Don't make it sound so cheap.
I'm sorry, fiddling
with yourself in the bathtub
is a real class act.
Thank you.
So, shall we get started?
Sure.
But can I ask you
a question first?
Do you want to play
Cylon and colonist?
No.
I want to know why you're
playing make-believe with me
when you could be out
with a real woman tonight.
You mean, Bernadette?
No, I mean Princess Leia.
Of course
I mean Bernadette.
She's a wonderful girl
and she really likes you.
I know, but she's not you.
I'm not me.
The real me is in Beverly Hills
going out with a tall,
handsome, rich guy.
Really? Tall?
Six-four.
Ouch.
But come on, you got a wonderful
girl in your life
and you're ignoring her
in order to spend your nights
in the bathtub with mental
image and a wash cloth.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Howard!
What are you
doing in there?
I'm taking a bath!
I hope that's all you're doing.
We share that tub!
Don't remind me!
Oh, man.
All soaped up
and no place to go.
(knocking at door)
How ya doin', buddy?
I was humiliated
on national radio.
How do you think I'm doing?
Come on, it wasn't
that bad.
(sighs):
What do you want?
We represent
the Lollipop Guild,
and we want you.
Okay, so Kripke
played a joke on you.
It wasn't funny.
I thought it was funny.
Raj.
You laughed.
Did you laugh?
I fell on the floor.
All right, he got you.
You can get him back.
I refuse to sink to his level.
You can't sink.
With all that helium in you
you're lucky you don't
(high pitched): float away.
Are you really admitting defeat?
I’m never admitting defeat.
Good.
However, on an unrelated topic,
I am never getting out
of this bed again.
What if you could
make Kripke
look even sillier
than he made you look?
I don't think
that's possible, dude.
You're not helping.
I didn't come to help,
I came to mock.
Sheldon, what you need to do
is figure out a way
to exact vengeance on Kripke,
like, uh
like, how the Joker got back
at Batman for putting him
in the Arkham Asylum for the Criminally Insane.
That's true.
He didn't just stay there
and talk about his feelings
with the other
psychotic villains.
He, he broke out and poisoned
Gotham's water supply.
Well...
I suppose I could poison Kripke.
No!
No.
It's a simple matter.
There are several toxic
chemicals
that'd be untraceable
in an autopsy.
Okay, uh, that's the spirit,
but, um, let's dial it back
to a non-lethal form
of vengeance.
Oh!
How about we whoopee cushion
on his office chair?
He'll sit down,
it'll sound like
he's flatulent,
even though he's not.
Let's keep thinking.
Oh, gee,
you're too late.
Scarlett Johansson and
Wonder Woman were just in here
trolling around for
neurotic, little weasels.
I came to talk to Bernadette.
She's working today, right?
Yes, but I don't think
she wants to see you.
Why not?
Come on, Howard.
You hurt her feelings
by not calling her all week.
Plus, I've kind of been
talkin' some smack about ya.
Hello, Howard.
Wait, Bernadette,
I need to talk to you.
I can't now, I'm working.
This will only take a second.
You asked me
to think about where
our relationship
was going, and I did.
Bernadette?
Will you marry me?
Is this more comedy
that I don't understand?
No. I'm serious.
I'm never going to find
another girl like you
who likes me and is,
you know, real.
So, this isn't a joke?
No.
Then you're insane.
I prefer to think
of myself as quirky.
Howard, we've only
been on three dates.
We haven't even had sex yet.
Fair enough.
When's your break?
Wow.
Don't you just hate
when this happens?
Wow.
All right,
how's this for revenge?
A solution of
hydrogen peroxide,
and one of saturated
potassium iodide.
What's this?
Mountain Dew.
Ahh, refreshing.
Now, we're going to
combine these chemicals
with ordinary dish soap,
creating a little exothermic
release of oxygen.
(all exclaiming)
Foamy vengeance.
Yes, exactly.
This is brilliant, Sheldon.
How are we going to deploy it
in Kripke's office?
Already taken care of.
Observe.
(typing)
This is a live shot of Kripke's lab
via a mini webcam I was able to install,
thanks to a dollar bill
discreetly placed in the night
janitor's shirt pocket.
At the same time,
I also secured large quantities
of these chemicals above
the tiles in the drop ceiling.
Oh, Sheldon,
you remind me
of a young Lex Luthor.
(chuckles)
You flatter me, sir.
- Let me guess. Motion sensors?
- Yes.
The reaction will be triggered
when Kripke reaches
the center of the room.
Mwa, ha, ha.
I gotta say,
I am really impressed.
This is truly the Sheldon Cooper
way to get even.
(whoopee cushion expels)
It may be low-tech
but I still maintain the whoopee
cushion has comic validity.
Here comes Kripke!
LEONARD:
Who is that with him?
KOOTHRAPPALI:
I believe that's
the president of the university.
And the board of directors.
Abort! Abort!
There is no "abort."
How could you not put in
an "abort?"
I made a boo-boo, all right?
KRIPKE:
I think the board
will really appreciate
how well we're using that
NSA grant, President Seibert.
Right here we have
a micro-controlled plasma...
Wow. Looks like the
Ganges on laundry day.
At least they don't know
it was you.
(chiming)
SHELDON (on computer):
Hello, Kripke.
This classic prank
comes to you
from the malevolent mind
of Sheldon Cooper.
If you'd like to see the look
on your stupid face,
this video is being
instantly uploaded to YouTube.
Oh, and a hat tip
to Leonard Hofstadter
And Raj Koothrappali
for their support
and encouragement
in this enterprise.
Well, I'm going back to India.
What's your plan?
Hey, he's your tip
from table seven.
Oh, thanks
Mm-hmm.
WOLOWITZ:
Testing. Check.
Check two.
Oh, now what?
You want me
to throw him out?
No, that's okay.
Are you sure? He's small.
I bet I can get a nice,
tight spiral on him.
I want to dedicate this number
to a great gal
who I've done wrong.
(plays The Four Tops "Bernadette")
* Bernadette
* I am so sorry for
* Trying to propose to you
* Bernadette
* You found it creepy
* But that's just
the kind of thing I  do*
* Ahh...
* I know now it was too soon
to talk of love *
* It was just a crazy idea that
came to me in my tub *
* But, Bernadette,
give me one more chance *
(falsetto):
* Sweet Bernadette
* I'll get the hang
of this thing *
* They call romance, Sweet Bernadette,
I dream to once again *
* Kiss your lips,
Sweet Bernadette *
* Sincerely yours
* Howard Wolowitz
* Bernadette...
Oh, I am so sorry.
Are you kidding?
That's the most romantic thing
anyone's ever done for me.
* Bernadette!
Thank you, Cheesecake Factory!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com