Okay, we've got
power to the laser.
I should've brought
an umbrella.
What for?
It's not going to rain.
I know that, but with
skin as fair as mine,
moon burn is a
real possibility.
That's a "bazinga," right?
One of my best,
don't you think?
(forced giggle)
Howard, do you want
to double-check
the equatorial mount
on the laser?
We need it locked onto
the Sea of Tranquility.
You got it.
Oh, Raj, no.
Billions of dollars have gone
into inventing the Internet
and filling it
with pictures of naked women,
so we don't have
to peep through windows.
It's not like that.
I'm watching someone's TV.
The Good Wife is on.
I tell you, this is
my new Grey's Anatomy.
Leonard, Leonard.
What is that?
Relax, it's just a dirty sock.
How on earth
can you say
"dirty sock" and "relax"
in the same sentence?
Sheldon, the world is filled
with dirty discarded socks.
Not my world.
Hey, you know who'd really dig
seeing this experiment? Penny.
I wasn't aware that
lunar ranging was her thing.
Although, I suppose the
retro-reflector left on the moon
by Neil Armstrong
does qualify as a shiny object.
Why don't you
ask her to come up?
I don't know, it's still
a little weird
since, you know...
She dumped you?
She didn't dump me.
We were just in different places
in the relationship.
I fail to see how a relationship
can have the qualities
of a geographic location.
Oh, it's very simple.
Leonard was living
in a little town
called "Please don't leave me"
while Penny had just moved
to the island of "Buh-bye."
Screw you guys.
I'm gonna go see if she's home.
If it's not
too much trouble,
I'd like to point this
at the moon now.
Wait a second.
The good wife is crying.
Something's very wrong.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool ?
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall ?
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
The Big Bang Theory 3x23
The Lunar Excitation
Original Air Date on May 24, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Oh, hi.
What's going on?
We're up on the roof bouncing
laser beams off the moon.
I'm sorry, what?
It's pretty cool.
We've got a two-meter parabolic
reflector and everything.
I thought you might
want to see it.
MAN:
That makes no sense.
Um...
How can you bounce
stuff off the moon?
There's no gravity.
PENNY:
Uh, Leonard,
this is Zack.
Zack, Leonard.
Hey.
Oh, sorry, I didn't know you
were busy. Maybe another time.
Yeah, maybe.
Hey, I want to see
this laser thing.
Oh, but what about
the party?
It's a surprise party-- doesn't
matter when we get there.
Okay, well, yeah, come on up.
So, how'd you two guys meet?
My company designs the menus
for the Cheesecake Factory.
Your company?
Well, my dad, but...
but me and my sister are VPs.
So... menus.
I know it sounds easy but there's a lot
of science that goes in designing one.
Happy now? I'm moving the dirty sock.
Thank you.
Raj, keep an eye out
for the other one.
Hey, guys, this is
my friend Zack.
Hey.
Hello.
ZACK:
Whoa!
Is that the laser?
It's bitchin'.
Yes.
In 1917, when Albert Einstein
established
the theoretic foundation
for the laser in his paper
"Zur Quantentheorie der
Strahlung," his fondest hope
was that the resultant device
be bitchin'.
Well, mission
accomplished.
Let me explain
what we're doing here.
Um, in 1969,
the astronauts
on Apollo 11
positioned reflectors
on the surface of the moon,
and we're going to
shoot a laser off
one of them
and let the light bounce back
into this photomultiplier.
Oh! That's very cool.
ZACK:
One question.
How can you be sure
it won't blow up?
The laser?
The moon.
See, now this is
a man for Penny.
That's a great
question, Zack.
No, it's not.
PENNY:
Sheldon!
Play nice.
It's not a great question.
How could somebody
possibly think
we're going to
blow up the moon?
That's a great question.
Don't worry about the moon.
We-We set our laser to stun.
Smart.
Now, we'll be able to see
the beam when it leaves,
but it won't be strong enough
when it comes back
to be seen by the naked eye.
Naked.
(laughs)
Right. Uh... funny.
Uh, that device,
there, will measure
the photons that return
and let us see it
on this computer.
Raj, get them
some glasses.
Cool, it's gonna
be in 3-D?
Preparing to fire laser
at the moon.
Make it so.
(metallic thumping)
(thumping stops)
There it is.
There's the spike!
2.5 seconds for the
light to return.
That's the moon!
We hit the moon!
(laughter, shouting)
That's your big experiment?
All that for
a line on the screen?
LEONARD:
Yeah, but, uh,
think about
what this represents.
The fact that
we can do this
is the only way
of definitively proving
that there are man-made objects
on the moon, put there
by a member of a species
that only 60 years before
had just invented the airplane.
What species is that?
I was wrong.
Penny can do better.
Okay, guys, thank you,
it's been fun.
Yeah, thanks.
Should we invite
them to the party?
No, just keep walking.
He must be very
skilled at coitus.
I'm telling you, dude,
the only way
to feel better about Penny
going out with other guys
is for you to get back
on the whores.
Horse.
What?
The phrase is "get
back on the horse,"
not "whores."
That's disgusting, dude.
No, it's not...
(stammering)
Never mind.
He is right, though.
If you want, I can turn
you on to this great new
dating site I found.
No, thanks.
You sure? They say they can
find a match for anybody.
Have they found
a match for you?
Tons. I've had, like, eight
dates in the last month.
And 12 if you count the ones
who showed up and left.
I can't bring
the nitrogen tank down.
Why not?
All right, let me restate that.
It's very heavy,
and I don't want to.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Lift with your knees,
not your back.
Good night.
You know what
would be fun?
Signing Sheldon up
for online dating.
(chuckles)
Yeah, right.
No, think about it.
We make it an
experiment.
Like when
Frankenstein's monster
was lonely and
he found a wife.
He didn't find a wife.
They built him a wife
out of dead body parts.
Okay, we'll call
that plan B.
(knocking)
(knocking continues)
Coming!
Damn you, you rat bastard.
Are you drunk?
Zack was a perfectly nice guy,
and then you ruined him!
How did I ruin him?
'Cause in the olden days,
I never would've known
he was so stupid.
Come on, he wasn't
that stupid.
Yes, he was!
He thought you were
gonna blow up the moon!
(chuckling):
Okay, yeah, he's stupid.
He spent the entire
night bragging
about how he invented
the word "appe-teasers."
(chuckling quietly)
How is that my fault?
You have destroyed my ability
to tolerate idiots.
Now, come with me.
Wh-Where are we going?
We're gonna have sex.
Why? I mean, okay.
What's going on?
Put on your noise-
canceling headphones,
'cause it's
gonna get loud.
Oh! Not this again.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
In what universe
is this low-pulp?
Good morning, Penny.
What, do you have eyes
in the back of your head?
When one gets beaten up
every other day in school,
one of necessity develops
a keen sense of hearing.
Incidentally, one can
get beaten up in school
simply by referring
to oneself as "one."
I'm making
English muffins.
Would you like
an English muffin?
Oh, thanks, I'm not hungry.
FYI,
my noise-canceling headphones
proved ineffective last night.
Yeah, sorry about that.
As a native Texan,
I must say I've never heard
the phrase "yee-haw"
used in quite that context.
Oh, God.
"Oh, God."
That I've heard
on multiple occasions.
In what universe
is that lightly toasted?
(scoffs)
This has to be
the worst day of my life.
Good morning, Leonard.
How many times have
I asked you not to do that?
Counting this instance? 317.
Where's Penny?
She returned
to her apartment.
I presume to shower and vomit.
Not necessarily in that order.
I wonder why
she didn't say good-bye.
Are you expecting me to offer an
explanation of human behavior?
I know. I just
thought as an outsider,
you might be able to provide
a fresh perspective.
I have no difficulty
believing you're not butter.
Oh, hey.
Oh, hi.
Um, I gotta run.
Early shift.
Okay, I'll walk
down with you.
So, last night was
fun, huh?
Yeah, it must have been.
I just threw up
in my closet.
Bummer.
Anyway, I was thinking
tonight maybe
we could catch a movie.
Oh, yeah, tonight's
not great for me.
Doesn't have
to be tonight.
I'm free
pretty much always.
Leonard, last night
was a mistake.
When you say "mistake,"
do you mean a fortunate mistake,
like the discovery
of penicillin?
Look, I'm sorry.
I was drunk, I was lonely,
I hated Zack.
Can we just forget
it ever happened?
No, it's pretty well imprinted
on my brain.
Especially
the whole rodeo thing.
Oh, God!
So, that's it?
Wham, bam, thank you, Leonard?
Look, I said I'm sorry.
Can't you please let it go?
How am I supposed to let it go?
You used me for sex!
Morning, Mrs. Gunderson.
Good morning, Leonard.
Or should I say "yee-haw"?
Holy crap.
What?
We finally have proof
that aliens walk among us.
Excuse me?
The dating site matched a woman
with Sheldon.
You're kidding.
An actual woman?
Yeah, look.
Breasts and everything.
Trust me, breasts doesn'
necessarily mean woman.
Since when?
I'll show you a picture
of my Uncle Louie in a
bathing suit sometime.
Leonard,
you gotta see this.
We found a match
for Sheldon.
LEONARD:
Great.
Maybe she can have sex with him,
and then walk out on him
the next morning without so much
as a "How do you do?"
Do you know what
he's talking about?
Nope.
Why don't you ask him?
Leonard, what are you talking
about?
I don't want
to talk about it.
That was
a lousy suggestion.
Whatever.
Right now,
Dr. Sheldon Cooper has
to send an e-mail
to his perfect match.
"Greetings,
fellow life-form..."
(giggles)
If she can do it, I can do it.
I can't do it.
Hello?
(stammering)
Oh, hi. Hey.
Hi, Leslie.
Leonard Hofstadter.
What're you doing here?
Uh, I know!
It's been a while!
Yeah, 18 months.
Right. Right.
So how you doing?
Fine. You?
Uh, not bad.
You remember when
we used to have sex
and you said that it didn't mean
anything, it was just for fun?
Yeah.
You, uh, want
to do that again?
What happened?
Blondie dumped you?
She didn't dump me.
We were just in different places
in the relationship.
Right.
Um... anyway,
apparently,
it's okay to go back to people
you're no longer seeing
and have recreational sex
with them.
Uh-huh.
So, what do you say?
Let me think about it.
(slams)
She's not coming back.
Uh-oh.
She wants to meet us.
Not us. Him.
Yes, but him doesn't
even know about her.
Well, him about to
find out about her.
Really? Us gonna tell him?
Who's going to tell
whom about what?
Sheldon.
Hey. Hi.
Your surprise confuses me.
I live here.
Right.
So, listen, what are you doing
tomorrow afternoon?
Be more specific.
4:30.
That's not afternoon.
That's preevning.
What?
It's a time of day I invented.
It better defines
the ambiguous period
between afternoon and evening:
preevning.
I'm fairly certain it will catch
on as it fills a desperate need.
Right, okay.
What are you doing
tomorrow preevning?
Well, tomorrow's Saturday.
Saturday night is laundry night.
So I'll be spending
the preevning pre-sorting
and pre-soaking.
Okay, what if I
were to tell you,
tomorrow, at 4:30,
you could meet a woman who has
been scientifically chosen
to be your perfect mate?
I would snort in derision
and throw my arms in the air,
exhausted
by your constant tomfoolery.
But it's true.
(snorts)
But we-we put all
your vital information
into this dating site,
answered all their questions
just like you would,
and they found
a match for you.
Her name is
Amy Farrah Fowler.
Please.
Even assuming
you could answer any question
the way I would,
the algorithms used
by matchmaking sites
are complete hokum.
And that's exactly the answer
we gave to the question:
"What is your attitude
towards online dating?"
Howard wanted to write
"mumbo jumbo," but I said no.
Our Sheldon would
say "hokum."
Come on, where's your
scientific curiosity?
Well, most of it
is being applied
to unraveling the secrets
of the universe
while the rest of it's
wondering why
I'm having this conversation
with you.
Okay, how about this.
Even Spock had a date
once every seven years.
He didn't date.
It was pon farr.
His blood boiled
with mating lust.
Well, why-why don't you
start with a cup of coffee,
and you can pon farr
Amy Farrah Fowler later.
I don't drink coffee.
All right, you can
have a hot chocolate.
As I will not be engaging
in this nonsense,
my choice of beverage is moot.
But for the record,
I only drink hot chocolate
in months with an "R" in them.
Why?
What's life without whimsy?
Okay, I'm out.
(sighs)
Sheldon, I've hidden
the dirty sock
from the roof somewhere
in your apartment.
Unless you are willing to come
with us to meet this girl,
it will remain there forever.
You're bluffing.
Are you willing to risk it?
Curse you.
(bottle shattering)
30 feet.
(sighs)
Oh. Hey, Leonard.
I was a perfectly happy,
geeky, little lonely guy,
and you ruined me!
Are you drunk?
Come on. We're gonna have sex,
and it's not gonna mean a thing!
Are you out
of your mind?!
(door slams)
I'm really starting to think
there's a double standard here.
In a few minutes,
when I gloat over the
failure of this enterprise,
how would you
prefer I do it?
The standard
"I told you so"?
The classic
"neener-neener"?
Or just my normal look
of haughty derision?
You don't know
we're wrong yet.
Haughty derision it is.
WOMAN:
Excuse me.
I'm Amy Farrah Fowler.
You're Sheldon Cooper.
Hello, Amy Farrah Fowler.
I'm sorry to inform you
that you have been taken in
by unsupportable mathematics
designed to prey
on the gullible and the lonely.
Additionally,
I'm being blackmailed
with a hidden dirty sock.
If that was slang,
I'm unfamiliar with it.
If it was literal, I share your
aversion to soiled hosiery.
In any case,
I'm here because my
mother and I have agreed
that I will date at
least once a year.
Interesting.
My mother and I have
the same agreement about church.
I don't object to the
concept of a deity,
but I'm baffled by the notion
of one that takes attendance.
Well, then you might want
to avoid East Texas.
Noted.
Now, before this
goes any further,
you should know that all
forms of physical contact
up to and including
coitus are off the table.
May I buy you a beverage?
Tepid water, please.
Good God, what
have we done?
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org