Left! Left! He's going left!
I'm gonna have a heart attack.
Nowhere to go, buddy.
What the hell was that?
What are we chasing?
Go that way.
Up, donny, up.
He's going for the roof.
He's going up, go.
Ow. Damn it.
Just go, go!
Donny, no! It's too far!
I can rest at home.
We can't release you
for at least two days.
You have two broken bones,
a severe concussion,
collapsed lung.
But you didn't find anything
life-threatening, right?
You fell 30 feet. You should have died.
- That was the point.
- Could you shut up?
You have suicidal thoughts?
Not once. Never.
He doesn't want to kill himself.
He just thinks he's gonna die soon,
so it doesn't really matter...
Now you shut up.
I'm the one you're not covering
when you pull your crazy stunts.
Why do you think you're gonna die soon?
Well, my dad, grandfather,
and great-grandfather
all dropped dead of heart problems
right after they turned 40.
Look who turns 40 next week.
- I can refer you to a cardiologist, if you...
- Nah, I've been there,
all of them.
I spent my early 30s going
from one doctor to another.
Every single one says my heart's fine.
- And you think they're wrong?
- I know they're wrong.
But what can I do?
At a certain point,
you just got to live your life.
By live your life,
you mean risk your life.
If there is something wrong,
I know a doctor who will find it.
Oh, God! I'll be back in ten.
I'm picking lint out of my belly button.
This is ridiculous.
I'm converting the study into a bedroom.
Huh...
Six weeks.
Longer than I thought it would take...
for you to notice that I'm
sleeping in your living room,
and offer other options.
I didn't expect
you to be here this long.
True, but that's not why
you didn't extend the invitation.
Do you really need to deconstruct this?
You didn't want me to sleep
where you and Amber slept.
- Okay, yes, you do.
- After she died,
you converted the study to a bedroom
and the bedroom to a study...
Except it's not a study, it's a shrine.
Can I tell you something?
I wasn't picking lint
out of my belly button.
Okay.
I am not ready to transition
from my dead girlfriend's shrine
to your... morning glory.
I'll have a mattress delivered
and set up for you in the tabernacle.
I just need it tuesdays
for animal sacrifices.
Oh, man!
Ugh.
Patient's a genetic time bomb.
There's no fuse.
He's not a bomb.
Right now he's not a patient either.
You saying we ignore three
generations of cardiac problems?
I'm not ignoring it.
I'm labeling it a coincidence.
You hate coincidence.
We reconciled. It was a whole thing.
Big country.
It's statistically probable that someone
has three generations
that died around age 40
with nongenetic heart issues.
- Dice have no memory.
- Genes do.
If we ran a battery of tests
on every nonsymptomatic
statistical anomaly...
The guy goes every day assuming
his life will end at age 40.
Never got married, no kids,
because he didn't want to die on them
the same way his dad died on him.
You want to take this case
'cause he's yet another
lonely, sad puppy.
You should have been a vet.
It's a legitimate case.
Differential diagnosis
for genetic heart conditions.
That sold you?
- Marfan syndrome, brugada.
- And you?
Emilio hypercholesterolemia.
He's only agreeing with you
'cause he wants to have sex with you.
And by the way, I agree with you too,
especially in those pants.
We're not wasting our time.
And last week, Chase said
that I was the de facto boss.
Hospitals don't recognize
de facto medical licenses.
Let's start with genetic tests.
Get an EKG, cardiac cath...
and an echo to check
the integrity of his heart.
I'll start on blood samples.
Ugh...
- Forgot my watch.
- Could have sworn
- I saw you put it on this morning.
- Must be in the locker room.
I'll be right back.
I need to know what your plans are.
First we take Berlin.
And then we circle around behind Poland
and yell, "surprise!"
With regards to your employment.
I like things the way they are.
I get just enough puzzle to solve
without the scornful visits from you...
Until now.
Pretend time's been going on
long enough.
I don't have a medical license.
All I can do is pretend.
And I'm gonna have payroll send you over
some pretend checks starting tomorrow.
You need to complete 120 hours
of rounds to re-qualify.
No, I don't.
I'm not saying you don't win.
I'm just saying do you really need
to punish me by making me carry a clipboard
for your lackey of the week?
It's a state requirement.
I have to certify that you've
completed all your require...
Exactly.
The requirement sets out
what you have to do...
Certify, which you can do
with one hand tied behind your back.
Now, if you want to tie my hands...
Dr. Singh supervises rounds on thursdays,
starts at 7:00.
Nothing.
So what now?
Send him home.
To continue believing
he's gonna drop dead?
When he turns 70, he'll believe us.
There are other things we can check.
Skeleton of great-grandfather's
in decent shape.
Subsurface genetic material
from grandpa's fine,
leaving one bowl of purified dad.
You do the dad.
I take it he had a sealed casket.
The watch story was crap, right?
I forgot it.
It's no big deal.
You were avoiding the ICU
where Dibala died.
I'll sequence the gene
for the cardiac sodium channel.
I felt like I was gonna have
a panic attack.
I've crossed some line...
And I'm having trouble
getting back to the other side.
I can move the patient to another room.
Cameron will ask questions.
You should tell her.
She's your wife.
How'd you get a court order
to dig them up so fast?
We just needed the guy's consent.
- You find anything?
- Not yet.
But you're just in time to do the dad.
Doctor House?
He'll be back in the morning.
I read in the paper
you're treating a police officer.
- Donny Compson?
- Second floor.
A nurse will help you find him.
I don't want to see him.
Donny and I used to go out
a long time ago.
He doesn't want to see me.
I don't want to see him.
So did you come to see me
for personal advice?
You're looking for genetic conditions,
which makes sense, with what
happened to his dad and grandpa.
Unless you were
his girlfriend and his sister,
you got nothing to worry about.
I'm not worried about me.
Donny doesn't know this,
but he has a son.
Dial extension 742.
Tell Dr. Foreman you got
some cool information.
Good night.
You okay?
Yeah, fine.
Couldn't find any
consistent genetic mutations
across 15 areas
between Donny's ancestors,
possibly indicating there isn't one.
But the son gives us a new data point.
And undegraded DNA.
- I thought he didn't want kids.
- He didn't.
Where's House?
"Dear bleeding hearts,
"since your patient's
med history is a coincidence,
"and he isn't...
"sick,
"I've gone back to school.
"Back in 120 hours."
Charming. I'll get a blood sample.
If we're looking for something
as subtle as a mutation,
it makes sense to get the DNA
where it's most pure.
You're gonna ask the mom to
consent to a bone marrow biopsy?
She wants to know if there's
something wrong with Donny
just as badly as we do.
Right.
Spike a ten-year-old's hip
because grandpa was sick.
If she's right...
save two people.
I don't want to.
Can we speak outside for a moment?
Yeah.
You need to tell him.
I can't.
His father is down that hallway
through those double doors.
I've been lying to him his whole life.
What's he gonna think of me?
You're trying to protect him.
Donny never wanted kids.
He certainly doesn't want to meet him.
If Donny does die, this could be
Michael's only chance to meet his father.
After administration of immunoglobulin,
patient had no further pain, and
overnight liver function tests
are now normal.
Patient's ready to be released.
Stats are dropping.
- Doctor Singh?
- She's choking.
- On your fingers.
- She can't breathe.
House...
Please take your finger off the test button.
Oh!
See. Wow, sorry about that.
I could've slit her throat.
Well, we're all here to learn.
You know, Dr. Cuddy warned me about you.
She tell you how to stop me?
Look, I'm asking you
as an adult to please stop.
well, that obviously
didn't come from her.
But fair enough.
Excellent presentation, Nona.
Ah!
Now I've done it.
There's urine everywhere!
Gosh. The great thing
about the teacher-student
relationship is the teacher
can often learn more from the student.
You learned anything yet?
You have a son.
I was pregnant when we broke up.
I'm sorry I never told you,
but I knew how you felt
about having kids.
You had no right.
Maybe.
It's a little late for that.
He's here.
He wants to meet you.
I don't want to meet him.
I've never asked you for a dime.
He's here to help find
whatever's wrong with your heart.
I didn't ask him.
I didn't want him.
Just say hi to him.
Hi.
I'm Michael.
I'm your...
Yeah, your mother told me.
When you get better,
maybe we could do something.
See a movie?
No.
My dad died when I was your age.
It was the most painful thing
I ever went through.
Trust me, as much as I'm sure
this hurts right now, it's better.
Please take him out of here.
Chromosomes for 28
cardiovascular conditions
are normally numbered in structure.
No translocations,
deletions, or inversions.
I didn't notice that
the kid's D-A-D-D-Y chromosome
has been severely damaged
by someone else's
bleeding heart chromosome.
It was the only way to get
Michael to do the marrow biopsy.
I'm sure there are plenty of lies
would've worked just as well,
except without the years of therapy.
- Don't you have school?
- Recess.
So where does that leave us?
Chase?
Sorry. What?
I was saying, "do you think these shoes
"work in this color?"
- Send him home.
- He's not gonna believe he's healthy.
You're not very good at your job.
- You don't deserve candy.
- He's been preparing
his whole life to die at age 40.
He's had dozens of doctors
tell him he's fine.
You think you can change his thinking?
Yeah, I do. Chase, walk with me.
Great contributions back there.
There's no case. I had nothing to add.
You had nothing to add...
Because you were distracted.
A little devil on your shoulder
told you to kill a guy, and now
the little angel won't shut up,
telling you you're gonna burn
in a lake of fire.
I'm fine.
You shouldn't be.
Talk to someone.
Docs fixed me up in seven weeks.
You're... ten minutes, tops.
Thanks.
Glad we had this little moment.
Come on.
I'm Dr. House.
You couldn't find anything, could you?
You have ortoli syndrome.
Dr. Chase?
- You sure?
- Tests don't lie.
Right.
Uh...
Well, it's... It's a...
It's a very rare disorder
that short-circuits the adrenals,
which short-circuits the heart.
Blah, blah, blah, blah. Who cares
about medical mumbo jumbo?
Tell him the treatment.
It's... well, it's... It's complicated.
Doctors always want to make
everything sound so complicated.
It's Nabasynth.
- What?
- Nabasynth.
Yes.
So all we have to do now
is write a prescription
and, uh, have him pick up the pills.
That's it?
I take some pills, and I'm gonna be okay?
The real tragedy here is
that the tiburon swab technology
didn't exist to detect ortoli
back in your dad's day.
He could've lived.
Thank you.
You'll sign these discharge papers,
I'll get you a bottle of meds.
Take one twice a day for a week,
you'll live a long, healthy life.
Answer the door, House.
It's got to be for you.
Are you watching tv?
It's the door!
- Were you on the phone?
- No.
- Just now, were you talking?
- No. I'm alone.
You okay, House?
Why are you here?
Donny collapsed four hours
after we discharged him.
He's dead.
His apartment manager found him
on the floor in the laundry room.
Said he wasn't breathing.
He called the EMTs, but it was too late.
I sent the guy home with mints.
Whatever it is, we all missed it.
I missed the fact that
there was something to miss.
What is wrong with me?
You had good reason.
Patient presented with no symptoms,
and all his tests came back negative.
What's the official cause of death?
Autopsy hasn't been performed yet.
EMTs brought him to general,
but I requested they ship him back
to our morgue for the postmortem.
Good.
Hon. Wake up.
Why are you dressed?
You can't sleep?
I want to go tell Cheryl
that Donny died.
It's 4:00 in the morning.
They're nearly two hours away.
I figure by the time
I get there, she'll be awake.
Babe, come back to bed.
Call her in a few hours.
It's the sort of thing
she needs to hear face-to-face.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Why?
Last week, I understood
that you were stressed out
about the Dibala "M" & "M,"
and I gave you your space.
But that's over now,
and you're still acting...
I'm worried about you.
Don't be.
I'm fine.
Really.
And you'd tell me if you weren't?
Promise?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey.
I love you.
I love you too.
Donny Compson, age 39.
Can we cut to the money shot?
It's his heart,
so let's look at his heart.
Nice y-incision.
You can't perform an autopsy
without a medical license.
Really?
'Cause I don't think there's
anything I could screw up
that we haven't already screwed up.
Opening postmortem incision.
Beginning at the midline of the sternum.
That's odd.
It almost looks like he's...
Bleeding.
I think the autopsy's gonna have
to wait a little bit.
He was briefly conscious,
then his systolic dipped below 60,
and he was out again.
Differential diagnosis for resurrection.
- Go.
- Obviously he wasn't dead.
His heart slowed enough
that the EMTs...
Yes, the fact that he's not dead
means we did absolutely
nothing wrong.
There's several documented cases
where tetrodotoxin ingestion
caused apparent death.
It wasn't something he ate.
It's something he already had.
And his dad,
- and his grandpa, and...
- Extreme bradycardia
could be caused by sick sinus syndrome.
- Sinoatrial block.
- What if it's not his heart?
Let's work from the tenuous assumption
that we're not idiots
who've spent days examining a heart
up, down, sideways...
Declaring it healthy just a few hours
before it basically shut down.
So we need to think about causes
in places you didn't look.
Could be metabolic.
You okay?
Yeah.
What about a genetic predisposition
to an autoimmune disease?
Isolated anti-ro antibody
could cause complete heart block.
Could also be passed
through four generations.
Autoimmune it is.
Start him on steroids.
Hey. How you feeling?
My whole head is killing me.
You just came through a severe trauma.
What do you remember?
I was changing my laundry
over to the dryer.
That's it?
You were declared dead.
You made it all the way to autopsy.
My jaw aches.
And obviously I don't have
ortoli syndrome.
It's hard to get too excited
about coming back from the dead
when anything I do,
anything you give me...
It all ends the same way.
Outer and middle ear respond well.
Hearing thresholds are normal
at all frequencies.
Eardrum is perfectly healthy.
What if I, uh...
If I sometimes hear whispering?
Then you're probably hearing
someone whispering.
I had some dental work done
in the Philippines
when I was a kid.
Adjoining metal fillings could corrode
and pick up AM radio signals.
Open your mouth.
Your fillings don't touch.
So there's no reason
for me to be hearing things.
I can only tell you that you're
hearing sounds as you should.
If you're also hearing
sounds that you shouldn't,
well, that would be psychosis.
You'd have to talk
to someone who does brain.
I only do ears.
Bravo!
It's amazing how
you did 120 hours in one day.
I wasn't on my best behavior.
I admit.
Allow me.
From now on, I'm gonna supervise
- your practicum requirements.
- That won't be necessary.
You wanna annoy another doctor first?
- Eventually...
- It's not necessary,
because I'm not ready
to be a doctor again.
I'm sorry.
Are you sleeping out here?
Just... dozed off in front of the tv.
With bedding?
Maybe!
I can't sleep in there.
The heater's screwed up.
If you need to talk...
If... If you need more help...
I'm just tired.
I'm right here.
Great.
Can you be right here somewhere else?
My jaw still hurts.
My tooth... Actually, a lot.
I'm sorry, you're maxed out
on your pain meds.
Try to sleep.
Dentist looked at
the tooth the guy pulled out.
There was nothing wrong with it.
So aside from him being an idiot,
what else have we learned?
The pain is real.
It's coming from somewhere.
What about bone cancer?
You can't connect
bone cancer to the heart.
House figure this can wait
till the morning?
Actually, he told Cuddy
he's not ready to work.
He quit?
- Apparently.
- It's a power play.
He'll be back tomorrow.
Bone cancer could trigger
a paraneoplastic syndrome,
which shuts down the heart.
Primary bone cancer isn't hereditary.
Li-Fraumeni syndrome.
It's hereditary, and it increases
a person's risk of having bone cancer.
You have another theory?
My theory is it's not bone cancer.
Gamma survey would locate the tumors.
I had pea soup today.
You'd love my breath right now.
I didn't get a chance to run tonight.
House is... is having issues.
I missed you a lot today.
All I want to do is...
You know.
No cancers on the lateral cuneiform bone.
Navicular's also clean.
Chase is lying to me.
And I know you know.
Tell me what's going on, please.
I'm gonna tell you
the same thing I told him...
Talk to your spouse.
No breakfast?
Not today.
I'm hallucinating.
What happened?
It's nothing visual this time.
I hear whispering.
Is that why
you've been acting so weird?
- Is that why you quit?
- I'm losing it.
I'm sure there's
a rational explanation.
- The wind? A neighbor's TV?
- I checked everything.
What's really scary
is that I hear whispering
while not on Vicodin.
I'm gonna check myself back into Mayfield.
Okay.
Okay?
You don't think there might be
a logical explanation?
Something I missed?
You're the smartest guy I know.
If you haven't thought of it,
it doesn't exist.
I'll drive you over.
I just need to make some tea first.
You know.
That you're an ass? Yeah.
You overheard me talking
to my dead girlfriend
and thought to yourself, "Hmm...
"What kind of fun can I have with this?"
Why are you talking to her?
You run out of living people?
You can talk to me. I'm right here.
I miss her.
Talking to her makes me feel better.
You don't.
Patient Lauren Maybaum, 27,
presented two days ago
with severe abdominal pain.
Sorry I'm late.
Yesterday you said you weren't ready.
Yesterday I wasn't.
- Today I am.
- And tomorrow?
Is it possible for me
to get a five-day forecast?
I'm feeling much better.
Thank you for not asking.
Either you did have a problem...
Which I can't ignore.
Or you were jerking me around...
- Which I can't ignore.
- You are a woman. You can do anything.
For example, I can talk to you outside.
Are you sure you're only one woman?
This is the part where you play
the employee, and I play the boss.
I can see your nipples. Your turn.
- These kids are...
- No wonder she hates him.
Mm, that's not hate.
- It's foreplay.
- It's inappropriate.
Gamma survey revealed no tumors.
So it's not bone cancer.
Where's Chase?
Don't know.
Hm.
Two mysteries, cool.
Theories?
Did I come in too soon?
Okay, I'm gonna take another lap.
And I want three new ideas
by the time I come back.
One of them's got to be not stupid.
Where there's pain... there's nerves.
Hereditary sensory
autonomic neuropathy, type one.
Miscommunication in the brain stem
mistakes nerve pain for tooth pain.
It would explain the bradycardia too.
And I like the word "hereditary"
in the title.
Carbamazepine fixes him.
I'll get him started on the medication.
Nope, Chase specifically asked
if he could do it.
Sleep at home.
So I didn't do the gamma survey.
- Bbone cancer?
- No.
You should congratulate me
for not wasting your time.
Are you getting some help?
Or is this the way things
are gonna be from now on?
What's pathetic is
you haven't gotten help
because you wanna feel bad.
You wanna suffer,
'cause if you feel guilty,
then you're not a psychopath.
Patient needs some Carbamazepine.
Now, I don't care how much
that room scares you,
you're doing your job.
How long before you
cross this one off the list?
A couple of hours.
You ever shoot anyone?
Twice.
You ever kill anyone?
No.
I know a few guys who did, though.
Did they ever get over it?
A captain I know compares it
to taking out the trash,
like it's nothing.
Other hand, I got an ex-partner
who nearly drank himself into oblivion.
Did he get help?
Yeah.
Help didn't help.
Oh, God!
What is it?
I went to the bathroom.
Patient's lost bowel control.
Means we were wrong about h-san,
And it means he's getting worse fast.
Wouldn't want to be the duty nurse
assigned to his floor. Get it?
"Doody" nurse?
Fine. Do the doctor thing.
No an autoimmune disorder
could explain...
We put him on steroids.
He didn't respond.
- It's not autoimmune.
- Could be Wilson's disease.
A disease that advanced
would've hit the liver.
It is possible the liver's so far gone,
the labs look normal.
It's worth a shot.
Go treat with Penicillamine.
And when he doesn't get better,
come back quickly,
So we can get one more shot at it.
Bless me, father, for I have sinned.
Take your time.
How long has it been
since your last confession?
I killed a man.
Oh?
But it was the right thing to do.
Who lives or dies
is not your decision to make.
Sometimes in the operating room
it feels like it.
I'm a doctor.
Well, then you should know
more than anybody
that every human life is sacred.
Why?
Tell me what's sacred about a dictator
that kills hundreds
of thousands of his own people.
What is sacred about a doctor
who kills a patient?
Is it just the slippery slope
you're worried about?
Afraid that forgiving me for killing
the worst person on Earth,
such a bad president.
I promise...
I won't tell anyone.
Just forgive me.
Saying ten Hail Marys
isn't going to do you any good.
Then what do I have to do?
What does God need me to do?
You can't have absolution
without first taking responsibility.
You have to turn yourself into the police.
And go to jail for the rest of my life?
What's just about that?
I did the right thing.
There has to be another way.
You want absolution,
I've told you how to get it.
Send this into the state licensing board.
I've signed off on all your hours.
Why?
Because it's easier this way.
You're uncomfortable with me.
No.
Going by the book was pointless.
You were gonna learn nothing.
Good, I thought it was
because of the sexual tension.
There was no sexual tension.
There was tension.
And... it made me feel funny, so...
Here.
That's too bad.
I was kind of getting
into the whole
hot-for-teacher thing.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. False alarm.
What about us?
We're good...
Just like this.
You press my buttons, I press yours.
But buttons, you mean...
Oh...
You do make me feel funny.
You're not gonna die.
I've accepted it.
It's okay.
In addition to high arches
and some crystal bowl
in the shape of a tuna,
you also inherited
a self-destruct button.
It forms in the brain stem.
Technically, it's an aneurysm.
Presses on the nerves,
that control everything
from tooth pain to heart rate.
As you get older, it gets bigger,
until finally...
The button...
Which I'll call
intracranial berry aneurysm,
I had a friend in
high school with that name...
Stops the signal from
your brain to your heart.
And bam!
How do I know you're not
still lying to me?
Saying I'm healthy just
to make me feel better?
It does sound that way, doesn't it?
But this time, no sugar pills.
I'm gonna cut into your brain
to make you think that I'm fixing it.
And if our fake tests confirm it,
I'm gonna be cutting
into your son's brain too,
I'm just that committed.
Michael's gonna be okay?
Unless he walks out of here
and gets run over by a bus,
in which case, I will
reconsider your fate argument.
You want to give him a call?
Visiting hours
don't apply to my patients.
Yeah...
In a bit.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
The "saving the kid
from pain" stuff was crap.
You just don't want
anything in your life
that won't let you do whatever
the hell you want to do
whenever the hell you want to do it.
You've had it easy.
Sorry to screw you up.
Maybe when we get out of here...
What kind of movies you like?
He's been missing for eight hours.
Robert Chase.
- C-H-A-S-E.
- Hey!
Never mind, he just walked in, sorry.
You could've called me.
Oh, I-I forgot.
To call me? It's 2:00 in the morning.
Where were you?
You're drunk.
All right, I...
I needed to get wasted. I did.
And now I'm better.
What aren't you telling me?
Nothing.
Hi, dad.
I have been...
focusing on wrong thing.
There were some good times.
Wilson.
This is stupid.
You see, he really is getting better.