(SIREN WAILING)
(PANTING)
DONNY: Left, left!
He's going left!
I'm going to
have a heart attack.
(GRUNTING)
Nowhere to go, buddy.
What the hell was that?
What are we chasing?
Go that way!
(SIREN WAILING)
Don't move!
Nowhere to go.
Come on. Give it up.
DONNY: This way.
OFFICER: Come on.
Let's go, let's go!
BRIAN: Up, Donny, up!
He's going to the roof!
He's going up! Go!
Ow!
Damn it. Go. Go!
Donny, no,
it's too far!
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
I can rest at home.
I can't release you
for at least two days.
You've got
two broken bones,
a severe concussion,
collapsed lung.
But you didn't find anything
life-threatening. Right?
You fell 30 feet.
You should have died.
I think that
was the point.
Could you shut up?
Do you have
suicidal thoughts?
Not once. Never.
He doesn't want
to kill himself.
He just thinks
he's gonna die soon,
so it doesn't
really matter.
You shut up.
I'm the one you're
not covering
when you pull
your crazy stunts.
Why do you think
you're going to die soon?
Well, my dad, grandfather,
and great-grandfather
all dropped dead
of heart problems
right after
they turned 40.
And look who
turns 40 next week.
I can refer you to
a cardiologist if you...
No, I've been there.
All of them.
Spent my early 30s going
from one doctor to another.
Every single one
says my heart's fine.
And you think
they're wrong?
I know they're wrong.
But what can I do?
At a certain point,
you just gotta
live your life.
By "live your life,"
you mean "risk your life."
If there is
something wrong,
I know a doctor
who'll find it.
(DOOR OPENS)
Oh, God.
I'll be back in 10.
I'm picking lint out
of my belly button.
This is ridiculous.
I'm converting
the study into a bedroom.
Huh.
Six weeks.
Longer than I thought
it would take.
For you to notice
that I'm sleeping
in your living room
and offer other options.
I didn't expect you
to be here this long.
True, but that's not why
you didn't extend
the invitation.
Do you really need
to deconstruct this?
You didn't want me to sleep
where you and Amber slept.
Okay, yes, you do.
After she died,
you converted the study
to a bedroom
and the bedroom
to a study.
Except it's not a study,
it's a shrine.
Can I tell you something?
I wasn't picking lint
out of my belly button.
Okay. I am not
ready to transition
from my dead
girlfriend's shrine
to your morning glory.
I'll have
a mattress delivered
and set up for you
in the tabernacle.
I just need it Tuesdays
for animal sacrifices.
Oh, man.
(WILSON EXCLAIMING
IN DISGUST)
Patient's
a genetic time bomb.
There's no fuse.
He's not a bomb.
Right now,
he's not a patient either.
You're saying we ignore
three generations
of cardiac problems?
I'm not ignoring it,
I'm labeling it
a coincidence.
You hate coincidence.
We reconciled.
It was a whole thing.
Big country.
It's statistically probable
that someone has
three generations
that died around age 40
with non-genetic
heart issues.
Dice have no memory.
Genes do.
If we ran
a battery of tests
on every non-symptomatic
statistical anomaly...
The guy goes through
every day assuming his
life will end at age 40.
Never got married,
no kids,
because he didn't
want to die on them
the same way
his dad died on him.
You want to
take this case,
'cause he's yet
another Ionely,
sad puppy?
You should have
been a vet.
It's a legitimate case.
Differential diagnosis
for a genetic
heart condition.
That sold you?
Marfan Syndrome,
Brugada.
And you?
Familial
Hypercholesterolemia.
He's only
agreeing with you
'cause he wants to
have sex with you.
And by the way,
I agree with you, too.
Especially in
those pants.
We're not wasting
our time.
Last week,
Chase said that I was
the de facto boss.
Hospitals don't recognize
de facto medical licenses.
Let's start
with genetic tests.
Get an EKG,
cardiac cath and an echo
to check the integrity
of his heart.
I'll start
on blood samples.
(HEART MONITOR
BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(EXCLAIMING)
I forgot my watch.
I could have sworn
I saw you put it on
this morning.
Must be in
the locker room.
I'll be right back.
(DOOR OPENS)
I need to know
what your plans are.
First, we take Berlin,
and then we circle
around behind Poland
and yell, "Surprise."
With regards to
your employment.
I like things
the way they are.
I get just enough
puzzle to solve,
without the scornful
visits from you.
Until now.
Pretend time's been
going on long enough.
I don't have
a medical license.
All I can do is pretend.
Then I'm going to have
payroll send you over
some pretend checks
starting tomorrow.
You need to complete
120 hours of rounds
to re-qualify.
No, I don't.
I'm not saying
you don't win.
I'm just saying,
do you really need
to punish me
by making me
carry a clipboard
for your lackey
of the week?
It's a state requirement.
I have to certify
that you've completed...
Exactly.
The requirement
sets out what you
have to do, certify.
Which you can do
with one hand
tied behind your back.
Now, if you want
to tie my hands...
Dr. Singh supervises
rounds on Thursdays.
Starts at 7:00.
Nothing.
So what now?
We send him home.
To continue believing
he's going to drop dead?
When he turns 70,
he'll believe us.
There are other things
we can check.
FOREMAN: Skeleton of
the great-grandfather is
in decent shape.
Subsurface genetic material
from the grandpa is fine,
leaving one bowl
of putrefied dad.
You do the dad.
I take it he had
a sealed casket.
The watch story
was crap, right?
I forgot it.
It's no big deal.
You were avoiding the ICU
where Dibala died.
I'll sequence the gene
for the cardiac
sodium channel.
I felt like I was going
to have a panic attack.
(SIGHS)
I've crossed some line,
and I'm having trouble
getting back to
the other side.
I can move the patient
to another room.
Then Cameron
will ask questions.
You should tell her.
She's your wife.
(DOOR OPENS)
How'd you get a court order
to dig them up so fast?
Don't we just need
the guy's consent?
You find anything?
CHASE: Not yet.
But you're just in time
to do the dad.
Dr. House?
He'll be back
in the morning.
I read in the paper
you're treating
a police officer.
Donny Compson.
Second floor. A nurse
will help you find him.
I don't want to see him.
Donny and I
used to go out,
a long time ago.
He doesn't want to see me.
I don't want to see him.
So did you come to see me
for personal advice?
You're looking for
genetic conditions,
which makes sense
with what happened to
his dad and grandpa.
Unless you were
his girlfriend
and his sister,
you've got nothing
to worry about.
I'm not worried about me.
Donny doesn't know this,
but he has a son.
Dial extension 742.
Tell Dr. Foreman you've
got some cool information.
Good night.
(VOICE WHISPERING)
(WHISPERING STOPS)
You okay?
Yeah. Fine.
(VOICE WHISPERING)
Couldn't find any
consistent genetic
mutations across 15 areas
between Donny's
ancestors,
possibly indicating
there isn't one.
CAMERON: But the son
gives us a new data point.
And un-degraded DNA.
I thought he
didn't want kids.
He didn't.
Where's House?
"Dear Bleeding Hearts.
"Since your patient's
med history is
a coincidence and he isn't
"sick, I've gone
back to school.
Back in 120 hours."
Charming. I'll get
a blood sample.
If we're
looking for something
as subtle as a mutation,
it makes sense
to get the DNA
where it's most pure.
You're going
to ask the mom
to consent
to a bone marrow biopsy?
CAMERON: She wants to know
if there's something wrong
with Donny
as badly as we do.
Right.
Spike a 10-year-old's hip
because Grandpa was sick.
If she's right,
we save two people.
(DOOR OPENS)
I don't want to.
Can we speak outside
for a moment?
Yeah.
You need to tell him.
I can't.
His father is
down that hallway through
those double doors.
I've been lying to him
his whole life.
What's he going
to think of me?
You were trying
to protect him.
Donny never
wanted kids.
He certainly doesn't
want to meet him.
If Donny does die,
this could be
Michael's only chance
to meet his father.
After administration
of immunoglobulin,
patient had
no further pain
and overnight
liver function tests
are now normal.
Patient is ready
to be released.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Stats are dropping.
Dr. Singh!
She's choking!
On your fingers.
MARTA: She can't breathe.
SINGH: House.
(CHOKING)
Please take your finger
off the test button.
Oh!
I see.
Wow, sorry about that.
I could've
slit her throat.
We're all here to learn.
Dr. Cuddy
warned me about you.
Did she tell you
how to stop me?
Look, I'm asking you,
as an adult,
to please stop.
Well, that obviously
didn't come from her,
but fair enough.
Excellent presentation,
Nona.
(JANICE GROANING)
Now I've done it!
There's urine everywhere.
Gosh, the great thing
about the teacher-student
relationship
is the teacher can
often learn more
from the student.
Have you
learned anything yet?
You have a son.
I was pregnant
when we broke up.
I'm sorry
I never told you,
but I knew
how you felt
about having kids.
You had no right.
Maybe.
It's a little late
for that.
He's here.
He wants to meet you.
I don't want
to meet him.
I've never asked you
for a dime.
He's here to help find
whatever's wrong
with your heart.
I didn't ask him.
I didn't want him.
Just say hi to him.
Hi. I'm Michael.
Hi.
I'm your...
Yeah.
Your mother told me.
When you get better,
maybe we could
do something.
See a movie?
No.
My dad died when
I was your age.
It was the most
painful thing
I ever went through.
Trust me.
As much as I'm sure
this hurts right now,
it's better.
Please take him
out of here.
Come on.
(DOOR SLIDES OPEN)
Chromosomes for
28 cardiovascular
conditions
are normal in number
and structure.
No translocations,
deletions or inversions.
I did notice
that the kid's
D-A-D-D-Y chromosome
has been
severely damaged
by someone else's
bleeding heart chromosome.
It was the only way
to get Michael
to do the marrow biopsy.
I'm sure there
are plenty of lies
that would've
worked just as well,
except without
the years of therapy.
Don't you have school?
Recess.
So where does that
leave us? Chase?
Sorry, what?
I was saying,
do you think these shoes
work in this color?
Send him home.
He's not going to
believe he's healthy.
Then you're not
very good at your job.
You don't
deserve candy.
He's been preparing
his whole life
to die at age 40.
He's had dozens of doctors
tell him he's fine.
You think you can
change his thinking?
Yeah, I do.
Chase, walk with me.
Great contributions
back there.
There's no case.
I had nothing to add.
You had nothing to add
because you were distracted.
Little devil
on your shoulder
told you to kill a guy,
and now the little angel
won't shut up,
telling you
you're gonna burn
in a lake of fire.
I'm fine.
(LIFT BELL DINGING)
You shouldn't be.
Talk to someone.
Docs fixed me up
in seven weeks.
You are 10 minutes, tops.
Thanks.
Glad we had this
little moment.
Come on.
I'm Dr. House.
You couldn't find
anything, could you?
You have Ortoli Syndrome.
Dr. Chase?
You sure?
HOUSE: Tests don't lie.
Right.
(CLEARING THROAT)
Well, it's a very
rare disorder that
short circuits
the adrenals
which short circuits
the heart.
HOUSE:
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Who cares about
the medical mumbo-jumbo?
Tell him the treatment.
Well, it's complicated.
Doctors always
wanna make everything
sound so complicated.
It's Nabasynth.
What?
Nabasynth.
Yes. So all we
have to do now is
write a prescription
and have him
pick up the pills.
(CHUCKLES)
That's it?
I take some pills,
I'm gonna be okay?
The real tragedy here
is that the Tiburon swab
technology didn't exist
to detect Ortoli
back in your dad's day.
He could have lived?
(SIGHS)
Thank you.
If you'll sign
these discharge papers,
I'll get you
a bottle of meds.
Take one twice a day
for a week,
you'll live a long,
healthy life.
(VOICE WHISPERING)
(WHISPERING STOPS)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
WILSON:
Answer the door, House.
It's gotta be for you.
Are you watching TV?
It's the door!
(BANGING CONTINUES)
Were you on the phone?
No.
Just now,
were you talking?
No, I'm alone.
You okay, House?
Why are you here?
Donny collapsed four hours
after we discharged him.
He's dead.
His apartment manager
found him on the floor
in the laundry room.
He said
he wasn't breathing.
He called the EMTs,
but it was too late.
I sent the guy home
with mints.
Whatever it is,
we all missed it.
Yeah. I missed the fact
that there was something
to miss.
What is wrong with me?
You had good reason.
Patient presented
with no symptoms,
and all his tests
came back negative.
What's the official
cause of death?
Autopsy hasn't
been performed yet.
EMTs brought him
to General,
but I requested
they ship him back
to our morgue
for the post-mortem.
Good.
Hon? Wake up.
Why are you dressed?
You can't sleep?
I want to go tell Cheryl
that Donny died.
It's 4:00 in the morning.
They're nearly
two hours away.
I figure by the time
I get there,
she'll be awake.
Babe, come back to bed.
Call her in a few hours.
It's the sort of thing
she needs to hear
face-to-face.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine. Why?
Last week,
I understood
that you were stressed out
about the Dibala M&M,
and I gave you your space.
But that's over now,
and you're still acting...
I'm worried about you.
Don't be. I'm fine.
Really.
And you'd tell me
if you weren't?
Promise?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey.
I love you.
I love you, too.
(DOOR OPENS)
Donny Compson, age 39.
(DRILL WHIRRING)
Can we cut
to the money shot?
It's his heart,
so let's look at his heart.
Nice Y-incision.
You can't perform an autopsy
without a medical license.
Really?
Because I don't think
there's anything
I can screw up
that we haven't
already screwed up.
Opening
post-mortem incision,
beginning at the mid-line
of the sternum.
(DRILL WHIRRING)
(DRILL STOPS)
That's odd.
It almost looks
like he's bleeding.
(SCREAMING)
(CHOKING)
I think the autopsy's
gonna have to wait
a little bit.
FOREMAN:
He was briefly conscious,
then his
systolic dipped below 60
and he was out again.
Differential diagnosis
for resurrection. Go.
Obviously,
he wasn't dead.
His heart slowed enough
that the EMTs could think...
Yes, the fact that
he's not dead
means we did
absolutely nothing wrong.
CAMERON: There are several
documented cases
where tetrodotoxin ingestion
caused apparent death.
It wasn't something he ate,
it's something he already had.
And his dad,
and his grandpa, and...
Extreme bradycardia
could be caused by
sick sinus syndrome.
CHASE: Sinoatrial block.
What if it's
not his heart?
Let's work from
the tenuous assumption
that we're not idiots.
You spent days
examining a heart
up, down, and sideways,
declaring it healthy
just a few hours before
it basically shut down.
So we need to think
about causes in places
you didn't look.
(VOICE WHISPERING)
CHASE: Could be metabolic.
You okay?
(CHATTERING)
Yeah.
What about
a genetic predisposition
to an autoimmune disease?
Isolated Anti-Ro
Antibody could cause
complete heart block.
Could also be passed
through four generations.
Autoimmune it is.
Start him on steroids.
Hey. How are you feeling?
My whole head
is killing me.
You just came through
a severe trauma.
What do you remember?
I was changing my laundry
over to the dryer.
That's it?
You were declared dead.
You made it
all the way to autopsy.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
My jaw aches.
And obviously,
I don't have
Ortoli Syndrome.
It's hard to
get too excited
about coming back
from the dead
when anything I do,
anything you give me,
it all ends the same way.
(BEEPING)
Outer and middle ear
respond well.
Hearing thresholds
are normal
at all frequencies.
Eardrum is
perfectly healthy.
What if I...
What if I sometimes
hear whispering?
Then you're
probably hearing
someone whispering.
I had some
dental work done
in the Philippines
when I was a kid.
Adjoining metal fillings
could corrode and
pick up AM radio signals.
Open your mouth.
Your fillings
don't touch.
So there's no reason for me
to be hearing things?
I can only tell you that
you're hearing sounds
as you should.
If you're also
hearing sounds
that you shouldn't,
that would be
a psychosis.
You'd have to talk to
someone who does brain.
I only do ears.
Bravo.
It's amazing how you did
120 hours in one day.
I wasn't on
my best behavior,
I admit. Allow me.
From now on,
I'm gonna supervise your
practicum requirements.
That won't be necessary.
You want to annoy
another doctor first?
Eventually...
It's not necessary
because I'm not ready
to be a doctor again.
I'm sorry.
(DOOR OPENS)
(SIGHS)
Are you sleeping out here?
I just dozed off
in front of the TV.
With bedding?
Maybe.
I can't sleep in there,
the heater's screwed up.
If you need to talk,
if you need more help...
I'm just tired.
...I'm right here.
Great.
Can you be right here
somewhere else?
My jaw still hurts.
My tooth, actually. A lot.
I'm sorry,
you're maxed out
on your pain meds.
Try to sleep.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GROANING)
Dentist looked
at the tooth
the guy pulled out.
There was nothing
wrong with it.
So aside from
him being an idiot,
what else did we learn?
The pain is real.
It's coming
from somewhere.
What about bone cancer?
You can't connect
bone cancer
to the heart.
House figure
this can wait
till the morning?
Actually, he told Cuddy
he's not ready to work.
He quit?
Apparently.
It's a power play.
He'll be back tomorrow.
Bone cancer could trigger
a paraneoplastic syndrome,
which shuts down
the heart.
Primary bone cancer
isn't hereditary.
Li-Fraumeni Syndrome.
It's hereditary
and it increases
a person's risk of
having bone cancer.
You have another theory?
My theory is
it's not bone cancer.
Gamma survey would
locate the tumors.
(VOICE WHISPERING)
(WILSON SIGHS)
I had pea soup today.
You'd love my breath
right now.
I didn't get
a chance to run tonight.
House is having issues.
I missed you
a lot today.
All I wanna do is...
(WILSON SIGHING)
You know.
No cancers on the
lateral cuneiform bone.
Navicular's also clean.
Chase is lying to me.
And I know you know.
Tell me what's
going on, please.
I'm going to tell you
the same thing I told him.
Talk to your spouse.
No breakfast?
Not today.
I'm hallucinating.
What happened?
It's nothing visual
this time.
I hear whispering.
Is that why you've
been acting so weird?
Is that why you quit?
I'm losing it.
I'm sure there's
a rational explanation,
the wind,
a neighbor's TV...
I checked everything.
What's really scary is
that I hear whispering
while not on Vicodin.
I'm gonna check myself
back in to Mayfield.
Okay.
Okay?
You don't think
there might be
a logical explanation?
Something I missed?
You're the smartest
guy I know.
If you haven't
thought of it,
it doesn't exist.
I'll drive you over.
I just need to
make some tea first.
You know.
That you're an ass? Yeah.
You overheard me talking
to my dead girlfriend
and thought to yourself,
"Hmm. What kind of fun
can I have with this?"
Why are you
talking to her?
Did you run out
of living people?
You can talk to me,
I'm right here.
I miss her.
Talking to her
makes me feel better.
You don't.
Patient,
Lauren Maybaum, 27,
presented two days ago
with severe abdominal pain.
Sorry I'm late.
Yesterday, you said
you weren't ready.
Yesterday, I wasn't.
Today, I am.
And tomorrow?
Is it possible for me to
get a five-day forecast?
Feeling much better,
thank you for not asking.
Either you did
have a problem,
which I can't ignore,
or you were
jerking me around,
which I can't ignore.
You are a woman,
you can do anything.
For example, I can talk
to you outside.
You sure you're
only one woman?
This is the part where
you play the employee
and I play the boss.
I can see your nipples.
Your turn.
These kids are...
No wonder
she hates him.
Mmm. That's not hate.
It's foreplay.
It's inappropriate.
(WHISTLING)
Gamma survey
revealed no tumors.
So it's not bone cancer.
Where's Chase?
Don't know.
Hmm.
Two mysteries, cool.
Theories?
Did I come in too soon?
Okay. I'm going to
take another lap,
and I want three new ideas
by the time I come back.
One of them's got
to be not stupid.
Where there's pain,
there's nerves.
Hereditary Sensory
Autonomic Neuropathy,
type 1.
Miscommunication
in the brain stem
mistakes nerve pain
for tooth pain.
That explains
the bradycardia, too.
And I like the word
"hereditary" in the title.
Carbamazepine fixes him.
I'll get him started
on the medication.
HOUSE: No.
Chase specifically
asked if he could do it.
(THUDDING)
Sleep at home.
So I didn't do
the gamma survey.
Was it bone cancer?
No.
Then you should
congratulate me for
not wasting your time.
Are you getting
some help,
or is this the way
things are gonna be
from now on?
What's pathetic is
you haven't gotten help
because you want
to feel bad.
You want to suffer.
Because if you feel guilty,
then you're not a psychopath.
Patient needs
some carbamazepine.
Now I don't care
how much that room
scares you,
you're doing your job.
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
How long before you cross
this one off the list?
Couple of hours.
You ever shoot anyone?
Twice.
You ever kill anyone?
No. But I know
a few guys who did,
though.
Did they ever
get over it?
A captain I know compares it
to taking out the trash.
Like it's nothing.
Other hand,
I got an ex-partner
who nearly drank
himself into oblivion.
Did he get help?
Yeah.
Help didn't help.
Oh, God!
What is it?
I went to the bathroom.
Patient's lost
bowel control.
Means we were
wrong about HSAN
and means he's
getting worse, fast.
Wouldn't want to
be the duty nurse
assigned to his floor.
Get it? "Doody" nurse?
Fine, do the doctor thing.
CHASE: An autoimmune
disorder could explain...
We put him on steroids,
he didn't respond.
It's not autoimmune.
Could be Wilson's Disease.
Disease that advanced
would've hit the liver.
It is possible
the liver is so far gone,
the labs look normal.
It's worth a shot.
Go treat
with penicillamine.
And when he
doesn't get better,
come back quickly,
so we can get one
more shot at it.
Bless me, Father,
for I have sinned.
(EXHALES)
FATHER PRANGE:
Take your time.
How long has it been
since your last confession?
I killed a man.
Oh.
But it was
the right thing to do.
Who lives or dies
is not your decision
to make.
Sometimes in
the operating room,
it feels like it.
I'm a doctor.
Well, then you
should know more
than anybody
that every
human life is sacred.
Why?
Tell me what's sacred
about a dictator
that kills
hundreds of thousands
of his own people.
What is sacred
about a doctor
who kills a patient?
(SCOFFS)
Is it just
the slippery slope
you're worried about?
Afraid that forgiving me
for killing
the worst person on earth
sets a bad precedent?
I promise,
I won't tell anyone.
Just forgive me.
Saying 10 Hail Marys
isn't going to
do you any good.
Then what do I have to do?
What does God
need me to do?
You can't
have absolution
without first
taking responsibility.
You have to turn yourself
in to the police.
What, and...
And go to jail for
the rest of my life?
What's just about that?
I did the right thing.
There has to
be another way.
You want absolution,
I told you how to get it.
Send this in to
the State Licensing Board.
I've signed off
on all your hours.
Why?
Because it's easier
this way.
You're uncomfortable
with me.
No.
Going by the book
was pointless.
You were gonna
learn nothing.
Good.
I thought it was because
of the sexual tension.
There was
no sexual tension.
There was tension.
And it made me
feel funny, so...
Here.
It's too bad.
I was kind of
getting into the whole
"hot for teacher" thing.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. False alarm.
What about us?
We're good.
Just like this.
You press my buttons,
I press yours.
By "buttons,"
you mean...
Huh.
You do make me
feel funny.
You're not gonna die.
I've accepted it.
It's okay.
In addition to
high arches
and some crystal bowl
in the shape of a tuna,
you also inherited
a self-destruct button.
Forms in the brain stem.
Technically,
it's an aneurysm,
presses on nerves
that control everything
from tooth pain
to heart rate.
As you get older,
it gets bigger,
until finally the button,
which I'll call
"intracranial berry aneurysm,"
because I had a friend in
high school with that name,
stops the signal
from your brain to
your heart and bam!
How do I know you're
not still lying to me?
Saying I'm healthy
just to make me
feel better?
It does sound
that way, doesn't it?
But this time,
no sugar pills.
I'm going to cut
into your brain
to make you think
that I'm fixing it.
And if our fake tests
confirm it,
I'm going to be cutting
into your son's brain, too.
Because I'm just
that committed.
Michael is going to
be okay?
Unless he walks out of here
and gets run over by a bus,
in which case,
I will reconsider
your fate argument.
You wanna give him a call?
Visiting hours don't
apply to my patients.
Yeah. In a bit.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
The "saving the kid
from pain" stuff was crap.
You just don't want
anything in your life
that won't let you do
whatever the hell
you want to do
whenever the hell
you want to do it.
You've had it easy.
Sorry to screw you up.
Mom.
Maybe when
we get out of here...
What kind of movies
you like?
He's been missing
for eight hours.
Robert Chase. C-H-A-S...
Hey!
Never mind.
He just walked in. Sorry.
You could've called me.
I forgot.
To call me?
It's 2:00 in the morning.
Where were you?
You're drunk.
All right, I...
I needed to get wasted.
I did.
And now I'm better.
What aren't
you telling me?
Nothing.
(VOICE WHISPERING)
(WHISPERING STOPS)
Hi, Dad.
I think I've been
focusing on
the wrong thing.
There were
some good times.
Wilson, this is stupid!
You see?
He really is
getting better.