* got me mixed up,
so I turned out the light *
* and I don't know how... *
Are you ever coming to bed?
I still say
I'm a vegetarian.
Well, you can say
that you're an astronaut,
But that doesn't make it true.
A salmon is not a vegetable,
Frankie.
Well, apparently, eight out of
ten commenters agree with you.
Except for the part
where you said,
"I believe
what I want to believe."
That they found
a little judgmental.
You blogged our argument?
I asked you to quit
talking about me.
I don't want a bunch of people
that I don't know
Hearing stuff that's meant
to be between me and you.
I write about my life.
And you're a big part
of that.
That's great. I want to be
a big part of your life.
But I don't want to be
a big part of their lives.
Take it down,
erase it, delete it.
Make it go away.
Come on, man.
It's 2:00 in the morning.
These walls are made
out of tissue paper.
I gotta be up in three hours
to do a wiring job in Edison.
I'm sorry.
We'll try to hold it down.
Sorry.
Frankie,
what happened?
whoa, whoa.
That's not what you think.
Something's wrong.
We need a police car
at 152 Haverhill.
Whoa, what are you two
talking about?
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
I think it's coming
From my gums.
* House 6x14 *
Private Lives
Original Air Date on March 8, 2010
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com --
* *
what are you doing tonight?
Masturbating.
I'd invite you,
But people are
already talking.
It's pathetic.
You divide your nights
Between porn
and the discovery channel.
Right.
Playing dance dance revolution
Is a much better choice.
Okay, that was a gift
from a patient,
And it happens
to be great exercise.
I mean,
who rents porn anymore?
Can't you get this stuff
on the internet?
You can.
But you can't get disc two
with the director's commentary.
Come out with me tonight.
I'm going speed dating.
You mean you're dating
on meth?
Count me in.
You need to meet somebody.
This way,
you meet 20 somebodies.
Over a five-minute discussion
of proust?
Speed dating's
a meat market.
Yeah, dozens of women
just waiting to be hit on.
Your odds of a happy ending
are nearly as good
As staying home
and watching porn.
You plan on doing
any work today?
I thought I might do
a little light doctoring
In the afternoon.
28-year-old female
sudden unexplained coagulopathy.
Could be
congenital thrombocytopenia.
Platelets look normal.
patient makes money
doing freelance photography.
Some photographic processes
produce toxic gases.
she's a blogger.
I can't see her photos
being anything but digital.
What does she blog?
Politics?
Dominatrix? Cooking?
'cause I need recipes.
it's a personal journal.
I don't get putting
your whole life online.
it's not that crazy.
Privacy's basically
a modern invention.
Towns used to be too small
for anybody
To keep any secrets.
What if it's not the platelets,
but the glue
That holds 'em together?
No.
Thrombin and von Willebrand
factor are normal.
and knowing too much
about each other
Is exactly
why people leave small towns
And move to the city.
and a lot of people
choose to stay
Because, in return
for zero privacy,
You get community,
connection.
Big red as for our tunics.
Connections are for airports.
For people, we have
over 300 cable channels.
her photos may be digital--
Doesn't mean
she couldn't have been exposed
To some other toxin.
We should search
the apartment.
Eeny, meeny, miny,
Thirteen and tiny.
This one's locked.
I'm supposed you took
the pro-community position.
I have friends.
I like people.
You also like secrets.
You deny it,
It sort of proves
my point.
When we're left
to our own devices,
We make lousy choices.
Ignore it.
I can hear you in there.
Open the door,
or I'm calling the cops.
We're four stories up,
but there's a fire escape
On the other wall.
The ledge
might be wide enough.
We're doctors.
We aren't stealing anything.
We're collecting samples.
Who are you?
The neighbor.
Did they say that you could
come in here and--
Yup. What do you know
about Frankie and Taylor?
Not much.
The guy works a lot.
I see Frankie around.
We argue
a few times a week,
And then we go back
about our business.
What do you argue about?
Frankie's got
some strong opinions.
Wants to recycle
every molecule of trash.
You take
the anti-recycling position?
Trash piling up
for composting's
Attracting every rat
in the neighborhood.
I had
to put down poison.
It's her private drawer.
What are you doing over there?
She said
she doesn't have any secrets.
I'm taking her
at her word.
Is there any chance
Frankie touched the rat poison?
Touched it?
She grabbed a chunk of it
Right out of the mouth
of the schnauzer
From down the hall.
Now every time I put the stuff
down, she picks it back up.
* oh *
* *
* come on *
* can you feel it *
* everybody can make up
their own mind *
* running round in circles *
* gettin' left behind *
You brought a date?
Wilson seemed to think
it was a good idea.
You need to dive back
into the pool.
And he has to swim
in ours?
You go to a bar,
you bring your ugly friends.
It's not a beauty pageant.
Life is a beauty pageant.
Little girls who kiss frogs
expect them to turn into you.
Oh, come on.
I'm not that good-looking.
Yeah, you are.
You kind of are.
So you attribute
every relationship
I've ever had to the height
of my cheekbones?
Not the whole relationship.
Just the beginning.
The rest is your hair.
This is ridiculous.
Women aren't as distracted
By appearances as we are.
They look deeper.
You wanna bet?
You can't tell anyone
you're a doctor.
You're unemployed.
You're also a little slow,
Misunderstanding
everything they say.
And lose the accent.
A hundred bucks says
you still walk out of here
With a dozen names.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the fun is about to start.
When I strike this gong,
each man should sit at the table
You've been assigned.
When I strike it again,
date's over,
Move on.
I'm an oncologist.
Oh, my aunt and my grandma,
they both died
From breast cancer.
Do--do you wanna
talk about it?
I'm a diagnostician.
I find out what's wrong
with people, and I fix it.
Don't all doctors do that?
Yeah, but they can't dance
like I can.
I play video games.
Oh.
Professionally?
I wish, bro.
After six months of chemo, we
thought he was out of the woods.
I don't want kids.
Check.
I'm thinking about going
from a "c" to a "d."
Quadruple check.
And I'm on fire
for the lord.
I'm a chocolatier.
I could tell
by your hips.
Yeah, I guess I could afford
to lose a few pounds.
I don't think I know anybody
who died of cancer.
Thank God.
For you, I mean.
Obviously.
Except my cat.
she died a few months ago.
I hate these things.
What, are you here
at gunpoint?
You need me
to call 911?
Friend dragged me.
She keeps trying
to fix my life.
Which, admittedly,
could use it, but...
Still annoying.
You like puzzles.
I hoped my job would let me
play with puzzles all day long,
But it didn't work out
that way.
Police detective.
Turns out
criminals are idiots.
If they're not gonna bother
to challenge you,
What's the point?
Is there a fire alarm
we could pull?
Maybe get out
of here.
Hmm.
Except...
Maybe you're
just too swoft.
Beg your pardon.
Swoft.
It's one
of your crossword answers.
I believe it means
lying manipulator
Who tells men anything
they want to hear.
You brought a prop
as a conversation starter.
Folded the paper
to make it look read,
Filled in some answers,
but you couldn't be bothered
To work at it, so you just
put in random letters.
You have some natural talent
as a liar,
But not enough brains
to see it through.
I'm gonna assume
you're not a cop.
Are the five minutes up?
These women would welcome
a call from you.
And these women would
welcome a call from you.
My.
It's nice
to have visitors.
I'm updating my blog.
And I'm reading it.
You realize
you're in the same room?
Sorry.
So I've been thinking
about what you said.
And I'm sure
I washed my hands
After I threw out
the rat poison.
Apparently you did it
multiple times
Over a course of days.
Can't be too certain.
you must be Dr. Foreman.
Got to get back
to work.
Okay.
Take it easy.
What?
She reads my blog.
Personally, I don't think
you're condescending at all.
That's not what I wrote.
When you were taking
my history,
I told you I went whitewater
rafting six months ago,
And you said,
"it was unlikely to be related."
I was just giving information.
Let's face it.
You got a little snarky.
You can't convey a tone
of voice in writing.
I just put what you said.
If you don't want people
To think you're condescending,
Maybe you shouldn't say
condescending things.
Can this wait a second?
'cause I have to pee.
You know, I think
people behave badly
Because there are no records
Of what we say or do.
And nobody believes anymore
That God's watching.
Well, God's not,
but I am.
Everything is on the record,
Including everything I do.
I don't think
My pee is supposed
to be mud-colored.
We were wrong
about the rat poison.
Coagulopathy plus kidney
equals what?
hemolytic uremic syndrome.
Normal creatinine levels.
She has
elevated cholesterol.
Hey, Wilson!
Can't find my pornos.
Have you tried
offering a reward?
gaucher's disease.
It would affect her ability
to synthesize vitamin k.
She's on a semi-vegetarian diet.
Means she gets plenty
of vitamin k.
Sjogren's is more likely.
I assume you moved them
while you were dusting.
I checked the drawers,
windowsill,
Dvd player
in your room.
The quiet ones
are always deeply repressed.
I returned them to the store.
she had a fish dinner
a couple of nights ago.
Could be haff disease
causing rhabdo.
What? Why did you
return them to the store?
It's no trouble.
I had to stop next-door
for my dry cleaning anyway.
sjogren's wouldn't inhibit
the clotting enzymes,
Infiltrate the kidneys--
explains everything.
So does haff disease.
I'm not thanking you.
I'm asking you why.
because if I did happen
To bring a woman home
last night,
I wanted it to be
a porn-free zone.
You do realize things
don't have to be socks
To go into a sock drawer.
I'm sorry.
Horribly, horribly sorry.
I thought you'd...
Watched them all.
You completely ruined
my morning.
I had to pull out
your old family photos.
Your mom
was pretty hot.
Haff disease
fits the timing best.
Start her on saline
and mannitol.
You reading
your patient's blog?
Nope.
You should.
Could be some clues.
Too many. Be like doing
a whole body scan.
Send us up
eight blind alleys.
That's why Chase
is doing it.
She mentions you.
She's never met me.
You're an unseen
presence,
Like the wizard of oz.
He was a fraud.
She couldn't have gone
with keyser soze?
Speaking of movies
that don't make any sense,
I stopped at the rental store
to get those pornos back.
I told the guy at the counter
I was so grateful
That you'd returned them,
but I wanted them.
Guess what.
You only returned two.
You lost the third.
It's decent of you
to pay for it,
Not let them put it
on my bill.
You know...
I can explain
what happened.
I'm sure you could.
But rather than listen
to your lies,
I thought it'd be more fun
to drive allver town
And get another copy.
You have--
you have it here?
* *
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
Okay, first,
That's not me.
It's not--
mostly not--
I was in college.
I don't--
my roommate was minoring
In film.
Are you hyperventilating?
Remember that covering your
mouth and one nostril can help.
He had to get this in
for some grade,
And he was desperate.
And the only reason I did it
Was because no one
would ever see it.
Who knew he'd become
an actual director?
He's not a director.
He's an artist.
The way he plays with light
and darkness and...Boobs.
that's not me.
What are you?
Where are you taking me?
Be not afraid.
The forest nymphs have taught me
how to please a woman.
That's not me.
That's not--
I mean, you can see
It's not me.
He added extra scenes
So he could release it
as a porno.
Be not afraid,
Wilson.
You took risks
for your art.
oh, boy.
No one--
hey, look at me.
No one can know
about this.
From this moment on,
my lips are sealed.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Be not afraid.
Find anything?
Relevant? No.
Interesting. I guess.
There's nothing
that she doesn't share.
"angry sex
is overrated.
"how can he expect me
to be aroused
When I'm so pissed
at him?"
Revelations like that might
just earn her a new kidney.
An hour after she blogged
About her kidney failure,
The hospital got a call
from Singapore.
One of Frankie's readers asking
how hard it would be to donate.
How good-looking am I?
I'm not asking
if you're attracted to me.
I'm looking
for an objective answer.
Oh, okay, then it's
an appropriate question.
Last night, I acted
like a complete tosser
To prove to House
that women don't go out
With me for my looks.
Cost me a hundred bucks
And my definition
of myself.
And women.
So date men.
They're not shallow
at all.
Everything's physical.
Yes.
We are physical beings.
Some more than others.
Please don't define my entire
gender based on one night.
No, what if the patient's
problem is a physical reaction,
Not an emotional one?
What if her lack of arousal
Had nothing to do
with their fight?
Sjogren's would inhibit
her normal secretions.
sorry for keeping you up.
I thought it better
not to wait till morning.
Oh, it's no problem.
I'm a night owl.
Thanks.
So you think I might have
this sjogren's
'cause of my lack of discharge?
Yeah.
It's lucky
you wrote about that.
And a little crazy,
you're thinking,
To share that much?
Not crazy.
Unusual to be so intimate
with people you don't know.
But I do know them.
They read my blog,
I comment on theirs.
Just 'cause you haven't met
someone physically
Doesn't mean
you don't know them.
What about you?
Are you in a relationship?
It recently ended.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Lie flat on your back
all the way.
But you saw each other
every day, right?
How much did you tell her
about what you were thinking?
Or did you just
end up talking
About where you were going
to dinner
And who needed
to do the laundry?
Is that what your relationship
with Taylor is like?
No.
Oh, maybe a little.
You know, he's great,
but sometimes it's easier
To open up to people
who aren't looking at you.
You need to lie flat
for us to get the x-ray.
I'm actually not comfortable
on my back.
Can't we do it
this way?
Did you strain a muscle?
No.
What's wrong?
I've booked our patient in
for heart surgery.
I was doing a sialogram
on her,
And she didn't want
to lie on her back.
That's a complaint you hear
from people
With heart valve issues.
It fits.
Sjogren's damaged her heart,
Causing her clotting problems,
Causing her kidneys
to fail.
you based all that
on the fact
That she didn't want
to lie down?
Well, that
and the cardiac echo I performed
After she didn't want
to lie down.
Her mitral valve
is nearly gone.
Which means
she's nearly gone.
God, you're pretty.
so we can replace
the mitral valve
With a pig valve
or with a plastic one.
from an actual pig?
it's the better choice
if you want
To have children someday.
A plastic valve requires you
to be on anticoagulants,
Which are known to cause
birth defects.
On the other hand,
The pig valve wears out quickly,
So you'd need to have
heart surgery again
In ten years.
I know that you're on the fence
about having kids,
But Taylor really wants them.
It's in the blog.
I'm afraid you two will need
to agree on that decision
Earlier than planned.
It's your call.
Can you pass me
my laptop?
Seriously?
I want to get
some feedback.
You really think
that asking strangers
For some off-the-top-
of-their-head response
Is gonna be helpful here?
A lot of your readers
are into animal rights.
They've got you 2/3 of the way
to vegan.
What are they gonna say
about you buying your life
With the life of a pig?
Whatever they say,
I don't have to do it.
It won't work out
that way.
And we're the ones
that are gonna have
To live with this.
Please, Frankie.
Don't tell them.
If I start picking
and choosing,
I'm being dishonest.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Though I guess
I should thank
Whoever taught you
how to please a woman.
Maybe it was
the forest nymphs.
Get my Vertigo poster back.
Be not afraid.
It's exact change.
Okay.
Hello?
I'm looking to get something
on House.
Couldn't you just ask
the love nymphs for the secret?
Don't.
My mission is to find
Something that House would not
like to see made public
And make it public.
In.
But you know him better
than anyone.
Why do you need
my help?
House would never leave anything
secret around the condo.
But you've worked
in the same office with him,
On and off,
for years.
Think back.
Were there ever
any odd phone calls
Or visitors
from the past?
He openly brings prostitutes
into the hospital,
And he gambles with bookies
'cause he's too lazy
To go to the otb.
And you're asking
for some--
What?
He's reading
the golden bowl.
The gold--
by Henry James?
Yeah.
No, no,
he's not really reading it.
Okay.
I don't understand.
That book's
at least 400 pages long.
Whatever he's reading
is only half that thick.
Maybe he's reading a version
with a smaller font.
He's not using
his reading glasses.
That's a good point.
He took the cover
off the golden bowl
And put it onto this other book
so no one would know
What he was reading.
Whatever it is,
he's ashamed of it.
Huh.
I'm going with plastic.
It just makes
more sense.
I don't want
another operation later.
That's not
why you're doing this.
Look, when you were
first telling me
About why you love
the internet, you said
That no one has
to be alone again.
Whoever you are,
whatever you love,
You can connect
with someone.
If you want to recreate
the Boston Tea Party
While dressed
as imperial storm troopers,
You can find
the ten other people
In the world that have always
wanted to do that.
That hasn't changed.
But you have.
This thing that you do, it's
not about connection anymore.
It's about an audience.
It's a performance,
and you've got one eye
On the number of hits.
You've turned our lives
into their entertainment.
You're smart,
You're fun to read,
It's okay.
But don't give them this.
Or if you do, don't...
Expect me to be here.
Well,
it's a good cover choice.
It's not like anyone
would pick it up.
It's Cameron's favorite book.
I don't even know
what it's about.
Don't do that
to yourself.
what the hell?
Giving him a computer is like
giving plutonium to Dr. No.
Got it.
Step by step:
Sermons for everyday life?
These are literal sermons,
Written by a minister.
Loving thy neighbor
Even when thy neighbor's stereo
is keeping you up at night.
Why would he read this?
Why would he hide it?
He reads the bible,
he reads the koran,
He says he likes to know
what mistakes people are making.
You think
he's sincere?
You think that he's actually
getting something out of this?
I don't know.
What a hypocrite.
How can we use this
in a cruel yet funny way?
You know what?
Don't mention this
to anyone.
Well, so what was the point?
Are you gonna be here
when I wake up?
I hate that you don't
have a blog.
I hate that I don't know
what you're thinking.
Let's not get into it
right now.
We need to get you
through surgery.
I don't want
to go in there
Knowing that you'll stick
with me through surgery
'cause that's
what good guys do,
But once I'm better,
you'll be gone.
Let's not get into it now.
It hurts.
Is it her heart?
no, it's here.
Here.
Get her inside.
Your appendix burst.
We had to remove it.
And the biopsy confirms
it was full of abnormal cells
Consistent with lymphoma.
I have cancer?
We've postponed
putting in the new valve.
So I mean, I guess we do, what,
chemo and all that stuff?
Yes, but apparently
you've had this for some time.
When your appendix burst,
it was like a dam giving way.
The cells went streaming
throughout your body.
So you're saying you'll treat,
but you don't expect it to work.
That's why no valve.
It's pointless.
our dean of medicine
Has approved
an experimental treatment.
We use your unique
cancer cell signature
To create a targeted
lymphoma vaccine.
Okay, so that'll cure me?
Well, we're not actually sure
what it'll do,
But the intention is to train
your immune system
To recognize and kill cells
Bearing the same
malignant signature
While leaving
healthy cells alone.
But, as Dr. Foreman says,
It's experimental.
I see.
So without it, what kind
of time are we talking about?
An exact prognosis
is impossible.
Well, how about a guess?
Something, please.
Based on people
in situations like yours...
Maybe a year.
Baby, whatever we have to do,
we'll do.
I can take care of you.
I can work from home.
Sounds good.
Thank you
for letting me know.
We'll start with the treatment
whenever it's ready.
Is she being a good soldier,
or is she in denial?
Denial's not unusual
for a first reaction.
Or it could be
a symptom.
Some lymphomas
affect cognition.
If it is denial,
she needs time to process.
If it's a symptom,
Hopefully treatment
with the vaccine will help.
Hey, sandy.
Can I borrow your car?
She gave me the keys.
You're a doctor.
She was doing you a favor.
She barely knows me.
I've been deluding myself
That I'm actually
connecting with people.
The first person
I ever fell in love with
Turned out to be
a total tool.
I mean, he came across
all funny and charming
And thoughtful,
but it was an act.
He saw something he wanted,
And he knew he had to behave
a certain way to get it.
In retrospect, the fact
that I was 17 and he was 30
Should have been a clue.
Figuring out who people are
takes time.
It takes twice as much time if
they're trying to impress you.
Now I could take from this that
anyone who loans me their car
Has an ulterior motive,
Or I can accept that it's just
a nice thing to do
And take people
as they come.,
You wanna do
the first injection?
Why are you reading a book
by a unitarian minister?
Book club.
Oprah was going on and on...
I'm serious.
This--this is messed up.
Patient wrote it.
No, you've never treated
a patient with this name.
I looked it up.
It's an assignment
from my therapist.
No, it wasn't.
No one you respect
Would give you this
and expect it to be helpful.
It's a book!
Of sermons.
For anyone else,
spiritually enlightening.
For you, it's practically
a psychotic break.
I know that you have trouble
sometimes with the pain
Without the vicodin--
is that it?
Are you so out of options,
You're looking for answers in
what you consider irrationality?
I'm all right.
Trust me.
Are you all right
because you're back on vicodin?
I said, "trust me."
I know
this means something.
Do you mind?
I haven't finished it yet.
Thanks for the gift.
Obviously differs
From my own personal beliefs,
But if these stories
have helped you
Through some
spiritual turmoil--
Read chapter six,
Entitled "shut the hell up."
I appreciated the inscription
about the benefits of prayer
Before medical treatments.
And I think it's great
That you have been called
to witness by the lord.
Chapter two,
"bite me."
Hi.
Thirteen's giving our patient
Her third vaccine injection.
She's responding well
so far.
Where'd you get
all these copies?
It's out of print.
I called the author.
He's got cartons of the thing
in his basement.
You called him?
What'd you say?
That I knew some people
who could benefit spiritually
From the book.
Did you mention me?
Mm, no.
Fever's at 104.
The antibodies tripped
her autoimmune response.
The vaccine is killing her.
well, clearly it's not working.
You have to stop
the vaccine.
sure. Give up.
Let her die on schedule.
It's better than speeding up
the schedule.
How quickly did this come on?
She was all right
when I woke her this afternoon
To give her
the second injection.
of the stimulating agent,
Which,
added to the first injection,
Switched her immune reaction
into overdrive.
Why was she sleeping?
Who can sleep in a hospital
during the daytime?
I'm not surprised.
She's tired.
She's always been
a night owl.
Just by treating her,
We've completely disrupted
her schedule.
Is that what her blog says?
She's a night owl?
No, she told me.
in what tense? Is? Was?
Will have been?
I'm not sure.
What are you onto?
Look at the time stamp
on this post.
2:30 a.M.
Here's one at 4:00 a.M.
Whatever he's onto
doesn't change the fact
That she has lymphoma and we
gave her a dangerous vaccine.
We need to--
six months ago,
She's posting
in the daytime.
Two years ago,
daytime.
That's her natural rhythm.
Day-night reversal.
Sign of liver disease?
which doesn't fit lymphoma.
But we know
she has lymphoma.
We know she has
the cell atypia
That indicates lymphoma.
Biopsy her liver.
That was pretty cool
what I did, right?
You wanna make out?
You don't have lymphoma.
But you said my appendix
was full of cancer cells.
your appendix was full of cells
That showed
a lymphocytic atypia.
We now think they were
a granulomatous buildup
From some unknown cause.
So...
I'm not dying?
You're actually dying
more quickly than we thought.
unless we figure out
What's causing
your liver failure...
You have three or four days.
What the hell do you mean
I have three or four days?
Well, we're past denial.
Maybe we didn't cause
the fever.
We gave her
the vaccine,
And her fever spiked.
Seems to me--
yes, but it persisted
After we took her
off the vaccine.
What if it's a new symptom?
Okay.
So we add fever
to cell atypia, coagulopathy,
Kidney, heart, liver...
It has to be an infection.
but which one?
No one she knows is sick.
She hasn't traveled anywhere.
There's nothing in the history
she gave us.
Nothing in her blog.
There has to be something unique
to this infection.
Something
about its transmission
And the way it manifests.
There has to be something
she's not telling us.
There isn't.
She's told us,
and everyone else, everything.
Start her
on broad-spectrum antibiotics.
Since we know everything,
We might as well treat
for everything.
* *
* all those simple thoughts *
* all those
peaceful dreams *
* share the space *
* with a hard-worked,
hard-worked day *
* *
* glory, glory *
* hallelujah *
* *
* the sun is shining *
* shining down *
I picked up one of the copies
of the book
That Chase left
in the lounge.
If you're gonna be this way,
I'm not gonna invite you
to my baptism.
First time I'd seen
the real dust jacket.
The inside back flap, there was
a picture of the author.
Imagine how surprised
I was when I recognized him.
Your biological father
is a minister?
Natural selection
is not an infallible force.
I don't get it.
I mean, okay,
he was a friend of the family.
You'd only known him
when you were a kid.
But if you wanted
to meet him now,
Get an idea of what he's like,
Why not just go talk
to him?
"hi, it's greg.
You slept with my mother."
You're capable of it.
I was mildly curious.
Enough to read a book,
not enough to make a phone call.
Please.
You didn't read this.
You studied it.
Why?
All your life,
you've thought
This was crap.
You can't suddenly turn around
And build a whole new worldview
based on crap.
Crap.
You better not be faking this
Just to get out
of a tough conversation.
Do you poop?
Come on.
Everybody poops.
I read the book
in medical school.
Sinkers or floaters?
This is the wizard.
greasy and soft
Or hard and pellet-like?
Um...
Floaters and the first one.
You just had to be so swoft.
You're a hypocrite.
No lies, no secrets,
But everything stops
at your colon.
4,000 pages,
not one word about bms.
And I bet yours
don't smell at all.
Nobody wants to hear
about that stuff.
readers don't.
People who don't really
care about you don't.
But doctors might.
The icky stuff changed,
right, a few months ago?
Well, I became
a vegetarian.
A lot of people misunderstand
how a vegetarian diet works.
You take in
less unusable material,
And your waste
gets more efficient.
Harder and rounder.
Just look at the feces
of rabbits.
Seriously.
I think I might have some.
malabsorption.
Her system's not retaining
the necessary nutrients.
A g.I. Infection
causes malabsorption,
Granulomatous buildup
of cells.
It's not contagious since no one
around her got sick--
Whipple's disease.
Let's split the credit.
Start her
on co-trimoxazole.
We all need some secrets.
As long as they don't kill us,
they keep us safe and warm.
I'm...
I'm gonna be okay?
You'll still need
a new heart valve,
And you'll be on meds
for a few years,
But, basically, yeah.
Your odds are good.
Thank God.
I think I wanna go
with the pig valve.
I know you'll go crazy
if you don't tell people.
Thank God
you're an enabler.
Do you think people can actually
know each other better
On the internet
than face-to-face?
Faces can be distracting,
But there's nothing better
than looking into someone's eyes
And, well, everything
that goes with that.
I don't know.
People meet, they like
something superficial,
And then they
fill in the blanks
With whatever they want
to believe.
Why are you so hung up
on this?
I refuse to believe it's all
because you just noticed
You have a nice face.
You just came
off a relationship.
You know things
go deeper than...
Is that what this is about?
You and cameron?
I was the one
that pursued her.
Maybe I was just filling in
the banks.
Maybe...
Maybe the first reaction
was right.
We were just two people
who were in proximity
And found each other attractive,
and I never should have...
Paranoia.
You felt something real.
So did she.
Don't try
to take it back now.
Can I borrow your car?
No.
* she's on my mind *
* I swear it's 10,000 degrees
in the shade... *
Why would it make
more sense
For you to read
your father's book
Than to go
talk with him?
Can you write a book?
So I can stop talking
to you?
* 'cause every minute,
every second *
* every hour,
lord, every day... *
You weren't looking
for some big catharsis.
You didn't want
to hug the guy.
You just wanted
to know how his head works.
How he thinks.
'cause I'm fascinated
with how ministers think.
Because you're not
ordinary, House.
You're way out there
on the fringe somewhere.
I'm your best friend,
and half the time,
I don't understand you.
You're alone.
Been alone
your whole life.
When you read that book,
you were hoping that
Somewhere, underneath
all that talk of God,
There would be
a way of thinking,
A mind that you
could recognize.
You wanted
what we all want.
The power to transform
into any water-based object?
To look across the gulf
And know there's
someone else like you.
At least tell me this--
did you find something there?
Underneath the God stuff...
More God stuff.
* lochloosa,
she's on my mind *
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.com --