Okay.
"Therafy" me.
You're late.
You're fat.
It's unusual.
You know how far
the parking lot is?
My leg's been hurting.
Anything been on your mind lately,
any particular stress?
No. Probably just gonna rain.
Mm-hmm. You like the
new Monet reproduction
in the waiting room--
the Water Lilies?
I was late.
I wasn't focusing on the decor,
but it sounds appropriately
bland and calming.
Stress can also make you absentminded.
I'm not stressed...
Beyond the stress induced
by you telling me
how stressed I am.
Just an ordinary week.
Okay.
Tell me about it.
I had a patient.
House.
Good. I have a case for you.
Beer?
Amnesia.
She was found jogging in
the street, disoriented.
She almost got hit by a truck.
The MRI showed no abnormalities.
No I.D. on her.
Just her jogging clothes and
her heart rate monitor.
We know absolutely
nothing about her.
We know she has money.
Blaze outriggers-
400 bucks a pair.
People who have money don't
just disappear.
Sooner or later, someone's
gonna show up looking for her.
Can I have something to eat?
She just ate 15 minutes ago.
She keeps forgetting.
You don't eat because you
remember it's time to eat.
You eat 'cause you're hungry.
Her metabolism is in high gear.
She is an extreme
long-distance runner--
Why were you in the ER?
That's your question?
You're a psychotherapist.
You're hearing about
a great amnesia case,
and all you're asking
me is geography.
Just curious.
I was avoiding Wilson.
It's not something you
couldn't have seen
eight miles away.
Wilson's a processor.
I knew there were some things
that he'd want to process with me...
At length.
Sam's moving in.
If it's before Friday,
your assistant wins the pool.
I was just wondering
what your plans were.
Tonight?
In life.
Sam likes you...
But she wants me to move out.
No.
I want you to move out.
I didn't know things with
Sam would happen so quickly.
I didn't--
I don't want to
make a mistake here.
I've made a lot of mistakes.
By moving too quickly.
Given your usual
rate of commitment,
I'm surprised you're not
already re-divorced.
I could help you find a place.
What's wrong with my old place?
Nothing. I just thought...
You might want to
find somewhere new,
somewhere...
Where I didn't abuse
drugs and hallucinate.
Yes.
I'm fine.
You're fine?
Your best friend
is tossing you out,
and you're fine?
Why wouldn't I be?
? House 6x20 ?
Baggage
Original air date on May 10, 2010
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --
? ?
You're not feeling a little...
betrayed and angry?
Wilson bought a two-bedroom condo
specifically so that you
could move in with him.
It wasn't that long ago.
You don't feel a little...
jerked around?
He couldn't foresee Sam
coming back into his life.
That's a very rational
defense of your friend.
And, uh, I'm not buying it.
Based on what?
Based on the fact
that you were late,
and you didn't notice the
pictures in the outer office.
Those aren't symptoms.
They are to me.
And here's another one.
You took the case. Hmm?
No negotiating, no bargaining.
No clinic hours changed hands.
Were you looking for something
to distract you from the fact
that your best friend
just threw you out?
Case was interesting.
It's not organic.
It's not mysterious.
Most likely some psychologically
traumatic event occurred
that made the patient's brain
choose to forget everything.
Or not.
Here.
Loss of differentiation
between gray and white matter.
That's subtle.
But it's in the area
that controls memory.
Not likely it's a coincidence.
Bacterial infection?
Do I need to know this?
Fine. I'll give you the
cliff notes version--
chase--m.S. Taub--physical trauma.
I can tell you why
we ruled them out.
Or not.
It's probably a toxin,
and we need to find it
before it kills her.
We should search her House.
Good luck with that.
Her heart rate monitor
has a serial number.
The distributor can match
the number
to the store that sold it.
She's a serious athlete.
She might have been there
often enough to be remembered.
Brilliant.
Did he really say that?
Subtextually.
Long shot.
Even if the store clerk
doesn't know who she is,
the store's probably
close to where she lives.
Just seeing those surroundings
might spark a memory.
You want us to take her there?
No.
I'll take her.
Really?
Uh, it's unusual for you to
spend time with a patient,
isn't it?
Patients are boring...
As people.
This one I'm sure was no exception,
but her situation was interesting.
Besides, I was still
avoiding Wilson.
And no better way to avoid
than leaving the hospital.
Maybe.
Or were you avoiding going home?
There's a reason they tell addicts
to stay away from old geography.
I wasn't avoiding going home.
I'd already gone home...
Before I came into work that day.
I went straight
there from Wilson's.
Hey, take it easy! You're gonna kill me!
God, why don't people knock?
House, it's you! Where you been?
Hold up a second.
Alvie?
Juan alvarez-- you let
him stay at your place?
Not exactly.
I was beginning to wonder if
you were ever gonna show up.
Su casa, mi casa. Casa!
Why are you here?
When I left Mayfield,
I went back to the
old neighborhood.
You know, you shouldn't leave
the bathroom window unlocked.
Yeah, thanks for the safety lesson.
Why are you here?
Like I said, when I went
back to the neighborhood,
I found out immigration
was looking for me.
So I decided to visit
my old buddy House!
And turn his apartment into
a giant prison jumpsuit.
Juan alvarez is no freeloader.
I do my part, earn my keep.
The first week I made your dinner,
but you never showed up.
The second week i organized your stuff.
My stuff?
But still, you never showed up.
So this week, since I'm a real
good painter,
i decided to-- coffee table--
where'd you put it?
In the bedroom?
The paint's not cheap, House.
It's a custom color.
It's a mix of titanium,
yellow, and ochre.
Ochre--I don't even
like that stuff.
It's like a fruit.
It's got hair on it.
But they say it's a vegetable--
you sold my table to pay for
paint that I don't want?
I had to sell some
other things too.
Get out.
No, papa, just give
the color a chance.
Look, I'm going to work now.
And when I come back,
the walls will be a
less exciting color,
and you will be gone.
So Wilson threw you out,
and you threw alvie out--
just, uh, another week?
Unlike me, alvie didn't leave.
I took my motorcycle
to work that day.
When I went home to get my car,
he was painting the
ceiling magenta.
So I brought him with me
to protect the apartment.
Why?
To protect the apartment.
Whoa. Deja vu.
Tossing him out
or, uh, sending him to the movies
or, uh, locking him in the bathroom
would also minimize
alvie's destructive force.
But you chose his
company deliberately.
Why?
Obviously because he's a Wilson
substitute.
You can barely tell the
difference between them,
especially when Wilson
raps about the hood.
I'm not suggesting
alvie's a substitute,
but he would make a
great distraction.
From what?
That's what I'm trying to find out.
Go on.
Maybe the heart rate
monitor was a gift.
That's why no one recognized her.
Shut up, alvie.
Anything familiar...
Church, grocery store?
Sorry.
It's okay, Ms. x.
Maybe she's never been
to this town before,
bought the heart rate monitor
on the store's website.
You know that puerto ricans are U.
S. citizens, right?
Instead of working the case,
why don't you contemplate
the inanity of an American
with American immigration issues?
I had a birth certificate.
I lost it.
So get a new one.
I tried that, House.
But the town hall had burned
down when I was a kid,
destroyed the records.
There's only one copy?
They tried to make me fill
out a whole bunch of forms
before they'd give it to me.
I decided it would be quicker
and easier to do it myself.
How'd that go? They
figured out it was forged.
And now, for some reason,
they don't believe anything I say.
They actually think I'm lying
about being puerto rican.
Told me I had to go to a
special hearing to prove it.
What if nothing
ever looks familiar?
Then someone will show up-
a spouse, a friend--
to tell you who you really are
and what you should be feeling.
They always do.
I don't know who that is...
But I miss him.
What did they say at the hearing?
I didn't go.
I lied once.
Your mother is puerto rican,
therefore, you are puerto rican.
All you got to do is prove
your mom's your mom,
find some documentation--
people like that don't
listen to people like me.
Doughnuts! Hey, House,
let's get doughnuts!
Alvie, the hearing-
everyone loves doughnuts--
glazed, crullers, elephant ears,
even doughnut holes.
Much better than the
sporting goods store.
I went Mrs.
x went there all the time.
We're not here--
And then I realized...
You make a good point.
Really? I was making that up.
Dozen glazed, dozen jelly-filled?
You want the usual, right?
Your old friend,
the fried carbohydrate.
She needed the
calorically dense food
to support the running habit.
Do you know her name?
Sandy...
Or shelley.
I don't know.
The guy she's with
called her that once.
I just work here.
Do you know where they live?
He left a business card
in our free doughnut jar.
It's up on the wall of winners.
Sidney.
God, I was so worried about you.
What happened?
The police said it was
too soon to do anything,
so I started calling hospitals
on my own.
Princeton Plainsboro wasn't
even on my list.
You really think something
around here
could have made her sick?
Here, work, anywhere she could
have been exposed.
Why wasn't Princeton
Plainsboro on your list?
Well, I mean,
it's a long way to run,
even for her.
What is it I do besides run?
You're a lawyer--
civil rights, class action suits.
It's a stressful job.
Running's the way you deal with it.
That doesn't sound like me.
Do you have any idea
what would sound like you?
Good point.
So what were you thinking during all this?
That it was a strange position to be in.
At that moment, she was
more comfortable with me
than with her husband.
And he was picking up on it.
What about you?
What about me how?
Well, there was a sort of, um,
artificial intimacy between you?
She'd been dependent on you.
Uh, did you find that attractive
on some level?
Disturbing?
Those are my two choices?
None of the above.
She was just a patient.
She was interesting.
So we're really...
Married?
For four years.
Ms. X, you lead a lemon fresh life.
Found three different cleansers
under the sink.
Cleaned out the
medicine cabinets too.
You know, she just won a settlement
for some families whose
housing development
was built on an old methane field.
Toxic exposure to methane
could explain this.
I surf?
You stopped before we met.
You've been too busy.
And we're married?
Yes.
All right, it's nothing personal.
Bet she didn't think
you were her type
back when you first met either.
We'll take her back
to the hospital,
test her blood and urine
and start treatment.
Oh!
I'm all right.
What happened? I don't know.
My foot suddenly went numb.
Her pants are wet.
Urinary incontinence.
She's having complex
partial seizures.
This isn't methane.
You can leave the bucket.
We need to get her to--
Seizures?
This is the second diagnosis
you've come up with
that has a personal
resonance for you.
I'm choosing my diagnoses
based on personal issues?
You think she fell down the
stairs and peed her pants
'cause Wilson dumped her too?
You're choosing to tell
me about this case,
so let's look at it.
First you were fixated on a
harmful toxin from her past,
possibly because you're worried
about a harmful toxin
from your own past.
Chase had the toxin idea.
Maybe he's obsessed with my past.
And now you're talking
about a seizure disorder?
Which is also not a toxin.
But which is most likely caused
by an old injury to the brain.
W-why do you see your
past as such a threat?
Not only am I unthreatened by it,
I was trying to get it back.
There's a ding mark.
It's a piece of junk.
It was dinged when it came in.
Sure, the--the cup marks and
the scuffs and the paint
and those three chips.
This fourth one is new.
I run a pawn shop,
not a storage company.
Do you want it or not?
That should be it.
You said you pawned five books.
There's only four.
That's all there is.
Where's approach to the acute abdomen?
Sold it.
To?
I can't tell you.
It's a law, and it should be.
Crazy bastards like you try
to hunt down their stuff.
How much for the pile?
$500.
You said it was junk.
No, no.
It's your junk. You want it.
$500-- take it or leave it.
? ?
why is it so important that
you get your stuff back?
Unlike the rest of humanity...
Who's okay when their
belongings are taken.
Everyone wants their stuff.
That's why it's their stuff.
Everyone doesn't pay five
times what it's worth.
I like my stuff.
I hate it when Wilson moves it--
oh...
This is not about Wilson!
Say it.
I wasn't gonna say anything.
31, 31! Hike!
First down!
One more, you get a touchdown.
Whoo!
Hike!
Huh!
House,
you can't run for the touchdown.
And...Hike!
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
You seriously thought you
were gonna tell me
that Wilson showed up but
not tell me what he said?
Because I thought
you were a smart guy
who didn't need the obvious
spelled out to him.
Wilson noticed
that I didn't come
to my office all day.
He came to find me,
wanted to make sure I'm okay--
boring, boring, boring.
Um, but you thought
it was important
to tell me about nerf football?
Sorry. Your story.
Continue.
House, House, stop! Stop,
stop, stop.
You okay?
Yeah.
It was my mother's.
She died when I was four.
It's all I have left.
That's very sad, alvie.
Listen, I set up an
immigration hearing.
No, House,
I'm gonna end up in jail or worse--
the Dominican or someplace.
Que se yo. Que no.
Um, interesting.
You present yourself as,
uh, not giving a damn
about other people's emotions,
but your actions indicate otherwise.
You dismiss alvie's
story about his mother,
but you cared enough
to schedule a hearing.
I cared for eight seconds.
Then I got distracted.
Yeah.
We've kept the patient up for 12 hours now.
No hint of seizure-like activity.
We should shut this down.
Try a strobe light,
add more stress.
I think there's plenty
of stress in here.
Don't we ever do anything but work?
You run. That's just more work.
What about fun?
God, how can we be this boring?
Apparently, without her memory,
the patient's
personality has returned
to what you might call
its natural state.
Seems she had a wake-up call while
she was at college.
Her brother died in a car accident.
She decided to make her
life mean something.
Went to law school.
Now that's all gone.
The thing that caused
the change is gone...
So the change itself is gone.
Yeah.
I knew the psychological
aspects of this case
would interest you.
Bet you got a theory already.
What is it?
It's not relevant.
Why do you care about my theory?
I think he just...
Bores her.
She's at an earlier stage
of development.
She's looking at her grown-up future,
and it puts her to sleep.
If he just bored her,
she'd hide it to be polite.
Their problem is synchronicity.
Just like you and me, House,
they're not on the same page.
He talks to her
like someone he
shares history with.
But from her point of view,
he's a stranger
forcing intimacy on her.
Of course she doesn't like him.
He's not helping.
He can feel he's losing his wife,
and it makes him come on stronger.
He almost did lose his wife.
The breathing problem
was caused by fluid
overload in the lungs.
Diabetes insipidus.
And the d.I. Came from
damage to the hypothalamus.
Hypothalamus here, hence the d.
I. And incontinence.
They mingle here.
There's the global amnesia.
And the motor cortex-
that's the foot paralysis.
What do they all have in common?
Okay, now you're just doing this
to mess with me.
What possible relevance
does this differential
have to your problems?
It ends with a diagnosis
of spongiform encephalitis.
I convinced the team to cut out
part of this woman's brain.
That's not interesting to you?
No.
Not even if it's the amygdala?
She'll lose all her
long-term memory.
Well, this is where you tell me
that being cavalier
with someone else's past
has nothing to do with
avoiding your own past.
The case is irrelevant.
You just found it,
uh... Interesting.
Aren't therapists
supposed to be nurturing?
Nowhere...
Is that in the manual.
Look, you--you've been
in therapy for a year.
You know when I ask you
to talk about anything,
I mean anything that affects you--
what upset you, what made you mad
or relieved or joyful.
You want me to believe that
this case means nothing?
Then, um...
Why should I listen to it?
Are you charging me for this time?
Yes.
This is ridiculous.
What's that?
On the back of your arm?
It's just a bruise. And I fell.
You remember falling?
No.
I was drunk...
Hence the balance issues.
Well, it looks like you fell
on the tip of someone's boot.
I said something that
someone objected to.
Well, if you don't remember,
then how can you--
it's usually the way it is
when someone hits me.
People who kick when
you're down are jerks,
but they're generally
not irrational jerks.
Yogot drunk enough to
get into a bar fight
and not remember,
and you've been insisting
that everything's fine?
W-why--why go out
and get blind drunk?
Were you looking for a fight?
I don't know.
What have you screwed up?
What?
You say that when you've been
hit in the past,
it's because you provoked it
with something that you said,
which means you're well
aware of the risks.
So on some level,
you were in that bar looking
for someone to hurt you.
Logically, people punish
themselves
for something they did or
something they didn't do.
So what...
Did you screw up?
I don't know.
Okay, there may be a problem.
All right...
Let's talk about Wilson.
I told him your book
was contaminated
with Anthrax spores.
Then I gave him $300.
The address of the buyer.
Maybe I was hasty in
asking you to move out.
Why don't you stay with me
and Sam for a little while?
There's no need to hurry things.
What prompted this?
Look, the whole idea
was that after Mayfield,
you wouldn't be on your own.
I can touch base with
you a lot more easily
if you're staying with me than--
God's sake, Wilson.
You really span the chasm
from wishy to washy.
If you're gonna be an ass,
be an ass.
Stick with it.
Why were you being so hard on the guy,
when he was being conciliatory?
Come on.
Cuddy played on his guilt.
She put him up to this.
How do you know that?
How do you know this wasn't
entirely his own idea?
Two reasons--
first, he wants to create
the perfect environment
to be with Sam.
He's been thinking about asking me
to leave for a while.
Finally he does it and
immediately turns around
and changes his mind--no.
He talked to somebody.
Maybe it was Sam.
Yeah, that's a possibility.
I want this to be the
last serious relationship
I ever have.
I want this to be the one.
Me too.
Where's House?
It's not as meaningful without him.
Okay, um...
Not Sam.
Uh, that still doesn't answer
why Cuddy.
Because they've been
talking about me.
She called me to check on the patient,
which she never does
without a reason.
I asked why, and she said...
She's a barracuda attorney, House.
These are the kind of patients
we like to keep happy.
Right now the patient's lucky
if she can spell jurisprudence.
Yeah, but when she gets that memory back,
which we are trying to make happen,
she'll be able to spell lawsuit.
I'm just touching base.
Touching base.
Wilson used exactly
the same phrase.
Colluding about me is
her favorite pastime.
Okay, you think they talked.
How do you think that
conversation went?
I'm worried about House.
Me too.
Couldn't you have waited?
It's way too early for
him to be on his own,
back in the old apartment.
What makes you think
he can handle it?
I offered to find him a new place.
You have to let him back into your condo.
Sam and I just got him out of the condo.
You know what House is like.
He's self-destructive.
Without constant supervision,
he's gonna slide back into drugs.
If you're not watching him,
I've got to.
Yeah.
So they don't trust you.
They assume you'll fail.
Are these their fears or yours?
Let's turn on the lights, Hmm?
In your brain.
Maybe they did talk
about you, but...
How do you know it
didn't happen like this?
I'm worried about House. Why?
It's the first time
he'll be on his own
since Mayfield.
Now you're being overprotective.
House doesn't need to be wrapped
in cotton wool.
But you know that,
or you wouldn't have
asked him to move out.
Okay. I guess this
is really about me.
It's just... I feel like a jerk.
Sure, Sam and I are gonna want
to be on our own eventually,
but I kind of sprang this on him.
The right way would have been
to just tell him to take as
long as he needed,
that there's no hurry.
So it's not what you did,
but how you did it.
That matters in a friendship.
I need to fix this.
Why don't you talk to him
about moving back in?
Just touch base.
We're having a consent
issue with the patient.
Wait a minute. Taub's not here.
Yeah, he is.
We're having a consent
issue with the patient.
What's Taub doing in
my imaginary version
of a scene with Wilson and Cuddy?
Your version needed to be ended,
'cause it's crap.
It's all sweetness and light and...
Faith that I'm gonna
choose the right path.
Yeah, that sounds like Wilson.
I have as much evidence
for mine
as you do for yours.
I know Wilson's your friend.
So he could be wondering
if he did right by you.
And I know he wouldn't
have asked you to move out
in the first place
unless he was convinced
you could handle life on your own.
And I know that he and Cuddy
have gone behind my back before
to strategize about
the House problem.
So there's truth in both versions.
But you choose to
focus on the parts
that make you uncomfortable.
So...
Why are you and Wilson...
Friends?
Do you think this friendship
is the best you can do?
Wilson is not a consolation prize.
There... You're defending him.
And a minute ago,
he was skulking around
in the background
like some sort of
manipulative iago.
He's my friend.
So what do you value in him?
I can say whatever I want to him,
and he'll never leave.
He's sort of leaving.
At least, he won't
be around as much...
Because he's putting Sam first.
For now.
After the divorce,
he'll probably ask
me to move in again.
I take the long view.
You say that to Wilson?
Are you kidding?
That's the kind of remark
that leads people to hate you.
Uh, maybe you've been
right from the beginning.
Maybe this isn't about Wilson.
You say that now that I
finally agree with you?
Do you just argue the
opposite of whatever I say?
I don't mean the Wilson thing
doesn't, uh, bother you,
uh, but it sounds like he's
the closest you can come
to a safe relationship.
You'd have to do something
major to screw it up.
Um, what--what else have you
been involved in this week?
What would you want to
punish yourself for?
I told you, I don't know.
Okay, um, let's approach
it from a different angle.
Have you gotten any other
people angry at you
over anything?
Well, yeah.
That's why I called
it an ordinary week.
Okay. Tell me about it.
You'd be losing a part of your brain.
It is my brain.
Why is it not my right to consent?
I'm sorry, but...
I'll take this to
court if necessary.
All right, Sidney's in no position
to make decisions about
herself right now.
She doesn't even know who she is.
I read your consent form,
and I understood it.
I want the surgery.
Why wouldn't she?
Of course she's willing to risk
losing her memories permanently.
She has no idea how important
those memories are.
Does she even know what risk is?
She's never lost anything.
Without the surgery,
she'll lose everything.
The prion infection
will continue to advance and
destroy her whole brain.
Well, there has to be another way.
Please.
I'm speaking for my wife,
the wife I lived
with for four years
who isn't here and can't
defend herself.
Dr. House, are you listening?
Well, you can stop arguing,
'cause it doesn't matter anymore.
Look at the variability
in the heart rate.
The s.E. Has spread
into the brain stem.
W-wherever it is,
you--you can still cut it out.
No. We can't cut the brain stem.
This thing's moving too quickly.
Surgery's no longer an option,
which I guess means you've won.
Congratulations.
Put in a pacer and start
her on chemo and radiation.
It won't cure her,
but it'll buy a couple weeks
so she can find out who
she is before she dies.
That was pretty rough.
Do you always break the news to
your patients that way?
Or were you short-handing it for me?
Husband was being an idiot.
Well, he was asking for it.
But, um, to punish him you
have to punish the wife too.
Why--why did he make
you so angry, Hmm?
Because he didn't want
to cooperate with you?
He'd rather risk his wife's
life than their marriage.
People's brains stop working
when they think they're gonna
lose someone they love.
Your leg hurt?
It's all right.
Okay.
Anyone else you pissed off?
50 bucks for the book.
Forget it.
You paid $25. That's 100% return.
That's what I paid.
But it's a rare surgical text,
nearly 100 years old-
plate's in mint condition.
That book's worth several
thousand dollars.
$2,000-- I'll write you a check.
Nice try.
Face it-- I had the wit
to recognize something
valuable when I saw it.
In the great darwinian race,
I get my just reward.
You become roadkill.
Yo, House, you want to
stop by the library?
'Cause I got a book to return.
Ta-ka-plow!
? Old Professor
tried to hoard/hog ?
? you can't stop alvie
with no guard-ass dog ?
anyone see you?
Yeah, prof saw me walking
down the driveway.
He said the roses
need more fertilizer.
I didn't know there was
a section of the brain
just for hope.
It's very, very tiny.
We used fluoroscopy to
guide pacemaker placement
in the patient's heart.
Hello.
Rapidly progressive
dilated cardiomyopathy.
This isn't s.E.,
and whatever it is,
it's not just in her brain.
It's attacking her whole body.
You work for House?
I guess we're teammates.
Isn't that cool?
Hello.
Juan alvarez?
What the hell?
We're taking you into custody-
deportation order.
I'm a citizen.
You're disrespecting Puerto Rico.
If you're a citizen,
why'd you miss your hearing?
You called them?
What's going on?
We're trying to
stabilize her heart.
She's still tachy and hypotensive.
Brain, heart,
and rapidly progressing.
Endocarditis--slow-moving
infection in her heart
throws clots to her brain.
I'm not talking to you.
How could you turn me in?
Her extreme exercise suppresses
her immune system,
allows the infection to smolder.
Or allows an old infection
to reactivate it--t.B.
Start her on a multidrug regimen.
I don't like you, House.
I hate you.
Even I.V. Antibiotics will
take time to work.
A general reminder--the use
of cell phones is prohibited.
Give her the first dose
directly into the lungs in the O.R.
Before the less gentle arrest
for contempt.
Put her in an isolation
room with U.V. light.
And get yourselves tested.
You've all been exposed.
Docket number 4378.
You are?
I am Mr. alvarez's doctor.
Your honor, DNA evidence
proving the matriarchal
lineage of Juan alvarez.
My mother's DNA was
still on that cross?
It could be.
You faked it?
It wasn't just me.
You lied to them too!
I'm better at it than you are.
I'm gonna repaint your
whole apartment now,
make the drapes match the carpet now!
Lungs sound wet.
O-2 sats are dropping.
May need to tube her.
Grab some I.V. Furosemide.
Wait, wait. She's crashing.
We need to get her on
a vent.
There's something on her ankle.
Tattoo.
"Eddie would go.
" It's a surfing phrase.
Must be from her earlier life.
She tried to get it removed,
but they only took off
the top layers of skin.
The ink is still in
the deeper layers.
Set off an allergic reaction.
She was fine until she started
the long-distance running.
The ultra-marathoning
modified her immune system,
set off the allergic reaction.
We did a full thickness skin graft,
and she'll be okay.
So you were right... In the end.
It was her past.
Did she get her memory back?
Not yet.
Will she?
No way to know.
I think roses are my favorite.
But I guess I told you
that at some point.
I don't remember.
He's treating her as though they just met.
He's courting her.
Whose idea was that?
He was doing the opposite
of everything he should.
Suddenly he's changed.
Taub thought it might-
that was your idea.
And you asked me
what I thought was
going on between them.
It's their relationship
that's on your mind.
That's why you've been
thinking about this case--
relationships.
Lost one with Wilson,
gained one with alvie.
Not exactly.
Alvie?
You gonna tell me what the note said?
Alvie was very grateful
that I'd gotten him out of trouble.
It allowed him to go stay
with his cousin in Phoenix
without worrying about immigration
looking for him there.
You didn't think he was
gonna stay forever.
No.
What happened next?
? ?
Nothing happened next.
That's all I got.
Relationships.
Bergman.
What do you want me to say?
I don't know.
You're the one who said the thing-
-
something about relationships
made you go out and
provoke a fight.
Wilson and Sam have a relationship.
You're not thrilled about it.
They're happy.
Why should I screw that up?
Everyone's happy.
Everyone's moving in together--
Wilson and Sam, Cuddy and Lucas.
Even alvie's--
Cuddy and Lucas are
moving in together?
You didn't mention that.
They talked about moving
in together before.
It's not big news.
Cuddy...
Cuddy.
Approach to the acute abdomen...
Written by Ernest t. Cuddy, m.D.
Any relation to your Cuddy?
Her great-grandfather.
I've had it for years...
Always meant to give it to
her for a special occasion.
Like her... Housewarming?
It's just a gift.
A woman you care about
is taking one step
further away from you
and closer to someone else?
I-I think I can safely say
yes, it's significant if
you don't mention it.
You were willing to punish
the husband of your patient
because you identified with him.
He was also losing
someone he loved.
I'm not gonna go out
and get hammered
because a woman I'm not even with
is moving in with someone.
That'd be pathetic.
To hell with this.
When I first came to you,
I told you that I
wanted to be happy,
and I followed your advice.
And instead, I'm just miserable.
How is this working for me?
It takes time.
For a year, I've done
everything you've asked,
and everybody else is happy.
I run on my treadmill.
You just sit there and watch.
You're a faith healer.
You take advantage of
people who want to believe.
But there's nothing
in your bag of tricks.
House...
Whatever the answer is,
you don't have it.
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --