Good explosion!
Drive it! Drive it!
You watching 77?
I'm watching everybody.
You don't need to watch everybody.
You need to watch 77.
You his agent?
Just an objective mom.
His explosion is impressive.
It's not just burst.
He can pull too.
He went to a double "a" school,
he was a bit of a late bloomer.
He's a big man now.
You should be his agent.
Nice pancake, 7-7!
- You're moving up those draft boards!
- Thank you, sir!
- On one, on one. Ready?
- Break!
Blue 90. Hike!
Good job!
Second level, nice!
Get off our quarterback!
Play's over! The play is over!
Save the aggression
for between the whistles!
All right, back to work!
Daryl.
Daryl, stop!
R[H]?sus AB+ Team
.:: La Fabrique ::.
- What are you doing?
- Canoeing.
But I seem to be taking on water.
This is not okay.
Use your own bathroom.
No canoe in my bathroom.
My leg hurts.
Soaking it makes it feel better.
You were the one
who had to have this condo.
Maybe next time
you should consider amenities,
like two full baths, instead of the joy
of outbidding Cuddy.
The guy who signs the loan
gets to pick the bedrooms.
Stay out of mine.
You owe me 35 bucks
for the grab rail I installed.
Hit the kill screen.
Boss is here.
It's not porn.
It's our new patient.
Bummer.
22-year-old male...
6'7", 310 pounds.
Clearly has brain involvement.
The guy has no recollection
of this entire incident.
Football player.
Those the ones that get hit
in the head a lot, right?
E.R. CT'd him...
No concussion, no stroke,
no cortical degeneration.
And he had a full psyche evaluation.
He's not crazy.
So it's roid rage. I don't think
they grow them that big naturally.
E.R. also tested for steroids.
He's clean.
Only proving that our guy
got his hands on the good stuff.
The negative test at least means
steroids is less likely.
- We should discuss other possibilities.
- Why?
He injects his sore ankles
with lidocaine every game.
You think
he's above injecting steroids?
Repeated head trauma
could damage the base of the brain,
leading to a pituitary adenoma,
which leaks GNRH.
Pituitary damage
wouldn't be visible on a CT scan.
Could cause the excess hormones
that could cause the rage
and would elude
the E.R. steroid test.
Fine.
Bilateral venous sampling
to find the elevated GNRH.
MRI to find the pituitary damage.
Unless, of course,
there is no pituitary damage,
in which case, our guy
got his hands on the good stuff.
Let the peasants
handle the peasantry.
Your brother needs to get picked up
this afternoon...
from prison.
Your older brother,
in case your confusion is...
- How do you know about that?
- He left a message.
Said he couldn't get you
on your cell or at home.
I get it.
You're busy.
You'll pick him up the next time.
Is that all?
You're officially unbusy.
Family is family.
Take the rest of the day.
Go see your brother.
I have work to do.
Do you feel any pain
that's deep and persistent,
not just muscles or joints?
Everything hurts all the time.
That's football.
It might not be just football.
We're gonna test for damage
to your pituitary.
If there is,
it could create excess hormones,
which could be causing your pain.
It would also explain your rage attack.
If my pituitary is damaged,
how long would it take to treat?
I don't want to get ahead of ourselves
and start promising deadlines.
Sorry, doctor,
but he's playing
in front of pro scouts,
coaches, and GMS this Saturday.
This is the job interview
for the rest of his life.
If we do find something wrong,
we can go in through the nose
and repair the damage...
Nothing too invasive.
You'll need a couple days
of recovery,
and then we can have you back
by game time.
There's nothing wrong
with your eyes.
Then your gizmo's broken.
- I'm seeing spots.
- Or you enlisted,
you got the cool haircut
and the awesome pants,
then you realized that your plane ticket
to the Middle East was coach,
and you decided to rethink
your promise.
I've already been there...
Three deployments.
Now they want me to go again.
But my wife's pregnant.
So our homeland should be unsafe
because your private was unsafe.
My wife and I planned this perfect.
My enlistment was supposed
to be over last week,
so we got pregnant six months ago.
Now they tell me
I'm getting stop-lossed...
Army speak for they don't care
that I've already finished my contract.
I don't care about the fact
that they don't care.
Come on.
I waited an extra hour
just to make sure I got you.
Why?
I saw you limping out there.
Vietnam?
How old do you think I am?
I don't know, Vietnam age?
Back in my day,
the real dodgers had the stones
to run up to Canada
or shoot themselves in the foot.
They didn't come to free clinics
whining for doctors' notes.
Go hug your wife.
Tell her to get a babysitter.
You'll be back in time to video
the kid's first steps.
I don't need to see the scan.
I can tell from your puppy-dog eyes
that his pituitary's fine.
Are you gonna say it, or should I?
You were right about the steroids.
You're a genius.
Next time with feeling.
Put the cheater on a somatostatin analog
to clear it out of his system.
Send him back to his football game.
I've never done steroids.
Somehow your GNRH got elevated.
This will help get it back down.
- Mom, I swear.
- Who's gonna draft you, Daryl?
You're stupid enough to try that stuff,
the week you're getting tested.
You guys must've mixed up your labs
or got somebody else's blood,
because I never...
What is that?
Tachycardia.
Lay back down.
- Why's my heart beating like this?
- It's not steroids.
I need some adenosine!
And get that crash cart over here!
House, next time...
Marcus.
Right.
You two know each other.
What are you doing here?
Interviewing.
Who are we kidding?
Interview's over.
You got the job.
What job?
My new assistant.
Part of his parole...
He needs a job.
Just trying to do my part.
You were wrong about the steroids.
Patient had a paroxysmal tachycardia.
We cardioverted him
back to sinus rhythm.
We're gonna get an EKG
and a sestamibi scan.
Let's talk outside.
Family is family.
Good to see you too.
Did you have a hard stretch?
No, not bad.
I hardly got raped at all.
You can't work here.
- Your boss says I can.
- I'm not playing.
Lighten up.
Man, this could be fun.
I get to see your world.
You get me access to the pharmacy.
I am playing.
Come on, man.
You look good.
I'd know that if you came to visit
every once in a while, but I get it.
It's cool.
You don't want to see me.
You don't want to pick me up.
It's all justified.
I'll just have to win you back over.
Let me explain something.
This man who's offering
you the job...
- He's not a philanthropist.
- He seems more helpful than you.
He doesn't want to help you.
He only wants to use you
to screw with me.
You know how you can screw with him?
Act like your brother getting a job
doesn't screw with you.
Trust me,
it'll be better for both of us
if you go back in there and tell him
you can't take the job.
I'm not a person who has the luxury
of turning down jobs.
Figure something out...
'cause you cannot work here.
We spent all night,
used all the fancy machines.
Patient's heart looks fine.
If it was fine, it wouldn't go aflutter
just 'cause you walked into the room.
Light whip, two extra shots.
Thank you, sir.
Judging by the look on your face,
I assume you're upset
that big bro didn't take your advice
and skip town.
- You told him about our conversation?
- He bought me breakfast.
It was fun.
Put lunch in the books,
just you and me.
Our patient could have a PFO.
Naturally, you jump right
to a urinary issue.
PFO's not urinary.
It's a heart issue.
It is?
Naturally, you think
it's not a urinary issue,
'cause you're so embarrassed
about your own past urinary issues,
you don't dare broach the subject.
Come on.
You spending the night
over at Bobby Samson's.
I did not wet the bed.
- I spilled a drink.
- We're not buying it, Eric.
- We never bought it.
- Why are you telling him these things?
What's the big deal?
It was 25 years ago.
Oxygenated
and deoxygenated blood mix,
the rough flow causes a clot,
explains the heart and head.
Like that power forward
from Loyola Marymount,
when he...
Hank Gathers?
That's not what happened to him.
Let your brother speak.
What happened to Hank Gathers?
Conference tournament...
alley-oop dunk, jams it home.
Then he runs up the court and splat.
He dropped dead of a heart thing
on the court.
I remember that. On autopsy, they found
he had a hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.
Rage and tachycardia
are warning signs.
Seriously?
Because my brother
remembers a basketball game?
I don't care
where an idea comes from,
as long as it makes sense
and embarrasses someone.
- Are you out of your mind?
- As a former psychiatric patient,
- I take offense at that terminology.
- All I did was ban you from my tub.
Whatever happened
to proportional response?
to coherent conversation?
That... thing...
broke tiles, gashed the walls,
and pooped everywhere.
Expect a bill for repairs...
and payback.
- What was that?
- I have no idea.
Everybody else thinks hypertrophic
cardiomyopathy makes sense?
Good. Stick the patient
on a treadmill.
Stress his heart until it stops.
You want to induce cardiac arrest?
Only real treatment is for the patient
never to stress his heart again,
which means we have to tell him
to retire at the ripe old age of 21.
Stopping his heart
speaks louder than words. Go.
Maybe it's a good thing.
He gave your brother a job,
responsibility.
I'm not arguing
that he shouldn't have a job.
I just don't want him
having one here.
I understand that House
did this to annoy you.
But why is he succeeding?
You know what my brother did
the last time he got out of prison?
He stole money
from my parents to buy drugs.
He robbed a liquor store. Then he moved
on to jacking luxury cars...
Last time.
Every time.
I've known my brother
for over 30 years.
You haven't even known him a day.
I'm sorry.
The exterminator charged $250
to get the opossum out of there,
and the contractor estimates
$1,500 to fix the bathroom.
And why are you
jerking Foreman around?
Because it's fun.
Maybe you should give
those bills to the guy
who left his own
bathroom window open.
Your motives always run deeper
than simple fun.
I want to learn more
about one of my employees
so that I can manipulate him
and destroy him
if and when I choose.
- Information is power.
- Not buying it.
Why don't you tell me
my real evil plan?
I don't think there is an evil plan.
You regret not having a relationship
with your own family,
and you don't want to see
Foreman go down that same path.
I think...
You're actually being nice.
Shut up.
You can't accuse me
of an opossum attack
and underhanded kindness
in the same visit.
Then I'll come back.
Treadmill test was a bust.
The guy's in unbelievable shape.
We couldn't get his heart rate
above 150.
Your boss is secretly
a very nice man.
I know.
If we can't re-create
the cardiac event,
we can't prove
hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.
Either we find a bigger treadmill...
Or...
Did I miss the memo
about you being released?
I'm feeling fine.
I can't keep laying here
missing practices.
All excellent points.
Give me your arm.
What's in the shot?
It's a vasodilator.
Since we can't exercise
your son's heart on the treadmill,
I'm gonna have to do it chemically.
- What's wrong?
- You're turning white.
What does that mean?
He doesn't need football
to get a good job anymore.
Raynaud's phenomenon...
Vasospasms cut off the blood supply
to his fingers.
Could be early onset
rheumatoid arthritis.
- Rheumatoid factor is negative.
- Arterial plaque throwing clots
would explain the fingers,
head, heart.
You really think a guy with stenosis
could've aced that treadmill test?
You're kidding me.
You got him a desk?
And a nameplate.
Man's got to have a place
he can call his own.
What about Takayasu's arteritis?
Lymphoma's a better fit.
We should remove his spleen.
Bold move to skip
straight to surgery.
His big game's coming up.
We don't have time to biopsy,
wait for the pathology report,
and resect.
Right.
We should remove his spleen
without confirmation
so he won't miss the big game.
Hang an ethanol drip.
That won't treat
for either lymphoma or Takayasu's.
If it's lymphoma,
the ethanol will make him itchy,
and Foreman can remove his spleen.
Or he'll lose his radial pulse,
and Chase can start him on steroids.
- What are you doing here?
- My new assignment is...
to shadow you in enemy territory
and document your every word
to the patient.
Just don't say anything stupid.
You're not an idiot.
Don't do this.
Come on, man.
I'm a new person now...
No more drugs, no more lying.
And if I can't get my own family
to give me an opportunity to prove that,
what's the point?
Mom and Dad gave you a chance
and a second
and a third.
I'm not about to give you a 54th.
Why isn't your minion
fetching your lunch?
He's busy spying
on his little brother.
What?
That's very demeaning.
You obviously have a theory
as to why demeaning is not demeaning.
You're escalating to prove I was wrong
about you being nice,
which you would only do
if I was right.
Do you listen to yourself?
23-year-old just came into the E.R.,
asked for you.
What's her cup size?
I don't think his cup size
is relevant to his condition.
He accidentally shot himself
in the foot.
Seriously?
I give you a choice
between moving to Canada
and shooting yourself in the foot,
you chose the bullet?
- I didn't want to be a fugitive.
- This is gonna get you discharged?
- We'll patch it up and send you back.
- Don't patch it up.
You got screwed over
by your own government, and that sucks.
But all you're gonna get out of this
is a five-day vacation and a band-aid.
When I signed up, I was just a guy.
Now I'm about to be a dad.
I go back over, there's a chance
my kid grows up without a father.
You got a girl pregnant.
You're still just a guy.
How much longer we have to wait?
We have to keep going
until you feel something.
Might help if you told me
what I'm supposed to feel.
If I do that,
that's all you'll be thinking about.
You'll be telling me that's what
you're feeling. Power of suggestion.
The other black dude
who was in here, he your brother?
- What gave it away?
- The way you looked at him.
I have two older brothers,
and we always want to kill each other.
Something wrong?
Not really.
It just feels itchy.
- Is that what you're waiting for?
- Means lymphoma's most likely,
but that's actually good news.
- How could that be good news?
- Because it's treatable.
We can remove your spleen
tonight laparoscopically.
Will I be able to run by Saturday?
We can get to the radiation
in the off-season.
Hey, ma.
Wake up, ma.
Wake up.
I'm itchy.
Means I can play.
- What are you doing in the dark?
- Lying in wait.
Jeez. What happened to your face?
Right...
Play innocent.
You weren't looking for revenge
for the prank I didn't pull.
It's karmic justice,
but I didn't do it.
Of course you realize,
this means war.
Isolating the gastroepiploic artery.
Nearly there.
Foreman,
come and take a look at this.
Liver's inflamed.
So the itching
wasn't caused by his spleen.
It's not lymphoma.
What happened?
Wilson annexed the Sudetenland.
No abnormal T cells or B cells.
It's not lymphoma.
Liver biopsy only revealed
nonspecific inflammation.
Kind of like the time
you took your mom's
birth control pills on a dare
and ended up with swollen nipples.
- That never happened.
- Right.
And your nickname all the way up
through high school wasn't Erica.
It wasn't.
I made that one up,
with the understanding
he still had a sense of humor
and would play along.
Polymyositis would explain the head,
liver, heart, even the white fingers.
It would be accompanied by a decrease
in muscle power.
Chance to redeem yourself.
Does our patient look strong to you?
Sorry, Eric.
Big brother disagrees
with your diagnosis.
Felty syndrome?
The liver was inflamed,
not the spleen.
Can you believe
they let this guy perform surgery?
- What?
- Requesting permission to share my idea
without being belittled.
Permission denied. Continue.
Our patient has cartilage damage
in both ankles.
He gets lidocaine shots
before every game to mask the pain.
Team doctor uses the same needle twice
by accident, viral hepatitis.
You think he's an idiot, Marcus?
I don't think he's an idiot.
Go test his blood.
Come on.
We have a lunch scheduled.
You jerked me around.
Your allegiance
lies with your brother.
I get it. Admirable.
Here's the problem.
I hired you to tell me the truth.
If you don't,
you no longer have a job.
I don't know what secret
you're looking to uncover,
but my brother is a decent guy.
He was arrested
for grand theft auto.
You're gonna be disappointed.
Try me.
- He tell you I was with him?
- Was it your idea?
We did everything together,
I don't know whose idea it was.
I was 16, he was only 14.
He couldn't even see
over the steering wheel.
He's quicker with a flathead screwdriver
than most people with a key.
Sorry to interrupt
my character assassination
with boring medical stuff,
but when we drew the patient's blood,
it clotted in the vacutainer.
So the problem is not in his blood,
it's the blood itself.
He's been working out in the cold,
it's got to be cryoglobulinemia.
I usually love breaking bad news,
but in this case...
Start him on Warfarin.
I'm so sorry about that.
You were saying...
We drove for about ten minutes
before we got caught, and that was it.
When our mom
came down to the station,
she didn't say a word
the whole ride home.
She came up to the driveway,
turned off the car.
We're sitting in silence.
Then without turning around,
she said,
"I'll pray for you."
And she got out of the car.
You got off easy.
Easy for you, easy for me,
not easy for Eric.
His life mission became
to never disappoint her like that again.
Because he is a good guy.
I thought he would tell that story
at the eulogy.
But he didn't give one.
Your mother's dead?
If he didn't tell you,
I'm sure he had a reason.
Look, you can mock him all you want
about peeing in the bed.
Please...
Don't bring up our mother.
Your blood contains
an abnormally high volume
of proteins called cryoglobulins.
They become thick
when it gets cold outside.
It's like a car trying to run
after the oil's turned to sludge.
We think
that's been causing your problems.
So I just need a quick oil change
and I'm good to go.
This oil change isn't so quick.
We have to put you on blood thinners
and other medications.
The process will take
two to three weeks, but after that,
you should be able to play.
It won't matter!
Doctor, if Daryl doesn't play
in front of the scouts
on Saturday, he won't get drafted.
- Can't you wait until after the game?
- If we wait and let him play,
there's a good chance he dies
right on the field.
I had an epiphany.
Usually that precedes you
walking away with purpose, so...
Flathead screwdriver.
And then I say...
It's not a game.
It's proof that you didn't rig
the grab rail and make me fall.
I already have proof of that.
I didn't do it.
I can't go on that.
But I can go on the fact I had to borrow
a flathead screwdriver from Nora
to install the thing.
We only had a Phillips-head.
Then, I returned it late that night
in a completely successful effort
to see her braless.
Wait a minute...
Which means you didn't have the tool
to sabotage the grab rail.
Braless under, like, a sweater
or like a...
Now I also have proof
that I'm not responsible
for the opossum,
because I'm absolving you
instead of escalating,
which is not my nature.
So someone is breaking
into our place just to screw with us?
The opossum...
was meant for me.
I'm so tired.
It was exciting till about 2:00 a.m.
Now it's just torture.
Did you even go to college?
This is the escalation, isn't it?
Keeping me up all night,
nothing happens,
then you keep me up all night
again tomorrow.
- This is your retaliation.
- You see, that's just illogical,
Cause I'm staying up too.
Maybe you napped all day.
I gave you empirical proof
that I did not prank you.
No, you did not.
You created empirical proof
that I didn't prank you,
selling me on the notion
that you didn't prank me.
Maybe you self-pranked.
- I don't master-prank.
- Is that cut on your cheek even real?
See, this is exactly
what our nemesis wants.
Divide and conquer.
Can't you see that?
I'm going to bed.
I'm telling you, if you sleep now,
you're gonna wake up
next to severed horse heads.
Or worse, the rest of it.
The flat screen!
You would never sacrifice
the flat screen.
This guy is good.
Is there a reason for this?
There is a reason
for everything, mes amis.
I am troubled to report that we have
a criminal in our midst.
Guilty of what exactly?
Last night, the fire sprinklers
flooded our apartment.
And before that,
I found an opossum in my bathtub.
You each had motive,
you each had opportunit?.
This is the emergency
you paged me about?
Not so fast,
mademoiselle Cuddy.
No one leaves until they can account
for their whereabouts
the evening last.
No one who is employed by me
leaves until they account
for their whereabouts.
- What about you, professor Chase?
- Why would I?
Because you hold me responsible
for breaking up your marriage.
I was with Thirteen, monitoring
our patient's IV blood thinners.
- Can either of you prove that?
- The patient's alive and improving.
- Is that proof enough?
- For now.
What about you, colonel Taub?
- I was out to dinner with my wife.
- Really?
Your wife?
Yes, really.
Good enough.
Cause I had you pegged all along.
You had all the motive in the world.
First of all, I'm not interested.
Second,
I don't even know where you guys live.
Yesterday
I confirmed that you are a liar.
What are you talking about?
At least a liar by omission.
- Don't.
- Get this, class.
Foreman's mom died.
He ever tell any of you?
You're getting off topic here.
Is he serious?
Did your mom pass away?
About three months ago.
- I'm so sorry.
- Why didn't you tell anybody?
And to top it off,
you refused to say anything nice
at the funeral.
I didn't talk
because it isn't anyone's business.
Stop.
You don't have to explain yourself
to this guy.
You wanna hit me, don't you?
Don't.
I quit.
You should stop him.
He needs this job.
Our patient needs a fresh IV.
I don't need two or three weeks.
See?
Got my color back.
You're getting better.
But it doesn't...
I am better.
My coach had the team doctor come by.
He cleared me to play.
Did your team doctor
realize you're on blood thinners?
- I'm off them now.
- You're still sick.
- You're not ready to go off your meds.
- Daryl, it is not worth the risk.
I'll come back on Sunday, Mom.
You can give me the meds I need then.
The treatment doesn't work that way.
Please go with him.
Antibiotics aren't working.
We're gonna switch you
to different ones.
But you're gonna lose your toe.
Outstanding, soldier.
As a general rule,
before you celebrate,
do a little research.
The army's medical evaluation board
is perfectly fine
with nine-toed infantrymen,
As long as they can walk and run.
- So I lost a toe for nothing?
- Afraid so.
Unless you want me to keep you
on the old antibiotics,
let the infection spread,
and we could amputate
more than just a toe.
Why are you risking your life
for this?
Your mom doesn't want you to.
My mom sacrificed everything for me.
Her telling me not to come here
is just another example of that.
I do good out there,
I could take care of her
for the rest of her life.
Who am I
if I don't sacrifice for her?
That's family.
You okay?
Everything's blurry.
I can't see.
Take me back to the hospital.
The blindness means
we were wrong about his...
I'm responsible for that.
Spiked his water with nitrates,
dropped his BP, robbed oxygen-rich
blood from his brain, making him blind.
Figured a temporarily blind patient
is better than a permanently dead one.
Vision was coming back
when I dropped him off at the hospital.
Well played.
If only we could combine
your medical chicanery
with your brother's ability
to fetch me mochas, you'd be perfect.
- Where are you?
- I'm busy.
Great. We don't have a new symptom.
We should stick him back
on his blood thinners,
and he can leave in a couple weeks.
Actually, we do have a new symptom.
Any of you take a look
at his readmittance chart?
Between the time he checked in
and the time he rechecked in,
our patient lost a single pound.
Patient like that
would usually shed over ten pounds.
The obvious answer
would be steroids,
but since we've already
ruled them out...
So he's not injecting.
But he could be getting them
naturally.
Paraneoplastic syndrome.
The body produces antibodies,
which battle cancer,
which could act like growth hormone.
We've eliminated lymphoma.
What other cancers
mimic growth hormone?
Lung, pancreatic, renal, breast...
It was a rhetorical question.
I don't really care.
Test him for all of them.
- What are you doing here?
- You need a job.
Maybe I can talk to House,
see if I can get your job back.
Soon as he knows
you're okay with me being there,
he won't want me back.
Maybe I can help you
figure out something else.
I promise...
- I won't let you down.
- Don't do that.
Let's just...
see how it goes.
Do they mandate you
to stay here at the halfway house?
Or can you stay with family?
It's Foreman.
It should stop now that Marcus left.
That's the whole point.
I'm sorry, was my leg sticking out?
I'm so distracted trying to think
of something funnier
than fire sprinklers
going off
in the middle of the night.
Any ideas?
Easy, I know where you live.
You know how I know?
Cause my girlfriend and I...
we tried to buy
that very same condo.
Leave me out of this.
Wilson bought the place.
And you're living there.
You...
deserve to suffer equally.
Actually, I suffered more
now that you just tripped me.
His suffering will equal out,
'cause he actually feels remorse.
Why would you out yourself?
You can't even imagine
the retribution.
There won't be any.
I am ceasing
all offensive operations.
I have both made my point
and established my superiority.
And if you even get
to the planning stages of retaliation,
I will tell Cuddy
she lost her dream place to you two.
See, she's under this odd impression
that you are her friends.
There's no cancer.
We scanned him head to toe,
we checked blood smears for leukemia.
We even ultrasounded his chest
for breast cancer.
Maybe I was wrong
about the weight loss.
You weren't,
we found blood in his catheter bag.
- His kidneys are failing.
- So it has to be cancer.
Paraneoplastic syndrome
is the only thing that can link kidney,
heart, and liver, even the rage.
Why can't we find it?
We've looked everywhere.
What if it's not inside?
You know why you're black?
Cause god loves me
more than he loves you?
I was going for melanin.
You got lots of it.
It makes your skin dark,
protects you
from the sun's harmful UV rays.
What you doing?
Unfortunately, it also prevents
even those with advanced medical degrees
from considering melanoma
as a diagnosis.
Other hand.
On the rare occasion that black people
do get skin cancer,
they usually get it
on the white parts.
Palms and soles of the feet.
But your hands and feet
are so smashed up from football,
my team are likely
to have written off
any skin blemish as a bruise.
But now that I know that melanoma
is the only thing that fits...
Come take a look at this, Mom.
There's the thorn
in the panther's paw.
Paraneoplastic syndrome.
Your body forms antibodies
to fight the tumor.
Those tiny little proteins
travel through your blood
and wreak havoc.
We remove the cancerous mole,
everything should be fine.
I'll tell Dr. Chase
to schedule the surgery.
Why bother? I missed my shot.
What life am I gonna lead now?
Did you study really, really hard?
Then the same crappy life
that the guys you'll be graduating with
are gonna lead.
Minus the student loans.
- You ready?
- Almost.
Done.
I heard House and Wilson
are getting pranked.
You wouldn't know anything
about that?
- Why should I believe you?
- You said I had a trusting face.
I still don't understand
why you wouldn't let me retaliate.
They stole your dream.
That's overstating it.
It's just a condo.
It's not because you feel guilty
about hurting House
or guilty for being with me?
We'll buy another one. I just don't see
the need to make a war out of it.
I think you're rationalizing,
which a less confident man
might take as a sign
you're second-guessing.
Okay, you know what?
Forget that last part.
I heard Foreman and his brother
are trying to work things out.
- That's nice for them.
- It's nice of you.
You didn't provoke Marcus to quit
so the pranks would stop.
You were becoming the common enemy
they could bond over.
You are the diabolical,
yet benevolent puppet master.
I provoked Marcus to quit
because he was no longer
useful to me.
I hired him to get information,
I got information.
And how are we gonna get back
at Lucas?
We're not.
I win.
www.sous-titres.eu