So I'm thinking 35.
Seems high to me.
That's a fair price for quality like this.
I'll give you 30.
What? I thought you were joking.
I didn't...
Who am I dealing with here, eddie?
Him or you?
Mickey, relax.
Now, if things move forward with gorski,
He lets us into philly,
Then maybe I cut you a break.
You cut me a break now,
Or maybe you don't get with gorski.
Marco...
I thought we had an understanding.
Whoa, whoa.
Tommy, don't be stupid. Put the gun down.
First, he shows you some respect.
Hey, you just-- just listen to your boss,
All right, moron?
You shut up!
Just relax, buddy.
agh!
Oh, god!
What the hell were you thinking?
I didn't shoot him! Are you sure?
Look at him. He's face-down on the
pavement!
I nailed myself in the foot!
God!
I--I don't think he's hit.
Then what happened?
Let's get outta here!
Come on, mickey, wake up.
mickey! Wake up!
* *
We almost done here?
Assuming you did this
shaving your forehead...
Okay, then.
I'm ordering a head c.T.
No, I don't have a headache. I'm not dizzy.
Eddie, I gotta get back.
You gotta stay here.
We'll straighten out that mess
with marco tomorrow.
Let the doc do his job.
Actually, stitching you up
Is really the e.R. Doc's job.
Yeah.
Too long of a wait.
Yeah. Also, a lot of cops in the e.R.
Not that you care about that.
So how did this happen?
Yeah, you're right.
That was a stupid question.
'cause the answer's kind of obvious.
No scrapes on your hands
Means you didn't try to break your fall.
Means either out cold
Or totally disoriented when you went down.
No sign of trauma other than the cut
Means no one hit you in the head.
Powder burn on your jacket sleeve
Means someone shot a gun.
All right, eddie. Come on, let's go.
I don't care what you guys are into.
If you don't get this checked out,
It'll happen again.
Whoa. What will?
This.
Cool.
32-year-old man,
Recent developed loud-noise-induced vertigo.
C.T. Was clean.
No internal bleeding, no edema.
Everything else is in the file.
Cameron get your hair in the divorce?
This guy strained his back three years
ago.
And that's it.
All the rest of these pages are blank.
Yes, he won't tell us anything.
Understandable, since he's a drug dealer.
So he's dangerous and withholding,
Which you find irresistible.
But guys like that, they never call.
he actually said he was
a drug dealer?
Not out loud.
But he was wearing a solid
gold patek philippe.
His friend had a rolex.
But their phones were
prepaid burners,
So they can toss 'em as
soon as they're done.
it doesn't matter
If this guy's a drug dealer or not.
Noise-induced vertigo means ear or brain.
Head ct was clean,
So I'm thinking acoustic neuroma.
We need to do an a.B.R. To test his hearing.
Acoustic neuroma fits.
So does lidocaine toxicity.
Or benzocaine--depends what
he's cutting the coke with.
So now he's not just a drug dealer,
He's a cocaine dealer.
He seemed peppy.
You test his ears.
I'm gonna go test his cocaine.
You think this guy's just gonna hand over
A briefcase full of illegal drugs
Because you ask nicely?
I hope not.
So the best coffee's at geena's,
And the best pizza is at gino's.
Yeah, and don't mix those up,
Because the coffee at gino's could kill ya.
And how's the drycleaner on the corner?
Go two blocks over to eco-clean.
The one on the corner
Used to shred all my boyfriend's shirts.
Good to know.
In retrospect, I should
really thank those cleaners.
We broke up.
This is my stop.
So if you have any more questions
About the neighborhood,
I'm your girl.
Uh, favorite sushi place.
Maybe we could get dinner sometime.
Sure...If you promise to
bring that good-looking guy
With the cane.
You mean house?
Your boyfriend's name is house?
H-he's not my boyfriend.
Oh...
Heh, I'm sorry.
Wh-what do you call each other?
Husband? Partner?
Lover?
We're not gay.
Seriously?
You're gonna hear a series
of clicks and hisses.
Sensors measure electronic activity
To your auditory nerve.
How long is this gonna take?
An hour, maybe an hour and a half.
Or you could walk away
with a tumor in your ear.
Guy's probably late to a stabbing.
Impedances look good.
Starting at 13 clicks per
second at 50 decibels.
Check this out.
13's middle name is beauregard?
Wave three latency is 3.8.
Slightly delayed, but nothing significant.
That's what sticks out to you?
House is clearly screwing with us.
It's a fake paystub.
Looks real to me.
There's no way she makes that much money.
I make that much money.
And...Apparently, you don't.
I need the drugs.
We're in textiles.
I need the drugs!
Hmm...Works for jack bauer.
Is this really necessary?
The chairs in the hall
are way more comfortable.
But way less genre-apopriate.
Okay, here's the deal.
I need information.
You have reasons not to
give me that information.
So either I can force it out of you...
Or I can't.
I wish I could tell ya.
Okay...Well, let's work with that.
Forget the drugs. Let's talk about textiles.
What's your major product?
Is it "h"?
And by that I mean "hosiery."
We do more with...
Culottes.
Is that with a "c" or a "k"?
"c."
Nobody wants "k" anymore.
Does your friend cuthe thfae fabr
No, he's a sales guy.
Well, he must cut a culotte here and there.
No one touches the culottes.
I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you for a second?
I'm interrogating a suspect.
Make it quick.
Everyone in our building thinks we're gay.
We're grown men over the age of 30
Who moved in together.
We're two tigers away from an act in vegas.
They'll figure out we're
straight eventually.
Eventually is not when I want to go out
With the cute girl in 3-b.
Any chance I could get some water over here?
If only there was some way
To communicate that information to her.
Perhaps using, I don't know, sounds.
If only the larynx was capable of--
She didn't believe me.
She sidestepped my dinner invite.
And a woman would only reject you
Because she's worried
That you might not be interested in her.
We were chatting, having fun.
There was definitely a spark.
When she thought you were gay.
You sure your friend isn't secretly tr--
What is a culotte, anyway?
Pants that hang like a skirt.
Just...
Mickey hates the stuff.
He's one of the few guys I trust
To watch the product overnight.
They took him away an hour ago.
You think he's okay?
It's an ear test.
Pretty sure he'll live.
Pupils are constricted. Pulse is bounding!
airway's clear.
Need a crash cart in here!
Gotta be his blood pressure.
We need to get it down
before he strokes out!
At least we know his ears are okay.
We put the patient on vasodilators,
Got his hypertension under control.
He got worse here at the hospital.
Means thug life probably
isn't what's making him sick.
Which means we can stop the
bloodhound gang routine
And go back to being doctors.
But we're doctors all the time.
It's so boring.
Fine.
Could be sick sinus syndrome.
No chest pain, shortness of breath.
Brain aneurysm secondary to
polycystic kidney disease?
normal urinalysis.
Kidney's impalpable.
Is...That a new watch?
Thought I'd give myself a little treat.
What if it's not his brain,
But it's on the way to his brain?
Carotid stenosis.
Get an ultrasound of his carotids.
See if his arteries are clogged.
How much money do you make?
I want a raise.
And I will be happy to talk about that
At your next review... In August.
I know that you're paying me
Less than everyone else on the team.
I can't discuss other people's salaries.
You know that.
Now that they know I'm
making less than they are,
They'll never respect me.
And who told them how much you make?
It's not fair for me to make less
Than the people I supervise.
Salary isn't about fairness.
It's about what you can
leverage in negotiation.
Which isn't much without a
competing offer on the table.
And we both know you don't have one.
Ultrasound showed no narrowing
Or obstruction in the patient's carotid.
-Not that he's worried-
-keeps asking me when he can leave.
a place in the business of healing
people,
You'd think they'd have better chicken
soup.
You bugged his room?
Our patient sleeps in the building
Where they keep their stash.
Eventually, he'll say something
That gives away where that is.
And we'll find out what's making him sick.
But we ruled out environmental causes.
You ruled out environmental causes.
and you pretended to agree,
Just so we'd take him out of his room
So you could plant the bug.
Carotid stenosis was a decent idea.
But an even decent-er idea
Is that he's got toxins
stored in his fat cells.
Every calorie he burns makes him sicker.
If we're going with toxic exposure,
We should just start testing
for the most likely suspects.
Bug's a better idea
Than blindly running tests for days.
Tell him it'll take weeks.
It'll be faster.
What do you mean weeks?
These tests take time.
There are a lot of possibilities.
No, but I--I can't sit here this long.
I got things I gotta take care of.
If you're worried about all
the poor school children
Going without their drugs,
I'm sure someone--
I wanna be discharged.
I'll get the forms.
this is ridiculous.
Beats sitting in a lab all day.
In the lab,
There is significantly less
chance of getting killed.
You're too close. Slow down.
We're in a car in broad daylight.
What's gonna happen?
You honestly think he doesn't
have a gun in that car?
That he's gonna use to shoot doctors?
Just...Back off.
Hey, well played with the watch, by the way.
Borrowed it from a friend.
How much longer are we
gonna keep lying to him?
Until it's no longer fun.
We all thought he needed to be taken down
A few notches.
So we're just having fun, not getting even?
Oh, crap.
whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's gonna get away.
Shut up.
3-b?
You're nora, right?
My roommate tells me you're the one to thank
For all the tips about the neighborhood.
Greg. Nice to meet you.
I hear you thought that wilson and I
Liked to polish each other's swords.
And by swords, I mean pistols.
Of course he told you about that.
Oh, don't worry.
Actually, I'm surprised that
doesn't happen more often.
We're both straight.
Oh, my...God.
That is beautiful.
We finally have the room
To display it the way it deserves.
Would you--would you help
me get this upstairs?
Absolutely.
Nice shoes, by the way.
Louboutin?
You talk to cuddy?
Shot me down.
So, uh, what are you gonna do now?
I'll wait for my review in August.
Oh.
What?
Nothing.
That's what I would do.
But I'm a coward.
His friend brought him in 15 minutes ago.
Temp's 105.
Pulse is weak and thready.
He's not making any sense.
It's too much money, eddie.
That wasn't the deal.
Is he gonna be okay?
Eddie!
we gave him antipyretics
and soft steroids
To reduce the fever and
prevent organ damage.
He's no longer delirious.
Patient went out,
came back worse than before.
Points us back to environmental,
Tied to wherever he went.
No, it doesn't.
Where's foreman?
He had a meeting with cuddy.
What do you mean, "no, it doesn't"?
We screwed up the tail.
My car was impounded.
True,
Amusing, and irrelevant.
Foreman fall for the paycheck thing?
Uh, yeah.
Mazel tov.
Should be fun to watch.
You're off environmental?
Wherever he went,
It wasn't for long enough.
Add in the fever and
infection's way more likely.
And if it is an infection,
His symptomsuggest it's moved to his brain.
Which means...
We'll do a lumbar puncture.
Next time you're tailing someone,
Take two cars.
You knew we were following you?
I'm sorry. I had to lose you.
I had business to take care of.
Right, because you're a businessman.
Do you know how many junkies
Come into the e.R. Every week
with their brains melting?
I'll bet there's more drunks
with their livers giving out.
A liquor store owner
Laying on this table--
I'm guessing he doesn't get attitude.
Aah!
I hit bone.
His old back injury
Must have flattened out his discs.
Sorry, but I've got to try this again.
You okay? Yeah.
An adult wants to get wasted,
Why is it anybody's business
what substance they use?
Because some of those
substances are against the law.
So your problem isn't that it's immoral.
Your problem is that it's illegal.
I got the same problem.
I'm in.
Look at his heart rate.
It's normal.
I know.
I ran into nora this morning.
She told me about your evita
listening party.
The london and new york
recordings are so different.
You were supposed to tell
her that we're straight.
She didn't believe me, either.
You're doing this to mess with me.
Correction--I started doing
this to mess with you.
Now I'm hostly trying to hit that.
By pretending you're gay
And in a relationship with me?
We're in a relationship
and we're really unhappy.
Communication's never been easy for us.
Probably 'cause we're so closeted.
I got it all figured out.
Nora and I spend the next few weeks
Hanging out,
Become best girlfriends.
I confide in her about our issues.
I can't decide if this plan
Is more despicable or illogical.
Then, one night, we get drunk...
Back rub turns into a front rub...
The next morning,
"I've never felt this way
about a woman before."
That's...Quite a commitment you've made
To jumping the girl I'd like to date.
I'd like to date her.
In the sense that I'd like
to jump her repeatedly.
I saw her first.
Seriously? You're invoking the guy code?
We're guys. It's a code.
You're only bringing this up
'cause you know you're gonna lose.
It's not an infection,
But it might be an autonomic nerve disorder.
The hair is still bumping me.
Did you get it cut
Because you're ready for
the next chapter or--
We stuck a needle into
his spinal bodies twice.
His heart rate stayed normal.
If we add that to his
other symptoms...
That would be a mistake.
She's never gonna fall for it.
Well, then, you got nothing
to worry about, sweetie.
You're a wuss.
Say that when I'm better.
What, are you gonna beat me up?
That sounds stressful.
Maybe you should pop one of
your beta blockers first.
You have a heart problem?
Medically, no.
He would have told us about that.
Metaphorically...
It's an effect from operating
outside of the law.
Sometimes, I have to do bad things.
And not always to bad people.
Last few months,
That hasn't been so easy.
A guy got me the pills.
And they control the stress.
Look, don't-- don't say anything to eddie.
All right?
The last thing I need
Is the guys thinking that I've gone soft.
When was your last pill
Before we originally admitted you?
Um, the night before.
And we stuck you in here,
And you went into beta blocker withdrawal.
That's what caused the hypertension.
When he got out of here,
he took another pill,
And the hypertension went away.
Which means it was never a symptom.
We take that off the table,
We've got vertigo, fever...
And stress.
He's been in this game for a while.
Either he grew a conscience
over the last few months
Or he's producing excess adrenaline.
Pheochromocytoma.
What? It's greek for,
"you'll be back doing bad
things to good people
In no time."
M.R.I. His adrenal glands.
You're okay with that, right?
You're not gonna put a pillow over his face?
Oh, great.
Cable guy came.
you know what? It's going good.
How about I just learn to keep
people out of our business?
And that's the real thing.
Hello.
Hi, james.
We've got some kung pao left.
Oh! God. Right there.
Oh. Oh.
We're having a picnic... With wine.
I'll pour you a glass.
He doesn't drink.
Oh. Well, more for us, then.
Well...
I think I might...
Have a little...
How'd it go with cuddy?
She told me I needed leverage.
So, I told her about an offer I had
to help run the neuro department at mercy.
Wow.
Are you really gonna take the job?
There is no other job.
I bluffed. She called it.
I'm not gonna beg to be underpaid.
I'm leaving when this case is over.
House is lying to you.
I know.
And so are you.
It's 2010, I mean...
You know, nobody cares
if you're gay anymore.
I mean, you don't have to be in the closet.
I'm not, I...
Look around you.
Does this really look like a place
Gay men live?
A-apart from the poster.
Those stools are our only furniture.
There are no window treatments.
Well, my ex-boyfriend didn't even know
What window treatments were.
Is that greg's carpenters album or yours?
Look, house hates musicals and fashion
And meringue.
This whole thing is an act
Designed to earn your trust...
In order to sleep with you.
I get it.
Finally.
You're jealous.
You know, if you want to
spend more time with greg,
U should just tell him.
you were wrong.
M.R.I. Revealed no sign
of a pheochromocytoma,
Which means mickey's stress
Is just stress.
We're back to vertigo and fever.
And environmental is back at the top
Of our list of suspects.
We're trying to narrow
down the possibilities.
That receiver doesn't respond
to manual stimulation.
Maybe if you took off your shirt.
Actually, I resorted to
something more exotic.
I call it reading the instructions.
Turns out if you screw the antennae
Into the wrong sockets,
It doesn't actually work.
We lost mickey just outside trenton.
It's supposed to search
for an open frequency.
Most buildings there were built
Between 1920 and 1940.
We're compiling a list
of toxins most common--
There's got to be at
least one open frequency.
I need a few minutes with your friend.
Or stay if you want.
Rectal exam.
I'll check out the cafeteria.
Why the beta blockers?
What do you mean?
Valium and xanax actually reduce stress.
Beta blockers just control
the symptoms of stress.
Whoa.
Keep the heart from racing,
Hands from shaking,
And all those stage fright issues.
That's why some people take
them when they perform.
What the hell is that?
This is my bug.
And this...
Um... This...
This is yours.
You bugged your own room?
Are you...An informant?
An informant would have
sold his pals out to us
At the first sign of a sniffle.
This guy...Is a cop.
I don't see how this is relevant.
In the land of no fun,
You got a really sensible piece of property.
Give him a break.
Knowing this guy's an undercover cop
Doesn't get us any closer to curing him.
Good point. You know what they say.
Information is not power.
Wait...
You're saying we should
Use the cop thing to force him to talk?
Force?
I'm talking about the
womanly art of persuasion.
I said womanly.
If you won't talk to us,
We'll find someone who will.
I mean, you must have a supervisor.
A...Handler.
Good luck with that.
You don't know my real name.
You don't know if I'm local or state,
F.B.I., d.E.A.
But, by all means, get on the phone.
I get it. These guys are lowlifes.
You want them off the street.
They're not just lowlifes.
Eddie killed a snitch three weeks ago.
Boss' orders.
The boss, he's one of the
biggest cocaine importers
In the entire state.
And he wants to expand down to philly.
Tomorrow night, he and eddie
Are meeting the big fish.
And the cops are gonna bust it.
But if you guys get caught
poking around there,
The whole thing gets called off.
That's noble,
But you can't put your life at risk.
I've been undercover for 16 months.
I haven't seen my wife...
My house, my dog.
I have put far too much into this,
And I will not let it fail.
So just...
Just keep me alive for another 24 hours.
And I will tell you
everything you need to know.
Hey.
Uh, can I come in?
Nurses out here can't keep their hands off
of me.
He's a casanova, huh?
What, you bringing me my sandwich?
No, because, guess what.
I don't read minds.
You okay?
Aggh! Gah!
He had a g.I. Infarction caused by a clot
In his superior mesenteric artery.
We had to remove a foot of bowel.
If more clots keep forming,
He may not last 24 hours.
And the moron still won't talk.
Bad guy, cool; good guy, moron?
Pretty much.
Guy's a hero.
He's risking his life to
put these dealers in jail.
I'm sure the dealers who take their places
Will be very grateful.
So vertigo,
Fever, and thrombosis.
We've already ruled out
cancer and infection.
He got worse on steroids,
Which suggests it's not autoimmune.
So we're stuck with environmental.
But what kind of environmentals?
Toxins, parasites, allergens.
We should just pick the
top ten possibilities
And treat for all of them.
Except that treating for everything
Could kill him faster than
whatever's killing him.
Got a better idea?
Sort of. Chase is right.
Our patient is holding
out for noble reasons:
Protecting his bust.
Anybody else on that crew got sick,
I'm guessing they'd be a
little more self-serving.
Thanks.
Surgery went well.
You'll be able to see him soon.
Yeah, used to be all about
ferberizing your kid.
Now they're saying it could mess them up.
Heh.
My--mine's 6 1/2.
Mickey's getting worse.
The clot is a very bad sign.
We really need you to
tell us where he's been.
Heh.
I do that...
There's a very good chance
That I could end up john
doe at the county m.E.
Look, mickey got sick because
he had the most exposure.
Other guys are at risk too.
You don't want to...
You okay?
I--I feel dizzy.
Are you diabetic?
No.
When was the last time
you were at your office?
Whoa...Did you drug me? What?
You're trying to make me think that I'm sick
So I'll take you to the stash.
Of course not, but if you are sick--
No, I don't feel sick. I feel drugged!
Trust me, I know the difference.
You didn't even drink half of it.
You'll be fine in an hour.
You think mickey could die?
Ah, it's just a deal.
I'll take you.
Couldn't have given us a heads up
That he was living in a drycleaner?
It's like living in a vat of poison.
Is that it? Can we get out of here?
I gotta cover all our bases.
Okay, fine. Look...Back there.
Hurry up.
What are these, more chemicals?
Oh, not exactly.
Uh...If this stuff was the problem,
There'd be a lot more sick people.
Did you call the cops?
No.
No one's supposed to be here.
come here.
I said no kissing!
Eddie.
I didn't know you'd be here.
Um...Uh...
Look, the deal was just for you.
This guy wants to watch, it's an extra 50.
Yeah, private party, man.
Uh...I got it covered tonight.
Nice.
The jealousy is... Killing me.
Well...He clearly cares about you.
Very much.
Why can't he show it in a-- in a normal way?
I'm so tired of...
The whole silence and the resentment.
I don't know if I can go back there tonight.
I need some time.
Come stay at my place.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
It'll be fun.
You know, like a-- like a sleepover.
That would-- that would be...
It would be such a help.
Thank you.
House.
What are you doing here?
I'm here because...
Nothing you can say is
going to change anything.
I love this man.
And I am not wasting another moment
Of my life
Denying that.
Gregory house...
Will you marry me?
Wow.
This is unexpected.
Say yes!
I'm gonna go.
No--no, no, no.
You two obviously
Have some talking to do.
excuse me.
How's it coming?
So far, nothing.
Carpet, paint, insulation.
Even the gross food in the fridge.
Everything's coming up clean.
Which leaves the dry-cleaning chemicals.
Should have the results in a few minutes.
Foreman's already started him
On inhaled albuterol.
Chances are, this case is over.
We have to tell him.
We can't tell him.
Won't change the fact
that cuddy let him walk.
It'll just let him know
It was all because of a stupid prank.
We have to tell cuddy.
We confess and beg her
to take him back.
If begging worked, he would have a raise,
And we wouldn't be screwed.
Albuterol is not helping.
Patient started coughing blood.
What about adding ipratropium?
That might-- don't bother.
We assumed this place was
using perchloroethylene.
Turns out... Petroleum solvents.
The drug dealers are
running a green drycleaner?
I hate to push past the irony,
But our patient's bleeding into his lungs,
And we've got nothing.
The v/q scan last night
Showed a pulmonary aneurysm.
Explains the coughing blood.
I did an embolization to stop the bleeding,
He then started up again
this morning.
Three more aneurysms.
Those look like mycotic aneurysms.
Indicates a fungal infection.
That'd be consistent
with his other symptoms:
The vertigo, the fever.
I didn't see any fungus at the location,
And none of the samples--
Looks like somebody missed something.
Which is embarrassing for somebody.
And...The steroids we gave him
Would have suppressed his
immune system.
If that was a fungus,
he'd have 30 aneurysms.
Somebody's got a good point.
One bleed to four in less than 12 hours?
That seems like an uptick to me.
We need to start him on antifungal meds
Before he drowns in his own blood.
Do it.
How long till it starts working?
Give it a few hours.
We'll be back to check on you.
There you go.
Take it easy.
You shouldn't have taken her there,
You imbecile.
They found nothing.
You could have got your brains blown out.
I had to do something.
I couldn't just sit and watch and...
You're my friend.
Thanks.
You'd do it for me.
Ah.
I-I should get going.
Got the big man from
philly coming in tonight.
You want me to stay, I'll stay.
Jimmy knows everything that we know.
No.
The six months
We put in on this...
You gotta be there.
I'll swing by tomorrow.
Hey, eddie.
Yeah?
I'm sorry.
You know that... I can't go with you.
It was all our fault.
We were screwing with foreman,
Trying to make him think
he made less than we did.
Obviously, things got out of control.
Well, someone does something
Stupid and insensitive,
I always figure it was house.
Good to know it's catching.
Look, there is no other job.
He was just trying to get a raise.
Even if you gave him a little more money,
I know he'd stay.
I'm not giving foreman a raise
Because the three of you
decided to amuse yourselves.
We know, and that's why
We want you to take it out of our paychecks.
You two okay with this?
Is there any other option?
We're okay with it.
Foreman is a good team leader.
He deserves it.
Okay, then.
That is what I will do.
And just so you know...
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I haven't seen foreman in three days.
The phrase "who's your daddy?
" comes to mind.
Want to grab some coffee?
Kind of a bad time.
Sorry.
Uh, you told me to drop by, so...
This is when I could make it.
Right.
Come in, yeah.
This whole thing with wilson...
It's all my fault.
We're not closeted, because we're not gay.
For real.
Wilson thought you were cute,
And I was just yanking his chain.
Maybe that's not the best phrasing.
So you were only spending time with me
To screw with him?
God, no.
I was spending time with you
Because I want to touch your boobs.
Enough to listen to evita, twice.
And I really hate evita.
That's how much I like your boobs.
Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait.
Wilson... He's a really good guy.
And he really likes you.
Well, it's really...
It's sweet of you to stick
up for your friend like that.
And you're still trying to sleep with me.
You know, maybe I will call him.
It would serve you right.
Wilson's a jerk too.
Well, at least he tried
to do the right thing.
He's been divorced three times.
He slept with a dying patient.
Sure, he looks like a boy scout,
But then...
the aneurysms
Look mycotic, but they're not.
They're inflammatory.
Because this is not a fungal infection.
The hypertension was a real symptom.
You've been unwittingly
Treating it with beta blockers.
You stopped taking them,
and your blood pressure went up.
It's hughes-stovin.
Okay, so how-- how do we treat this?
We don't.
Hughes-stovin is an
autoimmune disease.
Once it's this advanced,
There's not much we can do.
The aneurysms keep multiplying.
Eventually...One of them will rupture.
Are you sure?
If you die in the next day or so, I will be.
Even if you had told us
everything we wanted to know,
It wouldn't have made a difference.
You did the right thing.
I think I should call my wife now.
* *
I'm sorry about your patient.
He died a hero in his own mind.
Guess it's better than nothing.
Ran into Nora in the elevator.
She no longer thinks we're gay.
Now she thinks we're mendacious dirt bags.
Mendacious dirt bag comes
much more naturally to me.
Least we can get rid of that.
I kind of like it.
Unlike this sofa.
It's 500 bucks.
And... It reclines.
* one *
* singular sensation *
* every little step she takes *
I will punch you in the face.
I'll stop, if you get rid of the sofa.
No chance.
* buh duh duh duh duh duh *
* one *
* thrilling combination *
* every move that she makes *
* buh buh, buh buh, buh buh *
* one smile, and suddenly *
* nobody else, boom *
* will, boom *
Sync by www.addic7ed.com