[Birds chirping]
[Subdued chatter]
[Approaching footsteps]
Hey.
Hi.
The car's full of gas.
You sure?
And if I'm not?
You'll be paying me back
for those damn invitations.
Oh, well, then never mind.
[Laughs]
Ted is a wonderful man,
dad.
He's the second greatest guy
I ever met.
[Pachelbel's Canon]
[Takes a deep breath]
Guess that's us.
Mm-hmm.
[Exhales]
? ?
Hmm.
Into this Holy estate,
these two persons present
now come to be joined.
And so if any person
may show just cause
why they may not
be joined together,
let them speak now or forever
hold their peace.
[Silence]
That's what
I like to hear.
[Soft laughter]
Do you,
Theodore Philip Taylor,
take Nicole Margaret Murray
to be your wife
and promise before God
and these witnesses
to be her loving
and faithful husband,
in plenty and in want,
in joy and in sorrow,
in sickness and in health,
so long as you both
shall live?
[Voice breaks]
I--
[whispers]
This isn't funny, Ted.
[Rasping]
Uh...
Ted.
Are you all right?
Teddy.
[Gasping]
Teddy!
Ted.
? House 6x19 ?
The Choice
Original air date on May 3, 2010
[Massive Attack's ? Teardrop ?]
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --
? ?
[sighs]
Hey.
What time is it?
Happy time.
I'm still asleep.
Just think of this
as a dream.
What about House?
I said a dream,
not a nightmare.
He's in the next room.
Sound asleep.
[Snoring]
Hmm.
[Pounding on door]
Oh...
I met the neighbors.
Sir, do you
know this man?
Hmm.
I don't need a temporary.
I need a permanent.
Yesterday.
Please do.
Good morning.
Hardly.
One of my P.A.s
quit an hour ago,
and I have to reshuffle
next month's schedule.
That's nothing.
I woke up in the wrong bed
this morning.
Any bed you're in
is the wrong one.
That's not what
your mama said.
Oh! Snap.
I'll be going now.
To human resources.
He started it.
It was
the neighbor's kid's bed.
Luckily, Esteban still
likes sleeping with mommy.
How drunk were you?
About yea drunk.
Are you okay?
You shouldn't be drinking
at all, much less--
you sound just like
Esteban's mom.
I need you in the clinic.
Sorry, I'm busy.
Tell me you have a case.
You know,
even if you don't.
I have a case.
Sounds interesting.
I'll take it.
I owe you one.
Now tell me
you don't have a case.
I really do have a case.
We're even.
You guys
know how to honeymoon.
This is Dr. House.
Aphasia and syncope.
He can't speak.
"Aphasia" is Greek
for loss of voice.
We've ruled out infection,
vocal cord damage, and stroke.
A lot of guys
syncope at the altar.
It's Greek for
"having the vapors."
We ruled out all the common
causes of fainting:
Low blood pressure,
hypoglycemia,
dehydratio
don't say "ah."
Do you know
what it is?
Roll on your side
and lift up your gown.
There's one thing
they didn't test for.
A test for what?
Faking.
Ow!
Test was positive.
I-I can--I can talk.
I-I wasn't faking.
My voice
just came back right now.
Hey, I'm not the one
you have to convince.
I know he wasn't faking.
Well, if she's buying that,
she might just be a keeper.
What about the syncope?
Well, the--
is she buying this too?
Why would he fake
anything?
Kryo podia.
It's Greek for "duh."
Still, you get to keep
the engagement ring.
I don't think
he was faking.
That's because you're
more gullible than I am.
For instance,
I don't believe
that you called off
your open marriage.
I believe your wife
called it off,
and you called off
telling her
that you weren't calling it off.
[elevator bell dings]
A guy doesn't just throw
a golden ticket in the trash.
The same way
a guy doesn't give up
a lucrative medical practice
to come work for you?
That's exactly
why you dabble.
You're compensating for
your professional conquests
with sexual ones.
I'm not
that predictable.
For example, you're
probably not expecting me
to ask you out
for dinner tonight.
No, thanks.
You won't even
consider it?
I did,
just very quickly.
The truth is, since
I called this thing off,
my wife has been
very grateful
and I could do
with a down night.
If I go out
with the boss,
nobody can blame me.
Okay.
If you bring your wife.
No. That's the point.
I need a little--
you're lying.
I'm not lying.
Then I'm not going.
Okay.
Fontina at 8:30.
[Siren blaring]
You believe me, right?
Of course I believe you.
Then let's do it.
We'll tell a cab
to take us to AC right now
and get it done.
You're serious?
You just walked out
of the emergency room.
Exactly. I walked out.
I feel great.
Well, we do have
the clothes for it.
[Coughing]
Ted, what's wrong?
Are you--what's wrong?
Oh, my God.
Can somebody help us?
Please!
Please hurry.
Just breathe.
Oh, my God.
There's gotta be a better way
to call off a wedding.
A Tweet, for example.
Pleural effusion.
You think his lung
is faking it?
There's at least 200 ccs
of fluid in there.
Okay, let's say
all his symptoms are real.
Explain how one of them
suddenly went away
without using the words
"virgin" or "mary."
If the pleural effusion's
caused by something systemic,
it could explain
his other two symptoms.
And so whether you
believe him or not,
all we have to figure out
is what caused the pe.
ER ruled out infection.
Eosinophil count
ruled out parasites.
A medication he's not
telling us about.
You really don't
trust this guy, do you?
I don't even trust the ER.
Let's rule out
infections ourselves.
Tap his lungs,
send cultures,
run cytology for cancer,
and check his blood pressure.
We already--
this time, talk about
nuptials while you do it.
Check his home
for everything else.
He just moved in with his
fiancee three months ago.
Toxic exposure could take
longer than that to manifest.
You check his love nest.
You two check
his swinging bachelor pad.
That somebody else
now lives in?
I assume so.
Not the glass. No!
[Shattering glass]
[Sighs]
The place
looks like...1960s?
Could have lead paint.
You think
a 27-year-old has pica?
If it gets us out of here
before the owner
comes back, yes.
What'd you tell
that cute physio?
That I changed my mind.
No, you didn't.
You're more nervous
than usual.
Because this B and E
has actual B.
Wha...
That's
a suspended ceiling.
What are you doing?
I want to see
what's above it.
More ceiling.
Made of 40-year-old
acoustic tile.
Asbestosis.
I like it.
I'll be in the car.
(Cotter)
What the hell?
Uh, it's okay.
We're doctors.
Nobody was home, so--
well, I'm calling
the police.
Do you know Ted Taylor?
He used to live here.
Yeah. What about him?
He's our patient
at Princeton Plainsboro.
Is he okay?
We think he may
have asbestosis
from your ceiling tiles.
They're not asbestos. I had
'em checked when I moved in.
How sick is he?
Is he a friend of yours?
(Cotter)
He was.
Actually, he was my boyfriend
for three years.
I'm not gay.
(House)
Really?
'Cause it would certainly
explain the cold feet.
Oh, and the boyfriend.
So you're bisexual?
No, I'm straight.
Cotter, the guy you met,
he's gay.
He had a crush on me.
I left.
After three years?
Well, it's possible.
It doesn't mean you're gay
just 'cause the guy
you're sleeping with is.
We weren't
sleeping together.
What's this got to do
with anything?
Lung tap turned up
mononucleosis.
ER doesn't routinely
test for it.
It explains the pe
and can be virtually
asymptomatic.
So we got to wondering, how
does a 27-year-old get mono?
You're a little old
for the kissing disease,
unless your immune system
is compromised.
If there's been
any unprotected sex,
we'll need to test
for HIV.
There's been no sex
of any kind.
Okay. I'll go test
your fiancee for HIV.
Is she the curious sort?
Wait.
There may have been
some contact,
but I'm not gay.
Sodomy,
one of the top ten
most common household
accidents.
I did a lot
of stupid things,
but I turned my life
around.
I'm as straight
as any of you.
You don't have
to believe me.
I'm just saying
you can test me...
As long as you
don't tell Nicole.
What business is it
of hers?
(Chase)
I don't see anything wrong
with him marrying
a straight woman.
How about, it'll make
them both miserable?
Just like
most straight marriages.
He's got the right to life,
liberty, and unhappiness,
like the rest of us.
Absolutely no reason
to look at me.
(Chase)
I'm not saying
it's a great choice.
Just saying
it's his choice.
It has to be hers as well,
which it can't be
as long as she doesn't
know he's gay.
Which is how
it's gonna stay
since we have no right
to tell her.
Like you've never
bent the rules.
You date guys.
You date girls.
I assume at some point,
you're gonna make a choice.
I don't lie
about who I am.
Patients lying never
bothered you before.
Patients weren't lying
about their
sexual orientation before.
So you're only judgmental
when it gets personal.
Does it bother me
that people hurt others
because they're too weak
to face the truth?
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
Tell me she's not
looking at me.
He's negative?
Yep.
Looks like being gay
didn't make him sick.
So maybe
being straight did.
The test was negative.
No HIV.
I told you.
What you didn't tell us
is how you turned
your life around.
It can be pretty hard.
It was.
Downright impossible
on your own.
I talked to some people.
It was more than just talk,
wasn't it?
I know this is
personal stuff.
I'm here to help you,
not out you.
I had therapy.
Conversion therapy.
Went to a camp for three weeks
of intensive rehabilitation.
They injected him with emetics
while he watched gay porn.
Apomorphine?
Or lithium chloride
or cyclophosphamide.
He doesn't know.
And when that
didn't work,
they shot him up
with male hormones.
A chemical assault like that
could explain the pe.
And the ECT
explains the rest.
They gave him electroconvulsive
therapy to make him straight?
To zap the fabulous
right out of him.
Neural damage accounts
for the aphasia.
ECT doesn't cause
neural damage.
Unless it was done
at Dr. Liberace's
he-man quackery camp.
Run an EEG.
See if they straightened him
or just scrambled him.
Sorry.
I completely forgot.
My wife just started a ceramics
class Tuesdays at 8:00.
It's a half-hour drive
from here.
She won't be back
till 10:30.
She's taking it
with her girlfriend marly.
She hopes to make
a tea service.
You want to call her?
No need.
I already texted her.
And here she is now.
I think you're still
seeing the physio.
You've got a backup suit
in your car.
Don't want to be
bringing home da stank.
Okay, yes, you're right,
about everything.
But please, House.
Don't tell her.
Hi, Rachel.
Hi, Dr. House.
I didn't know
you'd be here.
Hi, honey.
Got your text, obviously.
I'm just leaving.
I've got
a ceramics class.
Really?
I love it.
Even managed to talk Chris
into signing up for one.
Of course, he's in
the beginners' class.
You're in
a ceramics class?
Friday nights, right?
Friday nights.
Sounded like fun.
You should join Chris'.
You know, I should.
Well, gotta go.
Making a tea service.
Hi, I must have
fallen asleep in the lounge.
What are they doing?
An EEG.
What's it for?
We're looking for
neurological damage
that could have caused
his symptoms.
Damage from what?
A head trauma.
He had an accident?
It wasn't an accident.
It was
before he met you.
Well, what happened?
Was he hospitalized?
You should ask him
about it.
They have the results.
Everything looks normal.
Look at this.
Beta waves are spiking.
What's that mean?
I'm not sure.
(Chase)
He's coding. Crash cart.
What's happening to him?
He's having
a heart attack.
(Chase)
Charging. Clear.
EKG showed
no abnormalities.
So what caused
the arrest?
(House)
Four ways to stop a heart.
Electrical problems,
restricted blood flow,
blood
where it shouldn't be,
shocks, blocks,
or bleeds.
I think that's
three things.
And cheating.
Oh, no. Sorry.
That's how
you break a heart.
I found a ceramics class
in Trenton on Friday nights
that was full
so my wife couldn't join me.
Ep study ruled out shocks.
Now you just have to find
some pottery by Taub.
The lamer it looks,
the better.
(Foreman)
So we'll do an angio
to see if it's
blocks or bleeds.
You should be a doctor.
I'm gonna check out this
new lesbian bar tonight.
Your life is awesome.
You want to come?
[Door closes]
[Click]
I was telling
a 33-year-old woman
that she has breast cancer.
No, you weren't.
How do you know?
Because if you were,
you'd need to see
the pain in her eyes so she
could see the concern in yours.
Why are you setting me up
on dates with my team?
Taub asking me out
was quirky,
but Thirteen doing it
is a barking cat.
I'm doing it to help you.
By setting me up
with a hottie
that I can't sleep with?
And Thirteen?
I've been spending
more time with Sam.
I know
it's been hard on you.
I figured if you
had some company--
I don't need your help.
Then consider it helping
our neighbor's four-year-old.
I gave him a dollar.
How much did you
have to pay?
Nothing.
I just told them
you might be feeling down
and it was
in their self-interest
to keep you company.
100 bucks.
Foreman held out for 200.
House,
I'm worried about you.
You could have ended up
in jail or worse.
Racking you with guilt.
So I do something really
stupid and you reward me.
Read any parenting manual.
That's not helping me.
That's helping you.
Fine, I did it for me,
for my relationship,
out of pure self-interest.
Okay.
You'll do it?
For you.
Thank you.
It's not gonna work, though.
Maybe.
But how bad can a night out
at a lesbian bar be?
Hey.
How are you doing?
Heart attack at 27.
Um, they said
you had a head trauma.
I fell off a stepladder
and--and hit my head.
It was a stupid accident.
An accident.
We need to prep you
for your angio.
Valium will help you relax.
(Thirteen)
We're gonna run a line
through your femoral artery.
Ted?
He's having
another heart attack?
I don't think so.
His heart rate seems normal.
Are you okay?
You weren't discussing
wedding plans, were you?
[Laughs] No.
I guess I just...
Fainted.
(House)
P.O.T.S.
Postural orthostatic
tachycardia syndrome.
BP plummets
when he's upright,
reverts to normal
when he's lying down.
He was lying down
both times we took
his blood pressure.
Protracted hypotension
could have induced
his heart attack.
Also explains
the syncope.
And his aphasia.
He was upright,
then you laid him
down on the bed
to test him.
BP reverted to normal.
Voice came back.
Jabbing him with the needle
had nothing to do with it.
P.O.T.S. can be brought on
by a viral or bacterial
infection such as mono.
So load him up
with fludrocortisone.
You didn't read your ceramics
course description, did you?
Yeah. You did?
As I'm sure
your wife did.
So we all know they're doing
a fourth of July theme.
She'll be expecting
something star-spangled.
(Cotter)
Nicole?
Yes?
Cotter Macklin.
I'm an old friend
of Ted's.
Hi.
How's he doing?
Um, he had a heart attack.
Oh, my God.
They have him
on some new meds.
Really knocked him out.
Well, how are you
holding up?
I'm okay. Thanks.
Um, I brought this
for him.
That's his favorite thing
in the whole world.
I know.
You weren't at the wedding,
were you?
No, I-I wasn't invited.
Ted and I had
a-a falling out.
How did you
know each other?
Um, we met
senior year of college.
Yeah, we--we shared
a house for a while.
You were roommates?
For three years.
[Sniffling]
I'm--I'm sorry.
I-I just miss him.
I think you should leave.
I shouldn't have
done that.
Now.
Please.
I hope he gets better.
[Door slides open]
[Door closes]
Hey, how are you feeling?
Hmm. Don't know yet.
(Taub)
Your numbers look good.
We're gonna keep you
on these meds.
You had a visitor
while you were asleep.
Oh, yeah? Who?
Cotter. Who is he?
I shared a house
with him after college.
I don't know why
he would show up.
That's it?
Yeah.
Why? What did he say?
I need to hear it
from you, Ted.
[Exhales]
One night,
I got really drunk
and I went to bed.
And he came into my room.
One thing led to another.
The whole thing
was a mistake.
Are you saying
you had sex with him?
I was drunk and confused.
You're gay?
No.
I thought I was.
I even made up my mind
to tell my family.
I stood in front of
the bathroom mirror,
psyching myself up.
All I could see
was disgust.
And that's when
I realized,
I didn't hate the thought
of admitting I was gay
because I was ashamed.
I hated the thought
because I wasn't gay.
And that was the day
I went to get help.
So you're not gay?
They cured me, Nicole.
That's what all
the head trauma is about.
I'm sorry
I didn't tell you,
but it's--it's all
in the past now.
It doesn't matter
anymore.
What is it?
[Groans]
Oh, my head!
He's got
severe headaches.
So do I.
Should I call or raise
with a double gutshot draw?
No.
What about infection?
That's what we're thinking.
Cerebral infection
would explain the headaches,
could have caused P.O.T.S.
If it's fungal, it could
have spread to the heart.
I was talking about you.
Has the little gent
been wearing a tent?
Remind me why that has
anything to do with you.
A distracted person makes
a distracted professional.
And destroying my marriage
will help me focus.
Probably.
Do a spinal tap.
Run the CSF.
Still talking about you.
But you can do it on
the patient, too, if you want.
[Club music plays]
? ?
what about her?
The bartender?
She's the only one
who's not here for fun.
Trust me,
she's not straight.
If your gaydar
is so great,
how come you didn't know
about the patient
till you
met his boyfriend?
The guy walked in
with his bride.
It took me a while
to rotate my dish.
It's unbelievable
what he's doing to her.
You don't think
he loves her?
He may love her,
but he needs to have sex
with other men.
Taub loves his wife,
but he needs to have sex
with other women.
Yeah, it sucks what
he's doing to her too,
but it's hardly the same.
To be faithful
to his wife,
our patient has to deny
his identity.
Taub just needs to--
to resist
a biological imperative?
It is easier
to say no to dessert
than to pretend
you don't eat.
Says someone who's obviously
never been on a diet.
Oh, yeah.
My life's a breeze.
You're successful, smart,
and you attract
everything that moves.
If you want to focus
on the fact
that you're not gonna see 50,
that's your choice.
You know what?
I agree with you.
My self-pity's optional.
What about yours?
[Cell phone rings]
Yeah?
CSF was negative
for infection,
and his headaches
are worse.
We were just
talking about you.
Please don't.
It's not P.O.T.S.,
so we're back to square one.
Not quite.
You did a spinal tap,
but the headaches got worse.
We're maxing him out
on morphine.
He sprung a leak.
He's losing CSF
from the tap site.
We made
his headaches worse?
(House)
Just you, actually.
That still
wouldn't explain
why he got the headaches
in the first place.
The low pressure in his
brain caused the P.O.T.S.,
not the other way around.
Patch the leak
and top him up
with artificial CSF.
There. That should
stop the leak.
You should be feeling
some relief soon.
I spoke to my parents.
How are they doing?
They're still worried.
Well, tell them not to be.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Ted?
What's happening?
He's stroking.
Both eyes are responsive.
Tell me your full name.
Theodore Philip Taylor.
This isn't a stroke.
Then what is it?
What's happening to me?
It's really not P.O.T.S.
We're really
back to square one.
So what's masquerading
as a stroke?
Voted the worst Halloween
costume, by the way.
MRA showed no problems
with blood flow to the brain.
Rules out T.I.A.
Chest x-rays
showed no hilar masses.
Any luck with the pottery?
Wasn't easy.
Bought
a suitably cruddy set
of fife and drum
napkin rings online.
Scleroderma?
Skin's fine.
A.N.A. was negative.
So what did that set you back?
Too much.
I got into a bidding war
with some lunatic.
Histoplasmosis.
EIA was clear.
Hey, could have gone
a lot higher than $215.
You're kissmyasthma99?
(Chase)
What about melas?
Mitochondrial
encephalomyopathy,
lactic acidosis,
and stroke-like episodes.
Nillas.
No, idiot.
Lactate levels are stable.
We're missing something.
(Taub)
We've run every test
that makes sense,
asked every question
we can think of,
gone over his history
a dozen times.
We know how much
we can trust his history.
If history is written
by the Victor,
how do we find out
what really happened?
Talk to the loser.
Call the boyfriend.
Let's get them all
in the same room.
Or we could
question them separately
and not torture them.
Or we could get them
all in the same room
and get the truth.
Oh. Drinks are on me
and Foreman tonight.
Can't. Pap smear.
We don't want
to do it either,
but Wilson
already paid us.
It's gonna suck.
I know.
Where and when?
Any incidents
of dizziness?
Seizures?
Blackouts?
Other than
our wedding day.
Don't you think I would have
told you if there were?
My sister's birthday.
I was drunk.
You had one Martini.
On an empty stomach.
Look, he was just
sitting on the couch,
and then he--he--
he fell over and that was it.
Well, once I slept it off,
I was fine.
Well, I stayed up
that night,
checking on him
every 15 minutes.
What about sex?
Yes, I have sex
with my girlfriend,
because I'm not gay.
We have sex.
Thank you.
No problems?
Um, well,
there have been some...
Nic.
Issues.
Erectile dysfunction?
Every guy has it
sometimes.
We never had
that problem.
Gee, that must be because
Ted doesn't like girls.
(Taub)
Or because it's vascular.
I know we did an MRA,
but arterial disease
causing acute ischemia
could explain the heart,
neuro symptoms,
and maybe even P.O.T.S.
Might I suggest
a diagnostic test?
(Taub)
The penile plethysmograph
measures changes in
blood flow in your penis.
Tells us if there's
a circulatory problem.
You just need to be
in the right... state.
What's your pleasure?
I feel terrible.
I-I don't think
anything's gonna work.
Then we'll have
to give you a shot.
Where you don't
want to get one.
Shot it is.
[Midnight Train to Georgia
playing]
? He kept dreamin' ?
? dreamin' ?
? ooh, that someday
he'd be the star ?
? superstar,
but he didn't get far ?
? but he sure found out
the hard way ?
? that dreams don't
always come true ?
? dreams don't always
come true ?
? oh, no ?
? uh-uh, no ?
? oh, he's leavin' ?
? leavin' ?
? on that midnight train
to Georgia ?
? leavin' on
a midnight train ?
? mm-hmm, yeah ?
? said he's
going back to find ?
? going back to find ?
? ooh, a simpler place
and time ?
? when he takes that ride ?
? oh, yes he is ?
? guess who's gonna be
right by his side ?
? I'm gonna be
with him ?
? I know you will ?
? on that midnight train
to Georgia ?
? leavin' on
a midnight train ?
? oh ?
? to Georgia ?
? whoo-whoo ?
? I'd rather live
in his world ?
? live in his world ?
? than live without him
in mine ?
? world,
world is his ?
? his world ?
? my world,
mine and his alone ?
? his and hers alone ?
? I've got to go ?
? world ?
? is his ?
? I've got to go ?
? his and hers alone ?
[cheers and applause]
[Glasses clink]
Nobody wants
to follow that.
The night just keeps
getting better.
To Wilson.
Wilson.
Everything looks fine.
You sure?
Medically,
that's good news.
Are you feeling feverish?
You're sweating.
No. I feel lousy, but I don't
know why I'm sweating.
What is it?
You're not sweating.
You're lactating.
Can't tell
his fiancee he's gay,
how is he gonna tell her
he's pregnant?
His therapists loaded him
with hormones.
Male hormones
don't make you lactate.
Except they could
screw up your thyroid.
(Foreman)
That was over
three months ago.
We just started milking him
last night.
So something else
screwed up his thyroid.
Graves, hashimoto's.
Nope. TSH was normal.
(Taub)
Pituitary tumor.
Could also explain
his libido
and heart issues.
And if the tumor's big enough,
his headaches and syncope.
Except we--
we cleared him for cancer.
(Taub)
Didn't say "cancer."
Prolactinomas
can be benign.
Check his prolactin level,
then MRI his pituitary.
Sounds like
you had fun last night.
You believe Chase?
I believe Foreman.
And they had fun
with you.
What happened?
I realized that they
could be my friends.
You're serious.
And then I sobered up.
You weren't that drunk.
You managed
to find your way
into your own
little bed last night.
I think I sleep better
in rocket ship sheets.
No, you want to blame this
on the booze, but that's easy.
Change is hard.
And wisdom
is knowing the difference
between what
you can change...
And what you were
born with.
And cowardice is labeling
what you don't want
to change as innate.
I was winning
this argument.
Pituitary MRI--
was normal.
How are the headaches?
Terrible.
Give me your head.
What the hell?
I know.
It's the first time
you've heard that sentence
with a possessive pronoun.
[Winces]
Oh, wow, that--
that's better.
[Groans]
[Sighs]
Okay, enough.
How cool is that?
You have
a chiari malformation,
a narrowing
in the base of your skull
that can
cut off CSF flow.
But it wasn't a problem
until the ECT
at breeder boot camp
caused your brain
to swell
just enough
to plug the opening.
And when your brain pressed up
against your pituitary,
it signed you up
for la leche league.
You still won't be pitching
a tent for your lady,
but that's just because,
you know, she's a lady.
Its orthostatic effect
was mimicking P.O.T.S.
It also does
an uncanny Christopher Walken.
Unfortunately, if you
treat it like P.O.T.S.,
it gets worse.
So as far as that goes,
oops.
Proper treatment
is surgery.
We'll get you in
right away.
So how did I
get this thing?
Overbearing mother.
Kidding.
CM's congenital.
Like so many other things,
you were born that way.
I thought you might
be running low, so...
Thanks.
I'm not coming back.
[Sighs]
Ted, this is a mistake.
I know you're hurting,
and I'm sorry.
I'm talking about
hurting her.
I love her.
Ted.
Thank you for your support.
We both really
appreciate it.
Good luck.
[Door slides open]
Hey.
You know
what I've been thinking?
It's your birthday
in three weeks.
What do you say
we rebook the church
and make it
a doubleheader?
I don't know, Ted.
Less than a week ago
we were standing at the altar,
perfectly happy.
Nothing's changed.
Really?
I still love you.
Do you still love me?
Yes.
But--
then that's
all that matters.
But I think that
you still love him.
I'm not gay, Nicole.
I promise you.
How can you
promise me that?
Because I believe
that we get
to choose
how we live our lives,
and I've made my choice.
So now I have
to make mine.
Nic.
I'm sorry.
No. No.
[Kiss]
I'm not saying good-bye.
Yeah.
I want to marry you.
I have to marry you.
Nic!
(House)
It's Friday night.
I called it off.
For real this time.
Frees you up
for the next one.
One day at a time.
Napkin rings.
My way of saying thanks.
For trying to wreck
your marriage?
For trying to save it.
And I get napkin rings?
Expensive ones.
[Box thuds]
I hired a replacement.
For my P.A.
She seems great.
Good work.
You too.
Your patient's
going home tomorrow.
He doesn't have a home.
You want to grab
a bite to eat?
So Wilson
got to you too?
No. This is just me.
Lucas?
Working late.
I'm buying.
I'm not that hungry.
Okay.
I just want us
to be friends.
Funny.
That's the last thing
I want us to be.
[Retreating footsteps]
-- Sync by elderman --
-- for addic7ed.Com --