Help!
Help me!
Dry heaves are gone,
so am I.
I'll check
with the doctor.
No, no, no, no.
I'm here voluntarily,
just got to check with me.
I'm sorry. Dr. Nolan left
specific instructions.
She's not sick. She's scared.
So tell her to tell--
wow.
And he's black.
I thought you'd be a little more
sensitive on the slavery issue.
Can't keep me.
Dr. House,
you look a lot better.
I am a lot better--
No painkillers,
no hallucinations.
Leg hurts,
but it's manageable.
Great job.
Gonna miss you.
Want to start missing you
as soon as possible.
Well, legally, you're free to go
whenever you want.
But I suggest you stay.
I'll take it
under advisement.
If you thought
the hallucinations
Were from your
vicodin problem,
Why didn't you just check
yourself into a rehab facility?
I was deluded into thinking
I might be crazy.
But you had been abusing vicodin
for years.
Never had delusions,
never had trouble sleeping,
Never had any problems,
Other than narcissism
and antisocial behavior,
Until two colleagues died.
Your father died.
Your issues
Run deeper
than vicodin.
Well, that's not gonna
cheer me up, is it?
You need to be transferred
to our long-Term ward,
Started on medication,
talk therapy--
Yeah, I get it.
Uh, just one thing
I'm getting hung up on.
I can leave
whenever I want.
How about I start
with that?
You can't go back
to practicing medicine.
I don't want
to practice medicine.
I've decided
I want to be an astronaut.
Well, if you want
your state astronaut's license,
You're gonna need
my recommendation.
Is that a popular,
new treatment--
Blackmail?
You need to get better.
Welcome to ward six.
So brass tacks--
What do I have to do,
And how long
do I have to be here?
Depends on you.
Process is pretty basic.
If you follow the schedule,
agree to take meds,
Participate in group
and individual therapy,
We can work on goals.
I set a goal.
Excellent.
What is it?
My goal is to get your boss
To write the letter
that I want him to write.
Now let's talk process.
I can smile through
gritted teeth and play nice,
But there are serious risks
of violence
Involved in that choice,
So I'm going with turning
this ward upside down,
Making you
and your boss' job and life
So unmanageable
that he'll write
Whatever he has to write
to get rid of me.
He's all set.
Thanks.
I've never been
in the end unit before.
Yo, I don't need an escort.
Get off me.
Who are you?
You believe these guys?
Lecturing me
on manic depression,
Like I couldn't write
a book or two.
I stop taking my meds, because
I want to stop taking my meds,
Because nothing
is wrong with me.
No reason to keep
dragging me back here.
When I'm on them,
everything slows down.
That's when
the problem is.
Hey, nice to see you.
My roommate last time
couldn't stand me.
Really?
I'm juan alvarez.
J.A.'S my stage name.
But alvie's what everybody
around here calls me,
Like the woody allen character
in, uh, annie hall,
But the puerto rican version
and not as neurotic.
So what do I call you?
You're actually waiting
for an answer this time.
You can call me House.
Ow!
* he's a brick *
* House *
Hey, wait up.
I've already got
the whole place wired,
So I'll give you
the rundown.
Yo, everybody!
This is my new roommate,
House, y'all.
Main thing
you got to know--
Is this the line?
Hey, gabby, meet
my new roommate, House.
You can call him "heezy."
No, you can't.
Don't worry.
She won't call you anything.
She hasn't talked in, like,
ten years or something.
Good you came here.
You need to know
the lay of the land.
I need to request
a new room.
Ha ha.
You're funny.
You're also gonna come here
to get your meds.
I'm not on any meds.
You either?
Good for you.
Tell me my mind
works too fast.
Probably tell usain bolt
he runs too fast.
Excuse me.
I know you're busy ignoring me,
but my minibar is empty.
You think bolt could do
the long jump?
That sport
needs to evolve.
Had the same world record
for, like, 20 years.
I think if one guy launched
himself headfirst
And right before
he hits the ground
Does a front flip instead,
Get three extra feet
out of that, easy.
Go be that man.
Aah!
My head!
Oh!
You're not getting
any haldol.
Sorry.
That's Hal.
His real name is Connor,
But we call him hal,
because he--
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I got it.
We can't play that.
They keep it locked up.
I wish we could,
but at the same time,
You can imagine
how annoying that could be.
Crazy people playing on it
all the time--
We'd never get any peace.
Come on, I want to introduce you
to everybody.
Do you think
he's serious?
He's a doctor.
He knows that acting out will
only reinforce our diagnosis.
or it'll work.
You actually think
this is something
We should be
concerned about?
A patient makes a threat,
you should always be concerned.
There are two new additions
to our ward.
You all know alvie.
Thank you, thank you.
Hold your applause.
It's great to be back here
in mayfield,
Not just for the food,
Not just
for the ladies--
Well, okay,
maybe just for the ladies.
And you should also welcome greg
to the floor.
Don't worry about the name.
I'm just passing through.
Don't want to break
any hearts.
Can we go outside now?
Not now, jay.
So he's
claustrophobic, right?
You're claustrophobic?
Can I get a pen
to write this stuff down?
Where are
you going?
Where's
he going?
It's okay.
Paranoid-
-Check.
Dr. Beasley...
I am having an issue
with the food.
What's the problem?
I swear I'm eating
less and less,
And I just keep getting
bigger and bigger.
A crayon?
Anybody?
We'll talk
about it another time.
I understand you all
Had art therapy
yesterday.
Maybe we can hang some
of the new pieces on the wall.
Cut your wrists, huh?
Greg, there
are certain topics--
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is suicide taboo?
Gosh, if I've broken a rule
on my first day,
I will kill myself.
Group's over.
That flew by.
You realize you're not
the first uncooperative patient
On this floor?
Really?
Is there a club?
Yes.
Come with me
to the clubhouse.
That didn't take long.
I'm that good.
Come on, Alvie!
Let's see some action!
Oh! You got nothing!
Pass, pass, pass!
Good.
Come on, guys!
Ready to play nice?
Would you believe me
if I said yes?
No.
Then, yes.
You do know
I'm trying to help you.
I also know you're trying to be
sweet, caring, and effective.
You're just not.
You want out.
Just talk.
Be honest.
Try to work
with people.
Try to deal with people.
Okay.
[Little cabin song
by billy moon,
sharkey & zooks from the spark]
House, House!
He's on my team!
Shut up.
Nobody likes you.
Am I crowding you?
What?
Can't see the sun?
Huh?
Oh, no, everything
is closing in.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
He's the claustrophobic one,
right?
'Cause I'm doing this
from memory.
You have to dribble.
Why?
The cia satellites
aren't watching me.
They're watching you,
'Cause you're wearing green.
That one
was just too easy.
Seriously, anorexia?
What, are you supposed
to be a girl?
And in answer
to your implicit question,
Yes, those pants
do make you look fat.
How upset were you
when you woke up in the e.R.
And you were still alive
and a failure?
Whoo-Hoo!
2-0, good guys!
You're right. It is rewarding
when you reach out.
You can't go up there.
It's yard time right now.
Put it on my tab.
[Playing schumann's
kinderszenen op. 15 ]
I think you'll find
music therapy's more effective
If the patients are inside
To hear it.
Where'd you get
the key?
[German accent]
they gave it to me.
So if she ever talks,
Are we gonna get
a german accent?
No.
She's, um,
my husband's sister.
So let him come play
the piano.
He doesn't know
how to play.
Nice.
You're a little heavy
on the right foot, though.
See her head?
It bobs to the music.
It's the only real reaction
I'm getting from her.
It feels like
we're talking.
You're not talking.
Her head is bobbing
to her pulse.
Are you a new doctor
on the ward?
Technically, yes.
Can I lead this time?
Leave the lid unlocked
when you're done.
[Iron & wine's
love vigilantes plays]
* oh, I've just come *
* from the land of the sun *
* from a war that must be won *
* in the name of truth *
* with our soldiers so brave *
[door opens]
* your freedom we will save *
Can you close the door?
You're letting
all the cool air out.
* and some help from god *
If you keep up
this scorched-Earth policy,
You're gonna end up
living in this room.
Are you ready to try
another strategy,
Or do you want me
to leave you in here?
Unh!
21.
2-1, that's game.
Hey, House is back.
I'll get the ball.
Come on, I need some meat.
I got no one left to play.
I'll play you.
[Scoffs] girl.
Come on, House.
You can serve.
I've had some time
to think about the approach
I've been taking.
I know I'm unhappy here,
and I--
I've been taking it out
on you guys...
Unfairly.
It was...
Misdirected anger.
'Cause when you think about it,
the real jerks here...
Are the doctors.
House.
See how they give you
a ping-Pong table,
But no paddles, no net?
It's like
they're mocking you.
Preach!
The game is called table tennis,
not table volleyball.
Greg, you know where this
is gonna end.
Who ever saw
A tennis court
without a net?
Little run-Down park across
from my apartment growing up--
Three courts, no nets.
No one ever used it.
No one's gonna try to hang
themselves with a ping-Pong net.
Of course not.
Yeah, that's ridiculous.
It ain't right, doc.
You treat us like little kids.
No, little kids
are allowed to play ping-Pong,
And they can play
the piano.
Yeah,
worse than little kids.
All right, why don't we just go
and sit down
And discuss it?
No, no, no.
No, I want to discuss it
right here.
Guys.
Uh...
Guys!
House is right.
I think everyone here
can handle these.
Seriously?
Is that your strategy--
Give everybody
what they want except me?
You're a natural leader.
You could do
something useful down here,
For them,
definitely for you.
Or we could keep
fighting...
If you think
you can break me,
If you think I'm not every bit
as stubborn as you.
* came to fight the man *
* and he had
the master plan *
* but it started
to unravel *
* nolan smashed him
with his gavel *
* like blah! *
Shut up.
So you gonna keep trying
to make them miserable?
No.
New plan?
Yep.
What is it?
I don't know yet.
* his mind
is burning *
* the wheels
are turning *
* the butter
is churning *
* you think nolan can keep
House from strolling? *
You know, it's easier to come up
with a new plan in silence.
Right. Cool.
I want you all to welcome another
new addition to our ward--Steve.
Uh, freedom master.
Steve Elkerton
Is just a cover.
It's like Clark Kent
or Bruce Wayne or Peter Parker.
Cool.
We got more jesuses
than superheroes.
Well, I try to blend in
in the outside world,
But I figure in here,
everybody gets it.
Hey...
We're living
in the ward of justice.
Alvie.
Can you explain
a little more
About what you think
everybody gets?
There's good and evil
in the world.
And some people
are--Are special,
And they're chosen to help keep
evil forces at bay.
You don't think
You can stop bullets,
do you?
I move out of their way.
Can you read minds?
No.
It's group time, greg.
Why isn't she talking?
She needs help.
She needs somebody
to save her.
That's what
we're all trying to do.
Let's take five minutes.
Everybody
get to know steve.
I can fly.
I know you're scheming,
Working on your next elaborate
plan to get out of here.
Why don't you put the plan
on hold for a few days?
See what happens.
Just let me do my job.
If you prefer private to group,
we can do that,
Maybe try some ssris.
If you think nothing's working,
you can always go
Back to your schemes.
God, if only you'd said that
two minutes ago,
Before I came up
with my new scheme.
Now I'm committed.
Ha. Get it?
unh!
* shaq up in my area *
* I'm a better baller
and a better rapper *
* what? And I'm good
at basketball too *
Do you have
third-Floor privileges?
Ever since I shared in group
about my uncle fondling me.
waah.
Is that true?
Yeah. And now I can use the
third-Floor vending machines.
You eat sour cream
and onion chips?
I mean, the whole point
is the dipping.
Sure, we save time by not adding
the mix and sour cream,
But you're missing out
on the--
I need you to break
into nolan's office.
Commando style.
I want you to focus.
You want me
to mess him up?
Go into nolan's office.
Look at his calendar.
I need the name of the woman
he met with at 11:00 today.
No problem. And I'll get you
some old-School chips.
If they have them,
I'll get you some dip,
But I've never seen dip
in the vending machine.
Yes, get me
chips and dip.
What else?
I get it, I get it.
Plan "b."
"B" is for blackmail.
I got you covered.
commando style.
[Plays beethoven's
symphony no. 5 in c minor]
Let me go!
I just wanted a little snack.
That ain't right!
Yo, I didn't know
the machine was moved!
I want some ritz bits!
Yo, I might be pregnant!
I get these cravings!
You get the name?
Nolan's schedule book
just has a big "x"
Marking out the whole middle
of the day.
Well, then we can assume
the girl he's with
Is called "nooner."
* nooner, nooner *
* Nolan's
gonna spoon her *
He's gonna "fork" her.
* and then he's
gonna knife her *
I didn't get a chance
to check the phone
Or anything else.
That's okay.
I got her license plate.
I call my friend.
He gets the name.
I get the letter
that gets me out of here.
You got
phone privileges?
I'm on level minus four.
I'm still writing with a crayon.
You?
You got to be
at level five.
That's like the top
of the space needle.
Hal's the only one
that's up that high.
Hal's at level five?
They give him a point
every time he clears his plate.
I've been eating
his potatoes.
Will he sell you
some minutes?
No. I pay two cigarettes
for the potatoes.
Phone's worth
a lot more.
Can you cheek a pill?
No.
That's too bad
for you.
[Stanton moore's
poison pushy]
You sure you're good
with this?
Yeah, yeah.
Got to be done.
So how do we start?
I think
we just start.
Make it good.
Make it real.
Just do it already.
Aah!
Code gray!
Give me five milligrams
of haldol!
aah!
Help!
Get him off me!
Give it to him!
Dude, that was awesome.
Think hal will mind
if they're wet?
House?
No, it's your other friend
at the asylum.
How's it going?
Hallucinations are gone,
so is the vicodin.
How's the leg?
How's the pain?
They got me
on some nonnarcotic.
I'm dealing.
I need you to run
a license plate.
Was there a hit-And-Run
on your floor?
House, just do
what you're supposed to do.
Listen to the doctors,
And I'll be able
to visit soon.
Track down
the owner of this car,
And I'll be able
to visit you
In your office
tomorrow.
My doctor is too smart,
Too old, and too well-Dressed
to only be running one ward.
He screwed up something
in his life,
And I think
he's doing it again.
I need her name so I can
blackmail the blackmailer.
House.
He called me.
What did he want
to know?
He wanted to know
about you.
He wanted to warn me that
you'd be calling for something.
And he told me if I wanted
to help you get better,
I had to let him
do his job.
Well, now I'm calling you to
tell you that if he calls you--
House, I'm so sorry.
I wish I could help you.
You can.
It turns out...
You're my only friend.
* House ain't a newbie,
now he living on this floor *
And I hate you.
I'm gonna cooperate.
That's not much of a plan.
That's actually their plan.
No, I'm pretty sure
their plan is for me
to actually swallow
the pills,
To actually cooperate.
I'm so proud
of my little roomie.
I only taught him
Everything he knows.
One, two, three.
Okay, stomp,
you start the betting.
Highest card wins.
That's probably a fold.
Richter.
Uh...
Two cigarettes.
He's not confident,
alvie.
Crush him, in the form
of a rhyme if you want.
* no regrets,
raise ten cigarettes *
Whoa, that's
a lot of nerve
For someone with a two
on their head.
You're messing
with me.
You can't raise ten.
I only have five.
Throw in
your phone card.
I'm not gonna throw in
my phone card.
Can I play?
Come here.
Why?
I want to see if you've got
what it takes.
Give me
your best poker face.
* well, now before
the judge gets back *
Too rich for my blood.
You can take my seat.
(Nurse safer)
med time!
How are you feeling today?
Better than yesterday,
not as good as tomorrow.
* smoke without fire *
[Playing schubert's
impromptu #3 in b flat]
I've been humming
to her.
She sways.
It might be significant.
Are you ignoring me,
Or are you just letting
my charm wash over you?
Kind of tough
to play and chat.
A couple of weeks ago,
you told me
Playing to her
was a complete waste of time.
You're right.
Your playing does get worse
When you talk.
I assume she loved music.
She played for
the philadelphia philharmonic--
Cello.
Well, if she responded
to the piano,
She might respond even better
to the cello.
I play a little.
Hmm.
Maybe I'll bring one in
tuesday.
Thank you.
Different desk,
different doctor.
You've been on meds
for a while now.
I'll be checking in
with you periodically
To see if we need to adjust
your dose.
Any dry mouth,
trouble sleeping?
Nope.
Can I go now?
There's a manic out there with
a fresh carton of cigarettes,
And he's
a terrible bluffer.
It's nice to see that you
and alvie are friends again.
Tell me
about your fight.
He hit me.
I hit him back.
Repeat until pulpy.
Alvie told me
you instigated the thing.
Well, that tends to be
the way fights work--
Different interpretations
of the same circumstances.
Very understanding
attitude.
There's that tone again.
You're smart.
How come every time
you compliment me,
It sounds
like an accusation?
You're not having
any side effects
From your meds,
which is unusual.
It's not
that unusual.
The story about the fight
isn't adding up.
Why don't you
stop pretending
That you haven't reached
a conclusion?
You don't trust me.
Actually, it's
more fundamental than that.
You don't like me.
I didn't say that.
You think
I'm not taking my meds.
Are you?
Yes.
So what do you
want me to do?
Want me to take
a urine test?
Will that earn
your trust?
Actually, yeah.
Have at it.
A little dignity,
please.
You know the rules.
I have to watch.
Yeah, but you don't have to have
courtside seats.
Can I at least use a stall?
* *
* for he himself
has said it *
* and it's greatly
to his credit *
* that he is
an englishman *
* he I-I-I-I-S *
* an englishman *
Get it
while it's hot.
I'm sorry
I doubted you.
Freedom master,
Think you
could help me out?
You need help?
Of--Of course.
That's--
That's what I do.
Great.
Could you move
the piano for me?
It's 500 pounds.
That's not too much, is it?
Well, is there something
trapped underneath or...?
No. I just want to move it
away from the window.
I'm sorry my powers
aren't for frivolous--
Just one quick lift.
Why are you doing that?
House, it's none
of your business.
I'm curious.
As a doctor,
what are you doing?
Either he is freedom master,
and he shouldn't be here,
Or else he's suffering from
a serious and dangerous delusion
That he needs
to deal with.
So...
Legit medical reasons.
You're not just trying
to break the guy
Because he's
a little different.
He's not different.
He's delusional.
Can you help me out?
What is she looking at?
You're not
a superhero, steven.
You're just
a regular person.
I can save her.
That's okay. We're--We're all
just regular people.
It's what we do.
They stole
her voice box.
They have it in there.
That's what
she's staring at.
She's always staring--
Your wife is dead.
Good can defeat evil.
Not every time.
Evil people killed a lot
of good people that day.
You couldn't save her.
No one could save her.
It's in there.
Her voice is in there.
Code gray.
Her voice is in--
Her voice is in there!
Aah!
No!
Don't do it.
I'm not doing
anything.
You're thinking.
Things go from thinking to doing
way too fast in this place.
You keep thinking, you're gonna
wind up with no mo in your mojo.
I'm thinking
of hitting you again.
You hate medina.
You hate all of them.
You want to hurt them.
You got to keep pretending.
Step away from the hate.
What's the difference
between pretending to cooperate
And cooperating?
Pretending is pretending.
It's not real.
You don't mean it.
I sat and watched while he did
something stupid and pointless.
I cooperated.
In a few days,
you won't have to watch,
Because you're going home.
You'll be getting
your job back.
Everybody inside!
Closing ceremonies.
Everyone attends.
One of you is going home.
It's been a great week.
Um, a number of you
have made tremendous strides.
But today we're here
to congratulate
Susan.
We're proud of her!
We wish her well,
and we hope
to never see her again!
Yeah, isn't it pretty?
And, um, dr. Beasley,
do you want to cut the cake?
Yeah, I'll do that.
Okay.
Where's freedom master?
He isn't able
to take part.
Get out there.
They said everybody
has to get out there.
Talk!
Say something!
Dr. House,
leave him alone.
Did you drug him?
Of course
I didn't drug him.
He's in flat affect.
He's practically catatonic.
Hey, we got cake.
He's fine.
Double chocolate.
Yummy, yummy.
Don't tell me
that he's fine!
You did this!
He was functioning.
He was happy.
He was delusional.
Yeah.
He's way better off now.
dr. House...
Let's talk.
Thinking sucks.
I'm not allowed
to get angry?
They screwed him up.
And for the record...
I am two privilege levels
above susan,
And I got the same
depression-Scale score.
Every patient
is different.
It's not about scores
And levels and--
Happiness
is happiness.
The test is the test.
Coping is coping.
And you think you're--
Absolutely!
I need to address
some deeper issues,
Which I can do
on an outpatient basis.
Three hours a week?
And that's just
my opening offer.
If you want to counter,
I'll likely fold.
No.
"No" is not
an argument.
Are you trying
to frustrate me?
No.
"No" again?
I can cope!
I'm coping.
In fact...
I'm coping
better than you think.
I've not been taking
my meds,
Not one.
And yet, I still scored
a "high functioning"
On your depression test.
So your proof of your well-Being
is that you lied?
Manipulated.
My proof is
That I can fool the test,
I can fool you,
Which means
I am high functioning.
I am sane,
rational, capable.
I should not be here.
These are your pills
from today?
I'm not gonna take it.
I'll just cheek it again.
Lick it.
You want me to lick
your hand?
I washed.
It's sugar.
Your test results
Were improving
too regularly
And too quickly.
I was concerned that
you weren't taking your pills,
That it was all an act,
So I switched you
to a placebo...
To see if your...
Improvements
would continue.
Your psych tests
told me nothing,
But your urine tests
Told me
you were faking.
You need to stop fighting
the system.
You need to let me
do my job.
So...
What's the next plan?
There is no new plan.
I'm out of plans.
So what do we do?
We stop talking.
I see you've got some cello
in your trunk.
And, no,
that's not a euphemism.
Are you spying on me?
I'm living
in a psychiatric hospital.
Staring out of the window
is what we do.
I assume you'll need help
carrying it up.
I still got
grounds privileges.
And who's going to carry you
when you're carrying the cello?
Yes, cast aside
the useless cripple--
How very german of you.
Seriously, the thing
weighs a ton with that case.
I think
I'll need a dolly.
Or we could ask clark kent
to pitch in.
The dolly's probably easier.
Eh, the dolly...
Already feels good
about itself.
He was a happy-Go-Lucky
superhero
Until they told him
he has no powers.
We let him help out,
he feels good about himself.
Might be
less depressed.
Why do you put
your life on hold
to visit your sister-In-Law
five times a week?
Am I somehow a bad person
for showing compassion?
No.
You're not even
a bad person
For lying about
why you're doing it.
(House)
oh, that
is impressive.
That is
a superhuman feat.
Why don't
you take a rest
Before you fly that thing
up to the ward?
He's still depressed.
Give me
your car keys.
You gonna dangle them in front
of him to entertain him?
I'm gonna make him feel
like he's flying.
I'll just drive him
around the grounds, top down,
Wind in his hair.
Seriously...
You're gonna say no
to that?
[Engine turning, revving]
Why are you
so nice to me?
I think you have
a good heart.
Would you still be nice to me
if I told you that I lied?
I'm not just driving
Around the grounds
in your convertible.
I'm kidnapping him
and stealing your car.
You sure?
I was just starting to feel
a little heat between us.
Thought we had
Kind of a "bonnie and clyde"
thing going there.
Bonnie and clyde
get shot to pieces.
[Car door closes]
hmm. See you.
You can do this.
If you hold my hand,
I can do it too.
Whoo-Hoo!
Whoo!
Don't let go!
Aah!
Going up!
Whoo!
Freedom master's back!
Keep it down,
freedom master.
Whoo!
You're scaring
the good citizens.
That was the coolest moment
of my life.
It was fun.
You can repay me
by telling nolan he's an idiot.
Smell that fresh air
And the warmth
of your yellow sun.
We do enjoy it.
[Imitates whooshing]
Careful of the traffic.
Don't go damaging
any fenders.
Hey.
Hey!
Come on, get down.
There's no cry for help.
There's no cat
in a tree.
Thank you, greg.
No!
(Nolan)
he's lucky to be alive.
He's got
a lacerated spleen,
Rotational
pelvic fracture,
Compound break
of the femur and humerus.
Everything in your life has been
about finding the truth.
But suddenly,
with this guy,
You decide to reinforce
a sick man's delusions.
You just wanted to take
a swing at me, hmm?
You don't care
about getting out.
about him.
You don't even care
about the truth.
You don't care
about anything, House.
I'm transferring you
to winslow psychiatric.
You'll have better luck pulling
the wool over their eyes.
I'm done.
Don't.
I need help.
So how is this
supposed to work?
You sit. I sit.
We talk.
About what?
About whatever you want.
You want me to whine
about my mother?
Do you want to whine
about your mother?
I can tell you about the time
I was five and my goldfish died.
If that's where
you'd like to start.
I've had a billion things
happen to me in my life.
How am I supposed to know
which ones are relevant?
As far as I'm concerned,
they're all relevant.
Well, we better get moving,
'Cause this session
could take 50 years.
Yes, you are the sum
Of everything
that's happened to you.
And, yes, some events
are more relevant than others.
But, uh, the only way
we can figure out which ones are
Is to talk.
So tell me,
What's on your mind?
What do you want?
I want to get better...
Whatever the hell
that means.
I'm sick
of being miserable.
So you'd like
to be happy?
Again with the reflecting--
Yes, I'd like to be happy.
Being happy
is an excellent goal.
Not many patients
can crystallize
Exactly what they're hoping
to get out of this.
Well, bully for me.
So now all we have to do
Is figure out how to get you
from here to happy.
Ssris?
That's your
genius technique?
I don't think we should ignore
any tools that can help.
I know you don't have
a problem taking drugs.
For my leg, for pain.
Well, think of this
as being for psychic pain.
I don't want to change
who I am.
Miserable?
Do you think
that by taking meds
You'll lose your edge,
stop making
the unique connections
that make you
a successful doctor?
If van gogh
was your patient,
He'd be satisfied
painting houses
Instead of
the starry night.
Van gogh
would still be making inspired
paintings of the night sky,
just maybe not
from the room of his asylum.
You don't know that.
I know
both his ears
would be intact.
And I know his life
would be better.
I know this doesn't come
naturally to you.
But you want my help,
which means
you need to trust me.
Hmm...
Delicious.
Why are you here?
I'm waiting
for my communion wafer.
You're cheeking it,
right?
Nope.
Tell me
you're cheeking it.
I swallowed it.
No, you didn't.
We don't take meds.
You don't take meds, alvie.
I decided to get sane.
You're scamming again.
You can tell me.
I'm not scamming,
alvie.
They broke you.
They didn't break me.
I am broken.
Now stop worshipping me
And go and worry
about your own loser life.
I hate you.
Prom?
Got an assignment
for you.
Role-Playing?
I'm not sure how pretending
to be a businessman
with a foot fetish
is gonna help,
but I'm game.
Have you connected
with any of the other patients?
You've been here
four weeks.
Tell me about
your relationships
With the other patients.
Diane...
Is convinced
that silent girl hates her.
Richter's not
as paranoid as you think.
He just likes
that you think that.
And my roommate
hates me.
Only one
of the things you said
Indicated how somebody else
feels about you.
So...
I'm sure that
they've done some form
Of rudimentary analysis on me,
concluded that I'm a jerk.
You know, there is a way
For them to find out
things about you
Without
deductive reasoning.
I have had
relationships.
You've screwed up
relationships,
Every one of them--
Almost like that was the goal.
I want you
To trust...
People.
Try.
Get dressed.
[Playing no moon at all ]
Just open up?
Just open up.
Trust.
Strangers?
We'll start
with strangers,
Then work our way up.
If it helps,
I find "hello" to be
an excellent icebreaker.
[Jazz combo playing
night train]
Hi.
It's like "hello,"
only shorter.
Yes.
I'm glad we were able
to save that time.
Judging by the fancy suit,
I'd say you were a donor.
The nervous demeanor
says maybe you've had issues,
Probably is why this place
has personal meaning.
But this is supposed
to be about me.
I take advantage
of my friends.
Friend, really--
I've only got one.
It can be tough
sometimes.
I'm not gay.
Oh, neither am I.
Actually, I am.
See that guy
over there?
He's my lover.
He's also
my psychiatrist,
Which some would argue
is a little inappropriate,
but they just don't know
what love is.
Am I right?
You're not gay.
No, but I have to tell
intimate secrets to people.
Maybe they
should be true.
Hadn't thought
of that.
To be on the safe side,
I should probably do both,
Starting
with the fun ones.
Come on,
let's get me better.
[Playing I love paris]
Hi.
Yeah.
I'm a philanderer.
Oh.
Philanderer doesn't mean
that I give a lot to charity.
It means--
I-I know
what it means.
Uh, you were asking me
if there were any nuts
in the hors d'oeuvres.
What?
Honey.
What did my husband
just say to you?
I...
Was asking him
if there were nuts...
In the hors d'oeuvres.
Then where
is your epipen?
My what?
No one with an allergy would
walk around without an epipen.
Give me your purse.
No.
Stop!
Come--
No.
What really happened
Is...
I thought he was cute.
I hit on him.
We're going.
[Combo plays
every time we say goodbye]
You having fun?
I did connect
with one guy.
But then
my propensity
For screwing things up
overtook me.
Then my desire to have fun
overcame my propensity.
You didn't screw it up.
The assignment wasn't to get you
to trust people
With a piece
of your soul.
The assignment was to teach you
that you can trust.
Did any of these people
rat you out
As the obnoxious womanizer
Or the porn producer
that they think you are?
Why do you think
That people would treat you
worse if they knew the truth?
Good night, doctor.
Are you
in trouble?
Apparently not.
So what's next?
You want to be
my pimp?
Why don't
we just talk?
Okay.
How come you weren't pissed
at me for stealing your car?
It was a nice thing
to do.
Hmm.
I'm not sure
About the german-English
translation of nice.
You mean the stealing
was nice or...
Ruining
freedom master's life?
What you did
was misguided
And irresponsible,
But it was also nice.
You gave him a moment
of pure happiness.
You asked me why I come here
so often to visit annie.
She was
my best friend.
Then she started
pulling away...
From everybody.
The doctors
don't know why.
I think
I married her brother
because...
He was
the only other one
Who was going through
the same thing.
But he stopped visiting
after a couple of years.
I just...
Couldn't stop.
I miss her.
I should go.
Good night.
So what happened?
You're talking
to me now.
No.
Was it fun?
She kissed me.
Don't read
into the phrasing.
We kissed each other.
And how do you feel
about that?
How do I feel about that?
It was a kiss.
Kisses are good things.
Okay.
That was
a loaded "okay."
Not at all.
Why would you assume that?
'Cause you're being
judgmental.
If I had said that I'd had
some delicious chilean sea bass
For dinner last night,
Would you say, "and how
do you feel about that?"
If the sea bass
was married, I might.
See, you're being judgmental.
Isn't that against your code
or something?
I'm simply stating
the obvious.
It's complicated,
not just because
she's married
and not just because
you're institutionalized.
I know you spent
the last 12 hours
trying to figure out
what that kiss means.
Who's that woman you
were with in the parking lot?
When you deflect,
it's more effective when
you're not that transparent.
Obviously you have no problem
with the infidelity.
You're trying
to rationalize that,
"If it's okay for your doctor,
it's okay."
But just
for the record,
I am not having
an affair.
Then who is she?
Why do you think
you're working so hard
To figure out the details
of my personal life?
I might not have
to work so hard
If there were
some personal items in here.
You got one number
on speed dial.
It says "dad."
Come on,
how old are you?
Why are you so afraid
to talk about this?
I want to talk about you.
I want to know
who I'm taking advice from.
I'm not giving you advice.
I'm asking you questions.
I think that kiss
meant a lot.
I think that scares you.
I think there are
no personal items in here
Because you have
no personal life.
How do you think
you and Lydia will end?
You are a lonely man.
You've screwed up every
opportunity you've had in life.
What's the ending
to the story?
I don't know.
Visiting time!
Why did you kiss me?
How many reasons are there?
I like you.
It felt like a nice way
of showing you that.
[Playing schumann's
kinderszenen op. 15 ]
Open it all the way.
Keep it open.
How'd it go with Lydia?
I found out
you can only be happy so long
Before the catatonic guy
with two broken limbs
Rolls off the elevator,
Philosophically speaking.
Why do you value your failures
more than your successes?
My mother
caught me masturbating...
To pictures
of her mother.
Can we get past
these cute deflections?
Successes only last
until someone screws them up.
Failures are forever.
So you accept
that fact.
You accept that
there's nothing you can do.
Okay, I accept the fact
that there's nothing I can do.
Now, what can I do?
You acknowledge failure,
And you move past it.
You apologize.
Wow.
Powerful things
these apologies.
Get someone to jump
off a building.
You say two words,
and you move on with your life.
Hardly seems fair.
Is that the issue?
You caused him pain.
If the world is just,
you have to suffer equally?
You're not god, House.
You're just another
screwed-Up human being
Who needs to move on.
Apologize to him.
Let yourself
feel better.
Then you can learn
to let yourself...
Keep feeling better.
Hey.
Dr. House, everything okay?
Yeah.
Time for group.
Group time, everybody!
I have a surprise.
Two weeks from today,
we're going to have
the Mayfield talent show.
Talent show?
Who's in it?
I'd really love it if everybody
here could participate.
Then who's gonna watch?
The staff will come,
friends and family.
You gonna tape this?
No, it's just for us.
Well, if it's just for us,
I vote we don't do it.
Think of it as a fun way to work
on--On our therapeutic issues.
Alvie, maybe you could sing
one of your songs.
I don't sing. I rap.
Okay, well, you can write
something just for us.
I don't write.
I just do, freestyle style.
I think you're gonna
want to be prepared.
Make something
special.
Always special.
How about you, Diane?
Is there something
you'd like to do?
I don't have
any talents.
Sure you do.
You all do.
Steve, don't you think
that Diane has hidden talent
That we'd all like
to see come out?
You really think
he's gonna answer?
Eventually.
Why?
Because things pass.
Things change.
It doesn't mean
they get better.
You got to make
things better.
You can't just keep talking
and hope for the best.
Diane, maybe you and I
can work together
And figure something out.
I can save him.
"They stole her voice box"--
That's what he said.
That's what
she was staring at.
That's why he's staring.
Dr. House, please.
'Cause there's
a music box in there.
Orderly.
Come on, just give it to me.
I can--
I am not having
a psychotic break.
I promise you
this will work.
It's the blue box there
On the top shelf.
This is what you wanted.
This is what you needed--
A voice.
You thought you could cure
silent girl with this.
So by your own rationale,
it should cure you.
There's nothing wrong
with you.
You're healing.
All the parts work.
Just speak.
Come on, speak!
Say something!
I think maybe everyone
should take a break now.
You're trying to fix
instead of moving on.
I brought dvorak--
Four hands.
What?
I need to know
what this is.
It's sheet music.
I told you.
It's just...
Two people having fun.
There's two
possible outcomes.
It ends.
Someone gets hurt.
Or it doesn't end.
So the end sucks.
It doesn't mean
the beginning has to.
Everything ends.
Life ends.
It--It doesn't mean
that we can't enjoy it.
I can't--
I can't do this.
All I know is,
I was happy five minutes ago,
And now I'm not.
How's that better?
Good-Bye, Lydia.
I'm really worried
about E.C.T.
Apprehension's normal.
Has anyone else had it?
They shocked me, man.
Aagh!
Thanks.
That's very reassuring.
I don't know
if I should do it.
Oh, just do the treatment
or shut up.
Greg, there's
a process.
Yes, a process.
Wouldn't want to disrupt
the process with results.
Heezy had a rough night
last night.
Guess he decided to go
back to being an ass
Instead of a hypocrite.
let's move on.
Alvie, are you making
any progress writing your rap?
yeah.
But really, no.
I just don't want to write
my songs down.
It takes all
the spontaneity out of it.
It's not
of the moment.
Alvie, if you write
things down--
* when the time comes,
my rhyme comes *
* when my spotlight shines *
Yeah, you're a genius.
Rhymes with "penius."
Sorry to interrupt,
dr. Beasley.
Dr. Nolan asked me
to give you this.
Is this
a day pass?
He'd like to see you.
Thanks for coming.
I was hoping you could, uh,
take a look at my dad's chart.
A consult?
What happened--You went through
every sane doctor in town?
I thought you wouldn't mind
getting off the ward.
Cleaning lady found him
on the kitchen floor.
Doctors here don't think
that he'll recover,
That I should pull
the plug.
I want a second opinion,
so I--
I thought I'd be a fool
not to call you.
Lacunar infarct,
Converted
to hemorrhagic stroke.
It squashed his brain.
They didn't miss
anything.
That's what I thought.
That's what you knew.
His brain
has been replaced by blood.
It's over.
And that's obvious
to any doctor
Who looks at that scan,
even a shrink.
You want someone
to tell you
That what you need to do
is okay,
To give you permission,
absolution.
Not now, House.
You have no friends,
no family.
At some point,
You made a mistake.
You lost everything.
And now I'm the closest thing
you got to a friend.
Just shut up.
I don't need you here
To play this game.
I'm sorry
I pushed you away.
It's what I do
when I'm afraid.
Again, german-english
translation may be a little off.
I'm not--I'm not crying
because of you.
I'm crying
because I'm pathetic.
I brought her cello,
In case
she magically wakes up
For the show.
Oh, well, then I take
the apology back.
We're all pathetic.
It's wmakes
everything interesting.
I'm sick of life
being interesting.
* you're nobody *
* till somebody loves you *
* till somebody cares *
Ladies and gentlemen,
The one, the only,
Juan alvarez!
Yo, yo, what's up?
Ward six
is jumping off, y'all!
Give it up for dj richter
on the ones and twos.
Yo, dj richter,
spin that!
Unh! Yo!
* welcome to mayfield
where the day feels long *
* we act strong, but there's
got to be something wrong *
* see, we got hidden talents *
* you don't see
hidden secrets *
* if we could show you those *
Then we wouldn't have
no regrets.
* wanna know myecrets? *
* sit back
and let me explain it *
* my pops split,
mama got sick *
* cliche, ain't it? *
* now I'm a manic hispanic *
* I'm trying to make it work *
*
think I'm lazy *
And my roommate
is a jerk.
Dr. House is
in the House, y'all.
* give it up for dr. House
to the stage, y'all *
* paging dr. House
* are you there, dr. House
it's on *
* bring it on *
* on *
* oh, yo, he's coming
to the stage, y'all *
* unh, unh, it's dr. House
on the remix *
* dr. House
* yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah *
* they say
to take your pills *
don't be a creep *
* but how can I get
better *
If I can't get
no sleep?
* you got think
before you act *
* in order to progress *
* if you don't make
connections *
* then your whole life
is a mess *
Uh, uh, uh.
* yeah, so tell me, doctor,
what I really got to know *
* how do
I get better? *
* just do a talent show *
oh!
* oh, well, I guess
I'm just a mess, yes *
* preach it to me,
brother *
* a life
of restlessness *
* but at least
we have each other *
* oh, we got each other,
oh, we got each other *
* like two brothers
from another mother *
* duck and run for cover,
ward six *
How are you doing?
You hanging in there?
Usually I open
with that.
Thanks for staying.
So, um...
What do you want
to talk about?
Things are actually...
Actually good.
Okay, you're not--You're not
just saying that
Because you
don't want to complain
In front of the guy
who just lost his father?
I'm not that cured.
No, I still
got stuff to do, but...
I'm good.
I'm sorry.
I was trying to prove
a point.
I was trying
to be right.
I ended up putting you
in a dangerous situation,
And I was not equipped
to handle it.
You got hurt,
And it's my fault.
And I'm sorry.
I'm gonna try
those pink ones today. You?
[Mozart's the magic flute
playing]
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Got a surprise.
[Plays bach's cello suite #1,
prelude in g major]
Today we're here
to congratulate...
Annie!
We're proud of her!
We wish her well,
and we hope to...
never see her again!
If you go silent
for over a decade,
You don't just get to slide
right back into society.
She's going
to a rehab facility first...
In Arizona.
Her family's
moving there.
Sorry, House.
I just found out myself.
I want
an overnight pass.
I can help you
with this.
I've earned it.
You have, but--
Isn't extending trust
Part of the whole
"getting me better" thing?
If you insist on a pass,
I'll give it to you.
But I know
where you're going,
And I know you
haven't thought it through.
We need to sit down,
talk about this.
Please give me
the pass.
Hi.
Hello.
Who are you?
I'm--
Ben, go inside,
okay?
You didn't say
anything.
And now
annie's leaving,
And I hear
you're going to arizona.
My husband travels
to phoenix a lot.
His corporate headquarters
are there,
And we've been wanting
to move for years,
But we've been
tethered here.
And now we're not.
I don't want you to go.
I don't want to go.
But I can't break up
my family.
I-I can't leave
my children.
I just don't want it
to change.
I'm sorry that I didn't come
to say good bye.
I thought it ended
kind of perfect.
I have to go.
Not the most exciting use
Of the overnight pass
I've ever seen.
She left.
And...
I'm lost.
I'm gonna write
your letter...
To the medical board,
Recommending that they give
your license back.
You can't just console me
By giving me a lollipop
when I skin my knee.
Well, two things
just happened.
You got hurt,
Which means you connected
to someone else,
Strongly enough
to miss them.
And more important...
You recognized the pain
and came to talk to me,
Instead of hiding from it
in the vicodin bottle.
The fact that you're hurting
and you came here,
The fact that
you're taking your meds
And we're talking
right now...
Come inside
and get some sleep.
Tomorrow you can start saying
your good-Byes.
Today we're here
to congratulate greg.
[Applause]
We're proud of him.
We wish him well,
and we hope...
(All)
to never see him again!
House!
[Cheering]
[Cheers and applause]
Back off.
People already think
we're gay.
aw!
[The frames' seven day mile]
* your will *
* changes every day *
* it's a choice
you got to make *
* I can't help you *
* if I want to *
* down here *
* nothing gets a chance *
*t's a threat
that's real enough *
* we can burn this bridge *
* or stay here *
* it's a breeze *
* everlasting like time *
* making so sure that *
* I can return
just to see it *
What do
you need, alvie?
My meds.
I want to get better.
[The frames'
seven day mile]
* it's a sea *
* ever churning in tides *
* in the sureness of mind *
* and our words just repeat
now forever again *
* well, this might take
a while *
* to figure out *
* so don't you rush it *
* and hold
your head up high *
* right through
the doubt now *
* 'cause it's just
a matter of time *
* you've been running
so fast *
* it's the seven day mile *
* has you torn
in between here *
* and running away *
* running away *
Sync by honeybunny
www.Addic7ed.Com