How's your mom
holding up?
She's doing okay, but we just
lost another nurse.
How many is that now?
Two, and I know what
you're thinking--
she's eating them.
She's just so impossible,
they keep quitting.
So, who's
watching her now?
A bowl full of M&M's with
a few Ambien tossed in.
What up, guys?
Hello. - Hey.  -Hello.
Okay.
Well, now that
everyone's here,
Penny and I have
some big news.
We're engaged!
And I thought me having sex with
Emily was gonna be the big news.
Hey! Hey!
What the hell!
You guys propose all the time.
This never happens.
You're right!
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 7x24 ?
The Status Quo Combustion
Original Air Date on May 15, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Boy, I'm so
hungry today.
I wonder why?
Because you had sex
the other night?
You know what?
That may be it.
By the way,
it isn't like riding a bike.
Like, I fell off a few times.
Hey, buddy.
Hello.
You okay?
I just got called
into President Siebert's office.
The university
won't let me switch my field of
study to inflationary cosmology.
They're forcing me
to continue with string theory.
Why?
He said it's why they hired me,
it's-it's what my grant
was designated for,
and that everybody has to do
things they don't want to do.
He then gave an example
of something he had to do,
even though he didn't want to,
which was look
at my stupid face.
That's a rude thing to say.
Out loud.
It's an outrage.
Honestly, I'm tempted
to leave the university.
You know, if you're really
serious about that,
I hear there are
some exciting opportunities
in home care
for the old and fat.
Whatever you do, just don't
make any rash decisions.
I don't know.
I am really aggravated.
When I'm feeling low,
I have sex with a girl.
But that's just me.
Oh, come on, give her a chance.
No.
Life, it is too short.
I know you've only been
here a day and a half,
but you're like
part of the family!
I don't think the service is
gonna send any more people.
Yeah, maybe it's time we just
release Ma back into the sea.
That's not helpful.
Well, then, we may need
to get used to the idea
that we're gonna be living
here the next few months.
But we have jobs.
We can't baby-sit her
24 hours a day.
Well, what if we use
our vacation time?
I wanted to go to Hawaii,
not Hell.
I don't know
what else we can do.
Howie, I love you,
and as your wife, your
mother is every bit
as much my problem as
she is yours, so...
I want a divorce.
Hello, Leonard.
Hi, Mom.
I have some exciting news.
I'm listening.
Before I tell you,
will you promise to try
and be happy for me and keep any
concerns you have to yourself?
No.
Let me save you
all of your hemming and hawing.
Sheldon already told me
that you and Penny are engaged.
I-I hate that you talk to him
more than you talk to me.
Would you like for you and me
to talk more?
You know what?
It's probably fine.
In any event, while I've had
my misgivings about...
Penny...
...Sheldon spoke
very fondly of her,
and if she is good enough
for him,
then she's good enough for me.
I'm your son.
What about the fact
that she's good enough for me?
Sure.
Thanks, Mom.
Leonard,
would it make you feel better
to hear that your mother
approved of your life choices?
Yes, it would.
Yeah. Well,
you should work on that.
No, Mom, it's the same guy
I've been going out with
for the past two years.
Yeah, the scientist.
Well, it's complicated.
I mean, he works with lasers
and atomic magnets.
No, I did not see it coming.
No, we did not set a date.
Yeah, this is a first
for our family.
All right, tell Dad I love him.
I gotta go.
All right, bye.
Atomic magnets?
Shut up.
Sorry I'm late.
The leaf blower broke, so I had
to hand-dry my mother-in-law.
You want some wine?
Thanks.
Little warning
before you jump into
this marriage business:
You're not just marrying him,
you're marrying his family.
I think Leonard's mom's okay
with me.
It doesn't matter
if she's okay with you.
The question is: Can she go
to the bathroom by herself?
Hit me again.
So, what are the living
arrangements gonna be?
Well, haven't really talked
about it yet, but I figure,
at some point, I'll move in with
him, or he'll move in with me.
Well, with you not working,
that makes financial sense.
You're not working!
How would you like a job
in home health care?
Not a chance.
Please. I'm desperate.
No.
I'll pay you anything you want.
Okay, then, yeah.
No! Keep your money!
I could've ridden a bull
longer than that.
What you working on?
I'm writing an appeal
to the Faculty Senate,
so that I can move on
from string theory.
Oh. How's it going?
You tell me.
"Dear Esteemed Colleagues,
"As you may know,
I have requested
"to change my field of study.
"My decision
to do so
"is, I believe,
in the best interest of science.
"At your convenience, I'd be
happy to explain it to you
in words you'll understand."
It's nice
that you called them "esteemed."
You're right.
I'll take that out.
So, listen, there was something
I was hoping to float past you.
Mm.
Now that Penny and I are engaged,
I thought we might want to talk
about our living arrangements.
Of course.
She's spent many nights here,
and you're worried
about preserving the myth of her
virginity before the wedding.
I'm not.
Good, because not only has
that ship sailed,
if it hit an iceberg,
countless men would perish.
Actually, this is about where
she and I are going to live.
What do you mean?
Well... well, we might want
to live together.
Oh, yeah, well, I've already
given this some thought,
and...
I'm willing
to let Penny live with us
one day a week
for a trial period.
Now, obviously,
not when she's made cranky
by the shedding
of her uterine lining.
That's very sweet.
But we were thinking more of us
maybe living together with...
not you.
I don't understand.
How could we all live together
if I'm not there?
Look, I-I know
this is... this is change,
and that sounds scary, but...
Where are you going to go?
I don't know.
We just started
to think about this.
Maybe I'll move
in with Penny,
or maybe she and
I'll take this place,
and you can move
across the hall.
Move across the hall?!
Did you take a marijuana?!
No, I did not.
Did you get hit
on the head with a coconut?
No.
Well, then,
I'm all out of guesses.
What? Me move across the hall--
Why would you even suggest
such a thing?
Because I love Penny,
and want to give her
the life she deserves.
I see.
You're putting your future
bride's happiness above mine.
Well, yeah.
Wow.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
How dare the university force me
to go back to string theory!
They just don't appreciate you.
Yeah, and on top of that,
Leonard has the audacity
to suggest that now
that he and Penny are engaged,
he may not want
to live with me anymore.
Here, I made you some
Strawberry Quik.
I have real problems here, Amy.
I can't be mollified with a
beverage designed for children.
Mmm! Yummy.
You know, this might
work out for the best.
I mean, you're
always complaining
about what a terrible
roommate Leonard is.
Like how he turns up
the thermostat when
you're not there.
Ugh! It's like walking
into the Amazon.
And not the good Amazon
with one-day shipping.
The awful one
with birds and snakes.
You hate the sound of all
those keys on his key chain.
Four keys!
Who does he think
he is, a warden?
See? Maybe you'll
love living alone.
I don't know. Perhaps.
And if it turns
out you don't...
you and I could
live together.
You and... Oh, sure.
And while we're at it,
why don't we get engaged, too?
Why don't we get a little house,
start a family?
Enjoy our sunset years together?
Do you hear yourself, woman?!
Sheldon, it was just a thought.
No.
Here's a thought.
You're not moving in,
Leonard's not moving out,
everything stays
exactly the way it is.
and you're supposed
to use the powder!
It tastes the same.
No. The syrup tastes better
and I don't like it.
This is so sweet!
You never cook for me.
Well...
you cook for me
all the time and...
Ugh.
If you don't like my cooking,
why haven't you ever
said anything?
It's hard to talk with
so much heavy chewing to do.
Sorry. I'll get better.
I know you'll try.
So, should we talk
about setting a date?
Well, I'd like
to pick one that works
with my brother's schedule.
Okay.
And when would that be?
Uh, 12 to 18 months from now,
depending on good behavior.
Hi, is Sheldon here?
No, I thought he was with you.
He was, but he stormed off
and now he isn't answering his phone.
What happened?
He was really angry
that you suggested he move out.
Oh.
I also mentioned that he and I
could live together
but he was too mad at you
to realize
what a great idea that is.
Well, he's been having
a couple of tough days.
I'm sure he's fine.
He probably just
needs a little alone
time to decompress.
You're probably right.
So, what are you guys doing?
Well, Leonard cooked for me
and now we're just having
a nice dinner, you know,
as a newly engaged couple.
That's nice.
Anyway, as I was saying,
Sheldon probably just needs
a little alone time.
'Cause that's important.
Not just for him, but for...
most anybody, really.
Don't I know it.
What is that, polenta?
Amy, get out.
Right.
No.
Hey, Sheldon.
What happened?
I was cooking
in the back room last night
and the hot plate
caught on fire.
And you couldn't put it out?
I was across the street
at the do-it-yourself car wash,
taking a shower.
So when will you reopen?
Um, I don't know.
I'm waiting to hear back
from the insurance company.
So, tomorrow?
I don't mean to be rude,
Sheldon, but, uh,
my life is kind of
falling apart right now.
Your life?
The university is making
me do string theory
and my girlfriend loves me so
much she wants to live with me.
And now,
the place I need to go when I'm
sad is damp and smells funny.
Well, sorry I let you down.
No.
I do not accept this.
Everything is changing
and I hate it.
It stops now.
I'm helping you
get back on your feet.
I would like to purchase
this comic book, please.
That'll be $2.99.
Really? It's soaking wet.
Fine, a dollar.
Can you break a 20?
No, I only have hundreds.
You know what?
I don't always recognize
sarcasm, but I do right now,
and I don't appreciate it.
I'm sorry for your loss.
But you're not the only one
whose day has been a disaster.
That could have killed me.
I can't catch a break.
I haven't heard
from Sheldon in a while.
You think he's okay?
Oh, I'm sure he's fine.
I'm gonna see where he is.
How?
Oh, I know his password,
so I can track his phone.
You do that?
Not always, but ever since he
wandered off at the swap meet
chasing a balloon,
I get worried.
He can take care of himself.
Look, we went over
stranger danger
and gave him that whistle.
That's weird.
What?
He's at the train station.
So? He loves trains.
It's dark out and he's
alone, I don't like it.
Let's go get him.
Oh, it's sweet how you
look out for him.
You're a good guy.
It's not just that.
My mother would kill me if I let
something happen to him.
Dude, I'm so sorry.
Don't take this
the wrong way,
but did you do this
for the insurance money?
No. God, you sound like
the police, the firemen,
my parents, my therapist
and the insurance company.
We're here for you, man.
Whatever you need, okay?
Uh, actually, I was
wondering if I could
crash at your place
for a few nights.
Sure, of course.
Oh, actually, Emily was
gonna spend the night.
You slept with her? Nice.
Well, I can't take
all the credit.
She let me do it
to her, but...
Uh, but I can always
call her and cancel.
Hang on. I know
a place you can stay
and earn some money
at the same time.
Great.
I just have to warn you,
it'll involve humiliation,
degradation and verbal abuse.
So what's the catch?
Sheldon.
You tracked my phone?
Yeah.
Boy, you chase one balloon
for three miles.
We were worried
about you.
Don't be melodramatic.
I'm just getting on a train
and leaving forever.
Seriously?
You don't even have
a change of clothes
or a toothbrush.
My plan is to stop at malls
and buy what I need.
It's called
living off the land.
Okay, I know you're upset
and there's a lot
of stuff going on,
but it's nothing
we can't work out.
Come on, let's get you home.
No. I've reached
my breaking point.
I need to leave. Now.
And go where?
It doesn't matter.
So a few things
don't go your way
and your best decision is to
ride the rails like a hobo?
I suppose it is.
Except I have a credit card.
And I refuse to carry
my laptop at the end of a stick.
And I'd sooner die
than eat beans out of a can.
Come on, come home with us
and tomorrow I'll-I'll
take you to Legoland.
Legoland is not
the solution to everything.
And it's too much of a scene
since that movie came out.
Then what can I do?
Leonard, I am overwhelmed.
Everything is changing
and it's simply too much.
I need to get away and think.
Oh, c-come on, you know
you're overreacting.
Leonard, hang on.
Just... come here
for a second.
Maybe we need to let him go.
What?! Why?
It might be good for him.
Y-You know he can't
take a trip like this
by himself.
He's a grown man.
No, he looks like a grown man.
You've seen
Freaky Friday, sometimes
little kids end up
in big person bodies.
Leonard, we can't
protect him forever.
I know, but...
He'll be okay.
You taught him
well, Padawan.
Good Lord!
Padawan's the student,
not the teacher.
Seriously, let him go.
Sheldon, if you really
need to do this,
I'm not gonna
stand in your way.
I do.
Okay.
Good luck.
Be safe and call us.
I will.
Bye, buddy.
Sheldon...
Yes?
I'm gonna miss you.
Of course you are.
He just made that easier.
Mm.
Hey!
What are you guys
still doing here?
I got this, go. Go home.
You sure?
Yeah, she's fed,
she took her pills,
she's all tucked in
and watching TV.
So, she's not
too much for you?
Are you kidding?
I love her, she's great.
Stewie, you gonna watch
Wheel of Fortune with me?
Coming, Debbie.
You call her Debbie?
She insisted.
So, hey, guys,
thank you so much.
This job is a dream come true.
Was that a little weird?
Yeah. I don't know why,
but something
about it feels...
unnatural.
Okay, let's go.
Yep.
Okay, Sheldon,
thanks for checking in.
Talk to you tomorrow?
O-Okay, bye.
He's okay?
Actually sounds like
he's doing pretty well.
I really think
this is gonna be for the best.
Me, too.
And he was able
to take a sabbatical from...
How could you let him go?!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org