So, we're about to shoot
this scene in the movie
where the killer ape DNA
is slowly taking over my body.
Okay.
But I realize
they're gluing fur everywhere,
except my cleavage.
So, I asked
the director why
and he says, it's important
to the story that my boobs
be the last things to turn ape.
It's sweet that he thinks
there's a story.
Oh, and there's not even
a bathroom on set.
I have to go to the gas station
across the street.
I mean, I was dressed like
half an ape
and still not even close to the
most disgusting person in there.
Leonard, I could use
your assistance.
Sure. What's up?
Well, now that I've given up
string theory,
I'm struggling to find
my next area of focus.
So, in your
professional opinion,
which of these areas
do you think
is the most promising?
Huh, well, I-I think
there's some
really innovative stuff
going on in dark matter.
That's helpful.
Okay. Of these four areas...
PENNY:
Sheldon!
What did we say about
being a nicer friend?
Thank you.
Leonard, what did we say about
being a gullible weenie?
It is just so frustrating.
PENNY: 'Cause you're
trying too hard.
You need to do something else.
Get your mind off it.
Hey. How about we bring back
Anything Can Happen Thursdays?
Hey, that's good.
Why'd you guys stop doing that?
You made fun of us.
Said it was stupid.
Yeah. Sounds like me.
Come on, Sheldon.
What do you say?
All right.
I officially reinstate
Anything Can Happen Thursday.
Great! What do,
what do you want to do?
(Sheldon and Penny sigh)
I don't know.
What do you want to do?
I'm starting to remember
the problem with
Anything Can Happen Thursdays.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 7x21 ?
The Anything Can Happen Recurrence
Original Air Date on April 24, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hmm...
what could we do that's fun?
What could we do
that's different?
What could we do that's free?
(gasps) Got it!
We order a pizza.
Are you kidding?
That's what you always do.
Think harder.
You're right.
(gasps) Got it!
We order calzones,
cut them open,
eat them like pizza.
All right! All right!
I'll shake the brain bush
one more time,
see what falls out.
(gasps) Got it!
There's a live-action
role-playing group
that meets every Thursday night
in Griffith Park
and reenacts battles from
Lord of the Rings.
Uh, tell me more
about this calzone idea.
You know what?
Why don't we just
ease into this.
Let-Let's go for a walk
and-and-and see if
we find a new restaurant.
Any chance that restaurant
is near Griffith Park?
LEONARD:
No.
All right.
Raj and Howard
are at Howard's mom's,
but should we call the girls
and see if they want to come?
No. Bernadette's
working late.
Amy's sick.
Aw. What's wrong with her?
Well, she talks a lot.
She always wants to hold hands.
That's not what I meant.
Well, if you were
referring to her illness
your question should have been,
"What ails her?"
Oh. Who knows?
Come on,
anything can happen.
We can push him
down the stairs!
Hey. Thanks for
coming to hang out.
No problem.
How's your mom feeling?
Okay, but she'd feel better
if she took her medicine.
You know, when Cinnamon
won't take her medicine,
I hide it in a piece of cheese.
Good idea.
We can wrap the pill in cheese,
feed it to Cinnamon,
and then my mom
can eat Cinnamon.
What do you feel like doing?
I was thinking
we could watch a DVD.
Well, (sighs)
my mom doesn't have
a lot to choose from.
Unless you want to watch
the video of her colonoscopy.
Spoiler alert:
20 minutes in,
they find a prune pit.
Actually, how do you feel about
watching House of 1000 Corpses?
(scoffs)
A straight-up gore-fest?
You hate this stuff.
I do, but for some reason,
Emily loves it
and wants to watch it
with me tomorrow, so...
I thought if
I start with you first,
then I could act cool
about it with her.
That's actually
not a bad plan.
I can sit through
the colonoscopy now,
but that first time
I was like,
"Oh, My God, a prune pit!"
Uh, so... you'd watch it?
Sure.
(sighs)
You're a good friend.
I owe you one.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard!
Help me get out of the tub!
Not that one.
So, we're just randomly
choosing a restaurant
without researching it online?
Yep.
Great.
You know, this is how Anything
Can Happen Thursday turns into
It Won't Stop Coming Up Friday.
Hey, how about
that Asian fusion place?
Fusion and Asians?
I'm trying not to
think about science.
What the hell?
What...?
She's not working late!
And Amy doesn't
look sick.
Why would they
lie to us?
That's a good question.
(knocking)
Amy and Bernadette.
Why did you lie to us?!
Hey. Listen to this:
"Murder... cannibalism
"and satanic rituals
"are just a few
of the thousand plus
horrors that await."
I just helped my mom
out of the tub,
so, I'm one slippery horror
ahead of you.
You're a good son.
I don't know how you do it.
Beach blankets,
my friend.
It's all about
beach blankets.
All right,
let's get this over with.
Ew, it's got
someone's hair on it!
Oh, yeah, you're gonna
do great with this movie.
(blows)
You're not working late.
Why did you lie to me?
And Amy, you told me
you were sick,
but you look just as pale
and tired as always.
I'm sorry.
I just needed a break
from hearing you obsess about
what to do after string theory.
And we kind of just
wanted one night
where we didn't have to hear
about how miserable you are
making this movie.
But none of that means
we don't love you.
I haven't been complaining
that much about the movie.
Have I?
I also love you.
You know what?
Maybe I need a break from
all of you.
Come on, Sheldon.
Where are we going?
We're gonna have Anything Can
Happen Thursday, you're gonna
tell me all about your science
stuff and I'm gonna complain
about my movie, and we're gonna
support each other because
that's what friends do.
Okay.
'Cause if I
had to pick now,
I'd probably go with
dark matter because...
PENNY: Shut up.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(moans)
What's wrong?
I don't understand my food.
Chinese noodles with
Korean barbecue...
in a taco.
It's fusion.
Well, my mother would
lock her car doors
if she had to drive through
this hodgepodge of ethnicity.
Think I've been complaining
too much about the movie?
Not at all.
Thank you.
But to be fair, when you talk,
most of what you say
sounds like, "Wah,
wah, wah, clothes".
Hey, I don't understand
why you're not upset with Amy.
I am. So much so that
I'm gonna bring her here
for dinner on our
next date night.
(heavy metal soundtrack
plays on movie)
Okay.
So, in the last 20 minutes,
we've seen a crazy woman
kissing a fetus in a jar.
We've seen a guy
cut in half and sewn to a fish.
And the brutal dismemberment
of a rotisserie chicken
by my mother.
On the bright side, she didn't
even notice the pill.
Why does Emily like this stuff?
Do you think there's something
psychologically wrong with her?
What difference does it make?
What do you mean?
Oh, come on-- she could
have a freezer full of
ex-boyfriend's body parts and
you'd still go out with her.
I do like that
the ex-boyfriend's
out of the picture.
I feel so bad about
lying to Sheldon.
How am I gonna
make it up to him?
I'd tell you
what I do with Howard,
but I don't think dressing up
like a Catholic schoolgirl
is gonna work with Sheldon.
He'd probably give you homework.
Did you lie to Howard
about tonight?
Of course.
And you don't feel
guilty about it?
Between Penny's gorilla movie
and Howard's gorilla mother,
I had no choice.
Thankfully Penny and I have
a relationship based on honesty.
(snorts)
What?
I don't lie to her.
Oh, we know
you don't lie to her.
Thank you.
Hey, maybe the answer
to your career question is
in one of these.
Penny,
there's only one cookie
with something in the middle
that solves life's problems,
and that's an Oreo.
Or a Nutter Butter,
if you're in a pinch.
Come on, open it.
I bet it says something great.
This is Asian fusion.
For all you know, there's
a tiny Chihuahua in here.
Fine, I'll go.
Hmm.
"People turn to you
for guidance and wisdom."
Yeah, that's a good one.
No, it's not.
How is that not good?
"Turn to you for wisdom"?
Clearly,
that cookie is mocking you.
You'd never hear
that kind of sass
from a Nutter Butter.
Uh, since you're paying for
dinner, I'll let that slide.
Open yours.
Have you ever paid for a meal?
Not with money. Read.
"Your warm and fun-loving nature
delights those around you."
Oh, try again.
(clears her throat)
(loud thudding on TV)
(creaking on TV)
(movie stops)
(clears his throat)
Let me get this straight.
So, he kills this girl's father,
cuts off the guy's face,
and is wearing it as a mask
while he makes out with her.
I'm just gonna say it.
That's not okay.
Why can't I be in a relationship
with a girl
who likes The Sound of Music?
Raj, you are the girl
in the relationship
who likes The Sound of Music.
(ringtone playing)
Hey, Penny. What's up?
No, Bernie's working late.
Really?
Thanks for telling me.
What?
I'm having sex with a Catholic
schoolgirl tonight.
(laughs)
(Penny gasps)
Oh, I think I see
our next stop.
(shrieks happily)
You can't be serious.
If I wanted to waste my time
on nonsense,
I'd follow Leonard
on Instagram.
No, come on-- tonight,
we are trying new things.
(groans)
Oh! That's a lot of incense.
Or someone set a hippie on fire.
Yeah, honey,
I'm still stuck at work.
Really?
Penny said that?
Okay, it's true. I'm sorry.
I'll see you at home.
Yeah, yeah, I'll put it on.
You and I never just
hang out like this.
Why is that?
I know, it's weird, right?
Yeah.
We should do it more often.
Oh, no. I mean, this
is weird right now.
(phone chimes)
Oh.
Ah, it's Penny.
Is she still mad?
Oh, doesn't seem like it.
She got Sheldon to go
to a psychic with her.
A psychic?
He considers them
not just mumbo jumbo,
but extra-jumbo
mumbo jumbo.
Well, Penny can be
pretty persuasive.
She's gotten me to do a lot of
things I wouldn't normally do.
Because she has
sex with you.
Yeah, she does.
Can I confess something?
Once in a while,
I get a little jealous
of how close Penny
and Sheldon are.
Really?
I mean, not in
a romantic way.
It's just, she really has some
sort of connection with him.
Well... Well, they've known
each other a long time,
and Penny grew up around horses,
so she knows how to approach him
without making him skittish.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm glad they're friends.
I just wish he'd be that
comfortable around me already.
Well, it took him a long time to
get comfortable around me, too.
Really? What did you do?
Something terrible in a former life?
I don't know.
I gotta go.
Penny ratted me out.
FYI, she's getting you
a watch for your birthday
with money she took
out of your wallet.
I don't mean to be
rude or discourteous,
but before we begin,
I'd just like to say
there is absolutely
no scientific evidence
to support clairvoyance
of any kind.
Which means--
and again, no insult intended--
but you're a fraud...
...your profession
is a swindle,
and, uh, your livelihood
is dependent
on the gullibility
of stupid people.
Again, no offense.
All right, Sheldon,
just ask your question.
(clears his throat)
Okay, I just did.
What was it?
Oh, for God's sake.
Look, he's a physicist
who's trying to figure out
what his next field
of study should be.
For your information,
I was asking her
about the next Star Trek movie.
Okay, I can answer that one:
I'll be bored.
All right, why don't we begin?
(sighs)
(exhales deeply)
Your spirit guides
are telling me
that there's a woman
in your life
you're having problems with.
That's an easy guess.
I'm clearly an annoying person
and have problems
with both genders.
Yes, you clearly are.
But I'm seeing
a specific woman
that you're in a romantic
relationship with.
Oh, oh, here we go.
Does she have dark hair?
Yes! Yes! Your spirit guides
are on fire!
The majority
of people have dark hair.
Even you, at one time.
Does she work
in a similar field to you?
Ha! The opposite.
She's a neurobiologist, and
I'm a theoretical physicist.
My spirit guides
can go suck an egg.
They're telling me
that you have difficulty
being close with her.
Oh, he does. He so does.
What should he do?
(exhales)
He should give himself
to this relationship.
Once he does, all his
other pursuits will come
into focus.
Sheldon, do you hear that?
I mean, Amy is the key
to your happiness.
Exactly.
Personally and professionally.
Everything will fall into place
once you commit to her.
You know what this is?
Yeah, and I reserve this word
for those rare instances
when it's truly deserved.
This is malarkey!
Wow, you really struck a nerve.
I've never heard him use
the "M" word before.
Here we go:
House of a 1,000 Corpses.
Now, just so you know,
I was a nanny for three years,
so if you get scared,
I can totally change
your diaper.
Actually, I have to
tell you something.
These kind of movies
really aren't my thing,
so, last night,
I watched it
just to see what I was
getting myself into.
Okay.
And I have to be honest--
I thought it was
disturbing and weird,
and it made me wonder
what it says about
someone who enjoys it.
I wonder that, too.
Then, why do you
watch these things?
Can I tell you something
without you judging me?
Sure.
They kind of turn me on.
And play.
(eerie sound effects,
heavy metal soundtrack playing)
MAN (in distorted voice):
Attention...
(knocking)
Hello.
I didn't expect you
this evening.
Well, I was just feeling so bad
about lying to you
the other night,
I wanted to make it up to you.
And how do you propose
to do that?
Unless you have Gravity
on Blu-ray under that skirt,
I don't know
where you're going with this.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org