Item 28:
your pet name for me.
Time's running out on this.
You need to make a decision.
I submitted you
a notarized list.
I'm sorry, but "Gollum" and
"Flakey" are not acceptable.
Well, you don't like
"Princess Corncob""
you don't like "Fester"-- you're
just impossible to please.
We'll come back to that one.
This brings us
to the final item
in our annual State
of the Relationship Summit.
Item 29: Valentine's Day.
Ah, the worst for last. Hmm.
Classic Flakey.
Before you get upset, I believe
I've come up with a way for us
to celebrate the occasion
that we both can enjoy.
People usually start
a meeting with a joke,
but you go ahead--
end with one.
I propose we spend a weekend
at a bed-and-breakfast
in Napa Valley.
I hate every word
in that sentence.
Including "in""
"at," "we" and "a""
Come on, Sheldon. Why not?
For starters,
a bed-and-breakfast forces you
to eat with strangers
at your table.
One step ahead of you--
Bernadette and Wolowitz
are going with us.
Oh, very well.
What are the
sleeping arrangements?
We've only been dating
for three years.
If we were to share a room,
people might talk.
I got you your own room.
What if my room has
a claw-foot bathtub?
It doesn't. I know it makes you feel like
you're bathing inside a monster.
Look, I appreciate the effort,
but I'm still
unclear how this trip
is supposed to be
enjoyable for me.
We're going to have
Valentine's Day dinner
on a fully functioning
vintage train.
Vintage?
Be specific.
An Alcoa FA-4 diesel locomotive
leading a train
of meticulously restored
1915 Pullman
first-class coaches.
Wow.
I'm feeling the
urge to hug you.
And one... and two...
All right, Gollum,
we're good.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 7x15 ?
The Locomotive Manipulation
Original Air Date on February 6, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Are you sure you guys don't want
to come with us to Napa?
You could probably
still get a room.
No, I think we're just gonna
have a quiet weekend at home.
Plus, I'm not sure
it's a great idea
to take Penny to where wine
comes from.
What? It's a joke.
Oh, come on.
We bust on each other.
I wear dorky glasses,
you might have a problem--
it's all for laughs.
That would really piss me off if
I didn't have a buzz going on.
Howard, which pocket watch
will you be wearing
for dinner on the train?
I'm sorry, what?
Oh, I'm afraid if we wear
the same pocket watch,
it will be embarrassing.
I don't own a pocket watch.
Oh, my.
Well, then my apologies for
bringing up this sore spot.
Since you two are gonna be
around for Valentine's,
would you mind
watching Cinnamon?
You have Valentine's plans?!
Which came out sounding
way more surprised than I meant.
L-Let me try that again.
You have Val...
See? I can't do it.
I don't have plans
which is why I booked time
on the big telescope that night.
Well, an evening
looking at the stars--
that's still
kind of romantic.
Except I'll be alone.
I'm trying to put
lipstick on a pig here.
Work with me.
We'd be happy to watch Cinnamon.
Yeah.
Thank you. Oh, and I'd like
for at least one of us
to see some action, so if
you guys happen to have sex,
it's cool if she stays
in the room.
Hey, same goes for the two
of you with Amy.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
What do you think,
Sheldon?
It's magnificent.
This is going to be
the best Valentine's Day ever.
I'm so glad you like it.
I'm prepared to say
I love it, as soon as I confirm
there are no hobos aboard.
Okay.
Raj, I got it.
Bye.
That was your daddy.
He wanted me to say that he
misses... Why am I doing this?
Happy Valentine's Day!
Ooh, flowers and chocolates?
Somebody's trying to get
me out of my panties.
Don't be surprised if you find
five chocolates missing
and three gross coconut ones
with a bite taken out.
It came that way
when I bought it.
Got you a little
something, too.
Aw.
Jewelry.
Oh, my God.
Lakers tickets?!
It gets better. Instead of me,
you can take someone
who will actually enjoy it.
Aw!
You are the best boyfriend ever.
Thank you. Seriously,
please don't make me go.
Should we take this
little party to the bedroom?
Mm, don't have to-- we have
the whole place to ourselves.
Oh, that's true.
In fact, if you want,
we can do it right here
on Sheldon's spot.
That is the least sexy thing
anyone's ever said to me.
To the bedroom!
Yeah!
And for the entr?e, tonight's
special is a seafood risotto.
Do you have any questions?
Uh, I do.
Uh, does this train car have the
original link-and-pin coupler
or the Miller Hook and Platform?
I'm sorry, I meant questions
about the food.
Oh, of course. Um...
he seafood risotto
being served on a train car
with the original
link-and-pin coupler
or the Miller Hook and Platform?
I-I think we're
gonna need a minute.
Fun fact: it's neither.
They actually
use the AAR type E coupler.
If you listen carefully when
the locomotive disconnects,
you'll hear the characteristic
click-pshht-thunk
of the knuckle.
Get out of town.
Fun fact: I'm gonna
jump off this train.
Hey, Cinnamon,
guess who just did it
human style.
Oh, my God!
It's a little late,
but I'll take it.
No, Cinnamon ate the chocolates.
That's really bad for dogs.
Oh, crap. What are we gonna do?
We gotta get her
to a vet right now.
I don't have a vet.
I have a podiatrist,
an optometrist, an allergist,
a dermatologist, a urologist.
You'd think I'd have a vet.
Okay. There's one not far
from here. Come on. Let's go.
Okay.
Koothrappali was right.
We should have
let her watch.
Do another one,
do another one!
Okay.
Here's my impression
of the Amtrak
Acela barreling
down the Eastern Corridor.
It's like there's a train
in your mouth.
Oh, yeah.
I've got one.
Um, the Amtrak Wolverine
coming into Chicago.
I've been on that train.
And I just was again.
Hey, see if you guys
can guess this one.
Bang! Splat! Thud.
How many trains
have you been on?
Tons. A box fell on my head
at UPS six years ago.
Now I just collect disability
and ride trains.
Wow. Your life's amazing.
Not always.
A box fell on my head
at UPS six years ago.
Now I just collect disability
and ride trains.
Why do I even try?
I'm gonna fix
this right now.
Okay. Just make it look
like an accident.
Excuse me.
You are
at Valentine's dinner
with your girlfriend.
Now get back over there
and be with her.
You're right.
That was
insensitive of me.
I have to go back
to my table now.
You should join us.
All right.
Great.
Now there's two of 'em.
How much chocolate
did she eat?
A whole box.
Well, to be fair,
you ate a lot of it
before you gave it to me.
So the point is I may
have saved her life.
I'm sorry,
is this a joke to you?
No.
Maybe to her.
How big
a box of chocolate was it?
Uh, something like
this. I don't know.
It came free with
a full tank of gas.
Really? Do you know how much
those Lakers tickets were?
Do you know
how much gas is?
Hey!
Sorry.
Oh, my God, Cinnamon,
are you okay?!
I can't believe you two!
You do whatever it takes
to save her life.
If she needs new organs,
I'll buy any dog necessary
and scrap them for parts!
You're the owner?
Owner, father, soul mate,
and if anything happens to her,
your worst nightmare!
Well, she's not
throwing up,
which is a good sign.
So, I'm gonna take her in back,
put her on fluids
and give her something
to absorb the toxins.
Okay?
Okay. Okay, thank you.
Oh, if she's scared,
you can sing to her.
She likes Katy Perry.
Oh, but don't
do "Firework""
That gets her all riled up.
Got it.
Should have been a dentist.
Okay, what was
the best four-ten-four
U.S. locomotive
ever built?
Trick question.
There never was one.
Or was there?
What?!
In 1944, the Pacific Railroad
built number 6131,
which rearranged
the drivers and cylinders,
solving the problem
of the Q-1,
creating a duplex-drive
four-four-six-four.
In what world is
a four-four-six-four
a four-ten-four?
A world I don't
want to live in!
Seriously, I no longer want
to live in this world.
Hold on to your
conductor's hat.
You crank the second
and third axles,
creating a pair
of internal connecting rods,
and boom--
four-ten-four.
If you think
about it, the Q-2
was like the four-ten-four
America never made.
I may never stop
thinking about it.
Amy, what are the odds
we run into this guy?
Better than you think.
You know, if you ask nicely,
they'll let you visit
the engine room.
I never want
this day to end.
It's feeling like
it never will.
Come on.
Hey, did I tell you
what happened to me at UPS?
As if Valentine’s Day wasn't bad
enough, you try to kill my dog?!
And with cheap chocolate,
no less?
It wasn't cheap.
It was free.
We're really sorry.
It was an accident.
Yeah, we weren't even out
of the room that long.
Oh, no, come on.
It was a while.
Oh, is Cinnamon gonna be okay?
She's responding well.
We just want to keep her
a little longer for observation.
All right. Uh, would-would
it be okay for me to see her?
We're usually
in bed by now,
and I want her to
know that I'm here.
Yes, we sleep together,
and sometimes we spoon.
It's okay.
I sleep with my dog, too.
We're not supposed
to let people in back,
but I think
I can make an exception.
Thank you.
Come on.
By the way, I sang her Katy Perry.
Oh, yeah?
And I don't care
what that obnoxious
parrot back there says.
I crushed it.
I think there's something going
on between the two of them.
Maybe, but you also think
nine minutes isn't a while,
so what do you know?
You okay?
Why? Because my boyfriend's off
playing choo-choo
with some weirdo?
Well, to be fair,
they're both weirdos.
I don't know what made me think
tonight would be any different.
Well, just the fact that you got
him up here still says a lot.
To be honest, I bet Howie 200
bucks it wasn't gonna happen.
I'm going to the Lego store
to get a big-ass R2-D2.
See? It's not
just Sheldon.
They're all idiots.
She's right.
So, your boyfriend's
a fixer-upper.
Most of them are.
I mean, look at this guy.
You think he
came like this?
When I met him,
he was a hot, goofy mess.
Now, he's been to space.
That's all me.
I had a little
to do with it.
Oh, sure you did.
Who's Mama's
big space man?
I am.
They've been in there,
like, half an hour.
Yeah, for future reference,
that's a while.
How long should we stay?
I don't know.
I'm kind of hungry.
I saw a Thai place next door.
Oh. Okay.
Oh. Oh. Hey!
How's she doing?
How is everything?
Yeah.
She's gonna be okay; they're
gonna let me take her home.
Oh, good.
So I want you
to keep a close eye on her
for the next 24 hours.
Here are a few warning signs
to look out for,
and if you see any of them,
don't hesitate to call.
Oh.
Thank you for taking such
good care of my little girl.
My pleasure.
Have a nice night.
Yes, thank you
for all your help.
Yeah. I'm sorry if
you didn't think
we were taking
it seriously.
We love animals.
Oh, do you guys own any pets?
No.
Good.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Sorry.
You guys missed
a pretty great time.
The conductor and I have
the same pocket watch.
It was crazy.
Dare I say "loco"?
Oh, and, Amy, guess what?
The conductor said
as soon as he gets off work,
he can come back
to the bed and breakfast
and play his banjo for us.
Okay. I need to speak to
my boyfriend in private,
like, right now.
There's a car
with a glass roof.
Want to go look
at the stars?
Oh, that sounds
so romantic.
Oh, give it a rest!
Let's go.
Why are you still here?
Excuse me.
I think you're being
a little rude.
I'm being rude?
You've been rude to me
this entire evening.
How is that possible?
I've hardly spoken to you
since we got on the train.
I'm detecting a little friction
between you two,
and I don't want
to be a third rail.
Get it?
I get it.
Leave!
What is your problem?
It's Valentine's Day.
We're supposed
to be having a romantic weekend.
Oh, really? Because
I remember you saying
that this trip was going to be
something we could both enjoy.
Did you mean that, or were you
just trying to trick me?
Fine, it's true.
I deserve romance,
and I didn't know
how else to make it happen.
Well, if you want romance,
then let's have romance!
Oh, look, there's wine. Mmm.
Grape juice that burns.
Uh, now let's gaze
into each other's eyes, hmm?
You blinked. I win.
Sheldon...
Let's see. What's next?
Oh, kissing's romantic.
That was nice.
Good.
Um...
the conductor said if I come
back to the engine room,
he'd show me how to bring
the train through a crossing.
Okay, have fun.
Do you want to come with me?
Really? I do.
Hey, guys, wait up!
There you go.
All cozy wozy.
Here, let's see what the doctor
says to keep an eye out for.
Hmm. "Rajesh, I was dreading
Valentine's Day.
Thank you for spending it
with me. Yvette."
Cinnamon, she-she gave me
her phone number.
If I knew it was that easy,
I would have considered
poisoning you months ago.
Oh, what should I say?
Oh, I know. I'll point out
her name's Yvette,
and that she's a vet.
That's hysterical.
She'll love it.
Hello.
Oh, hey.
You're back. How was your trip?
It was wonderful!
Great. What did you do?
I made a new friend
who likes trains
as much as I do,
uh, I kissed Amy on the lips,
and, uh,
the conductor played his banjo
for me.
Good night.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
I'm gonna need
more details.
Oh, well, my new friend's name
was Eric.
Um, Amy lips tasted like
the brownie we had for dessert.
Oh...
the banjo-playing conductor
was missing a finger,
but he made up for it
with his can-do attitude.
No, hang on.
Hang on.
Are all those things
equal to you?
Hmm.
It never occurred to me
to pick a favorite.
Well, give it a go.
I can't answer that without
collecting additional data.
Additional data. You dog!
I'm not sure how
listening to other
nine-fingered banjo players
makes me dog, but all right.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org