Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This is nice,
that we all get to eat together.
Mm-hmm.
Absolutely.
Hmm.
Can we maybe
put the phones down
and have an actual
human conversation?
We can,
but thanks
to Steve Jobs,
we don't have to.
Guys, guys,
you're never gonna believe this.
What happened?
I just got a part on a TV show!
What? That's great!
Congratulations!
Guys!
Oh, yeah!
Yay, Penny!
What's the show?
Um, NC...II...
or, you know, NCSTD...
I don't know,
it's-it's the one
with the letters and
I'm gonna be on it!
That's amazing.
Yeah.
What's your part?
Um, I play a customer
in a diner
and I flirt
with Mark Harmon.
Ooh, Mark Harmon,
he's a dreamboat.
So i-it's just flirting?
Well, yeah. Why?
Uh, no reason.
I just think it's sexier
when things are left
to the imagination.
He's wrong.
? Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ?
? Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ?
? The Earth began to cool
? The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ?
? We built the Wall
? We built the pyramids ?
? Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ?
? That all started
with a big bang ?
? Bang! ?
? The Big Bang Theory 7x12 ?
The Hesitation Ramification
Original Air Date on January 2, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
So I-I read a study that
says a man with a dog
is three times more likely
to get a woman's phone number.
Is it true even when
the man lets his dog
lick peanut butter
off his tongue?
I don't see why not.
If you're really
desperate to meet women
and like having food
eaten out of your mouth,
I could set you up
with my mom.
Why is that funny?
That's just unhygienic.
It's a joke.
I don't think so.
I believe that a joke
is a brief oral narrative
with a climactic
humorous twist.
For example, uh,
Wolowitz's mother is so fat
that she decided
to go on a diet...
or exercise, or both.
See?
The twist is that people
don't usually change.
Well, they don't.
Hey, guys, don't forget,
my episode's on TV
tomorrow night.
We'll be there.
Can we bring anything?
Oh, that's so sweet of you,
but I was gonna steal food
from here.
You know... my treat.
Wait, if Howard's
mother is coming,
then you should
also steal marbles.
Because she's obese,
and hippos are obese,
and in the popular board game
"Hungry Hungry Hippos,"
they eat marbles.
Maybe I need to dumb
these down for you.
Leonard, do you
think I'm funny?
No.
Do you?
I think I'm hysterical.
I take it back.
That was funny.
The philosopher
Henri Bergson
says it's funny
when a human being
behaves like an object.
I bet that bit killed
at The Chuckle Hut.
Oh, he didn't perform
stand-up comedy,
he was a philosopher.
You know, I think
we're zeroing in on your problem.
Perhaps I'll
spend some time
developing a unified
theory of comedy,
which will allow me
to elicit laughter
from anyone
at any time.
Unless they're German,
'cause that's a tough crowd.
Are you set on people
laughing with you?
'Cause if you're
cool with at you...
I don't get it.
Raj, when you said you
were gonna bring a date
to watch Penny's
thing tonight,
I didn't think
you meant Stuart.
Really?
I never for a second
thought it'd be
anything else.
I almost met someone
last night, but I blew it.
I was walking Cinnamon
and this girl
introduced herself,
but she was so cute I panicked
and said,
"Wouldn't it be easier
if instead of talking we could
just sniff each other's butts?"
Well, Stuart's cute
in his own way.
When I was a baby,
my mother called me
her little possum.
Are possums cute?
Not at all.
If you're so intimidated
by talking to
attractive girls,
maybe you should practice
by talking to
regular people.
You mean like fatties and uggos?
Or maybe just stop talking.
I'm serious.
Go to the mall,
talk to anybody,
practice-- that way,
when you eventually do
talk to a cute girl,
it won't be so scary.
Or just keep dating the possum.
Parsa doesn't have
those kind of resources.
No, and that's why he had
Erin Pace rewire it...
I'm so proud of you.
We haven't even
gotten to my scene yet.
I know,
but you're going to be a TV star
and you haven't left me yet.
That takes guts.
I don't know about you,
but I'm very
uncomfortable with all this.
Why?
I've never seen this show before
and now I'm starting
with episode 246?
It's unnatural.
Just think of the first 245
as the prequel.
All right.
Okay, shh.
Guys, guys, this is it.
I guess it's you and me, kid.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make peace.
We're good.
Good.
Really? Because...
Are you kidding me?
What's wrong?
Well... the diner scene.
Where's my diner scene?
Well, don't ask me.
Until I see the prequel,
I'm lost.
No, there was supposed
to be a big scene
with me and Mark Harmon,
but i-it's... gone.
What happened?
They must've cut it.
Oh, Penny...
I'm... I'm sorry.
That stinks.
I'm sure you were great.
This doesn't make any sense.
I mean, I...
I thought I did a...
a really good job, I...
Excuse me.
I've been studying how
to make people laugh.
They say that comedy
is tragedy plus time.
Let's tickle some ribs.
No, Dad,
I don't think they
cut me out of the show
because I was too pretty.
No, I don't need
you to come out
and kick Mark Harmon's ass.
Daddy, I gotta go.
I love you. Bye.
How you doing?
Ugh, this is
such a disaster.
My parents had all
my relatives over.
They got one of those
six-foot sandwiches,
and got my brother
a day pass out of rehab and...
...now he's missing
and the sandwich
is missing, and...
They're probably
in Mexico by now.
So humiliating.
You still got the part.
That's a huge
accomplishment.
Yeah, but this was
supposed to be my break, okay?
People were gonna
see me in this show
and it was gonna
lead to bigger things.
More auditions,
more parts...
Now none of that's
gonna happen.
Honey, you only had,
like, three lines.
That wasn't gonna
happen anyway.
Unbelievable.
Oh...
Come on... no,
that's not what I meant.
Then what did you mean?
I don't...
Look, you know, words don't
always have to mean things.
I think you meant
that you don't believe in me.
Nope.
Uh-uh... I might not
know what I-I meant,
but I know that
I didn't mean that.
Not this guy.
Oh, no way.
I want you, right now,
to give me your 100% honest opinion.
Right.
Do you think I have
what it takes
to really make it
as an actress?
Yes.
So you think I'll be on TV
and in movies
and win awards.
Honestly?
Yes, honestly.
I don't.
How could you say that?
I don't know...
I got all confused when
you said "honestly".
Oh!
Look, do I think
that you are talented
and that you are beautiful?
Of course I do.
But isn't Los Angeles
full of actresses
who are just as talented,
just as beautiful?
All right, look...
we'll come back to that.
No, please.
Don't stop, go on.
Tell me how I'm
gonna be a waitress
for the rest of my life.
That is not what I said.
Look, I think
you're really good.
I truly do.
But this is an
incredibly hard thing
that you're shooting for.
I mean, the odds
of anyone becoming
a successful actor
are like a million to one.
Wow, thank you.
Should've let Sheldon come.
This is interesting.
Apparently,
a key component
in some forms of humor
is the element of surprise.
Well, that makes sense.
The prefrontal cortex
is responsible for
planning and anticipation,
and patients with
brain lesions on their...
Brain lesions!
Sheldon, you scared me.
That wasn't funny.
Or maybe you have a stick
up your prefrontal cortex.
Okay, the notion that
you can read a few
books and come up with
a definitive theory
of comedy is absurd.
I mean, humor is
a complex neurological...
Okay, that's pretty good.
Excellent.
How about her?
No!
No pretty girls!
The point is to talk
to regular people
and work our way up
to pretty girls.
Fine.
How about that old lady
with the walker?
That depends.
On any level,
do you think she's hot?
We'll find somebody else.
Kumquat?
I guess.
Ointment?
Sure.
Now, would you say
ointment
is more, equal to,
or less funny than kumquat?
I don't think I want
to go out with you anymore.
Will you please
stop joking around?
I'm trying to figure this out.
Sheldon, how many words
are you gonna go through?
All of them.
You didn't get your part cut.
All right, baby,
here's the deal.
And you didn't get
your part cut.
Yep, bunch of old guys
rocking out in a band,
all with erectile dysfunction,
you didn't get
your part cut!
Hey.
Can we talk?
We can, but the part
of Penny might get cut.
That was really
crappy of me.
What you're trying
to do is hard,
but people do make it,
and I really do believe
you could be one of them.
Thank you.
And...
to show you how much
I believe in you,
I kind of got you an audition.
Are you serious? For what?
The new Star Wars movie.
What?!
How did you manage that?!
There's this thing online,
you put yourself on tape
and just send it in--
anyone can do it.
Come on Leonard,
this is just a PR stunt.
So? Even if it is,
you have a huge advantage
because you're
an actual actress.
Most of the people doing this
are just weirdoes and nerds.
Wolowitz sent his in
two days ago.
Really, let it go.
Look, maybe it
is a long shot,
but sometimes
long shots happen.
Luke Skywalker was
only given one chance
to destroy the Death Star.
He had to get a torpedo
into an exhaust port
that was only
two meters wide,
but with the help
of The Force, he...
Wow, I can feel you
hating me right now.
How about that lady
in the sweat suit, speed-walking?
Yeah, she seems friendly
and easy to...
Never mind, she's gone.
Yeah, maybe talking
to people is too hard.
We could go over to
that department store,
practice on
the mannequins.
I don't know.
They're dressed
very stylishly.
They're probably stuck-up.
This is ridiculous.
The next person
that walks by,
no matter who it is,
they're the one.
We're gonna die here.
Hello.
Hey.
Where's Sheldon?
He's home trying to use science
to determine the basis of humor.
That's interesting.
It's exhausting.
Do you have
any idea how hard it is
to laugh at a knock-knock
joke that starts with,
"Knock-knock-knock, Amy,
knock-knock-knock, Amy,
knock-knock-knock, Amy"?
If you want him to stop,
sometimes the easiest thing
to do is just fake a laugh.
Fake a laugh?
Do you ever do that with me?
No, of course not.
Well, I'd be able
to tell anyway.
I don't think you would.
Please, I've made
plenty of girls laugh,
sometimes just by
asking them out.
Yeah? Well, I fake my orgasms.
Yes, how much for a hundred
long-stemmed red roses?
Really?
How much for three?
Hey.
Yeah, I'll call you back.
Look, I know you were
just trying to help
with your Star Wars thing.
I didn't mean
to call it idiotic.
Well, I don't think
you called it idiotic.
Oh.
Sorry, I meant to.
Anyway, um, I was just upset
with myself.
I wasn't mad at you.
I just feel like everything
is falling apart.
Come on. It's okay.
No, it's not okay!
Look at me, okay?!
I took a temp job
as a waitress forever ago,
and I'm still doing it.
I can't quit,
because guess what?
I can't do anything else.
And I finally get my big break,
and it goes away!
I'm such a mess.
No, you're not.
Really?!
'Cause this morning
at Starbucks,
a pair of old underwear
fell out of my pant leg!
And it wasn't the only
one in there.
Okay, listen to me,
this is just a minor setback.
No, it's not, okay?!
I've been out here
for, like, ten years!
I've nothing to show for it!
Well, you have me.
You're right.
I do have you.
Mm...
Let's get married.
What?
Ooh!
Leonard Hofstadter...
will you marry me?
Um...
Did you seriously
just say, "Um"?!
Look, you know I love you,
but-but you're-you're drunk
and sad and feeling lost...
Okay, so-so you don't
want to marry me?!
That is not what I said.
No, forget it! I take it back!
Offer's off the table!
Who's in the mood to laugh?!
Really not a good time.
But I used science
to construct the perfect joke.
I'm gonna go.
Penny, don't.
No, no, I just need
to be alone.
So, a sandwich, a rabbi
and yo mama walk into a bar.
Where are you going?
To my room.
Should I follow you?
No.
Leonard, wait.
What?
I forgot to tell you
the sandwich is promiscuous.
How about those guys
on that bench over there?
They look pathetic.
I bet we could
talk to them.
That's a mirror.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, fellas,
mall's closing.
Sorry.
Yeah. Good night.
Uh, excuse me.
Yeah?
Uh, do-do you like being
a mall security guard?
It's all right.
Okay, nice talking to you.
Smooth...!
Can't sleep?
No.
Would you like
to talk about it?
Penny proposed,
and I didn't say yes.
Why not?
That's a good question.
Does that mean the
relationship is over?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask her?
Because I'm afraid
to know the answer.
Well...
I'm sorry.
That's it?
You're not gonna make
some dumb joke
or some inappropriate comment?
No.
You're my friend, and...
I'm sorry.
Did you just put a "kick me"
sign on my back?
No.
That wouldn't be
funny at all.
Star Wars audition, take one...
starring Howard Joel Wolowitz,
real-life astronaut.
Vader is here...
now... on this moon.
I felt his presence.
He's come for me.
He can feel when I'm near...
How many times
do I have to tell you
to replace the toilet paper
when it's empty?!
I'm in the middle of something!
So am I!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org