Dean, what was that all about
back there?
All those extra shots after
the shifter was already dead.
Sure it wasn't something to do
with the Mark?
No, no. None of that.
Look, man, I gotta be honest.
I was a little anxious. I wanted
to make sure it was done right.
Why am I even explaining this?
Dean, I...
How did you do it?
Magic.
We're here for the witch.
Rowena.
Always nice to be recognized.
Impetus bestiarum.
We got her.
Time for
the coup de grace.
Something the matter
with you?
Mother?
My name is Jimmy Novak.
I'm from Pontiac, Illinois.
I have a family --
Amelia and Claire.
Bless this food and ourselves
to thy loving service.
Amen.
Aah!
Hi, Daddy.
You're possessing
some poor bastard?
Castiel, you promised me
my family would be okay!
What of the humans
whose lives we sacrifice?
Maybe it's time
to put them first.
Get your hands off me, perv.
I'll sue your ass.
What was it this time?
Shoplifting. The guy
ain't lookin' to press charges,
but I figured
you'd want her back.
That's 48 hours in isolation.
Ohh. Scary.
Ugh!
Who is this girl?
One of our frequent flyers.
Claire Novak.
Novak, you got a visitor.
Really?
Your father's here
to see you.
Daddy?
I am not your father.
Hello, Claire.
It's been a long time.
? Supernatural 10x09 ?
The Things We Left Behind
Original Air Date on December 9, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Can we have a moment?
I'll be outside.
I'm not your father.
Right.
"I'm not your father."
Those were the first words
you ever said to me. Remember?
I remember everything.
So do I, Castiel.
My dad...
Is he still in there?
No.
The human soul,
it can only occupy a body
while it retains a certain...
structural integrity.
And this vessel, it was --
it was ripped apart
on a subatomic level
by an archangel.
Well, then how are you...
I was reassembled.
Your father is in Heaven.
Well, yay for him.
Anyway, good talk. You can get
the hell out of my life now.
Claire --
What?
Huh?
You took everything from me.
What do you want now?
Nothing. I just...
I came here to help you.
Why?
Because I've hurt you so much.
Where's your mother?
About a few months after you,
she took off.
Dropped me off at my grandma's
and went to go "find herself."
I guess she's still looking.
And you're in a...
Child prison?
It's a group home.
After my gran died,
I didn't have anyone, so...
bounced around to
different foster families,
places like this.
Living the dream, you know?
Well, Claire,
I'm -- I'm sorry, and...
I can never replace
what I took from you,
but if there is anything
you need, anything at all...
Get me out of here.
How?
Do you own a tie?
Stop it.
There.
Now you look like a dad.
No, no.
So...
Mr. Novak,
I understand you want custody
of your daughter.
Yes, that's, uh, that's...
That's right.
Why?
Excuse me?
It's a simple question.
You vanish for years.
No contact,
not even a Christmas card.
Why come back now?
I, um -- I didn't, uh...
I was traveling.
For work.
Work. Yes.
Long trip.
And what is it
that you do exactly?
I...um...
I fight certain deadly threats
to humanity.
He's an exterminator.
I'm an exterminator.
Uh-huh.
You know, I think
I might have bedbugs.
Any tips?
Of course.
You should sleep tight
and not let them bite.
I'll try that.
It doesn't matter.
He's my dad,
and he wants to sign me out,
so I'm out.
That's the law, Sandy.
Claire, wait for me
in the hallway.
- You can't --
- Now.
I don't do well with liars,
Mr. Novak.
But --
save it.
I'm denying
your application for custody.
I'm not trying to be
the bad guy here. I'm not.
But until Claire turns 18,
she is my responsibility.
I know you're trying to do
what you think is best.
I know you wanna
be her friend.
I do.
And that's our problem,
Mr. Novak.
Claire's troubled.
The last few years
have not been easy for her.
And she doesn't need a friend.
She needs a father.
Easy now.
Aah!
Oh!
What are you laughing at?
Oh.
Hey. Hang on.
It's a -- this is a classic.
I'm glad
you're feeling better.
Oh, yeah, better than ever.
Oh. Hello, beautiful.
Oh, yeah.
Mmm!
You want some alone time
with that thing?
Mnh.
No, no. Wait.
You sure?
Yeah. Yeah. Watch this.
No. don't be...
Hey, stop!
Stop!
It's you.
What's going on?
I'm getting you out of here.
Is he...
He's sleeping.
Sit.
Stay.
Good dog.
Wait!
My son...
I need to talk to him.
It's been weeks.
Tell him I'm sorry.
Tell him --
Ugh!
Yeah?
Nothing.
It's just...you could eat
a vegetable.
Ketchup's a vegetable.
You've changed.
The Castiel I met?
He was crappy.
Like, super stuck-up
and a dick
and you just wanted to punch him
in his stupid angel face.
I don't think I was that bad.
You totally were.
And now you're just...
I don't know. Nicer.
And kind of a doof.
No offense.
Yes. Well, um...
Before, I was
very self-assured.
I was convinced I was on
this righteous path.
Now I realize that there is
no righteous path,
just people trying to do
their best
in a world where it's
far too easy to do your worst.
Wow. Deep.
Yeah. For a doof.
Thank you.
So...where do we go next?
Look...
I appreciate the meal.
And, you know, the felony.
But you don't need
to babysit me.
I can take care of myself.
What do you mean?
I mean you felt guilty,
so you busted me out.
So thanks, but we're good.
Even Steven.
No, we, um,
we committed a crime.
And you might need me again,
so I think we should
stick together.
Okay.
You wanna get some stuff
for the road, huh?
I have to pee.
Uh, oh, okay.
Oh! My bad.
I'm sorry.
It's for a teenage girl.
She's urinating.
My wallet's gone.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, can you help? Damn.
Help! Please?
Claire.
Thanks.
Go, go, go, go!
Wait! Hey! Claire!
This is why you called us?
This is your emergency?
Yes.
No, Cass.
An emergency is a dead body,
okay?
Or -- or --
or a wigged out angel
or the apocalypse, take 3.
Some chick bolting on you
is not an emergency. That's...
That's every Friday night
for Sam.
Dude.
Well...
This isn't just some chick.
I'm responsible for her.
Since when? You met her once --
how many years ago?
Look, Cass, even if we do
find Claire, then what?
She rolled you
and then she ran, okay?
It's pretty clear that
she doesn't wanna play house.
I understand,
but I need to know
that Claire is safe,
and I need your help.
All right. Uh...
Why don't we go ask around
at the group home?
Uh, you know what?
We're gonna stick here
in case she circles back.
You go ahead.
Thank you.
Is ketchup a vegetable?
Hell, yes.
All right, so spill.
What's with the family reunion?
I don't know.
Just been...
thinking about people.
No problem.
I've helped some,
but I've -- I've hurt some.
So you're having
a midlife crisis.
Well, I'm extremely old.
I think I'm entitled.
Cass, listen to me.
There's some stuff
you just gotta let go.
Okay?
The people you let down,
the ones you can't save...
You gotta forget about 'em,
for your own good.
Is that what you do?
That's the opposite
of what I do. But...
I ain't exactly a role model.
That's not true.
Yeah.
How are you, Dean?
Fine.
I'm great.
No, you're not.
Yeah, well,
I've lost the black eyes,
so that's a plus.
But I still have this.
The Mark of Cain
still affecting you?
Dean?
Cass, I need you to
promise me something.
Of course.
If I do go dark side,
you gotta take me out.
What do you mean?
Knife me, smite me,
throw me into the freakin' sun.
Whatever.
And don't let Sam get
in the way, because he'll try.
I can't go
down that road again, man.
I can't be that thing again.
That won't work.
I didn't ask you,
Braveheart.
Freedom!
So...what are we in for?
Small talk, darling.
Just passing the time.
I'm here because
I shouldn't be here.
Is that a riddle?
Crowley only allows certain
demons to come earth-side.
I wasn't on the list, so I had
to get myself smuggled up.
And what did that cost?
A favor.
Big?
Bloody.
Now...I figure the king
lets me stew for a while,
then he starts asking how
I Houdini'd Hell.
And he ain't gonna ask nice.
Hmm.
What about you?
What's your sin?
I was a horrible mother.
She was a horrible mother.
Did I tell you
the time that
she almost traded me
for three pigs?
Three!
I was an attractive child.
I could juggle.
I was worth five pigs
at least.
My ma used to burn me
with cigarettes.
Nobody cares, Gerald.
Don't get me started
about the name.
"Fergus."
It sounds like
a venereal disease,
and not the fun kind.
Look, boss,
if you hate this Betty
so much,
why not end her?
I have my reasons.
Oh, I killed my old lady.
Because of the cigarettes.
I have no problem
doing yours.
Claire's a good kid, Detective.
She's smart.
And underneath it all,
she has a big heart.
You know, there used to be
a boy here.
Dustin Tate.
He was older, but Claire
really took him under her wing.
Is he around?
He works at the Wiener Hut.
We tried to place Claire,
but she always ran away.
Sometimes for a couple of days,
one time for six months.
Wow.
Where did she hide out?
Wish I knew.
Hey, Claire.
Hey.
Is, uh, Randy here?
Oh. Look who's back.
It's been...What? Three days?
I know. I got busted.
But I come bearing gifts.
There's, like,
200 bucks in there.
James Novak.
Any relation?
No. He's just a guy.
Mm.
Well...
I appreciate the elbow grease,
but, uh, we're still short.
How much?
Too much.
When's Salinger coming
to collect?
Tonight.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have borrowed
so much money.
But, uh,
the holidays are coming,
and I like to spoil my kids.
Maybe he'll give us
some more time.
He's a loan shark. They're
not so big on second chances.
Kinda thought
you were gonna...
steal enough to pay down
the debt, like we talked about.
But, uh...
I tried.
Not hard enough.
Come on.
One last family meal.
There's gotta be something
we can do.
What?
It's nothin'. It's crazy.
I'd do it if I was
still under 18.
Tell me.
Dustin Tate?
Nah, man.
Oh, really?
Yes, you are.
And you're gonna tell me
where Claire Novak is.
Now.
I'd do what he says.
Quick in, quick out.
Watch out for the cameras.
Be careful.
Wait till you're alone,
then you hit
that register jockey hard.
Put the fear of God in him.
You understand?
Good.
You come back to me,
you hear?
You and Dustin --
you're the only family I got.
Excuse us.
Claire, wait!
Screw you.
Whoa.
Hey, Miley Cyrus, settle.
Eat me, Hasselhoff.
Claire, hold on a second.
Look, my name's --
Sam. And you're Dean.
We've met, remember?
Claire.
You were going to rob
that convenience store?
So?
So...It's...
Wrong.
You wanna talk to me
about wrong?
You killed my dad.
Is that wrong enough
for you?
No, I didn't.
Really?
Because without you,
he'd still be here,
and my mom would still
be around.
Claire, I'm...
Don't.
That won't hurt me.
Fine.
Whoa! Hey, come on.
Hold on a second.
Why?
Like you don't have it coming?
You stood there
while this monster took my dad.
I used to pray to you,
Castiel.
Every night.
I would beg you
to bring him home safe.
I know.
You know...
My father was a good man.
In what messed up world
does he have to die
and you get to live?
I'm sorry.
No. You feel guilty.
There's a difference.
So what,
now you run back to Randy,
the guy you steal for?
How do you know about that?
Dustin.
Claire.
That man is using you.
He was there for me.
When things got bad --
and they got real damn bad --
he was there
when no one else was.
He's my family,
and you're just...
You can go to hell.
Boss will see you now.
Mother.
Fergus.
Crowley.
So you haven't changed.
But you certainly have.
King of Hell. Bravo.
I always knew my boy
was meant for big things.
Really?
As I remember it, you said
I would die in a gutter,
covered in my own sick.
I was motivating you
to do better. Aim higher.
And clearly, it worked.
How did you die?
The point is,
you hated me.
Oh, please.
You said you'd be back
in a flash,
and then you disappeared!
I was 8 years old!
8!
Oh, now you're being dramatic.
I didn't even have a father!
Of course you had a father.
You were just conceived
during a winter solstice orgy.
And it's not like
I was taking names.
What do you want me
to say? I...
I had a...disagreement
with the locals.
And when they set their hounds
on me, I had to leave.
And never come back?
For hundreds of years?
But I'm here now.
We have a second chance.
We can be a real family again,
Fergus.
Crowley.
And I have a family.
Who? The demons?
Any one of them would
stab you in the back
if they thought they could
get away with it.
And you wouldn't?
No! Because we're family!
We're blood!
You can trust me,
and I can help you.
I understand you're angry.
I understand that you...
hate me.
And if you want to keep me
locked away,
then so be it.
But know that I'll always
be your mother.
And I'll always love you.
Give me a shot of, um...
Three whiskeys.
Cass, don't beat yourself up,
man.
Claire was...
Right.
She was right.
Who am I to tell her
how to live her life?
Well, somebody needs to.
It's not like we're talking
about Mother Teresa here.
The girl just about knocked over
a Gas 'n Sip.
She's got issues.
Because of me.
Well, you are wearing
her old man's meatsuit.
Probably didn't help.
I thought I could
make it up to her.
I don't think you can.
I mean, Jimmy was her father.
And to some people, that's...
that's everything, you know?
No. I don't.
I never knew my father.
He was distant,
to say the least.
What about you?
Did you love your father?
With everything I had.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, it wasn't
always easy, but yeah.
I mean, look,
John Winchester's not gonna win
any "Number one dad" awards,
you know? But...
You know, damn if he wasn't
there when we needed him.
Hey, uh...
Tell him about
that time in New York.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, okay. So, um...
We were working this haunting
in Long Island,
and -- and me and Sam
begged the old man
to let us go to the city
for once.
He had this thing
about New York, right?
Too big, too loud, too dirty.
Yeah, and he hated the Yankees.
Big-time. Yeah.
Somehow, we convinced him
to let us go.
So we all go. We all, you know,
see all the sights,
and, uh, ride the subway,
eat too much pizza,
the whole nine.
Well, by about midnight,
Sam and dad are zonked,
and I figure, screw it.
I'm going to CBGB.
So CBGB is --
I know.
It's where the Ramones
and Blondie got their start.
Right.
Well, anyways,
he was way underage
at the time.
Yeah, so I get there.
I sneak in,
and it is nuts.
I mean, people are drinking
and they're smoking
and they're --
they're snortin' whatever.
There's a 500-pound guy on stage
with a Mohawk just screamin'.
And, uh, my mind is blown.
I don't even know what to do.
Then this girl walks up
and she says,
"Hey, why don't you come over
and sit down with my friends
at our table?"
All right.
Yeah, and they get him drunk.
First time.
But not fun drunk.
I'm not quite sure
what was in that stuff.
But the room starts to spin.
And I feel like I'm gonna puke.
Forever.
And right about that time,
I hear him.
"Dean Winchester!"
My old man.
I don't know how,
but he found me.
And now
I'm really freaking out,
'cause he's just standing there,
not saying anything.
I look around. Everybody else is
freaking out, too.
In fact, nobody's even
looking him in the eye.
And finally,
this one guy with, like,
a safety pin through his nose
and a-a "kill everything" tattoo
looks up, and he says,
"Sorry, sir."
Yeah. Sorry, sir.
To John friggin' Winchester.
He saved you.
Yeah. And you know what
he got for that?
Me whining about
how much he embarrassed me.
Me telling him
that I hate him.
But then he stopped,
he turned around
and he looked at me
and he said,
"Son, you don't like me?
That's fine.
It's not my job
to be liked."
"It's my job
to raise you right."
Yeah. And he did.
You think Claire is in trouble?
She's hanging out with
a guy named Randy.
- She's in trouble.
- Coming right up.
Randy.
Hey.
Evenin', little lady.
Honey?
You have something
for me?
No! Ow!
Guns blazing, huh?
That was your plan?
Trust me.
This pile of crap?
He ain't worth it.
Put her in the other room.
She's got fight. I like that.
I married the last girl
that spit in my face.
Last few months,
you've lost a bundle
on the ponies.
How much you owe me now?
$5,000.
So how about
I give you a break?
And you give me the girl.
That's a joke, right?
Claire's like family to me.
Please.
I know the con, all right?
You find some kid
with major league daddy issues,
and then you get her
to steal for you.
Cut the proud papa act.
I'll make you a good deal.
Like I said,
Claire's family.
So it better be
a damn good deal.
Come on.
Aah!
Come on!
Stop!
I know who's been
smuggling souls up from Hell.
Really? Pray do tell.
Him.
What?
It -- it's true, mister...
Uh, my lord.
Gerald, he...
We made a deal.
She's lying.
Why? Why would she lie?
That's enough of that, Gerald.
I'll kill you, bitch!
That's enough, Gerald.
I said
that's enough, Gerald.
Thank you.
Coming?
You said that if I lied,
you'd get me out of here.
Oh, and I will, darling.
I'll be back in a flash.
Hi.
It's Claire, right?
You really are a pretty one,
you know that?
Uhh!
Aah!
Don't.
Back it up.
Where's the girl?
Aah! No! No!
Uhh!
Claire.
Claire. Claire!
Randy.
Get her outta here.
Yeah. Go.
Go.
Hey, back up!
Back up!
Don't be as dumb
as you look.
Hey!
You guys don't wanna do this.
Uhh!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Dean?
Dean. Hey.
Tell me you had to do this.
I-I didn't --
I didn't mean to.
No.
Tell me it was them or you!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man