Bobby: Here's to running
into you guys on the other side.
Sam: When we get to earth
and I release you,
it's an express
straight to heaven.
No time for goodbyes.
I'm here about Castiel.
Was there
any of his Grace left?
Question is,
are you willing to pay for it?
He must be returned --
intact.
Is that clear?
Told you last time I saw you
I'd get out of the slammer.
Sam:
We need to know
how to remove the Mark of Cain
from Dean's arm.
He's gone nuclear!
Who knew the Mark
was so toxic?
Ohh!
Actually, I did.
What is the next step in
removing this Mark from my arm?
The river shall end
at the source.
If you ever ask me
for help again,
I will choose death.
You're gonna get worse!
Crowley: Mommy.
Rowena: Fergus.
You think
I've been manipulating you.
I am your mother,
after all.
We can be a family.
I've been thinking
just how wretched it would be
if my own raison d'?tre
were taken from me.
Does this mean that you'll go
to the grand coven on my behalf?
Even better.
I've brought
the coven to you.
I believe
you know Olivette.
[ Grunting ]
These friends of yours --
the Winchesters --
I hear they are,
oh, what do you call it, um,
Men of Letters?
My relationship with
the Winchesters is my business.
I'll handle them.
I'm not killing them.
All right, deary.
Of course.
Whatever you say.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
Amate spiritus obscure,
Te quaerimus.
[ Electricity crackling ]
Te oramus,
nobiscum colloquere,
apud nos circita.
? Know when to hold 'em ?
? know when to fold 'em ?
? know when to walk away ?
? and know when to run ?
? you never count your money ?
? when you're sitting
at the table ?
? there'll be time enough
for counting ?
? when the dealing's done ?
[ Static crackling ]
Sam: Bobby?
[ Distortion ]
Bobby, can you hear me?
? ...Ing at the table ?
Bobby, we need your help.
? there will be time enough
for counting ?
Sam?
? when the dealing's... ?
? Supernatural 10x17 ?
Inside Man
Original Air Date on April 1, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ Dean screams ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Dean: Sam!
No.
No!
Aah!
[ Screams ]
Metatron: My story began
when I killed my brother,
and that's where your story
inevitably will end.
[ Gasps ]
[ Inhales sharply,
breathing heavily ]
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, just, um --
just be there.
Yeah. Got to go.
[ Beep ]
Hey.
How did you sleep?
Like a drunk baby.
What do we got?
Uh, nothing.
Really?
Yeah, I mean, uh,
no weird deaths,
no demon signs.
There's a Kitsune
working some truck stops
outside of Boise,
but Rudy's on it, so...
All right.
So, uh, snow day.
I say we get drunk
and shoot crap.
Yeah, except we do that
every day.
Actually, I was thinking
about seeing a movie.
Yeah,
that could be cool.
It's a French movie.
You mean
like nudie French?
Even better.
It's about a mime
that's secretly a cockroach.
I-I don't get it.
Dude, The New York Times
said --
Who cares?
[ Scoffs ]
All right, well...
It's playing in Wichita,
so I might not be back
till morning.
Well, I trust you.
Make good choices.
Right.
You know, I mean...
I don't have to go alone --
It's fine.
Besides, I could use
a little “me” time.
All right.
Stay out of my room.
Totally.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Footsteps depart ]
[ Brakes squeal ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
Thanks for coming,
Cass.
Of course.
Where's Dean?
This is about Dean.
Is he...?
He's getting worse.
Cass, we've gone through
every other option possible.
We got to talk about --
Don't say it.
Do you think
I want this?
I'm not a fan of it,
either.
But if we want to get rid
of the Mark...
I'm just saying
Charlie's gone radio silent,
everything else we've tried
has been a dead end.
So...
So I'll drive.
[ Car door opens ]
[ Door opens ]
Oh. God.
Please. It's nothing
you haven't seen before.
You're my mother.
I don't want to see anything.
I've been to hell,
thanks.
Next time, knock.
This is my domain.
I don't knock.
[ Sighs ]
Did you want something, Fergus?
It's Crow--
forget it.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
I mean you've been nattering
constantly at me for weeks,
and now you haven't
annoyed me for days.
You're up to something.
You're right.
I'm seeing someone.
I'm a woman.
I have desires, needs,
and Trent is --
Trent?
You're dating a...
He's an assistant manager
at Biggerson's.
He's not
the brightest bulb,
but he's so...
[ Sighs, pops lips ]
...firm.
Please stop talking.
You asked.
Just put
some clothes on.
[ Hinges creak ]
Dean: Rudy.
Rudy! Hey, look.
I know you can handle it, okay?
I'm just saying that,
uh, you know,
if you needed a little assist,
I could, uh, you know --
all right.
All right, all right, all right.
Chill out.
Sorry I asked.
All right.
All right, alheh heh. All right.
Ha. [ Scoffs ]
You know me.
I'm always good.
[ Grunts ]
[ Sniffs, exhales sharply ]
[ Toothbrush clatters ]
Hey, I'm fan-damn-tastic.
That's far enough,
Castiel.
Excuse me?
I have orders.
You aren't allowed upstairs.
Says who?
Hold, please.
Hello, Castiel.
Hannah.
I swore I'd never occupy
another vessel,
but...we need to have this
conversation face-to-face.
What conversation?
What do you want
in Heaven?
Metatron.
Why?
Is this about your Grace?
Are you fading?
I'm fine for now.
This is
about my brother.
Because you think Metatron might have
information about the Mark of Cain?
No.
We know he does.
So he says.
But Metatron lies.
Hannah, we just
want to talk with him.
No,
you want his help.
But we both know
the only way Metatron helps you
is if he's free.
And I can't let the scribe
out of his cell.
Not again.
He's too dangerous.
We won't --
Yes, you will.
Because
you're desperate.
After all I've done
for heaven...
...after all I've done
for you.
I'm sorry.
You should be.
Cass, let's go.
What? We're leaving?
Yeah, we can't fight off
four angels.
So -- so what? You just
want to give up on Metatron?
No, we need him.
Time for plan “B”.
We break him out.
[ Glass clinks ]
I'm told you run
Hell's switchboard.
Tough job.
It's not so bad.
I'm just happy
to do my part.
You sure
you're a demon?
Y-you can be damned
and a conscientious worker.
Oh.
Well, last year,
my son...Crowley,
was taken by the Winchesters.
I need to know
where they were holding him,
and I'm told
he made a call.
I was hoping
you could trace it for me.
O-of course.
Y-you are
the queen mother.
Oh.
[ Sighs ]
[ Stammers ]
H-h-he did call,
but t-there was
some I-interference.
I-I can't get
the exact location.
W-would a 10-mile
radius work?
I'll make do.
Yeah. [ Laughs ]
Hey, Donnie.
Hey, man.
[ Sighs ]
I'll do the, uh,
Herv? Villechaize.
You bet.
Thanks.
[ Rock music playing ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Boom!
[ Groans ]
Money. Now. Loser.
Gracias.
Ty: Give me your cash.
Now. Right now.
What's up with
the Abercrombie rejects?
College kids
“slumming it.”
Slumming?
What are you talking about?
This is a nice joint,
huh?
You got those custom
urinal pucks.
[ Chuckles ]
Come on, bitches.
Who's next?
20 bucks a game.
20 bucks.
[ Indistinct conversation ]
[ Clears throat ]
Yo! Yeah, I'll, uh --
I'll play.
[ Laughs ]
What, seriously?
Dude, he's blitzed.
No. No, no, no, no.
I'm -- I'm -- I'm fine, man.
I'm good to go.
Hmm?
Good to go.
He's fine.
Grab a stick.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
So, back in the '50s,
Oliver Pryce
was a kid psychic.
He performed
everywhere --
carnivals, Atlantic City --
you name it.
He was the real deal.
Now, the Men of Letters
were teaching him
how to control his powers
when they got -- you know.
Brutally slaughtered?
The point is,
he's one of the good guys.
He might be happy
to see us.
Or not.
[ Knock on door ]
Mr. Pryce?
Oliver Pryce!
[ Clears throat ]
I'll break it down.
Dude, dude, dude.
Chill.
What?
I'm helping.
Just follow my lead.
Mr. Pryce?
This is Sam --
Winchester.
You're Sam Winchester,
Man of Letters.
Yeah.
H-how did you, uh --
Mind reader, remember?
And you're...
What are you?
I'm an Angel.
That...
No, you can't be.
Why not?
Because
I'm an atheist.
Not anymore.
[ Door closes ]
That's you?
[ Scoffs ] Was me.
I don't do the psychic stuff
no more.
Being around people,
it's kind of...Hell.
All those brains
yapping all the time
drives a guy bananas.
Because you can hear
everyone's thoughts.
Well, not yours.
All I'm getting from you
is...colors.
But the hippie over here?
I'm seeing some creep-ass
hobbit-lookin' fella,
a prison cell?
That's heaven's jail.
Heaven's got
a freakin' jail?
Yeah. Yeah, it does.
And we're looking
to break someone out of it.
Okay.
We have an inside man,
but we need your help
to talk to him.
And if I say no?
You're the mind reader.
I'll get my crap.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Chuckles ]
I'll get it.
[ Rock music playing ]
[ Laughs ]
There it is.
[ Whistles ]
Corner pocket.
[ Groans ]
The king is here.
Okay, all right.
Again?
[ Chuckles ]
Sure.
? I ain't going back ?
Say $100 this time.
Yeah.
Make it $300.
[ Money thuds ]
? I ain't going back ?
? ain't going back no more ?
What do you say?
? I ain't going back ?
Uh...
Give me your cash.
? I ain't going back ?
? ain't going back no more ?
I think you're
a little short there.
Why don't you toss in the watch?
Good to go.
My dad gave me
this watch.
I'm sure
it's a very touching story.
Got a little tear in my eye.
[ Chuckles ]
Come on.
We gonna play or not?
Rack 'em.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
? I ain't going back ?
? ain't going back no more ?
? I ain't go... ?
You got anything that belonged
to the deceased?
Yes. Right here.
Good.
Now shut up
and hold hands.
Amate spiritus obscure,
Te quaerimus.
[ Electricity crackling ]
Te oramus,
nobiscum colloquere,
apud nos circita.
? Know when to walk away,
and know when to run ?
Sam: Bobby?
[ Static crackling ]
? You never count your money ?
Bobby, can you hear me?
? when you're sitting at the table ?
Bobby, we need your help.
? there will be time enough for counting ?
Sam?
? when the dealing's... ?
[ Blues music playing ]
[ Groans ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
That one.
[ Groans ]
You hustled me.
[ Chuckles ]
Well,
you're pretty quick
for a guy who's all hair gel
and body spray.
Thanks, fellas.
[ Door closes ]
Forget it, dude.
He's an ass.
Rowena: Hello, boys.
[ Sighs, sniffs ]
[ Water turns off ]
And, uh,
that's what's been happening --
the short version of it,
anyway.
[ Static crackling ]
You still there, Bobby?
Yeah, Sam.
It's just...
Real good to hear
your voice.
Yeah, you, too.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Okay.
If, uh,
I'm understanding right,
you got to figure a way
to get the Mark of Cain off Dean
before it turns him
back into a demon?
Pretty much, yeah.
So, just another day
at the office for you boys, huh?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Echoing ]
Put Dean on the line.
Dean's not here.
Why not?
We-- Dean's, um...
He's not in a good place
right now, Bobby.
[ Static crackling ]
So what's the play?
Each soul in heaven is locked
in its own private paradise.
That's where you are now.
U need to escape.
You need to find
the gate to earth and open it.
Then you and I
will find Metatron,
the scribe of God.
Hey, Sam,
you remember
when this job was just
chopping up some fang
and tossing back a cold one?
[ Chuckles ]
I miss that.
Ditto.
[ Inhales deeply ]
So, while I'm playing
Steve McQueen,
anyone gonna be looking
for me?
Everyone.
The Angels will not like
a soul wandering free.
We got a way
to slow them down?
Not exactly.
But, um, you'll --
you'll figure something out,
Bobby. You always do.
[ Scoffs ]
Listen,
I appreciate the warm fuzzy,
but I ain't exactly playing
on the big leagues these days.
I'm mostly drinking
and reading the classics.
Truth is, I'm rusty.
And maybe there's somebody
better out there.
There isn't, Bobby.
And w-with Dean
the way he is...
[ Inhales deeply ]
...This is all we got.
Hell,
I'm already dead.
What's the worst
that could happen?
Dean.
Rowena?
What's a nice girl like you
doing in a place like this?
I'm sorry.
Did I say “nice girl”?
I meant “evil skank”"
[ chuckles ] You say that
like it's an insult.
But nice girls,
they're pathetic.
Here's to evil skanks.
[ Grunts ]
[ Growls ]
Whoa, fellas.
What did she do to you?
[ Roars ]
[ Heart beating ]
[ Groans ]
[ Bone cracks ]
[ Screams ]
[ Cue clatters ]
[ Snarls ]
Someone's tougher
than he looks.
You have no idea.
A spiorad? an tsaoil,
?istig? liom!
D?ighig? an fear seo!
D?ighig? go luaithreach ?!
[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Not possible.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Saving my son.
Your son?
Crowley.
Crowley Crowley?
My son is a king,
a god --
or he would be
if you didn't --
you snap your fingers,
and he comes running
like a wee lapdog.
Lady, I don't know
what you're talking about.
You're a good influence
on him.
That's why
you need to die.
Well, sorry your little
light show didn't work.
Oh, I'll try again.
What, you think I'm just gonna
let you walk out of here?
I think you're a hero.
You could have killed
those men,
but you didn't
because they're innocent.
[ Clicks tongue ]
'Cause you're the good guy,
and you want them
to live.
But the spell I cast
will devour them
from the inside out
like it did that girl.
Impetus bestiarum.
[ Screaming ]
What did you do to her?
I'm the only one
that can save them.
What's it going to be...
Hero?
Bobby:
So, where do we start?
You need to find
your heaven's escape hatch.
Look for something
that shouldn't be there,
and that's your way out.
[ Static crackling ]
Just when I thought
I was out [Sighs]
They pull me back in.
[ Muffled up-tempo music ]
[ Alarm blaring ]
Balls!
Rough date, mother?
Dean Winchester
did this to me.
Get out.
Yes, sir.
[ Door closes ]
[ Glass clinks ]
Why were you anywhere near
Dean Winchester?
I was trying to kill him.
[ Sniffles ]
Been there.
Never seems to work out
quite the way you want.
The spell I cast should have
ripped him apart, but --
It was like Dean was protected
from on high.
It's the Mark of Cain.
It never lets its host
die easy.
The Mark?
It's just a curse.
T-the first curse.
But still,
it can be removed.
How?
I'll find a way.
You do that.
I assume
you had a reason
for this little suicide run
of yours.
The best reason --
you.
Those tumshies
have you on a leash.
I thought I-if
they were gone, you --
I know
what you thought.
And I know
that you were wrong.
I have Sam and Dean
exactly where I want them.
What do they say?
Friends close,
enemies closer.
Maybe they were
your enemies once.
But now? Please.
Do you even care
that Dean Winchester mutilated
your mother?!
Because
you were stupid.
Because I love you.
Well, if my suffering's
not enough,
you know how much
demons gossip.
Right now, word's already
spreading about all this.
If you do nothing,
you'll look weak.
Your subjects will start
to doubt you, mock you.
Then it's just
a matter of time
before you have a revolt
on your hands,
before you lose
your throne.
You're playing
a dangerous game.
And it's your move.
So you can't kill Dean.
Fine.
Take him, throw him
in some dank cell, let him rot.
But do something!
No more stalling.
No more excuses.
Show them how strong
you really are.
Be a bloody king!
[ Scoffs ]
[ Crickets chirping ]
You sure
he can handle this?
[ Scoffs ]
He's Bobby.
He can handle anything.
[ Alarm blaring ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
What?
Find out
how this happened.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Gentlemen...and lady,
I need you to return
to your heavens
in a calm, orderly manner.
Oh, yeah?
Well, who made you boss?
Right?
Who the hell you think do you are?
Let's go.
Hold off, gentlemen and lady.
[ Indistinct shouting ]
Gentlemen, easy.
Please!
Been waiting on you.
Squirrel.
Bos.
Where's Natasha?
Would it make
a difference?
Not really.
[ Inhales deeply ]
So, we gonna do this?
[ Glass thuds ]
Guardian: The Bobbys
are fighting back.
All hands.
We need all hands.
They're surly.
I repeat, the Bobbys are surly.
If I find a way out,
then what?
Castiel: The gate is behind
door number...
42.
Go.
Go!
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
Welcome to the party.
The prison, it's, uh --
it's close.
Uh-huh.
Cass, where's Dean?
What?
You heard me.
Dean's, uh --
he's resting.
He's...sick, and --
Try again.
[ Sighs ]
Dean doesn't know
we're doing this.
Well, that's a page
right out of
the Winchester playbook,
ain't it?
Dean has given up.
And you idjits haven't.
Would you?
Hell, no.
Look, I'm not saying
that I didn't want to
slice and dice the witch.
I'm just saying that
that's not how it went down.
So she's a liar.
Must run in the family.
Mother says that Mark
is just a curse,
can be removed.
Of course,
she doesn't know how.
Figures.
But I'm good, thanks.
Who's the liar now?
She says
I've gone soft.
[ Chuckles ]
You have.
What?
Yeah, maybe it's all
the human blood
that Sammy pumped into you,
you know? Maybe it's, uh --
I don't know.
But the old Crowley,
he would have come in here
with hellhounds and demons,
and he would have blown
the roof off the joint.
Now?
You didn't want to fight.
You wanted to talk.
And maybe I've changed,
too.
Here I am playing Dr. Phil
to the King of Hell.
[ Chuckles ]
Never saw that coming.
Maybe
we're getting old.
Never saw that coming,
either.
What is it, huh?
Why you letting mommy dearest
tie you into knots?
Because...
We're family.
Blood.
That's not
the same thing.
A wise man once told me,
“family don't end in blood.”
but it doesn't start there,
either.
Family cares about you,
not what you can do for them.
Family's there through the good,
bad -- all of it.
They got your back...
even when it hurts.
That's family.
That sound like
your mother?
[ Sighs ]
Well, howdy, fellas.
This is
the scribe of God?
He looks
like a Fraggle.
I'm gonna take that
as a compliment.
That was
an excellent program.
Metatron,
we are here --
I know why you're here,
“Asstiel,”
and I'm not interested.
I told you
I would rather die
than let Dean Winchester use me
as his personal punching bag again.
Don't worry.
Dean's not involved.
You're gonna be
my punching bag.
Ah.
The “B” team, huh?
Heh.
Interesting.
Keys are over there.
Chop chop!
Are you sure
this is the only way?
[ Sighs ]
Unfortunately.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Whoosh ]
Sam-tastic!
Miss me?
[ Sniffs ]
Oh, smell that?
That smells like freedom.
Well, let's go.
I call shotgun!
You don't get to make demands,
Metatron.
You're not
in charge here.
Oh, I'm afraid I am.
I know about the Mark.
I have your Grace.
I make the rules.
[ Chuckles ]
It's called leverage,
boys.
Learn it, live it,
love it.
[ Gasping ]
[ Groans ]
[ Gun cocks ]
Ow! Ow!
[ Groaning ]
We have your Grace, Metatron.
You're mortal now.
So you will answer
our questions,
or Sam will, um...
What's the phrase?
Blow your
fricking brains out.
It's called leverage,
Metatron.
Learn it, live it,
love it.
How do we get rid
of the Mark?
[ Voice breaking ]
I-I don't know.
I don't know!
No, I-it's old magic --
God-level magic.
Or Lucifer level,
but you can't ask him,
exactly, can you?
What about the tablets?
No, Th-there's -- there's
nothing in them about the Mark.
So when you said
“The river ends at the source,”
that was --
I was just making up crap,
trying to buy time
till I could screw you over.
No.
What?!
It worked before.
He's telling the truth.
What?
Shoot him.
[ Gun cocks ]
No, no! No.
your Grace.
I wasn't lying about that.
There's still some left.
I'll take you to it.
It's your call, Cass.
Is it done?
We're done.
Get your things
and get out.
You aren't serious.
Deadly.
But I'm your mother.
You may have brought me
into this world,
but you were never
my mother.
So you're choosing
the Winchesters.
I'm choosing me.
[ Scoffs ]
I put up with your lies,
your sad little schemes
because -- no.
Because maybe
you were right.
Maybe
I did lose my edge.
But that ends now.
Tell me, Rowena,
if I were not
the King of Hell,
would you have ever bothered
to pretend to care about me?
[ Voice breaking ]
You -- you can't.
I can.
I'm bloody Crowley!
I'm the King of Hell.
I do what I want,
when I want.
And I don't take orders
from you.
Everything you have,
I will watch it burn!
I'll give you
five minutes.
After that,
pray I don't see you again.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hey.
How was the movie?
French.
[ Chuckles ]
What about you?
What did you do last night?
Played some pool.
It was kind of boring.
All right.
I'm gonna clean up.
Yeah.
[ Sighs ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Car door closes ]
Sam.
Bobby asked me
to give you this.
Bobby: Sam...
So...this is weird, huh?
Look, I just wanted to say
that Cass told me
what you're doing for Dean.
And I'm not asking you
to stop,
but maybe going behind his back
ain't the best idea.
Your brother,
he can be stubborn.
But I think he'd understand.
And I know it's the life --
doing a little bad
so you can do a lot of good.
[ Engine turns over ]
But sometimes
the bad's real bad
and the good --
it can come
at one hell of a price.
I ain't there on the ground,
and whatever you do,
I know you'll make
the right choice.
You're a good man,
Sam Winchester --
one of the best.
And I'm damn proud of you, son.
I was content up here.
But getting the call from you,
it's the happiest I've been
in forever,
no matter what it costs.
So stay safe, keep fighting,
and kick it in the ass.
Bobby.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man