Open your eyes, Dean.
Let's go take a howl
at that moon.
Heaven needs your help.
Anything.
Daniel and Adina --
they must be found.
They must be brought home,
and they must be punished
for the sake of all.
Think of it --
the King of Hell,
Dean Winchester by his side.
Together, we rule.
Together, we create
the perfect hell.
And all of this that's bloomed
between us never ends.
Hey! don't turn your back
on me!
- What do you think you're doing?
- Oh, whatever I want.
You're here for Dean.
I'm here
to give him to you.
The little prat's
bad for business.
He's uncontrollable.
Must be the Mark.
Your pal Crowley
sold you out.
We know how to cure demons.
You remember that?
Little Latin,
lot of blood.
So, what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna kill me?
You are my brother,
and I'm here to take you home.
You really think
those are gonna work?
Stop! It's over!
It's over, Dean.
Hunc sanguinem sacro,
et donantibus sanguinem,
debita dimitto.
D-dolorem remitteat,
et voluntati dei serviat.
Doctor.
Father.
Really?
For whatever it's worth,
I got your blood type.
Sam, I know you think
you're gonna try and fix me,
but did it ever
occur to you
that maybe I don't want
to be fixed?
Just let me
go live my life.
I won't bother you.
What do you care?
What do I care?
Ritum sacrum...
Hanc terram consecro.
You think I'm just
gonna sit here like Crowley,
getting all weepy
while you shoot me up?
Well, screw that.
I don't want this.
Yeah, I pretty much
figured that out.
You don't even know
if this is gonna work, do you?
You know, I got a hell of a lot more
running through me
than just demon juice.
Mark of Cain -- got it.
That's right.
Buckle up.
Sammy...
You know I hate shots.
I hate demons.
Look, we got a whole bunch more
of these to go.
You could make it
a lot easier on yourself.
? Supernatural 10x03 ?
Soul Survivor
Original Air Date on October 21, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
How are you holding up?
Fine.
You say you're fine,
but you don't look fine.
It's what the humans do.
They say they're fine,
and even if I-I don't look it,
you say I look well,
and in that way,
we avoid talking about something
we can do nothing about.
I'm sorry.
I just can't see
how Sam Winchester could ask you
to drive all this way
to help with his brother,
knowing your condition.
He doesn't know...
about how badly
your borrowed Grace is fading,
does he?
Mm. He knows some.
And he didn't have to ask.
Sam is alone in this.
He's attempting to change Dean
from demon to human
with a cure
of sanctified blood,
but...there's no guarantee
that will work.
If it doesn't,
then Dean is gone,
and the demon
must be dealt with.
I just...
I worry about you.
For all you know,
you could be killing me.
Or...
You're just messing
with me.
Either way,
the lore doesn't say anything
about exceptions
to the cure.
“The Lore.”
hunters...
Men of Letters.
What a load of crap
it all is.
Oh, you got nothin'?
You want me
to debate you?
This isn't even the real you
I'm talking to.
Oh, it's the real me,
all right.
The new real me --
the me that sees things
for what they really are.
Winchesters -- do-gooders --
fighting the natural order.
Let me tell you
something --
guys like me,
we are the natural order.
It's the way
it was set up.
Guys like me
still got to do what we can.
don't be so full of yourself,
Sammy.
'Cause, see,
from where I'm sitting,
there ain't much difference
from what I turned into
to what you already are.
And what exactly
is that supposed to mean?
I know what you did
when you went looking for me.
I know how far you went.
Crowley told me
all about it.
So, let me ask you...
...which one of us
is really a monster?
Hmm?
Starting to come back
to you now?
What am I supposed to do now?
It's like
my life is over.
Thank you.
Bitch.
I should've seen it coming.
Why doesn't anything
ever work out for me?
Huh?
Hey, there.
Hi.
Sounds like, uh...
Things have been a little rough
on you lately, huh?
Rough?
My wife
kicked me to the curb.
Oh.
We haven't had sex
for four months.
Four.
Well, not that -- not that
she hasn't been having plenty...
With a guy
in her bowling league --
guy with tattoos.
Did him right there
on the kitchen table
while I was at work.
Man.
That's, uh...
That's cold.
Now all I think of
is revenge...
Payback.
But that's
not gonna happen.
I wouldn't be so sure
about that.
It is possible that you can...
have your revenge.
I mean, hell,
it's possible
you can have
pretty much anything you want.
You were trying
to get a 20 on Crowley and me
from any demon
you could snag.
But Crowley
didn't want to be found,
and no one showed
when you summoned.
But you find a way,
didn't you, Sam?
All right.
Stand right here.
When I say so,
read the words off the paper.
A-are you sure
about this?
Yeah. Trust me.
All right. Go ahead.
Okay, um...
Demon esto subiectus
voluntari --
tati! Voluntati!
Oh -- voluntati.
Who summons me,
and for what purpose?
Kill my wife...
Lester!
...and my soul is yours.
Don't!
Done.
No!
You would have liked
to have gotten there
before the deal went down,
but you didn't really care
about poor ol' Lester, did you?
Why don't we try that
again?
Nobody knows where Crowley
and your brother are.
They're off the radar!
Aah!
Kill me if you want to!
That's all I know.
I got nothing for you.
And you made that poor
son of a bitch sell his soul.
Oh, and so you know,
I killed Lester myself.
And that wife of his
married the tattooed guy.
I never meant --
Who cares
what you meant?!
That line that we thought
was so clear
between us
and the things that we hunted
ain't so clear,
is it?
Wow.
You might actually
be worse than me.
I mean, you took a guy
at his lowest, used him,
and it cost him his life
and his soul.
Nice work.
Aah!
Let me ask you this,
Sammy.
If this doesn't work...
We both know what you got to do
to me, right?
You got the stomach
for that, Sam?!
You stand accused
of high treason.
Take her away.
So, what's this, then?
Oh, goody --
something else to sign.
“Henceforth and forthwith...
“For the furtherance
and expedience
and regulation and...”
yeah.
Sure.
Majesty,
supplicants await without.
Without what?
Outside.
Let them wait.
They've waited
a long time.
It's Hell. You wait.
It's what you do.
You're still here.
I have an update
on the angel Castiel.
His Grace
seems to be fading.
He's losing strength.
If one were so inclined,
this would be a propitious time
for one to eliminate him.
“One”?
You, sire.
Borrowed Grace does have
a puny shelf life.
Castiel should have read
the warning label.
Follow him.
And keep me informed
as to his decline.
What's going on here?
What's it look like?
In my bed?!
Jerk.
Bitch.
Knock it down. Knock it down!
Stop talking!
You're bodging it!
Yeah!
The King of Hell,
Dean Winchester by his side.
Together, we rule.
Together, we create
the perfect Hell.
Great one?
Your majesty?
Are you...all right?
I was thinking
of better days.
Yes --
your sabbatical.
My what?
Uh, we were worried,
of course.
Your misadventure
with the older Winchester
was quite
the topic of speculation.
Uh, if you'll forgive
my boldness...
I could now be
your wingman.
Could you?
I, too, love to party,
and I do love the ladies
and the classic
rock 'n' roll.
Most importantly,
I can debauch by your side
without being
a personal embarrassment.
You'll see
what I'm worth.
Oh, I can see already.
Anyone else care to comment?
Sorry.
I...missed another turn.
I have no idea
where the main road is.
These things --
they're so confining
and primitive.
It's --
it's getting worse,
isn't it?
Castiel, it's time
we stopped avoiding the obvious.
You and I both know
how to fix this --
both you
and the situation.
I will not slit
some angel's throat
and steal its Grace.
Before you say it,
we definitely are not going
begging to Metatron.
What about
helping your friend
and sending the rogue angels
back to heaven?
Your preference to die
for your principles --
it's very noble,
but it is meaningless.
Then you carry on.
I'm not enough.
Sometimes, enough is
whatever you have.
Sam?
Cass.
Hey,
are you still coming?
I'm a few hours away.
Is the treatment
working?
No, not very well.
Look, I-it's not
like it was with Crowley.
Dean's in pain.
I mean,
he's in bad pain.
I-it's like
he's barely holding on.
Cass...
I might be killing him.
It might be.
So...What?
Should I stop?
And do what?
He's not possessed.
Exorcism is
out of the question.
The ritual of purified blood
is the only treatment I know.
Cass, did you not hear
what I just said?
I could be killing
my brother.
Sam, he's not your brother --
at least not now.
You have to be
prepared for --
Killing my brother.
I'll be there
as soon as I can.
Yeah, all right.
I'll, uh, I'll leave the entry
unlocked for you.
Just hurry.
Hey! Hey!
Dean! Come on!
- Come back.
- No.
Come back to me.
You there? Hey!
Dean, you okay?
Yeah, if you...
Consider
drowning in your own sweat
while your blood boils okay.
Look,
I can't stop doing this.
Sure you can.
You just stop.
There's no point in trying
to bring your brother back now.
Oh, I will
bring him back.
In fact, your, uh,
guilt-ridden,
weight-of-the-world bro
has been M.I.A.
for quite some time now.
But I'm loving
the new model --
lean, mean Dean.
Right.
You notice I tried to get as far away
from you as possible?
Away from your whining,
your complaining.
I chose the King of Hell
over you.
Maybe I was just...
tired of babysitting you
or always having to yank
your lame ass out of the fire
since  forever.
Or maybe --
maybe it was the fact that
my mother would still be alive
if it wasn't for you.
That your very existence
sucked the life out of my life.
This isn't
my brother talking.
You never had a brother --
just an excuse
for not manning up.
But guess what.
I quit.
No. No, you don't.
You don't get to quit.
We don't get to quit
in this family.
This family is
all we have ever had!
Well, then,
we got nothin'.
Would you say that
to dad?
Dad?
Oh, there's a prize.
Here's a man who brainwashed us
into wasting our lives
fighting
his losing battle.
Oh. Ooh.
Is this you manning up?
This is me yanking your lame ass
out of the fire.
You're welcome.
You have coerced others
into aligning with Abaddon.
You've spread rumors
and fostered doubt
as to the competence
and authority of the crown.
Guilty of treason.
The sentence is death.
Anyone else hungry to betray me?
Next.
You're guilty of...something,
which I won't tolerate,
whatever it was.
You are condemned to --
Stop! Stop!
Stop?
You cannot do this.
Weren't you watching?
'Course I can. I just did.
This is
your idea of ruling?
Yes.
We've killed and tortured
for you,
stolen souls,
destroyed lives,
tempted and tormented
with distinction.
And for all this,
what's our reward?
A slap in the face.
What is it?
You disappear,
binge on blood,
approach the edge
of becoming human.
And the salt in the wound --
you run off
with your boy toy,
Dean Winchester,
and now
he's running amok,
and you can't control him
or the kingdom.
What's he doing?
You've squandered
our loyalty.
What will you do?
Not live in the Hell
you've made.
It's holy oil!
Get back! Get back!
Gaaaaaaaaah!
Did not see that coming.
Huh.
Um, Hannah.
You know,
this -- this road we're on,
it's -- it's dangerous.
All right.
Um...
We can't afford
to lose our way.
I know that.
I'm sorry about the map.
No detours of any kind.
Castiel,
if these are metaphors
and you're attempting
another human communication,
it isn't working.
I'm just trying to say
that this mission is everything.
I know that.
Getting to Dean
and hunting these rogues --
I -- I'm not
at full capacity,
so I...
We n-need total focus.
Like a laser.
Got it.
Just -- I've been around humans
for long enough
to see...how easily
distractions occur.
“Distractions.”
Emotions...feelings --
they're
dangerous temptations.
How very biblical,
Castiel.
I don't mean
to be unkind.
You don't need
to be kind.
I just...
I'm trying to keep
our priorities clear.
Not to worry, then.
I am very clear
on my priorities.
And yours.
Hello?
Hey, there.
I've been tracking you
for days.
You will be punished
for what you did.
Daniel's death --
that was unintentional, Adina.
I feel you know this.
Unintentional?
You killed him!
Aah!
Seriously?
Just...kill me.
But let her go.
Stop.
“stop.” “kill me.”
I mean, so many suggestions,
I don't know what to do.
I know --
I will kill you, Castiel,
but very, very slowly
so your -- your honeybunch
can watch.
Sound good?
Hey, champ.
Look at you.
Talk about roadkill.
Attagirl, Hannah.
Suffer.
Just like my Daniel suffered
before you killed him.
Daniel's death isn't on my head.
It's on yours.
We did nothing.
We wanted nothing
but to be left alone.
You killed an angel.
You had to answer for it.
An angel who would have hauled us
back to that heaven of yours.
You should have
left us alone.
And that will do.
Why can't you people
just sit on clouds
and play harps,
like you're supposed to?
Come on, Sam!
don't you want to hang out
with your big brother?
Spend a little quality time?
Don't be an idiot.
Yes, it's hers, but she was
killing your girlfriend.
Your hands are clean.
Much as it pains me
to say this,
you're useless to me
dead.
You owe me.
Why did you help me?
Purely business.
Since you're 5 miles away
from the Winchesters' clubhouse,
I can only surmise
that you're headed there
and that Dean has become
a handful.
Having him as a demon has
caused me nothing but grief.
Fix the problem.
You realize --
worse comes to worst,
that means killing him.
I'm not sentimental.
Smart, Sam.
Locking the place down.
Doors won't open.
I get it.
But here's the thing.
I don't want to leave.
Not till I find you.
Sammy!
You're just making this
worse for yourself, man!
Oh, by the way,
you can, uh...blame yourself
for me getting loose.
All that blood you pumped
into me to make me human --
well
The less demon I was,
the less the cuffs worked.
And that Devil's Trap --
well, I just walked
right across it.
It smarted.
But still...
Yeah, that's more like it.
That's your big move?
Listen to me, Dean!
We were getting close,
okay?
I know you're still in there
somewhere.
Just let me
finish the treatments.
Dean?
You act like
I want to be cured.
Personally,
I like the disease.
Dean! Stop that!
Look, I don't want
to use this Blade on you!
Oh!
That sucks for you,
doesn't it?
'Cause you really mean that.
Look, if you come
out of that room,
I won't have a choice!
Sure you will!
And I know
which one you'll make.
Isn't that right,
Sammy?
But, see...
Here's the thing.
I'm lucky.
Oh, hell, I'm blessed.
'Cause there's
just enough demon left in me
that killing you
ain't no choice at all.
Sammy?
Come on, Sammy!
Let's have a beer,
talk about it.
I'm tired of playing.
Let's finish this game!
Well...Look at you.
Do it.
It's all you.
It's over.
Dean, it's over.
Aaaaah!
It's over.
What the hell
are we doing to him, Cass?
I mean, even after
I gave him all that blood,
he still said
he didn't want to be cured,
that he didn't want
to be human.
Well...
I see his point.
You know, only humans
can feel real joy, but...
also such profound pain.
This is easier.
You look worried, fellas.
Welcome back, Dean.
Hey.
How's he doing?
He's, uh...
He's still a little out of it,
but better, I think.
I mean,
I think this whole thing --
the blood cure and the...
All of it --
really wrecked him,
you know?
Yeah.
On the plus side,
he's hungry again,
so I'm just gonna go pick him up
a big ol' bag of crap food
and stuff it
in his face myself.
You mind keeping an eye?
Yeah.
Sam?
Yeah?
You realize --
one problem is solved,
but one still remains.
Dean is no longer a demon.
That's true.
But the Mark of Cain --
that, he still has,
and sooner or later,
that's gonna be an issue.
You know what, Cass?
I'm beat, man.
One battle at a time,
you know?
So I'm just gonna go grab
my brother some cholesterol.
And then
I'm gonna get drunk.
Yeah.
You look terrible.
You know, it wouldn't kill you
to lie every now and again.
No, it wouldn't kill me.
I just...you --
Forget it.
Well,
you, on the other hand,
you...
Looking good.
So...are you back?
At least temporarily.
Yeah, it's a long story --
Crowley, stolen Grace.
There's a female outside
in the car.
Another time.
Well, thank you for, um...
Stepping in when you did.
What does Sam say?
Does he want a divorce?
I'm sure Sam knows
that whatever you said
or what you did,
that wasn't really you.
It certainly wasn't
all you.
I tried to kill him,
Cass.
Dean, you two have
been through so much.
Look, you're brothers.
It'd take a lot more than
trying to kill Sam with a hammer
to make him
want to walk away.
You realize how screwed up
our lives are
that that even makes sense?
I'm glad you're here,
man.
Hey, maybe you should,
um...take some time
before you get back to work --
allow yourself to heal.
It's, uh...
I don't know.
Timing might be right.
Heaven and Hell -- they seem
reasonably back in order.
It's quiet out there.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man