Charlie -- she's been making
donations through her aliases
to Shawnee County General
here in Topeka.
Like, a charity?
A patient.
Gertrude Middleton.
She and her husband
were hit by a drunk driver.
I was at a sleepover,
and I got scared.
I called my parents
to come and get me.
They should never have been
driving that night.
This thing has got to go.
It will take
a very powerful force
to remove the effect.
Well, then burn it off!
I'm not living like this.
Sam: Cain still has
the Mark, right?
So he's lived with it.
Maybe there's a part of you
that wants to
give in to it,
and maybe you
have to fight that.
Part of that powerful force
has to be you.
Saving people, hunting things,
the family business?
I am down.
But...
Where's my quest?
Dorothy:
It's the key to Oz.
There are magical ways
into Oz --
this key will turn any
locked door into a portal to Oz.
You coming or what?
To Oz?
Yeah. You said you were looking
for adventure.
Well, here it is, red.
[ Insects chirping ]
[ Man screams, thudding,
glass shattering ]
[ Panting ]
[ Glass shatters ]
Aah!
[ Grunts ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Please...
I-I don't know
anything else.
Charlie: I know.
I'm gonna torture you anyway.
'Cause who doesn't love
a little torture?
? Supernatural 10x11 ?
There's No Place Like Home
Original Air Date on January 27, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
All right, well, just --
just keep me posted, okay?
Yeah, you got it.
Wait, Cass. You there?
Hey, thanks.
Yeah.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
You made
egg-white omelettes?
Yeah. Breakfast
of Champions --
you know,
if you're a dork like you.
And you slept past 7:00?
Yeah, well,
until we get answers
on this Mark of Cain,
I am on a 12-step program
not to backslide.
12 steps?
Yeah.
Hey, if Cain found a way to live with it
after going dark side,
then I just got to find a way
to keep it in check,
so haven't had a drink
in a week,
eight hours of rack time
every night,
and...now
this masterpiece.
That's three steps.
Shut up and eat.
Wow. That's --
that's awesome.
It's crap.
Ugh. God.
Soon as we get rid of this
demonic tramp stamp,
I am back on the booze,
burgers, and...more booze.
Tell me you got something.
[ Coughs, groans ]
What the hell?
Cain or Crowley?
Charlie.
Is she back from Oz?
She didn't call?
Yeah, uh...
She's been busy.
[ Keys clacking ]
[ Charlie grunting ]
What the hell
am I looking at?
[ Exhales softly ]
So, you know, I was looking
into the news,
checking for anything weird,
right?
I found this story
about a torture Vic.
Apparently, some kid
videotaped this
at his next-door
neighbor's house.
What are you saying,
Charlie tortured someone?
Uh...
Our Charlie?
Yea high,
wouldn't hurt a Hobbit,
practically sparkles?
[ Cellphone beeps, rings ]
[ Sighs ]
Come on, Charlie,
pick up.
The guy she went
all Jack Bauer on --
uh, Peter Harper.
She's not answering.
[ Beeps ]
District attorney
in Topeka.
According to this article,
he wasn't the only person
in town that was hit.
Uh, a court stenographer
was assaulted the night before.
Well, you know, Charlie
wouldn't go off on someone
without a reason.
Yeah, I wouldn't think so either,
but look at the video.
Oh, I'm looking at it.
But you know what we do,
taken out of context,
it doesn't look
that much different.
She could be hunting.
[ Sighs ]
Why don't we go talk to this asshat and
see what's going on?
Hey, ready?
Yeah. Yeah, let's do this.
Let's go.
Sam: Now, did you notice anything odd
before the attack --
any, uh, strange smells,
weird noises?
No, no, nothing.
I was just at home here,
getting ready for bed,
and that crazy bitch
jumped me.
All she wanted was to know
was about some case
that I worked on
years ago --
drunk driver
T-boned another car,
killing the driver,
and the passenger was declared
brain-dead on the scene.
The Middletons.
They had a daughter,
12 years old.
They were on their way
to pick her up.
Yeah, that's right.
How did you know that?
Well, we do our homework
at the FBI.
Okay, well, then you know
the case never went to trial.
Before I could even see the evidence,
it was off the books.
All the files were sealed.
Now, how is that
even possible?
I don't know.
But I looked into it
this morning.
There's no record of that case
anywhere,
and the arresting officer
has since passed away.
There's nothing,
except for this --
the social service file
on the Middletons' kid.
It's not very helpful,
to be honest with you.
The kid has disappeared,
until now.
Now, is there anything else
you can remember
about the case --
any names you can think of?
No.
Like I told the police,
it was so long ago.
Look, I'm sorry.
All right.
Here's the thing.
We talked to the other victim
on the way here --
the stenographer.
Now, she said the attacker
didn't let her go
until she gave up a name --
your name.
Okay.
But w-what does
that have to do
with m-me being attacked
in my own home, here?
What name
did you give up?
Look, I told you
everything
I told the police.
This woman comes in here,
beats the tar out of me,
but -- but there's no name
to give up,
so I-I don't know
what else to --
Hey,
w-what are you doing?!
Talk,
you son of a bitch!
Hey, look,
I'm the victim, here!
Aah!
Talk!
Okay. Okay.
[ Breathing heavily ]
All right.
Aah.
[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sighs ]
After the files were sealed...
I pushed.
And, uh...
They offered me money --
a lot of money.
Give me a name.
The money kept on coming in
from overseas accounts.
Give me a name!
I will be disbarred!
That'll be
the least of your worries,
I promise you that.
Councilwoman
Barbara Cordry.
[ Engine whirs ]
Celeste Middleton.
Celeste --
that's Charlie's real name.
Guess she's looking
for the person
who, uh,
destroyed her family.
Can you blame her?
You know,
we just got to find her
before she does something
nobody can walk away from.
[ Knock on door ]
Barbara Cordry?
Can I help you?
Yes.
I'm Special Agent Gabriel.
This is my partner,
Special Agent Collins.
May we come in?
What's this about?
We have some questions
about a drunk-driving case
from a while back
involving
the Middleton family.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Ma'am, if we could just --
Sorry.
I'm still on vacation.
Feel free to schedule
an appointment
with my assistant.
She'll pencil
you both in.
Guilty much?
Yeah.
[ Sighs ]
What the hell
is kale?
"Anti-authority disorder,
clinical depression,
violent outbursts."
Charlie was, uh...
Dude.
If a shrink interviewed us
at that age,
you think the report would be
all kittens and rainbows?
Come on.
She's a good kid.
There's got to be
an explanation for this, man.
There's just got to be.
[ Woman screams,
glass shattering in distance ]
[ Breathing shakily ]
Should have known Rocket and Groot
would track me down.
Let her go.
Who?
Oh, her?
Don't do this.
I just want answers.
Dean: Yeah?
Since when do you start
pounding on people
for those?
What the hell
happened to you in Oz?
Everything I wanted.
An adventure.
Even got my own little sword.
[ Whimpers ]
Charlie --
Oh, Sam, you're adorable.
You're not gonna hurt me.
In fact,
that's your problem --
all good-guy code,
no bite.
What a waste.
[ Whimpers ]
And you...
Always letting this albatross
hold you back.
Okay, all right,
you know what?
I don't know
what's going on here, okay?
But this --
this is not you.
Oh,
it's me, all right.
Charlie, put the knife down.
Let her go.
We don't want to hurt you,
kiddo,
but we're not gonna
let you do this.
Stop!
[ Muffled ] Crap!
[ Grunts ]
Sam!
You all right?
[ Shakily ] Yeah.
What did she say to you?
She -- she just --
she wanted
the bank statements.
[ Engine turns over ]
Dean:
Charlie! Hey!
Oh, you son of a bitch.
[ Horn honks ]
What's up, bitches?
Right.
Um [Chuckles]
we should probably catch up.
There two of you --
one good, one...bad?
Yeah, what, dick you
is some sort of a ninja?
She is a badass, yeah.
O-okay.
Hold on. Back up.
We were there for Dorothy,
Oz, yellow brick road.
B-but then...
War.
The war for Emerald City.
It was awesome.
[ Chuckles ]
Until not so much.
We were gonna lose,
so I made a deal
with the wizard...
of Oz.
Wears a hood
and a creepy mask,
kind of a jerk --
good times.
He said for us to win,
I had to unleash
my true darkness,
which he meant literally.
He used
the inner key of Oz.
It opens a door to your soul
and lets the darkness out.
Uh, we're still connected
physically.
If you hurt her,
you hurt me.
But bottom line,
she's bad, and I'm good.
And let me just tell you,
being good
is really annoying.
Normally in a place
like this,
I'd be pounding
Harvey Wallbangers
and checking out
the bartender's ass.
Now all I want to do
is sip club soda
and send her
to college.
Okay,
uh...good Charlie.
So, why is dark Charlie
gunning for revenge?
She's trying
to win me back.
Dark Charlie won the war
single-handedly.
But...
She did some truly
awful things.
But I told her
I didn't want any part
of her near me again, ever.
Going after the person
who mur-- mur-- uh...
Who took my parents away
is her messed-up way
of showing me how close we are,
or -- or could be.
I keep calling her "she,"
but she's me.
I'm the one doing this.
Charlie, that --
that's not who you are, okay?
It's -- it's
a twisted version of --
Me.
I've been following her
so I can catch her
before she does
something stupid
a-and just lock her away
forever.
Uh, Charlie...
That's not an answer.
Sam's right.
We'll go back to Oz,
and we'll --
we'll get the key
from the wizard of douche,
and we'll put you
back together.
Even if
I did want her back...
Look
dark me broke the key.
There's no way
to get back to the wizard.
Sam: Okay, okay,
first thing's first.
We need to find
dark Charlie
before she finds
the drunk driver.
So, we know Barbara
gave up
her old bank statements,
right?
That means dark Charlie
will probably follow
the money
back to whoever
made the payoffs.
That's what I would do.
All right.
I'll get some refills.
We need you...
to hack into
Barbara's bank accounts.
I can't.
What?
It's bad.
I told you -- being good is annoying.
How about this --
how about you guide me
through the process,
and then
I'm the bad one?
Okay, so, Barbara's payments all came
from offshore accounts,
which were routed through
dummy corporations,
which have all gone
belly-up.
All right, skip to the end,
dragon tattoo.
They all lead
back to this guy?
Russell Wellington.
And according to
his personal records,
he had a-a car
that was reported stolen
the -- the week
of the accident,
a-a car that
was never recovered.
And after
the supposed "theft,"
he went on a sabbatical
from work for two weeks
and returned to work
with bruises and a broken ankle.
So this is him.
This is the man
who, uh...
And you're done.
Sam.
Hey, dudes. Dudes.
Secrets are bad.
Charlie, I don't think
you should be anywhere around
this piece-of-crap
salesman.
And -- and I don't think
that finding dark Charlie
and locking her up
is gonna work.
I mean,
she may be...dark,
but she's still
a part of you.
[ Sighs ]
You're right.
I hate it,
but you're right.
Okay. [ Sighs ]
Let's go to the bunker.
Baum used the key to Oz.
Maybe there's something
in the Men of Letters' files
about the key.
If we fix it,
we can get back to Oz.
All right,
you guys dig into that.
I'm gonna keep
an eye on Russell
and, uh...wait for
dark Charlie to show up.
Are you sure?
Dean, maybe --
maybe I should be the one...
No, no, no, no, no.
I got . It's, uh --
I just can't believe
I have to...
protect
this piece of crap.
No, you got to
protect them both.
I mean, if dark Charlie
gets hurt, then...
So do I,
so...be careful.
Got it.
Is he okay?
Uh...
I'll tell you on the way.
Come on.
Man:
The key to quieting your mind
is minding your quiet.
Know and understand --
the lack of an answer is --
[ muzak plays ]
Okay, here we go.
Clive Dillon.
He is the Man of Letters
that first discovered
the key to Oz.
So, according to
this incident report,
Clive went to Oz,
but he left the key on earth,
and then L. Frank Baum
found the key
and went to rescue Clive
in Oz.
That's when Dorothy
snuck along for the ride
and got stuck there.
Right.
And then after Baum
rescued Clive,
Clive came back
and retired.
You can retire
from the Men of Letters?
[ Chuckles ]
Well, apparently,
they put him
in some sort of,
like, uh,
witness-relocation program.
Where did he end up?
Let's find out.
Mr. Presley?
Yes. Yeah. Hi.
Uh, actually, I'm, uh,
you know,
really into this article
on, uh...
...mammograms.
Riveting stuff.
If somebody else
wants to go...
Right. Yes. Okay.
Well...let's do this.
[ Knock on door ]
Woman: Mr. Presley for you, sir.
Is that it for the day?
Yes, sir.
Okay. You can head out.
Uh, I need
my, uh, dry cleaning
taken to the lake house,
and, uh, pick up Pepper
and take her to
the dog groomers, okay?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Mr. Presley.
Russell Wellington.
Please have a seat.
[ Sighs ] So...
What can you tell me
about what you're looking for today?
Uh, right.
Well, um...
Let me describe
my dream home.
Charlie:
The Men of Letters
gave Clive
a new name, a new house,
both of which
are still listed.
I think Clive
might be still alive.
Y-- well, he'd be, like, 100-something.
[ Sighs ]
Time passes differently
in Oz.
It's close by.
Let's go look.
If he's still kicking,
he is the only person
who might be able
to fix the key to Oz.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
I'm not saying that
I have to have a jacuzzi.
I'm just saying that
I really like bubbles.
Uh, Mr. Presley,
look, I'm just gonna
stop you right there.
Judging from your cheap shoes
and your faded jeans,
I'm guessing
the only house
you're in the market
for comes with wheels.
Now, look,
I'm a busy man.
My time
is extremely valuable.
I prefer not to have it wasted
by some hayseed.
I'm willing to buy
if you're willing to sell.
So why don't you show me
what you got?
Well,
I can show you the door.
Who the hell
do you think you are?
I'm the guy
who's gonna save your life.
Excuse me?
Hill and Oak Street.
Station wagon with
a man and a woman in it,
on their way to pick up their
little daughter from a slumber party.
That ring a bell?
I-I-I-I don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, no, you wouldn't,
'cause you were too drunk
to remember anything
that night.
I think you have me confused
with somebody else.
Or somebody that cares.
Or maybe somebody
who wouldn't
pay people off
to cover up manslaughter.
You're insane.
What the hell
is going on?
Stay here.
Do not leave this room.
Dean: Charlie?
Let's talk about this.
You Winchester boys
and your talk.
Blah, blah, blah,
repressed feelings.
passive aggression.
Come on, kiddo.
You don't want to do this.
I don't want to hurt him.
I just want to talk.
Yeah, like you talked to
all the others?
You're right.
I got out of hand.
But this was never
about revenge.
Right.
I want him
to see my face.
I want him to see
what he did to me...
to us.
That's all.
Please, Dean.
I deserve that.
And then we hand him over
to the cops.
Okay.
[ Door opens ]
Mr. --
[ breathing heavily ]
Celeste.
No one's called me that
in a long, long time.
Uh...
I am so sorry.
What I did -- it...
I was young.
I was stupid.
What I took, I...
I can never
give back to you.
But what I did
after the accident,
that never
should have happened.
And I wasn't
drunk for that.
I was
stone-cold sober.
It was selfish...
and wrong.
And I should pay for it.
And I will pay for it.
You took
everything from me.
Please...
Celeste,
I am so sorry.
Russell?
I forgive you.
[ Cries ]
[ Gasps ]
Wh--
Charlie!
[ Sword plunges ]
Don't do this, Charlie!
[ Glass shatters ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Dean.
Hey, hold on.
I'm putting you on speaker.
[ Beeps ]
What happened?
Dean: It's over.
What do you mean,
"it's over"?
She got to Russell.
She killed him.
Oh, my God.
Charlie, if you can hear me,
I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's mine.
No, no, no. don't -- don't say that.
This is not on you.
All right, let's, uh --
let's try and stick to the plan, guys.
Did you guys find
a way back to Oz?
Maybe.
Uh, look,
t-the Man of Letters
who originally found the key --
he's still alive.
He lives in Junction City
under the name
Michael Carter.
I'll text you the address.
Just come meet us.
All right.
I'm on my way.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Tamara: Are you gonna stare
at that all night?
I'm pacing myself.
Charlie:
She's cute.
You lied to me.
You lied to yourself.
That's kind of your move.
Something's off about you,
though, isn't it?
It's always something
with you boys.
I've made mistakes.
But I'll pay for mine.
And you'll pay for yours.
Come on, Dean.
I'm not the monster here.
He was.
He got what he deserved.
You know I'm right.
You know what I learned
about being dark?
It sets you free.
And part of you knows
that's right, too.
[ Knock on door ]
Hello?
Clive Dillon?
No. My name is --
Sam:
Michael Carter, right.
But it was Clive Dillon,
wasn't it?
Back in the Men of Letters?
Back in Oz?
You seem to be confused.
There's no
Clive Dillon here.
And Oz?
[ Chuckles ]
That's just a fairy tale.
It's best left on the bookshelves
where it belongs.
So you've never seen
this before?
Enjoy.
Delicious.
All right, listen, dark Charlie.
Oh, grow up.
There's no right.
There's no wrong.
There's just us...
And them.
Yeah, well, there's not gonna be a you
for very much longer.
Uh-oh. Did princess me
find a way back to Oz?
That's right.
Yeah, a former
Man of Letters, retired,
in Grantville,
two towns over.
They're gonna fix
the key to Oz, find the wizard,
and put you back
to where you belong.
Back into Charlie?
Is that where I belong?
Well...
Hm.
We'll just see, won't we?
In the meantime...
...if you're not gonna
ask her to dance,
then I will.
What happened,
did my friend strike out?
Tamara: Your friend?
She just
left out the back door.
[ Engine turns over, revs ]
[ Tires screech ]
No, no, no, no!
Oh, you son of a bitch!
Damn it.
[ Beeping ]
[ Ringing ]
Sam?
Sam: Hey. Where the hell are you?
Dick Charlie
just hot-wired baby.
She thinks she's on her way to you.
What?
I told her the wrong town,
so I probably bought you
a little time,
but, uh,
just be on the lookout.
I'll be there as soon as I can Jack a ride.
Thanks. Hurry.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Ah.
The six keys of Oz
were forged
from Oz steel.
They can only be repaired
in that magical realm.
So there's
no going back?
I can't put
my darkness away?
I'm sorry.
What happened to you in Oz?
It's in my report.
Your report just said
you were kidnapped.
By whom?
Bad people.
I know that look.
You're lying.
And lying is --
bad.
Yes, I know.
What happened to you, my dear,
happened to me.
What?
A coven of witches grabbed me.
They used the inner key on me,
unleashed my ID.
He was awful.
He killed all the witches
and went into a tantrum.
Was power-hungry, crazy.
He became
the wizard of Oz.
Frank's daughter, Dorothy,
runs Emerald City now.
The wizard, dark you,
he is right by her side.
If -- if --
if she's in trouble --
Well,
without the key to Oz,
there's no way we can
get back to the wizard.
But...
There may well be a way...
to summon him here.
If I am
mortally wounded,
he'll have to come back here
to save us both.
Wait, wait, wait.
There has to be another way.
What he has done
is my fault.
After all, he is me,
and I am him, so...
Maybe it's time
that both of us
answered for our sins.
It's the good thing to do,
right?
Right?
[ Gunshot ]
[ Engine revs ]
I figured you'd lie about
where to go to next.
That's what I would do.
What the hell do you want?
I just want to talk to her.
Oh, you're not going anywhere near her.
I'm not gonna let you corrupt her.
Corrupt her?
You take one more step,
I'm gonna put you down.
There's the Dean I love.
[ Groaning ]
[ Rumbling ]
Aah!
What have you done,
you fool?
You had but one task --
stay alive.
And you couldn't even
manage that.
Aah!
You hit like a girl
who never learned how to hit.
[ Groans ]
Aah!
That's it, big boy.
Let it all out.
Ow! Ow!
[ Breathing shakily ]
[ Grunts ]
Stop this, please!
Let me help my friend.
Your friend
wanted to be a hero.
And you know what happens
to heroes?
They die.
[ Choking ]
You hurt my friend.
I learned it
by watching you.
[ Grunts ]
[ Screams ]
Aah! Ow!
I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
We both do.
[ Gasping,
panting ]
[ Crying ]
[ Grunts ]
Charlie, hang on.
Hey, you okay?
[ Crying ]
Dean! Dean!
You did it,
didn't you?
You killed the wizard.
I knew it.
The magic was in you
all the time.
Celeste.
Charlie.
Charlie. Hey. I got you.
It's okay.
[ Crying ]
Sam:
Yeah, he's, uh, he's better.
I mean,
he's calmed down now.
Cass, we got to --
we got to find Cain,
or...
We got to find something,
you know?
Right.
Yeah, I know.
I hear you. Okay.
You got it.
All right. Thanks.
Hey. Uh, shouldn't you
be resting up?
I think sleeping
for two days in a row
is probably enough.
[ Chuckles ]
So...are you...
Good? Bad?
I think I'll just settle
for balanced.
Anything
about the Mark?
Yeah, maybe.
I found this book.
It's a lore book --
"The Book of the Damned."
Sounds legit.
It's in a library somewhere in Tuscany.
It might be a dead end,
but I figured...
I'll go check it out.
Whoa.
Look, there's no
going back to Oz.
And with
the wizard gone,
Dorothy will be fine.
So, does this mean
no more adventure?
I think we have
all the adventure
we can handle
right here.
What about --
dark Charlie?
She's, uh...
Quiet.
[ Voice breaking ] I just got to
keep moving forward.
We all do.
Charlie, I...
Charlie: We are going to fix this.
I'm not letting what happened to
me happen to you.
But it's
already happened.
Cain found a way to live with it.
Right.
Yeah, after centuries of murder.
Yeah, well,
there's one thing
that you have that he didn't.
You're a Winchester.
I forgive you, Dean.
Yeah, well, I don't.
I know.
How's that
working out for you, huh?
I'm so sorry, kiddo.
Then prove it.
Be careful out there.
Does that sound like
either of me?
If I find something,
I'll call.
If not...
I'll just keep digging.
Charlie, thank you.
Arrivederci, bitches.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Door opens ]
You good?
[ Door closes ]
No.
She's right, Dean.
You can do this.
We can do this.
Then let's get to work.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man