Castiel:
Metatron took my grace.
Angels.
They're falling.
Miss me?
[ Gasping ]
Metatron,
you're mortal now.
Aah!
How do we get rid of the Mark?
[ Voice breaking ] I-i don't know.
What about the tablets?
No, there's nothing in them
about the Mark.
Shoot him.
[ Gun cocks ]
No, no! No.
your grace.
I'll take you to it.
Anything
about the Mark?
Yeah, I found this
"Book of the Damned."
I'll go check it out.
Charlie, thank you.
Arrivederci, bitches.
Rowena?
Not possible.
The Mark of Cain
never lets its host die easy.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Saving my son.
Mother says that Mark
is just a curse,
can be removed.
I'm good, thanks.
I don't buy that the Mark
is a terminal diagnosis.
There has to be a way,
and we will find it.
Okay.
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Gags ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Chuckles ]
Who the hell are you?
And why are you
following me?
[ Cajun accent ]
I ain't following you.
I'm following
what you got in your bag there.
That don't belong
to you, girl.
Belongs to my family.
Yeah?
Well, sorry, Gambit.
Finders keepers.
[ Laughs ]
[ Sighs ]
It's beyond
your understanding.
Hell,
you can't even read it.
Are you always
so condescending
when someone's pointing
a blade at you?
Now, you look here.
You can cut me down,
but my people will never stop.
And you can tiptoe
through the tulips
like you did
in Russia,
or you can stow away
on the back of a train
like you did in Alaska,
but soon enough,
my kin will find you.
This ends
with you being dead.
[ Sword clatters ]
[ Gunshot ]
Aah!
You can't run forever,
little girl!
? Supernatural 10x18 ?
Book of the Damned
Original Air Date on April 15, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ slow-tempo music plays ]
Man: Our flashback playback
continues
with a song that climbed
all the way to number four
on the charts.
Here's Alanis Morissette's
"Ironic."
[ Radio turns off ]
Really?
That song is a classic.
Yeah, I hear you.
I do.
And you're right.
Inclement weather
on the day of your nuptials
and the wrong cutlery
at inopportune times
is hardly ironic.
But it sure is catchy.
Yeah, fair point.
Can't argue taste.
But [Grunts]
since I became human,
it's just so...strange.
All these feelings,
you know?
I mean,
I can feel music.
Like that last song,
"Sussudio,"
I don't even know
what it's about and I love it.
I always enjoyed
lyrics, words, stories.
Gives me goose bumps.
And goose bumps --
don't even get me started
on those.
Creepy.
And yet...arousing.
[ Dialing, ringing ]
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Beeps ]
Cass.
Can I just kill him now?
You know I can hear you,
right?
No, we need him alive.
For now.
Look, after he gives you
your Grace back,
you can do whatever you want
with him.
Well, I'd like to kill him
slowly.
I am like two feet
from you.
Anything
on the Mark of Cain?
Every word --
crystal clear.
No.
I mean, I've been digging for
something, for anything, but...
I don't know, Cass.
There is an answer
out there.
We will find a cure
for Dean.
[ Scoffs ]
I don't know
why you'd want to cure
that little
firecracker now.
He's finally interest--
Ooh!
Well,
just keep digging.
Yeah, uh, no one here
by that name. Sorry.
[ Click ]
Sam?
Lose reception?
Or did he hang up
on you?
[ Chuckles ]
He hung up on you, didn't he?
Oh!
So, I've been checking
through everything again,
double-checking,
and triple-checking, and...
The Mark is a curse.
Yeah,
tell me about it.
No, Sam, it's a...
it's an actual curse.
What are you
talking about?
Crowley told me.
Or rather
Rowena told him
after she tried and failed
to kill me.
What the hell happened?
The Mark protected me.
Rowena doesn't really
have a beef with me.
She was pissed
at Crowley
because she thinks
he's going soft.
She's not wrong.
Yeah, well,
after he and mommy dearest
got into a fight --
Mommy dearest?
Rowena
is Crowley's mother.
More about that later.
So...
then he came and told me
what she had said.
The Mark
is an actual curse.
So, anyway, I'm sorry.
I probably
should've told you that.
Yeah.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Yeah, I know.
[ Beeps ]
Winchester accounting.
How may I help you?
Charlie: Dean.
Charlie?
What's going on?
Where are you?
Uh, uh, I'm exhausted
and -- and I'm bleeding.
And I'm in a phone booth.
A phone booth.
I didn't know
these things existed
outside of
"Bill and Ted's" --
Okay, hey, hey.
Take a deep breath, kiddo.
Uh,
we're both sitting here.
Tell me what happened.
Why are you bleeding?
I, uh -- I got shot.
Did you know dental floss
works great on stitches?
I only passed out twice,
and I'm pretty sure my wound
is now minty fresh.
Charlie, you probably
need to go to a hospital.
No, no, I-I'm fine.
I just got to get
someplace safe.
These guys are still after me.
[ Car door closes ]
What guys? Who?
[ Engine turns over ]
Some southern-fried D-bags.
They've been after me
since I-I dug up
"The Book of the Damned."
You found it?
Where?
After some near misses
and some broken-into museums,
I found
historical documents
that led to a monastery
in Spain.
It burned down years ago,
left for dead,
but, uh,
I had this hunch about it.
Turned out I was right.
Okay, Charlie,
what does it say about the Mark?
I have no fracking idea.
The language
it's written in,
I've never seen
anything like it.
I, uh --
I found some research notes
in the monastery crypt, though,
by the friar that buried it.
"The Book of the Damned"
is a spell book
for creating or undoing
any kind of damnation
there is.
We translate this thing,
I think we can get
the Mark of Cain off you, Dean.
Charlie, you're a genius.
[ Chuckles ]
A genius fugitive.
I -- these dudes following me,
they are well-trained.
One of them
keeps talking about his family.
Family?
Did you get a name?
No clue.
I-I-I spotted a tattoo
on one of them.
Might be a family crest.
It seemed occulty.
Soon as the book
was out of the ground,
they were all over me.
I, uh...
I don't know how much more
running I got left in me.
T-they're tracking
the book somehow.
All right, then we need to
get you off the grid, Charlie.
Where are you right now?
Uh, just south
of Des Moines.
Uh, okay, you know what?
Our -- our friend Bobby
has a whole bunch of cabins
scattered all around,
places for hunters to crash.
You know, it's not much,
but there's some gear
and lore books,
stuff to keep you busy till we get there.
Okay, bring snacks.
And every Men of Letters
decoder ring there is.
This book is old and scary,
and I've never seen
anything like it.
Hey, check it out.
I found this
in the storage room.
It's lead-lined
and warded.
If those guys are tracking
this book,
pretty sure this bad boy
will take it off the radar.
You ready?
[ Thin Lizzy's "The Boys
Are Back In Town" plays ]
[ Chuckles ]
? Ba Ba Ba Ba ?
What?
Nothing.
? guess who just got Ba-- ?
[ Radio turns off ]
Nothing.
I just haven't seen you like
this in a while, that's all.
It's a good song, man. Shut up.
Yeah, it's --
Look, man, it has been
one crap sandwich after another
for the past few weeks,
okay?
You heard Charlie.
We got a shot at fixing
this thing,
so if that don't put gas
in your tank, well...
If by "shot," you mean a spell
in a book that we can't read
that's currently
being tracked --
We're due for a win,
okay?
Overdue.
I'll tell you another thing,
if this actually does work,
we're gonna take
some time off.
What, like a vacation?
Mm-hmm.
And I'm not talking
just like a weekend in Vegas
or sitting in some crap motel
watching pay-per-porn.
No, I'm talking
about a beach.
Drinking Cervezas,
go for a swim,
mingle
with the local wildlife.
When was the last time
either one of us was on a beach?
Never.
Sand between our toes,
Sammy.
Sand between our toes.
? Back today ?
? them wild-eyed boys
that had been away ?
? haven't changed
that much to say ?
? but, man, I still think
them cats are crazy ?
? the boys are back in town,
the boys are back in town ?
? I said,
? the boys are back in town ?
Metatron: Mmm!
O...M...Me.
Oh.
Food.
Glorious food.
Mmm.
All the countless descriptions
in so many books,
but those are just words.
Oh.
The taste,
the -- the actual taste...
I had no idea.
Oh.
And the process --
goes in here...
comes out here.
Sorcery.
I mean,
you used to be human.
Don't you miss all this?
No.
I don't miss digestion.
I don't miss indigestion.
No, no, no.
Not that.
I mean, don't you miss
the feeling of all of this?
Like the taste
of these waffles.
The sound
of a child's laughter.
Look at us.
We're a couple of angels
who've touched
not only the divine,
but the mundane.
You and I have
a lot in common.
Don't.
What?
I thought
we were having a moment.
Can't we be besties?
No.
Because you killed
my friend.
Oh, pbht.
Dean is fine, mostly.
Can't you get past that?
Never.
Now, we've hit three
of your so-called safe houses,
and all of them are empty.
So either you've lost my Grace
or you're stalling.
Can you blame me?
The minute I hand over
your Grace, I'm dead.
You have made your bed,
Metatron,
and nothing
is going to get you out of it.
[ Stomach gurgling ]
What are you doing?
[ Grunts ]
I think I need to use
the little boys' room.
Little help.
[ Groaning ]
Quick. Oh.
[ Ducks quacking ]
Dean: Charlie?
[ Gasps ]
Merry Christmas!
Hey.
Were you followed?
No, no.
How you feeling?
Um...
I may have just passed out,
but better.
Where's the book?
Okay, here's what I've learned
so far.
About 700 years ago,
a nun locked herself away
after having
"Visions of Darkness."
After a few decades
squirrelled away by herself,
she emerged with this.
Each page is made
out of slices of her own skin
written in her blood.
I told you, it's eekish.
According to the notes
I found,
it's been owned and used
by cults, covens,
and the Vatican had it
for a while.
There's a spell inside
that thing for everything.
Talking some black mass,
dark magic,
end-of-times nastiness.
As far as what language
it's written in,
I'm thinking
it's some kind of, uh...
Sam: Dean? Dean!
What?
I don't think it's a good idea
that I touch this.
I'll go get the rest
of our crap.
Sam: Right.
[ Door opens, closes ]
What the hell was that?
He's not getting better.
He's trying to cover,
but...
We need to find
that cure, fast.
Metatron:
Sorry about the mess.
I guess
I'm lactose intolerant.
Let's never
speak of it again.
Metatron and Castiel.
[ Chuckles ]
This really must be
my lucky day.
Two birds, one blade.
Who are you?
Oh, just a cupid.
Just an angry,
angry cupid.
I understand
you're upset.
You both corrupted heaven.
It's never gonna be
the same!
Aaaaah!
I owed you that one,
anyway.
This changes nothing.
You're welcome.
Okay, I got a pretty good look
at his tattoo.
It's something
like this.
The douche clan.
Got it.
Well, this is everything
Men of Letters had on occult families,
so there should be something
in here.
Sam, got anything?
Maybe.
Uh, yeah, it's all in an obscure
Sumerian dialect.
Actually found a rough match
for it in this book.
Great.
I thought so, too.
But I've been translating,
but none of the translated words
make any sense.
It's all just gibberish.
I mean, maybe
it's in a different dialect?
No, no, no.
You're right,
but I-I-I think...
I think this is in code.
An entire book
of unreadable text
that's also in code.
Great.
And you call
yourselves nerds.
Come on.
You got this.
[ Scoffs ]
He's right.
You know what, Charlie?
Why, uh...
Um, why don't we stick with
my notes for a little bit?
This book is literally
making my eyes hurt.
What is it?
Shh.
Damn it.
[ Sighs ]
She found a way
to hide the book.
It was here.
It was on this road.
She was on this road.
[ Chuckles ]
Send the boys
up and down the way,
see if anybody saw her.
Castiel: Oh, come on.
You expect me to believe that
you hid my Grace in a library?
Metatron: Nobody goes
to libraries anymore.
It's the safest place
in the world.
I can feel my Grace.
It's here,
but you've hidden it somehow.
Where is it?
Honestly,
I have no idea.
Aa aah! Aah!
Where is it?
[ Screams ]
Oh! Gah!
I don't know, I swear!
I had another angel hide it,
even from me!
[ Screams ]
[ Grunts ] You know,
in case someone
tries to torture
the information out of me!
Case in point!
[ Groans ]
Where is my Grace?
I told the angel
to hide some clues
in some of
my favorite books.
Mother, may I?
[ Sighs ]
"What is the maddest thing
a man can do?"
It's a riddle?
What -- what's the answer?
Beats me.
I've only been a man a day.
Um, the -- the answer
to the riddle
will lead
to another book.
And inside that book,
you'll find your Grace.
[ Stammers ]
We're gonna work this out
together, okay?
Teamwork.
Okay, even the Bletchley Circle
couldn't crack this thing.
I've tried every cryptographic
algorithm there is.
Goose egg.
Well, maybe that's not
such a bad thing.
Those people
following you...
Hmm?
All kinds of wrong.
Talking multi-generational,
centuries-old wrong.
The Styne family.
Men of Letters' files have them
dated back to the early 1800s.
They used spells
to create disease,
to destabilize markets.
Hell, they even helped
the Nazis
before they came
into power,
and they profited
from all of it.
So, they're like
the supernatural Du Ponts?
Basically.
All the spells they used
came from a book
of "Unspeakable Evil,"
which they lost
nearly 100 years ago.
Okay, so they're bad.
So what?
We faced worse.
Sam, read the file.
The way the book works
is when you use it,
there is a negative reaction.
I'm talking
biblical negative.
Dark magic
always comes with a price.
We know that.
We've been down
that road before.
Well, let's at least
translate it, see what it says.
You guys
don't understand.
The book's been
calling out to me
ever since
I laid eyes on it, okay?
Calling out to the Mark.
I can hear it like it's alive.
It wants me to use it,
but not for good.?
Look, I wanted it to be
the answer, too, okay?
I really did.
But we have got to
get rid of that.
Burn it, bury it,
I don't give a damn.
We'll just have to find
another way to fix the Mark.
Like what?
I don't know.
So, you're giving up?
No, I'm not giving up.
Charlie,
I don't have a death wish.
Okay, even if I did,
I can't die,
not with this thing
on my arm.
What I can do is I can fight it
as long as I can until...
Until what?
Tell me.
Until what, Dean?
Until I watch you
become a demon again?
Until then?
I can't do that.
I won't do that.
Well, then you'll
just have to lock me up.
Bind me to the bunker
like you did last time.
That doesn't
solve anything.
Look, just let us translate
the book, okay?
If there's a cure,
we'll do it
and deal
with the consequences later.
I can't lose you.
Really?
Yeah, really.
You change your mind
on that,
'cause that's not what you said
last time.
Oh, come on, man.
You know I didn't mean that.
This is my cross
to bear, Sam.
Mine.
And that book
is not the answer.
Now, we got to destroy it
before it falls
into the wrong hands,
and that includes me.
I'm gonna go
for a drive.
Uh, Charlie, we forgot
to pick up your snacks.
Dean, look --
Dean: We'll figure out another way.
And, Sam,
I'll get my vacation.
But not today.
Not like this.
[ Door closes ]
[ Sighs ]
Sam.
Maybe he's right.
No.
No, there's a way to fix it.
There has to be.
You know,
we really do make a good team.
Kind of like a buddy comedy
without the comedy.
Or the buddies.
Oh, now, come on.
Back at the diner,
that was some pretty awesome
dynamic-duo action.
What we did back there
was unfortunate.
No more of our brothers
and sisters should die.
Brothers and sisters?
[ Laughs, snorts ]
Listen to you.
Still spitting out
the company line
like anyone cares.
[ Chuckles ]
Like we're actually
a family?
When what we really are
are a bunch of glowing lights
filled with self-loathing
or delusions of grandeur.
Or both.
You shut up.
No!
If I'm gonna die,
I want answers.
Like, who are you now?
Like, you're obviously not
an angel of the lord.
And what about
all of this
"walking the earth
like Kane from 'Kung Fu'" crap?
Cleaning up
heaven's messes.
How many more rogue angels
are there out there?
And what are you gonna do
once you're done with all that?
Go back to heaven?
Please.
The angel formerly known
as Hannah
has restored order up top.
Smoothest it's run
since God cut the ribbon
on the pearly gates.
So tell me, Castiel,
truly,
what is
your mission now?
You shut up
and keep looking.
Well...
cannot say...
I didn't try.
[ Grunting ]
[ Coughs ]
[ Clicks tongue ]
Poor Castiel.
Swam so far just to drown
in shallow waters.
Isn't it ironic?
Don't ya think?
[ sighs ]
What did Dean mean?
When he said
you changed your mind?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Laptop closes ]
So, a while back,
we had a chance to, um...
Close the gates of hell.
And in order to do that,
I would've had to die,
and I was okay with that
and I am okay with that,
but Dean was not.
And so he, uh...
He saved you.
Yeah, he saved me.
And let me guess,
in doing so,
he did something you didn't want
and that pissed you off.
And you said something
that hurt him?
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, that sounds
about right.
Brothers.
You know, I haven't been
a hunter for very long,
but it feels like
this is the life.
Mostly ends in Sophie's choices,
death, or tears.
Usually
all of the above, huh?
[ Chuckles ]
How did this
become my life?
I mean, I was gonna own
my own start-up, marry ScarJo,
invent something cool.
Now I'm just...
I'm just happy
to be alive.
You know, when Dean
came to get me at school,
I-I told myself...
One last job, you know?
One more job.
And then when --
when I, um...
When I lost Jess,
I, again, told myself,
one more job.
There's always one more job,
you know?
And one more job
and one more job,
and then I was gonna go back
to law and -- and to my life.
You were
the dread pirate Roberts
of hunting.
Yeah.
I guess I really understand
now that...
This is my life.
I love it.
But I can't do it
without my brother.
I don't want to do it
And if he's gone,
then I don't...
I-I got it.
I do.
Metatron: All right,
first things first --
find what I really
came here for.
"What two things do you need
to succeed in life?"
[ Laughs ]
Ignorance and confidence.
They're quotes.
So, uh...
[ Grunts ]
...did you and samateur hour
really think
I wouldn't have
a backup plan?
Ah. [ Chuckles ]
Hello, demon tablet.
[ Coughs ]
[ Groans ]
The places I'll go
with this.
[ Chuckles ]
And your Grace.
[ Grunting ]
Well, one out of two
ain't bad.
What's the maddest thing
a man can do?
Let himself die.
God just don't build to last,
does he?
[ Bell dings ]
Afternoon, sir.
Howdy.
There we go.
That'll be it for you?
Uh, yeah, that's it.
Okay, then.
That'll be $15.75.
You heading home,
or you just passing through?
[ Register beeps ]
Just passing through.
Must get awful lonely out here
all by yourself.
Oh, I get by.
Don't move.
Hands where I can
see them.
Don't you want
your change?
Now...
Who might you be?
Well, hello, there.
Where'd a back-road nothing
like you
get their hands
on something like that?
What's it to you,
Mr. Styne?
[ Chuckles ]
My friends call me Jacob.
Well, I ain't your friend.
Mm.
[ Chuckles ]
These wouldn't happen
to be treats
for a redheaded little gal,
now, would they?
Y'all hid the book,
didn't you?
Lead-lined little number,
I'm betting.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
You don't?
See that?
That man back there,
well, he said the same thing
as all the others
at truck stops and gas stations
up and down the way.
Nobody had seen
that redheaded girl.
And then a man bearing that Mark
comes in here, to me.
[ Laughs ]
Well,
there's coincidence,
and then there's
just Providence.
See, "The Book of the Damned,"
it wants to be found.
It wants to come home.
Let me guess.
You want to use it
to get that gift off your arm,
don't you?
Power is wasted
on the weak.
Now, the book...
can remove that Mark.
But you mess around
with that,
you're gonna do far more harm
than good.
So, why don't you do
the right thing here, boy,
and tell me
where that book is?
Yeah, sure, I'll tell you.
[ Grunts ]
[ Mumbles indistinctly ]
[ Chuckles ]
One more time.
I didn't hear you.
I said...
What's going on?
The Stynes,
they found me.
Those douches are all jacked up, too.
What are you talking about?
I emptied a full clip into one of them
before the son of a bitch went down.
Dean, what are you doing
with the holy oil?
There is a cure for the Mark
in the book.
But it comes
at a price.
We got to destroy it.
Are you sure about this?
It's calling to me,
Sam, okay?
I can hear it.
It's calling to the Mark.
It wants me to take the book
and run away with it.
Burn it, now.
Sam, burn it now.
[ Dean grunts ]
You silly boy.
[ Panting ]
I was foolish,
selfish.
Should've
just killed him.
Who knows what he'll do
with that tablet?
Well, you know what,
Cass?
You got your Grace back.
You're back.
You did
the right thing.
That book
needed to be destroyed.
We will find
another way, Sam.
[ Door opens, closes ]
[ Bottles clink ]
We're back, bitches.
Whoa.
Is that
who I think it is?
Charlie, Cass.
Cass, Charlie.
I thought
you'd be shorter.
I'm gonna get these
to the fridge.
Heard you got
your mojo back.
Yes, my -- my Grace,
it's -- it's been restored.
So, can't you just,
you know...
cure Dean?
Unfortunately,
it's not that simple.
Oh.
Never is, is it?
Do you think
you could do anything
about my carpal tunnel?
[ Chuckles ]
Is that it?
Your carpal tunnel
and your bullet wound
are now healed.
You may want to continue wearing
your wrist brace at night, though.
Did we just become
best friends?
[ Door opens, closes ]
Hey,
look who decided to show.
[ Chuckles ]
So? You're back?
100%?
How did that happen?
Um, it was Hannah.
She managed to get the location
of the remainder of my Grace
out of Metatron.
Awesome.
I told you we were due
for a win.
Good to have you
back, pal.
? No one knows what it's like
to be the bad man ?
? to be the sad man ?
? behind blue eyes ?
? no one knows what it's like
to be hated ?
? to be fated ?
? to telling only lies ?
? but my dreams,
they aren't as empty ?
? as my conscience seems to be ?
? I have hours ?
Sam: I don't trust you.
? Only lonely ?
and...I never will.
? My love is vengeance ?
but I need help.
? That's never free ?
and this is right in your wheelhouse.
Sam, burn it now.
? When my fist clenches,
crack it open ?
? before I use it
and lose my cool ?
? when I smile,
tell me some bad news ?
? before I laugh
and act like a fool ?
? and if I swallow anything evil ?
You silly boy.
? Put your finger
down my throat ?
? and if I shiver,
please give me a blanket ?
? keep me warm,
let me wear your coat ?
My family will never stop
looking for that book.
I need the Mark of Cain
off of my brother.
And something tells me...
you can crack this book
and find that cure.
? No one knows what it's like ?
The only question is...
? To be the bad man ?
...Will you help me?
? To be the sad man ?
? behind blue eyes ?
Shall we discuss terms?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man