Who are you, cops?
[ Grunts ]
You guys are “X-Files.”
Sure. Yeah.
You could say that.
Cain still has
the Mark, right?
So he's lived with it
for years.
The Mark is --
is strong.
Maybe you
have to fight that.
Dean, how do you think
angry spirits are born?
They can't let go,
and they can't move on.
Like wounded animals.
Lost. In so much pain,
they lash out.
Why?
Why are they here?
Well, there's some part
of them
that's keeping them here.
Some spirits
hold on too tight.
Dean, you haven't
left the bunker in a week.
And?
You can't just
live the rest of your life
locked up in this room.
Look, I know you're worried
about the Mark.
Yes, Sam. I am.
Do I wish
the Mark was gone?
Yes, of course.
Absolutely, I do.
We'll figure it out.
We always do.
Damn right.
[ Truck engine revs ]
[ The Avett Brothers'
“Head Full of Doubt/
Road Full of Promise” plays ]
You sure
you're okay to drive?
Not really.
[ Scoffs ]
But it's nothing
a little grease can't fix.
Trini, find me the nearest Taco Town.
Trini: Searching...
Ooh, I'm gonna get
a quesarito and a chi-chi melt.
Turn right in 50 feet.
Um, Billy, I don't think
this is the way to Taco Town.
What do you know?
Your phone's 3g.
Trini doesn't make
mistakes.
Continue for .3 miles,
then turn left.
[ Sighs ]
It's freezing.
Can you please turn off the air?
It's not on.
What the hell?
Trini doesn't make mistakes,
huh?
? There was a dream ?
Trini,
find a different route.
Proceed ahead.
Go screw yourself.
You go screw yourself.
Janet,
get out of the truck.
Um, how does she
know my name?
[ Deep voice ] Janet,
get out of the truck, now!
? With a head full of doubt ?
Oh, my God.
? So, I'll scream till I die ?
? and the last
of those bad thoughts ?
Help!
No, wait! Stop!
Aah! Billy!
No! No!
No! Help!
Billy!
Stop!
Destination dead ahead.
? There's a darkness upon me ?
aah!
? That's flooded in light ?
? Supernatural 10x13 ?
Halt & Catch Fire
Original Air Date on February 10, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Sam: Hey.
What in the world?
A croissookie.
A croissookie?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, they're the new cronuts.
Okay. So, what?
Half cookie, half --
Who gives a crap?
They're freakin' awesome.
[ Chuckles ]
What did Cass say?
Uh, good news,
bad news.
Bad news -- he discovered
riverboat gambling.
Good news -- he thinks
he might be closing in on Cain.
Oh, wow. Thinks he might be.
Yeah.
Just east of the Mississippi
somewhere in Illinois.
So, maybe Cass finds Cain
in the land of Lincoln.
And then what?
And then we get him to tell us
how to get rid of the Mark.
Don't you think that if Cain
knew how to remove the Mark,
he would have done it,
like, centuries ago?
We won't know
till we try.
Sammy, I appreciate the effort,
man. I do.
But trying to find
a cure for this thing,
I-it's like
a dog chasing its tail.
There's no end in sight
and you just end up dizzy.
Dean,
where there is a will --
There is a case.
Hmm?
Check this out.
“Iowa teen claims
possessed pickup kills driver.”
Let's say we take our own trek
to, uh, the Midwest.
[ Engine shuts off ]
So crazy.
Sorry
I ever made you leave.
[ Chuckles ]
God,
they're everywhere.
Uh, which one of you
is Janet Novoselic?
I am.
Agents Grohl and Cobain.
Bye.
I already talked to the police
like nine times.
Yeah, no, this is, uh --
it's, uh, just a follow-up.
Yeah.
[ Sighs ]
I have finals tomorrow.
Then we'll make it fast.
I promise.
Janet: It's like
I told the detective.
I was drunk,
but I wasn't hallucinating.
The truck had
a mind of its own.
How so?
Like, the air went
full blast
even though it wasn't on
and the radio went crazy,
and so did Trini.
And Trini is...?
[ Scoffs ]
You have to excuse my partner.
When it comes to technology,
he is a little behind.
Uh...
He just learned
how to poke on Facebook.
Uh, um, Trini is
the nav app we were using.
It -- it's like
a talking map.
You're Gen X.
Right.
Okay, so, Trini
and everything else in the truck
went all “Christine.”
Who's Christine?
It's a Gen X thing.
Look.
I don't expect you
to believe me.
But I swear that truck
was hell-bent on killing Billy.
Did Billy have
any enemies?
Anybody who might have had
a beef with him?
Maybe his brother Joey.
They fought all the time.
It's so sad.
They never got to
set it right.
Because Billy died.
No.
Joey did.
In Afghanistan.
Do you know
where he's buried?
He's not.
Poor guy never came home.
I.E.D.
Did Billy happen to have
anything of his brother's
on him when he died?
Uh, dog tags, a hat,
something?
Just his pickup.
So, the truck belonged
to Joey?
Yeah.
It was his pride and joy.
Billy got it when he died,
and, you know, it's a thing.
Yeah.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Excuse me a sec.
So -- so,
what's a thing?
You know,
the truck thing.
You honor the deceased
by driving their truck.
Sam, they wrote
a whole country song about it.
Why don't you Google it?
All right, so,
we're looking for something
that used to resemble
a pickup truck.
All right.
Hey.
Here we go.
[ Train whistle blares
in distance ]
Yeah, marine.
I'm guessing
this ain't oil.
That is ectoplasm.
Huh.
Look at this.
[ Warbling ]
Joey?
Looks like it.
Yeah.
All right, so,
big brother didn't get along
with little brother,
was pissed
that he was driving his baby.
I get it.
What are you saying?
If you died and I drove
your car, you'd kill me?
If you stunk her up
with tacquitos, probably.
All right.
Let's do this.
Makes it looks like a-a pool
in Reseda.
[ TV shuts off ]
Ugh. I can't believe our
art history final's tomorrow.
I know.
This semester,
like, totally flew by.
Yeah. Time flies
when you're drunk.
[ Laughs ]
Want to come to the library
with me?
I still have
so much to memorize.
And I thought looking at pictures
of naked guys was gonna be easy.
Thanks, but I don't
really need to study for it.
I have a photographic memory.
#blessed.
Um, you don't need
to study for it
because you're screwing
the T.A.
#slut.
[ Scoffs ]
[ Pop music playing
in distance ]
[ Camera shutter clicking ]
[ Computer chiming ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Panting ]
[ Computer chimes ]
[ Panting continues ]
[ Shrieks ]
Aah!
[ Choking ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Coughing ]
Oh, my God.
Hey.
I'm not gonna make it.
[ Sighs ]
Focus.
Delilah Marian -- the roommate
found her this morning
after an all-nighter
at the library.
Strangulation?
Sicko used the power cord
from the computer.
Suspects?
None yet.
The odd thing was
the door was locked.
Hmm.
Have you talked to any of
the other girls who live here?
Well, most of them have
already left for spring break.
But the roommate
was really helpful.
She gave us
all of Julie's passwords.
And nowadays, the only way
to find out anything
about teenagers
is through social media.
Trust me.
I got two of them.
Excuse me, agents.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Revengeful spirit,
much?
Yeah, but is it Joey's
or another ghost?
I don't know.
[ Warbling ]
So, first it possesses
a -- a truck,
and then it possesses
a computer?
Both machine-related
kills.
So, what?
You think we're dealing with
a “Ghost in the Machine”?
Maybe.
But if it is the same ghost,
I mean,
they usually anchor themselves
to a place or a thing.
How is this one jumping
from one machine to the next?
Sam: We really appreciate
your help, Delilah.
We know this
can't possibly be easy.
Did Julie, by chance,
know a student named Billy Bass?
Everyone knew Billy.
He was the president
of Sigma Theta Delta.
STD?
Yeah.
It's the biggest frat
on campus.
Did, uh -- did Julie know
Billy's brother Joey,
the -- the soldier?
I don't think so.
I didn't even know
Billy had a brother.
Did she have any enemies?
Any reason why someone
might want to hurt her?
No.
Julie was really popular,
super-sweet.
I can't imagine
anyone wanting to hurt her.
You know
we're federal agents, right?
Lying to us
is a big-time offense.
I'm not lying, Agent.
There's just...
nothing else to tell.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
All right [Clears throat]
And a caf? Au lait
for the lady.
For me --
a heart attack?
[ Chuckles ]
This is unreal.
Look at this. I got Italian.
I got Chinese.
Serve-yourself froyo.
College is better
than Vegas.
What do you got?
Unfortunately,
a -- a lot of nada.
I-I...
I hit up Julie's Facebook,
Instagram, Twitter,
Instachat,
Snapchat, A.I.M.,
nothing but posts on Rush
and “Fifty Shades of Grey”,
the movie, not the book.
Yeah,
I didn't get half of that.
[ Chuckles ]
It doesn't matter.
Now I'm going through
her deleted files.
You can do that?
Yeah.
Hmm.
I mean, nothing ever really
gets deleted from the Internet.
You knew that, right?
Yeah.
[ Chuckles ]
All right.
Here we go.
This might be something.
It's a, uh -- it's a deleted
Instachat from last night
right around
time of death.
With who?
With princesselsa8.
Look at this.
“Liar.”
“I know.”
“you'll pay.”
Well, this princesselsa's
a bitch.
What is 810?
810?
Yeah.
Uh, it's a...
I don't know.
Maybe it's a date.
Maybe it's a time of day.
Or an area code.
Uh, area code
is for southeast Michigan.
You know what?
[ Keyboard clacking ]
Here we go.
Uh, there are
three address in Spencer
that have “810” in them.
I'll see
if I can get this to go.
[ Sighs ]
Sam: Yeah. You got it.
Thank you, Detective Petranzyk.
We will keep in touch.
[ Engine shuts off ]
So, princesselsa8
is not some crazed cyber killer.
She is a third grader
from lake Nebagamon, Wisconsin,
who is obsessed
with “Frozen.”
and she was fast asleep
when the Instachat occurred.
So, a hack job.
That's what I'm thinking.
[ Door opens ]
[ Sighs ]
Excuse me, ma'am.
May we, uh,
ask what you're doing?
Um, throwing away dead flowers.
Is that a crime?
Well, it's not a crime,
just a little strange,
uh, seeing as how
they aren't dead.
[ Sighs ]
It's not so strange when it
feels like they're taunting you.
My husband was killed
in a car accident here
nine months ago.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Our condolences.
Thank you.
We were newlyweds.
[ Sighs ]
Never even made it
to our first anniversary.
And to have to be
reminded of that
every time I look out
my window or leave the house...
Understandable.
Forgive me,
but did you notice anything...
weird after
your husband's death?
Any strange disturbances
or...?
I'm not sure
what you mean.
It's nothing.
Never mind.
Any idea
who's leaving the flowers?
Some teenage girl.
I think she goes
to the college
'cause she's always
in Greek letters.
Do you know her name?
No.
Uh, she has
long red hair.
Dean:
This is Agent Grohl again.
Listen, I know I told you
to call
at your earliest convenience,
but scratch that.
Call A.S.A.P.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Sighs ]
Look at this.
Uh, Andrew Silver,
“29-year-old
Spencer high-school teacher
“killed in fatal accident.
“Uh, car burst
into flames.
“Silver's body
was burned beyond recognition.
And he is believed to have been
killed upon impact”.
Okay.
So, Andy the angry ghost --
he dies at 810 Downs Drive.
And then he torments Julie
with 810 on her computer.
So,
what's his beef with her?
Yeah, and what's
his connection to Billy?
Does it say
where he's buried?
He wasn't.
He was cremated.
So, no bones,
and he's not tethered
to any object that we know of.
Yeah. How is Andrew
haunting his victims?
Are you gonna eat
all that?
Yeah.
You want some?
[ Beeping ]
Delilah: The feds called...
Like three times already.
Kyle,
are you listening to me?!
I think they know.
Maybe it's time
we should come clean.
Uh,
that's not gonna happen.
Look where
keeping our mouths shut got us.
I think it's karma.
Maybe we're being cursed
or something.
I don't know.
First Billy, now Julie?
Look.
It totally sucks
that Billy and Julie died.
But it's just a crappy
coincidence, not a curse.
If we don't do something,
I'm worried --
Delilah, stop.
I'm serious.
You better
keep your mouth shut
or you're gonna have a lot more
than a curse to worry about.
[ Rock music plays in distance ]
Hells yeah.
“Where are you?”
[ knock on door ]
Was that you?
Nah. [ Chuckles ]
What a tease.
[ Door slams ]
[ Cellphone rings, beeps ]
Hello?
Demonic voice:
What time is it?!
[ Music continues ]
[ Volume increases ]
Who the hell is this?!
Aah.
[ Groans ]
Lower the tunes, brah!
Trying to study!
[ Volume intensifies ]
Aah!
[ Groaning ]
Are you okay?
Not really.
[ Door opens ]
Hey.
What do you got?
Death by decibel.
What?
Kyle's brains
were jellied by his speakers.
Oh, and get this. The, uh --
the clock on his stereo
stopped at 8:10.
8:10?
Yeah.
Again?
Mm-hmm.
[ Sobs ]
Look, we know you're
the one leaving the flowers.
So, why don't you
just tell us
what happened the night
of Andrew Silver's accident?
Uh...
Delilah, please.
This is the third death
in five days.
Who knows
who's gonna be next?
I am.
The car accident...
Wasn't exactly
an accident.
? Take me to church ?
? I'll worship like a dog
at the shrine of your lies ?
Dude, I just
retweeted your Tweet.
Dude,
I just favorited yours.
Julie: [ Chuckles ]
Okay, here.
Oh, selfie.
? Good god,
let me give you my life ?
? take me to church ?
o-m-g.
Delilah: [ Laughs ]
I am such a hag!
I look like I'm 25.
Oh, that's what
filters are for.
Ugh! Ew. Delete.
[ Chuckles ]
Billy: Check this. Wait.
Okay, wait. Here. Again.
Come on.
I'm sending it to you, dude.
Here.
[ Horn blares ]
Let's do one more so I can --
[ tires screeching ]
Oh, my God.
Billy, call 911.
[ All breathing heavily ]
Call 9-- call 911.
Aah!
No. No!
[ Girls screaming ]
[ Tires screeching ]
What the hell
are you doing?
I'm getting out of here
before the cops come.
We -- we just killed
that guy.
No. Hey, you're not
calling the cops!
'Cause I already have
a D.U.I.,
and if they find out I'm driving
on a suspended license,
I'm going to jail.
Come on, Billy.
This isn't right.
Help me out here, guys.
It's not our problem, Dee.
What?!
Someone else
will call the cops.
Not a word.
You hear me?
[ Voice breaking ] I shouldn't
have let them talk me out of it.
It was wrong.
And now
we're being punished.
Seriously,
what are the chances
that three out of the four of us
die in one week?
It can't be a coincidence.
Sam: It's not a coincidence.
It's a ghost.
Dean: It's the vengeful spirit
of Andrew Silver.
A ghost?
Yeah.
They're real.
Yeah, it's sort of
what we do.
So, you're,
like...Ghostbusters?
Sure.
First things first, though.
You need to stay
inside this salt circle
while we take care of him,
okay?
How do you
take care of him?
Please tell me you know
how to take care of him.
Usually a ghost is tied to
a place or an object.
You get rid of the object,
you get rid of the ghost.
But with Andrew,
it's, uh...
It's different.
What's he tied to?
We're working on it.
But if we can figure out
how he's traveling,
we can figure out
how to stop him.
You know, this might be
a shocker situation.
The paper said
that he died from a collision,
but Delilah says
that he died from electrocution.
So maybe
that's how he's surfing.
He's using the power lines
as a conduit.
I mean,
that would make sense
with the computer and stereo
kills, but not the pickup.
I mean,
the truck runs on gas.
All right, it's got to be
something else, then.
[ Sighs ]
All right, I'll go back to
the accident site, check it out.
Stay here with her.
Yeah.
[ Door opens ]
[ Lock clicks ]
[ Sniffles ]
Thanks.
You getting tired?
No.
I'm used to it.
I stay up all night
studying.
Mostly to avoid
the nightmares.
My mom's thrilled with my GPA,
but I'm just...
miserable.
I think about Andrew
all the time.
And I've never
even met the guy.
[ Dog barks in distance ]
It's pretty crazy to obsess
about someone you've never met.
It's not that crazy.
The truth is,
I can relate.
Really?
I have made more mistakes
than I can count.
Ones that haunt me
day and night.
So...how do you deal?
Whiskey.
[ Sighs ]
Denial.
I do my best
to make things right,
whatever that may be.
For you, maybe it's...
maybe it's coming clean.
You know, finding a way
to ask for forgiveness.
But not breaking the bank
at your local florist.
I mean...real forgiveness.
You can't just bury
stuff like this.
You got to deal with it.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Beep ]
Hey.
What do you got?
Dean, Andrew's not using
power lines to move.
He's using Wi-Fi.
Come again?
The -- the wires
that electrocuted Andrew,
they -- they feed directly
into a Wi-Fi tower
right across the street.
So, even ghosts
are online?
Apparently.
I mean,
it would explain the truck kill.
Billy's cell must have been
using the local Wi-Fi signal,
so, uh, Andrew's ghost must have
just hopped on to Trini,
that -- that --
that nav app.
And then Julie's death
by computer,
Kyle's death by stereo
with the wireless speakers.
I mean,
it makes sense, Dean.
We're all just a bunch of
electrical impulses, right?
So, whenever Andrew died,
his impulses just transferred
to another current.
You got to get Delilah
somewhere safe.
Turn off all the routers
in that sorority.
Oh, yeah. Sure, Sammy.
We'll just kill the Internet.
Wait, can we?
Uh, no. No, not really.
Oh.
All right, so, then how the hell are
we gonna deal with the lawnmower man?
You know what?
I have an idea.
Do what I said.
Stay safe.
I'll call you back.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
You know
where the routers are?
I have no idea.
[ Electricity buzzing ]
Aah!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Is that gonna work?
Worth a try.
No!
Need you to turn off everything
that's connected to Wi-Fi.
Aah!
[ Knock on door ]
Hey.
Uh, I'm so sorry
to bother you, Mrs. Silver,
but I have an emergency
and I really need your help.
Now, this
is gonna sound strange.
It's my husband,
isn't it?
Come in.
Come on. Let's go.
Where are we going?
Someplace that doesn't have
a Wi-Fi signal.
[ Gasps ]
The basement.
The reception sucks
down there.
All right, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go.
Run.
I thought the salt
didn't work.
Because of the Wi-Fi.
There's no signal down here.
There's no computers.
There's no tablets.
There's no cellphones,
so Andrew can't bypass it.
At least,
I don't think he can.
It wasn't too long
after the accident
that Andrew
started contacting me.
Contacting you how?
Online.
[ Sighs ] At first,
I thought it was just a joke,
that someone was playing
a cruel prank
on a grieving widow.
But Andrew knew things,
things that only
he and I would know --
inside jokes,
the code to our alarm,
my obsession
with Lifetime movies.
[ Sighs ]
It was then that I knew
I had my husband back,
even if
it was just online.
Did you never think
to ask him what he was?
Come on, Agent.
I've read the books.
I've seen the movies.
I knew he was a ghost
or something, but...
I didn't care.
He was my husband.
And...it was great.
Romantic, even.
He'd send me love notes.
We'd stay up all night
reminiscing.
But then
he started acting strange.
What do you mean,
strange?
I don't know.
He'd just disappear,
radio silence.
And then out of nowhere,
he'd start e-mailing again.
But he was different,
focused.
He was focused on what?
Revenge.
When the kids at the college
started dying,
I thought
it might be Andrew.
But what
was I supposed to do?
Call the cops and tell them
the ghost of my dead husband
was picking off co-eds?
But mostly...
...I just didn't want
to face the truth.
Because I knew it was revenge
that brought him back,
and if I tried to stop him
that he might go away.
And I didn't want
to lose my husband again.
Just try to stay calm,
all right?
[ Muffled buzzing ]
What was that?
I don't know.
[ Buzzing continues ]
Aah!
[ Grunts ]
Please don't kill me.
We didn't mean to hurt you.
It was an accident,
I swear.
If I could do it
over again,
I would have done
the right thing.
[ Choking ]
Let's go.
Where?
The door.
It's locked.
Andrew, listen to me.
You have
every right to be pissed.
But take it from me...
[ Keyboard clicking ]
...the more you kill,
the crazier you'll get.
The blood fuels the rage.
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
So, it looks like to me
you've got two choices.
You can keep killing
and become something
that you won't recognize
or you can move on
'cause that is the only thing
that is gonna give you peace.
So, it's up to you, man.
Pain or peace.
Aah!
[ Grunts ]
Corey: Andrew?
It's Corey.
Please listen to me.
You have to stop this.
Revenge -- it's hollow.
And it's pointless.
It won't bring you back.
I should have said this
earlier...
But I couldn't let go.
But it's time...
for me to let go
and for you to do the same.
Please.
I'm begging you.
[ Gasps ]
Do this for me.
Do it for us.
Goodbye.
[ Sighs ]
[ Sighs, sniffles ]
[ engine shuts off ]
You sure
you want to do this?
[ Sighs ] Yeah.
I should have done this
a long time ago.
Come in.
Looks like Andrew wasn't
the only one who chose peace.
Yeah. Looks like.
I think
I'm gonna follow his lead, too.
What do you mean?
My peace
is helping people.
Working cases.
That's all
I want to do.
Is this about the Mark?
I'm done
trying to find a cure, Sammy.
Dean, Cass is so close.
To what?
We don't even know
if there is a cure.
So far,
we've got nothing.
We have found nothing
at the Men of Letters library,
Metatron may or may not
know something,
and maybe Cass is
onto something with Cain --
maybe.
Yeah, maybe.
Nothing is guaranteed, Dean.
So what?
We can't
just stop fighting.
Yes, we can.
So, this is it.
Y-you're just gonna --
you're just gonna give up.
No. No, I'm not
just gonna give up.
I appreciate the effort, okay?
I do.
But the answer
is not out there.
It's with me.
I need to be the one
calling the shots here, okay?
I can't keep waking up
every morning
with this false hope.
I got to know
where I stand.
Otherwise,
I'm gonna lose my freakin' mind.
So, I'm gonna fight it
till I can't fight it anymore.
And when
all is said and done...
I'll go down swinging.
[ Engine turns over ]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man