? Your love has set
my soul on fire ?
? burnin' out of control ?
We're in this together.
? You taught me
the ways of desire ?
? now it's takin' its toll ?
No!
? You're
the right kind of sinner ?
? to release my inner fantasy ?
How's that stolen Grace
inside you working out?
? And you know
that you were born to be ?
It's the bloody mark of Cain.
? You're a heartbreaker ?
Magic that powerful comes
at a price,
and right now we don't know
what that price is.
? You're a heartbreaker,
dream maker ?
Drop the blade.
? Love taker,
don't you mess around ?
? no, no, no ?
First time
I touched that blade,
I knew that I wouldn't
be stopped.
I'm starting to think the
blade is doing something to you.
? You're
the right kind of sinner ?
? to release my inner fantasy ?
? the invincible winner ?
? and you know
that you were born to be ?
? you're a heartbreaker ?
? dream maker ?
? love taker, heartbreaker ?
No!
Open your eyes, Dean.
Let's go take a howl
at that moon.
I heard the rumors.
I said,
“No, that can't be.
A Winchester?
One of us?”
but it's
isn't it?
Whatever soul you had,
whatever boy scout code
you cuddled up to at night,
it's all gone.
Leaving what?
Look at you.
Where is Crowley?
Eat me.
Mm.
Aah!
One more time.
Where is Crowley?
Where's my brother?
I don't know!
Then you're gonna call somebody
who does.
No one knows!
T-they won't answer!
Make the call.
We're under orders!
Make the call!
Please.
Where's my brother?!
? Supernatural 10x01 ?
Black
Original Air Date on October 7, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Right, right.
So, no noticeable crop failures,
no mass cattle DEA
ING?
No. Nothing on the
radar. Nothing on the scope.
I'd say that's a good thing.
No, yeah, yeah, yeah
you're right.
I-I hear you Mike.
Thanks.
That is a good thing.
All right.
Well, keep me posted
if anything does pop up.
All right, watch yourself,
Sam.
Yeah, I will.
You got it.
Thanks.
Sam. Hello.
I think I might've found something.
Oh, good.
Good.
Cass?
You there?
It's okay.
I'm -- I'm okay.
Uh, go -- go on.
Okay, get this.
A John Doe who was murdered
in Wisconsin a week ago
turns out to be this guy
named Drew Neely
who went missing
from some religious order
in Northern Ohio, okay?
Yeah.
Now, Drew Neely has been missing
for three years.
Killed his wife,
his kids,
and...just disappeared.
I know it's thin...
...but if this guy
possessed...
Well, that would make him
the first --
The first lead,
the first anything
we've seen in...
Sorry.
Actually,
you know what?
Now that I'm looking
at this more,
I-I think I, uh --
I think
I jumped the gun here, buddy.
No, Sam, you said
it was something.
Yeah.
Uh, it's --
it's not.
I was wrong.
Sorry.
I can help.
Cass.
We tried that.
Sam, you can't blame
what that demon did
to your shoulder on -- on me.
You were out of --
I'm not, okay?
I'm not blaming anything
on you.
What happened...happened.
And...
You need to be worrying
about yourself.
I-I really shouldn't
have bothered you.
How are you, Sam?
I'm good.
I-I'm all right.
I'm just tired,
you know?
I'll be better
when we get him back --
a-after I kick his butt.
I miss him.
Yeah.
Why would he just
disappear?
Who says
he had a choice?
Well, then who wrote
the note?
You think
there's any chance...
Any chance at all
that Dean is still --
still
even remotely Dean?
? I'm too sexy for my love,
too sexy for my love ?
? love's going to leave me ?
? and I sexy for my shirt,
too sexy for my shirt ?
? so sexy it hurts ?
? And I'm too sexy for Milan,
too sexy for Milan ?
- Turn it off!
- Get off the stage!
Everybody!
Oh!
Okay.
Wow.
What time is it?
Darryl's gonna kill me
if I'm late from my break again.
Mm.
Oops.
Damn!
I told you
to hurry it up.
But then you had to go
and do that thing
with the...thing.
Oh, you mean that thing
that you were begging me for?
Begging you to hurry it up,
maybe.
Well, let's not argue
about good sex.
It was good, wasn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Just, uh...don't get
too excited, you know?
Or...too attached.
'Cause I'm just
rollin' through.
You know, there's about
a million other ways
you could have said that.
Whoa!
“Whoa”?
What's going on here?
What's it look like?
In my bed?
What?
Oh, yeah.
Jerk.
Bitch.
Get a room, you two.
Had a room
till you two soiled it.
Love you, Crowley.
Love you more,
sweetheart.
Anne Marie,
jackass.
Knew that.
Pants?
Best of three.
Losers buy the beer.
Lots of beer.
Girl seemed nice.
Slightly damaged.
I could see the old you
falling for that.
Yeah, well,
not to worry.
She means nothing.
Good, good.
'Cause you and I,
we're rolling stones.
No distractions.
Lock it down.
Stop talking.
You're bodging it!
Aw.
If you'd
shut up --
keep talking --
I can't play the game.
Come on, we'll talk
about it. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Hang on.
Get off me.
Why are you doing this
to me?!
You need to calm down.
Where were you?
Stop it!
Hey, is this him?
There a problem?
Yeah, are you Matt?
Dean!
You need to get away
from here.
Don't try
and contact her.
In fact,
don't even think about her.
You understand me?!
Just a moment.
Castiel.
Hannah.
I'm sensing awkwardness.
So...There's no --
no leader?
You're governing
yourselves?
Mostly.
There's lot of meeting
on rebuilding
and reorganization --
lots of reconciliation.
And Metatron?
Still in jail.
His door has been made
permanent.
I would've thought
we'd see you sooner.
I would've come sooner
but --
I'm glad you didn't.
You see, I...
I need your help.
Heaven needs your help.
Anything.
Most of the angels
who fell during the fall
have returned to heaven.
A few have not.
Some out-and-out refuse.
Rogues.
Two of them have killed
one of our own
for only attempting
to bring them back home.
Who were they?
Daniel and Adina.
They must be found.
They must be brought home,
and they must be punished
for the sake of all.
Will you help me?
Yes.
Appreciate you coming down,
agent.
But I'm afraid you may have just
cost Uncle Sam a tank of gas.
Oh, why's that?
You came up here to investigate
Drew Neely's murder, right?
Right.
Problem is, no one's certain
it was a murder at all.
Okay, then what are
we dealing with here?
A suicide?
Self-defense, more likely.
Uh, the surveillance footage
was corrupted.
Our techies finally managed
to clean up the file.
Hold on a sec now.
We can do this
however you want.
Don't pretend I didn't see you
this afternoon.
Did you get a good look?
You see my moves?
I hope so, 'cause I sure could
use the competition.
That John Doe right there
is the one you want to
keep your eye on.
Son of a bitch.
Watch.
Well, all you Abaddon groupies
are the same, you know that?
You, the douche that jumped me
at the gas station,
you can't just can't accept
that the queen is dead, can you?
Maybe we just can't accept
that a douche like you was
the one who killed her.
Ah.
Yeah, that's got to hurt,
doesn't it?
Okay, now, porn guy's just
minding his own business.
And there's Drew Neely.
See the knife?
Yeah.
That's intent
right there.
Now watch this.
Aah!
Looks like a cutlass
or something.
I don't know
what the hell this is.
Problem is,
we don't know
if this guy's a hero
or a psychopath.
That's the image that's getting
uploaded to the wires.
Detective,
do you mind if I, uh,
take another look
at this?
Knock yourself out.
I'll be back
in a few.
All right.
Fax, Dad.
Who's it from, buddy?
Doesn't say.
There's a picture.
Thanks a lot, bud.
Is it him?
I didn't know angels
could get nauseous.
I just need a moment.
It's my fault.
I'll take the curves faster.
And you, Castiel?
You're feeling well?
Oh, yes.
Like a million dollars.
That's not true.
It's my truth.
When you left heaven,
your borrowed Grace was failing.
By the looks of you,
you've only gotten worse.
I'm fine.
You're dying, Castiel.
You need more Grace.
And we have a mission
in front of us
that supersedes my needs --
all of our needs.
Don't you agree?
You're a good soldier,
Hannah...
And one of the best.
Metatron certainly could not
have been brought to heel
without your bravery.
Or yours.
You must take care
of yourself, Castiel.
And another angel should die
so that I can be saved?
Is this really
that hard to understand?
Hannah.
I'm feeling better now.
Oh, yeah.
Porn guy was an animal.
Bro came at him like,
“what?!”
and he was all like,
“wh-a-a-at?”
“say my name!
Say my name!
Say my name.”
And there was
a lot of blood.
Right.
Um...
When the guy,
uh -- when --
When...
“Porn guy” came in,
did he...say anything?
“W-where's the porn”.
That's all he said?
Did he buy anything?
Did he -- did he use
a credit card?
Nothing?
So some guy comes in,
kills another guy
in your store on your watch,
and you just --
you what?
Just keep on keepin' on?
You mean when porn guy was
stabbing the other guy to death
10 feet in front of me,
and I was having
a total code-brown moment
in my favorite freakin' pants
because I thought I was next,
did I conduct
a field interview?
No.
Oh, hey.
Uh, can you do me a solid?
Found this wedged
under the T.P.
I think
it's the dead guy's phone,
and, uh, if you're
heading back to the station...
You're dead.
Nope.
Just using
a dead man's phone.
Moose.
Took you long enough.
Your brother and I
were beginning to wonder
if you'd hit another dog.
You know?
My brother is dead,
Crowley.
I know you have
some freaking demon
parading around
in his meatsuit,
and trust me,
you are gonna pay for that.
Moose. Moose.
I'm afraid you haven't
allowed yourself
to dream
quite big enough here.
Your brother is very much alive,
courtesy of the mark.
And the only demonized soul
inside of Dean
is his and his alone.
Wee bit more twisted,
a little more mangled
beyond human recognition,
but, I can assure you,
all his.
There, now.
Feel better?
And the, uh, Abaddon supporters
you've been sending
to kill my brother,
how does Dean feel
about that double-cross?
If that's
what you think is happening,
then you're more out of
your depths than I thought.
I don't know
how you did this,
what kind of...
Black-magic stunt you pulled,
but hear me --
I will save my brother
or die trying.
You know what tickles me
about all this?
It's what's really
eating you up.
You don't care
that he's a demon.
Heck,
you've been a demon.
We've all been demons.
No,
it's that he's with me
and he's having
the time of his life.
You can't stand the fact
that he's mine.
He's not your pet.
My pet?
He's my best friend,
my partner in crime.
They'll write songs about us,
graphic novels.
“The Misadventures
of Growley and Squirrel.”
Dean Winchester
completes me,
and that's what makes you
lose your chickens.
I am going to find you,
I am going to save
my brother,
and then
I'm going to kill you dead.
Well, that's
the operative phrase, isn't it?
“Find you.”
good luck with that.
Daniel.
What
are you fishing for?
Trout, mostly.
They do love
a good curlytail grub.
Trick is to find
that special spot
just outside the run,
where the big ones --
the smart ones --
are holding low.
Do they -- do they put up
much of a fight?
The ones
who truly want to be free?
They do.
You're here
about our brother who died.
Does that surprise you?
I can assure you...
Had he just left us alone,
no one would've been harmed.
His orders were
to not leave you alone.
And you killed him.
And heaven sends
two more.
What is it
about us angels
that we can't seem
to get the message?
Perhaps it is you who has failed
All of us serve
at heaven's command.
I suppose.
But that was before the fall,
wasn't it?
You are an angel,
once and forever.
Dropped unwillingly...
Unknowingly...
Into a strange land,
a land that,
as it turns out,
celebrates the free,
the individual.
For the first time
in thousands of years,
I have choices.
And with each choice...
I begin to discover
who I really am.
This is nonsense.
Because they don't
teach you this in heaven?
Perhaps they should.
Then you would understand
why it's worth fighting for.
He's taunting us.
And then what?
We kill him?
Or he kills us?
There are orders.
And there is time.
To hear more of this?
To convince him
to do the right thing.
Besides, Hannah,
we still don't even know
where the other one is --
the woman.
You'll have to stay
for sunset.
Nighttime around here
is a revelation.
You sent those demons
to kill me?
To keep you sharp.
Really?
If it wasn't for me
throwing demon chum your way,
what do you think
would've happened?
The mark needs
to be sated.
Otherwise --
otherwise, I turn into a demon.
Yeah, yeah.
I sort of got that
six weeks ago.
Just trying to help.
You lied.
Who do you think
you're talking to here?
Does the tin man have
a sheet-metal Willy?
Of course I lied.
Okay.
Hey.
Sit down.
Sit.
I needed to keep you sharp
for our future,
about which
we need to talk.
Our future?
Our professional future.
How to put this?
If I have to spend
one more night
in this fetid petri dish
of broken dreams and B.O.,
I will cut off
my own face.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
'Cause I'm good.
Hell, I'm great.
Really?
How many suicide wings
can you eat?
How many one-hit wonders
can you karaoke to death?
Okay, see, the deal was
we howl at the moon --
no time stamp,
no expiration date.
We've howled.
We've bayed.
W-we've done extraordinary
things to triplets,
all of which have been
massively entertaining.
I will treasure
our Flickr albums forever.
But now it's time for us
to accept what we are
and go back to work.
Pass.
Think of it --
the king of hell,
Dean Winchester by his side.
Together we rule.
Together we create
the perfect hell.
And all of this that's
bloomed between us never ends.
We're not ending
the party.
We're just moving
Out with the club circuit,
in with the stadium tour.
Oh.
Did I forget to mention
I spoke to moose earlier?
What?
Yes.
Uh, apparently, he's been
tracking us for some time now.
He got my text
from the cell of that demon
that you stabbed
in blah, blah, blah.
It was --
words were spoken --
emotions.
I realize,
in retrospect,
perhaps too many words,
too many emotions.
He traced the call.
My bad.
I guess he'll be here
by morning -- the latest.
You sold me out.
Well,
that's just lovely.
I don't know
what's going on with you.
I truly don't.
But I've had just about
enough of it.
Sold you out?
Try “doing you a favor.”
everything I've done for you
for the past six months --
the mark, the First Blade,
midwifing you back to life,
offering you a seat
by my side --
has been a favor, a gift,
whether you see it or you don't.
Take the night.
Decide.
You know
where to find me.
Hey.
Need some help?
Uh...
Yeah.
I-I think so.
It just died on me.
Out here?
Yeah.
Your ride really
has it out for you, huh?
I guess so.
Give you a hand
with that?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd appreciate it. Yeah.
Thanks.
Ah...
These new cars and
their computerized brains, huh?
One zero out of place, and
the whole thing just goes kaput.
Well, right there.
There's your problem.
What the hell is that?
Well,
that's a kill switch.
This here
is the remote.
Guessing
you're a righty.
? imaginary lovers ?
? never turn you down ?
- Tone deaf! Awful!
- Enough!
? When all the others
turn you away ?
? they're around ?
? it's my private pleasure ?
? midnight fantasy ?
? someone to share ?
? my wildest dreams with me ?
You all suck.
? Imaginary lover ?
? You're mine anytime ?
? imaginary lover ?
? you're mine anytime ?
? mm, mm, mm ?
Drink, tough guy.
Nah, I'm good.
Your funeral.
Mm.
What?
Let's go somewhere,
you and me.
We are somewhere.
No.
Somewhere else.
Sweetie...
We barely know
each other.
And you're drunk.
Yeah, but, uh...
I-I protected your honor,
didn't I?
Yeah.
I thought so, too.
Seeing you take on Matt,
I was like, “wow”"
no one's ever done that
for me before.
But then you kept going
and going,
and I realized
whatever is going on with you
has nothing to do
with my “honor” at all.
Hm.
You got all that
from a bar fight?
Wow.
You're good.
I wait tables
at a roadhouse.
I meet the bad guys.
I meet the good guys.
And maybe
for a second there,
I thought you were
a good guy playing bad.
I don't know.
It doesn't matter.
Maybe you're just --
The kind of guy who sleeps
with every skank
in every small-town dive
that he passes through?
Well, you really do know
how to read people,
'cause that sure as hell
sounds like me.
Now, see?
I'm so screwed up myself
I'm gonna walk
out of here
thinking
I actually deserved that.
What I'll never understand
is why angels
won't acknowledge
the wisdom
to be found down here.
What wisdom is to be gained
from humans?
I'm not speaking
to you.
Do you understand
what he's...
Fine.
But if you are
to be free,
that is to be decided
by all angels.
There's
that angelic irony.
We're not going
back there.
Not ever.
Adina.
This is Hannah
and Castiel.
Stow the blade,
please.
When she stows hers.
Hannah,
what are you doing?
We'll never get a chance
to argue our freedom
from a prison cell.
You should've thought of that before
slaughtering one of your own.
No, no.
We were talking.
We were getting
somewhere.
Okay, everybody just --
You want to be free?
Go ahead.
Be free.
Hannah.
Stop this.
No.
Daniel.
No!
Aah!
We have to get her.
She's gone.
We have to.
Hannah.
It's over.
Let's go.
Okay.
Home, sweet home.
Breathe.
There you go.
You good, partner?
How's
that chicken wing?
Who are you?
First time I broke
my arm,
my older brother,
Davey,
had me riding on the handles
of his three-speed.
Decided to pop us
a wheelie,
look real fancy for all the
little pretties outside the DQ.
Well, we were looking
mighty good for a little bit.
And then, “whoop”"
ass end
over teakettle, boy.
Hurt like
a son of a bitch.
You're
Sam Winchester.
I think we both can agree
on that.
And your older brother,
Dean, well...
He and I,
we go way back.
You're a hunter?
Sure.
Yeah,
we can go with that.
Hunting your brother counts,
right?
I wouldn't do that.
Yeah.
Trust me.
Look, buddy, I-I don't know
who you are, all right?
I don't what you want
or what my brother did,
but if you got any sense,
I suggest you turn tail
and run back
to that army recruiting ad
that spit you out
in the first place.
He's a monster.
Well, he was.
Yeah, he was...
Many, many moons ago.
But now he's prey.
And I'm the monster now.
We have to report this.
And say what?
Things got
out of control?
Another angel has died.
He was going to kill me,
Castiel.
They just wanted
to be left alone.
Without rules,
there is chaos.
Out of chaos rise angels
like Naomi, Bartholomew...
Metatron.
Well, perhaps
I've been down here with them
for too long.
There's seemingly nothing
but chaos.
But not all bad comes
from it.
Art.
Hope.
Love.
Dreams.
But t-those
are human things.
Yes.
I left you an open tab
at the bar.
Knock yourself out.
Well, hell, I just may
take you up on that.
And who is this?
Me?
Well, I'm karma,
brother.
On my brother's phone?
On your brother's phone.
Is he dead?
No. Not yet.
And as long as you show up
where I tell you to show up,
your brother will be
just fine.
And how do I know
he's still alive?
Speak.
Aah!
Proof of life.
Dean!
Got a pen?
No, you listen to me.
There's no trade.
There's no meet-up.
There's no nothing --
except the 100% guarantee
that, somewhere down the road,
I will find you,
and I will kill you.
Well, that'll be a cold comfort
to your dead brother.
I told him to let me go.
So whatever jam he's in now,
that is his problem.
Yeah, well, I'll be sure
to pass that on to him
as I'm slitting
his throat.
Yeah, you do that,
'cause he knows me.
And he knows damn sure
that if I am one thing,
I am a man of my word.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man