The name Olivette
means little to you.
A high-ranking member
of the Grand Coven,
the one who led the charge
against me.
She's just come back
to the states.
Now would be an excellent time
to strike
and take out
a miserable, old witch
who's been standing in my way
for centuries.
Mother, it's not happening.
What?
Something's come up.
Olivette can wait.
My peace is helping people.
Working cases.
That's all
I want to do.
Is this about the Mark?
I'm done
trying to find a cure, Sammy.
The answer is not out there.
It's with me.
So, I'm gonna fight it
till I can't fight it anymore.
Crowley:
What are you doing?
What's it look like?
I'm leaving.
Another
petty manipulation.
What do you want from me?!
...Why it breaks my heart
to see what a colossal numb nut
you've become?!
Sad, bored, wee boy
on the throne
who'll flop ass-up
the second those Winchesters --
hunters who'd as soon see you
dead as have you to tea --
ask you to.
You're their bitch.
[ Organ playing ]
Terry: I detest all my sins
because of thy just punishment
but most of all because
they offend thee, my God,
who art all good
and deserving of all my love.
I firmly resolve,
with the help of thy grace,
to sin no more and to avoid
the near occasion of sin.
Amen.
I absolve you
of your sins
in the name of the father and of
the son and of the holy spirit.
Amen.
Go in peace, Terry.
See you Sunday.
That you will,
father.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
[ Screaming ]
? Supernatural 10x16 ?
Paint It Black
Original Air Date on March 25, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Majesty.
I beg you
to speak with her.
What now?
Your mother remains...
vexed with your highness
and vents her frustration
by abusing the court.
No one dares retaliate,
of course,
and, yes, one expects
to suffer in hell,
but I fear
I've reached my limit.
To wit...
I mean, seriously.
[ Sighs ]
Mother!
[ Sighing ]
Yes, your royal highness?
You care
to comment?
Magnificent work
by an astonishing talent.
Mm, brava!
I always said
you were two-faced.
[ Chuckles ]
Look, mommy, enough.
I know
you're annoyed with me.
Annoyed?
No, Fergus.
I'm devastated,
betrayed
[voice breaking]
And brokenhearted.
Because I wouldn't go begging
to a bunch of witches
on your behalf?
The Grand Coven is the supreme
command of all witchcraft.
Without their sanction,
I'm forbidden to practice!
Forgive me.
I hadn't noticed you'd stopped.
That? Parlor trick.
I'm capable
of greatness.
Given free reign,
I'd be unstoppable.
I am this close
to throwing you
back into that dungeon.
Of course. Why not?
Why do anything
but cause me more pain?
Bad enough
that you wouldn't intervene
with Olivette
and the coven,
but you went
directly against my wishes,
siding with
those Winchesters,
refusing to kill them,
then delivering the First Blade
into their hands,
which you know
could slaughter us all.
You prefer them
to your own flesh and blood.
It's a bitter pill,
Fergus,
after all
I've done for you.
And what exactly
would that be?
I gave you life, Fergus.
Without me, Sunshine,
you wouldn't exist.
Abite!
All right, so, I'm thinking,
uh, curse, maybe.
Sam, a little help here,
okay?
I'm trying
to stay busy here.
You know, eye on the ball,
not on the Mark.
And this a case
until we know it's not.
Sam: Sure.
No, yeah, you're right.
Three suicides,
two weeks.
They're not
just suicides.
They gutted themselves.
And they took
their sweet time doing it.
I mean, that had to be
incredibly painful.
I can't seem to find any link
between the vics, either.
Yeah, probably a curse,
I bet.
Sister Mathias:
And this man, he was handsome?
Isabella:
[ Italian accent ] Exquisite.
He took my breath away.
But we are told
not to speak so much
of the time
before we joined the Order.
We all found our way
to this life for a reason.
Was he yours?
His name was Piero,
an incredible artist.
Sometimes,
I would pose for him.
And he called me
his muse.
As you can imagine,
we spent hours,
days with each other.
I felt so free with him.
Isabella:
[ Speaking Italian ]
I...
had never been close
with a man before that.
So...what happened?
I...
I can't right now.
It's okay.
Really.
We're a lot alike,
you know?
I think we're supposed to
enter the convent
for some...higher purpose,
but many of us
chose this
because of
the things that...
overwhelmed us.
All right, so,
what do we got?
Terry Sloane, ordinary guy,
not a lot of friends,
but no known enemies,
no relation to the other vics.
Well, not necessarily.
He's Catholic,
and so are the other two.
Dean,
this is Massachusetts.
There are a lot of Catholics
in Massachusetts.
You think
this is a case?
Who kills himself
with a candlestick, all right?
There's about a billion
better ways.
Yeah, but he did
kill himself.
All right, so,
it was not a witch.
There was nothing hexy
found on him.
Uh, possession?
Could have been a demon?
Yeah, but the point of a demon
possessing a living thing
is to, you know,
possess a living thing.
Okay, Agent, why don't you
get that cellphone
back to the Bureau's
crime lab,
get it hacked
like you told those guys,
and, uh, we'll figure out what's
going on with Terry Sloane.
Probably
nude selfies.
I'm feeling good
about this.
Amen.
[ Indistinct whispering ]
[ Floorboard creaks ]
Hi, sweetie.
You need
to come to bed, Frank.
You got to be exhausted
from all those night hours
you've been putting in.
[ Sighs ]
Yep, yep.
The old job's gotten
pretty demanding, all right.
Liar.
Aah!
[ Grunting, shouting ]
Oh, my God.
No! No!
Frank!
[ Screaming ]
Father Delaney:
I just can't believe
Lisa McCarthy
would murder her husband.
Sam: Right, well,
his blood was all over her body.
And her prints
were all over
the pair of scissors
that butchered him.
That's terrible.
Yeah.
Now, we also
have some questions.
Um, for starters,
she has no memory of it.
The last thing she remembers
is being here.
Frank had gone
to confession.
So, if he happened to say
anything in the confession
about, you know,
maybe problems with the wife...
I'm sorry. The nature of
confession is confidential.
Ah. [ Sighs ]
Father, all of the victims
attended your church.
Um, could you
at least tell us
if they had recently
been to confession?
Yes.
These men
were fairly regular,
but then, so are
the majority of the folks here.
Father?
Agents,
sister Mathias is
our director of social services.
I've asked her to show you
around and answer any questions.
Sure.
Dean: Sister.
Agent...?
Allman.
And this is
Agent Betts.
Sister, you're aware of the
recent string of deaths, right?
Yes, a terrible tragedy.
But I'm confused
as to why you're here.
These were all suicides,
weren't they?
Well, possibly not.
Murders?
Well, the actual method
of killing was all identical.
Ah, the M.O.
Yes, indeed. The M.O.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm gonna go, uh [Clears throat]
have a look around.
Uh, excuse me, sister.
Agent Betts,
uh, Allman.
[ Clears throat ]
Okay.
Dean: Uh, sister, d-did you
notice, um, any change in the --
in the McCarthys' lives?
You know, fighting,
drinking, cheating?
You know, the usual.
The usual.
A bit cynical, Agent?
Well, you know,
scissors to the gut
really, uh,
bring out the Grinch in me.
[ Chuckles ]
So...
Oh...
Now, Lisa McCarthy
said that they were
very devoted to each other.
Was that true?
That always
appeared to be the case.
But...?
We're looking
for a motive, aren't we?
We are.
An earlier victim's cellphone
showed some angry texts
between he
and his girlfriend
'cause he
had been fooling around.
There were rumors.
So, Frank cheated on Lisa.
So, she lied to me.
Oh, she didn't know.
My sources
are excellent.
And you didn't
hear it from me.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Warbling ]
I got a question.
How does
someone, uh, like you
end up, you know...?
Cloistered away from the world?
[ Chuckles ]
Are you making fun of me,
Agent Allman?
No. No, no.
I, uh...
I guess I'm just wondering
how somebody quits one life
for something
completely different
and -- and then
believe in it so much.
Well [Sighs]
In my case,
I felt I had no choice.
My life
had become painful.
There was hopelessness.
I felt I had to find
something larger
than myself to focus on.
A kind of mission,
I guess.
You have no idea what
I'm talking about, I'm sure.
Mm, don't be.
Sam: Sister.
I got a question.
I'm sure it's
a different question.
Is there
a cemetery nearby?
You could say that.
The entire church is built
over burial crypts.
Oh.
Have you ever, uh,
heard or -- or felt
anything strange
or unusual?
Unusual how?
Like, uh, spots in the building
that suddenly get cold
or, uh -- or maybe you
feel like you're not --
not quite alone?
Rattling chains and teacups
that fly across the room?
Sister, are you
making fun of me?
Really?
The FBI
believes in ghosts?
I'm afraid I don't.
If you'll excuse me, agents,
I have to get back to work.
Mm.
Tell me you didn't
think that nun was hot.
[ Chuckles ] I think she had
a little thing for me, too.
Dean, she was
married to Jesus.
All right, so,
Frank cheated on his wife, Lisa,
all right?
You know,
the whole theme of this case
seems to be about guys
doing their women wrong.
Notice that?
Yeah, but Lisa McCarthy
was pretty convincing
that she had no idea whatsoever
she had killed her husband.
Oh, hot nun said that Lisa had
no idea he was cheating on her.
So, maybe she was controlled
by someone who did.
Again, nothing witchy.
Ghost?
Hard to say.
I mean, there's EMF in the church,
but it's built on a burial ground.
You know that all the victims recently
went to confession?
So you think
Father Delaney's involved?
Or maybe something surrounding
the confessional.
Sammy, how long has it been
since my last confession?
You've never
been to confession.
Well, that's too long.
You summoned...
Your royal highness?
Mother.
Oh, he remembers!
What can I do for you?
It's what
I can do for you.
I've been thinking
just how wretched it would be
if my own
raison d'?tre --
wreaking havoc
and pain on earth --
were taken from me.
I see how stifled
you must feel, and I sympathize.
Does this mean that you'll go
to the Grand Coven on my behalf?
Even better.
I've brought
the coven to you.
I believe
you know Olivette,
high priestess
of the Grand Coven.
Speechless with joy?
[ Whimpers ]
You utter bitch!
Bottom-feeder!
Ah, the storm
before the storm.
As you can see, the iron chains
render her powerless,
so you can plead your case,
exact your revenge,
whatever it is that
puts a spring back in your step.
You kids have fun now.
I see
your time as outcast
has led you
from vile to loathsome.
I doubt
this strategy of insults
will get you
out of this pickle.
Mm, no.
I do not grovel before she
who lay with a non-magic
and hatched his spawn.
My personal life
was none of your business.
I could have been
your superstar.
Oh, please!
When we initiated your
thankless ass into the coven,
we did overlook your private
lapses because of your talent.
We thought you'd outgrow
your reckless, selfish ways,
but, oh, no, they just
grew out of control.
And now look at you,
consorting with demons.
Quite the speech
[Chuckles]
Considering you're
in my son's palace.
What?
[ Chuckles ]
You see, my son,
the spawn you speak of,
is now the King of Hell.
Tall Cinderella story,
I'd say.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, aye.
And now you,
dearest Olivette,
are prisoner
of the baddest of the bad
and his devoted mummy.
Sister Mathias: It was
the sadness in your eyes.
I saw myself there.
Was it Piero?
Is he the reason
you're here?
There is not much difference
between madness and devotion.
I was obsessed with him.
We shared
each other's secrets.
We were
on the same road.
I suddenly realized
how deeply in love with Piero
I had fallen.
He said it was only
after I posed for him
that his work took on
real power, real expression.
The painting I had posed for
was the beginning of his career.
In the end,
it was his masterpiece.
Sweet Jesus,
nothing in my love life
was ever so magical.
Magic can be ruinous,
especially if the trick
is on you.
I finally
confessed my heart to Piero.
[ Speaking Italian ]
I felt we could
read each other's thoughts,
but I said the words
inside out loud --
“I love you.”
I waited, dying inside.
And then...
He explained
he had feelings for me...
[ Speaking Italian ]
Isabella:
...But not of the same sort.
He loved another?
Indeed.
His art.
It was everything
to him.
Insomuch that I affected it,
he cared for me,
but beyond that, he could offer
me nothing but friendship.
I fell into
such despair.
I could not eat nor sleep
until my family
could stand no more.
And that's when
you entered the convent.
It's as if I'd died.
My father
sent me there
to escape my sorrow
and forget Piero.
His servants
dragged me from home one night.
All these things
from my father's estate --
I never saw them again
after that night.
Everything that was mine
was lost to me...
except my journal.
Things I could say
to no one,
things no one
wanted to hear.
Loneliness is...
Yes.
It is.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, I can't say
I'm surprised.
You always were petulant
and reckless
and overrated.
Banishment
was too good for you.
Ohh!
[ Chuckles ]
[ Panting ]
You were always
so envious of my skills,
you fool.
The only threat
I ever posed to the coven
was that I was smarter,
more gifted than you!
More blindly ambitious!
Why not?
You nits were content
to live in the shadows,
dicking around
with black cats and broomsticks
instead of greatness.
Ohh!
[ Grunting ]
[ Coughs ]
What was that one for?
Emphasis.
I will get
what I want from you.
No, you won't.
Because what you are looking for
no longer exists.
The coven is a pale relic
of its past power,
weakened by witch hunts,
burning at the stake,
endless persecution, and all
of it was engineered by them.
Them?
Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
Not as quick
as I'd have thought.
[ Gasps ]
All right!
It's a rabid group
of sanctimonious do-gooders
dedicated to our downfall.
They had equal magic?
Worse --
public relations.
They whipped the church
and public into a panic.
Our best were killed
or driven underground.
They then plundered
our spells and secrets
and shipped them to hidden
bunkers all around the world.
It appears you hate them
more than you do me.
They tried
to destroy our world!
Hoarding unbelievable power
for their own amusement.
Smug, self-righteous
bastards.
The Men of Letters.
[ Sighs ]
[ Knock on window ]
Yes?
Hiya, father.
Pardon me?
Pardon you? I thought it was
the other way around.
[ Chuckles ]
Just...
It's...
[ Clears throat ]
So, uh, I'm here to --
here to clean house.
I need to
get some things off my chest.
Oh. All right.
Continue.
Um...
It's the women,
father.
Where do I begin?
[ Chuckles ]
“Bless me, father,
for I have sinned,” is usual.
Right. Good. Yeah.
So, that, and, um...
So, the women.
Uh, and this is not
something that I'm proud of,
but I let them think
that we have more of a future
than we do, you know?
Ah, Gina.
Gina?
Well, now,
don't get me wrong.
I mean, she was --
it was good times.
I mean, you know how it is --
the sex, the lasagna --
but I was not
honest with her.
And sometimes,
I was seeing
two, maybe three girls
at the same time,
sometimes in
the same day.
[ Chuckles ]
You get the picture.
And it wasn't just Gina.
It was endless.
It's making me sick.
And you wish
to be forgiven, my son?
I do.
I need to clean up my act.
As penance, you shall say five
“hail Mary”s, two “our father”s,
and reflect
on your transgression.
And then, that's it?
Then I'm good to go?
One would hope some...
inner exploration might occur.
The prayers
are just the beginning
to some serious
soul-searching.
Hmm.
Is there anything else
on your mind, Agent Allman?
[ Chuckles ]
What if I said I...
I didn't
want to die...yet,
you know,
that I wasn't ready?
Are you expecting to?
Always.
[ Chuckles ]
You know, the life I live,
the work I do...
I pretty much
just figured
that that was all there was
to me, you know?
Tear around and jam the key
in the ignition
and haul ass
until I ran out of gas.
I guess I just thought
sooner or later,
I'd go out
the same way that I live --
pedal to the metal,
and that would be it.
But now?
Now, um...
Recent...events, uh...
make me think
I might be closer to that
than I really thought.
And...
I don't know.
I mean, you know, there's --
there's things,
there's...people,
feelings
that I-I-I want to experience
differently than I have before,
or maybe even
for the first time.
Go a little deeper,
perhaps, than with Gina.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just
starting to think that...
maybe there's more
to it all than I thought.
Learning there's more
to the universe
than your tiny world
can be a frightening discovery.
Do you truly
believe in God, Agent?
Because that can
be a comfort.
I believe
there is a God.
But I am not sure
he still believes in us.
So, you think you had
an eavesdropper in there?
Hope so.
You better
watch your back.
If we're right,
jerks like you
are just what
our ghost is looking for.
Isabella?
Are you here?
“Obscuri funesti dies...”
[ door creaks ]
Isabella: I found
no peace in the convent,
and my sorrow
turned to rage.
What was once love for Piero
had become hatred.
One night, I snuck out a window
and made my way to his studio.
I'm not sure why I went.
To confront him?
To ruin the painting
and destroy his love
the way he destroyed mine?
[ Woman moans ]
There they were.
[ Woman moaning ]
[ Screaming ]
Isabella!
[ Shouts ]
I never mentioned her to you
because it didn't occur to me
she was connected
with the murders.
Ever since I've been here,
I've come across
restless spirits of all sorts.
They're all kind of...
sad, harmless.
And eventually, the poor things
go to their final rest.
Wait a second. S-so, you're
just comfortable around ghosts?
As a spiritual person,
I've accepted
many planes of existence.
And as I said,
they've all been harmless.
Isabella was my friend.
We had a lot in common,
including...
painful love lives.
I wanted to protect her.
You said she showed up
about three weeks ago
when stuff
from her home arrived?
Yes, part of a shipment
from a monastery in Tivoli.
Her family's treasures
found their way to the church,
as with many of
the great houses of Europe.
You get
that she got here
just before the murders
started happening?
I finally realized that.
And then I heard
the two of you,
and it made me wonder.
That's when
I read her journal.
It was given to her father
right after her death.
Vengeful spirit,
just like we thought.
Yeah, but 16th-century
Florence.
She's probably
buried in Florence.
I assume.
The -- the journal ended
right after her trial.
Piero's death was so horrific,
she was convicted of witchcraft.
They sentenced her
to burn at the stake.
Okay, well, if she burned,
then so would her bones.
Yeah, but, Dean,
something here
is the tether
that ties her to this place.
It's probably the journal,
where she wrote about her life.
Why don't see if we can't find
Isabella, try to slow her down.
Sam, burn all this stuff.
Her...journal?
Is that necessary?
Believe me,
it's necessary.
Well,
I don't know, Dean.
I mean, there might be
more in here.
Sam, burn it.
Let's go.
[ Weakly ] I'm telling you
I don't know any more.
You're lying, just as you
lied about me all these years.
You're afraid I'll recover
all the stolen potions and spells
and become
more powerful than you.
Oh, poor, poor Rowena.
Always the victim of
one conspiracy or another.
You're so consumed
with your rise to power,
you can't see
the truth!
I see the truth,
and it's pathetic.
You let
these Men of Letters
pillage the greatest trove
of magical secrets in the world
and did nothing.
Ow!
We were weakened.
The plunder was dispersed
to bunkers
all around the world.
Those bunkers
are powerfully warded.
There was nothing we could do
to stop them.
How do I find
the Men of Letters?
I don't even know
if they exist anymore.
I've heard
that the American chapter
was extinguished
in the 1950s,
but apparently,
two of its members survive --
the hunters,
Sam and Dean Winchester.
[ Laughing ]
The Winchesters?
[ Spits ]
Again with
the Winchesters.
Perpetually,
[ Sighs ]
Olivette, dear...
...pleasant though
this little chat has been,
I feel it's come...
[ Gasps ]
...to a close.
What you're telling me
is that the coven is no longer
all powerful and, therefore,
that you are
no longer useful.
You'd better be careful,
Rowena.
There's a line
that cannot be crossed.
Witch-on-witch murder
is anathema to the community.
[ Scoffs ] The community?
[ Chuckles, snorts ]
Who needs them?
[ Sighs ] To think of all
the years I've lived in fear
for nothing.
You ruined my life,
Olivette,
and you shall pay
with yours.
[ Humming “Scotland the Brave” ]
Rowena, please,
you don't want to do this.
Please, Rowena,
don't do this.
Rowena, please.
Please stop.
Cruciatus letumque
crucianti!
[ Screaming ]
Halt!
[ Whimpering ]
I haven't
thought this through.
Why should I kill you,
give you
an easy way out
[chuckling] When there are
far better options?
Fatum tuum
est itersine
no!
Termino ad...
No! No!
Rowena!
Please!
...Nulum!
No!!
[ Laughs ]
Oh, I'm a genius.
Sister Mathias: I don't see how
she could murder these people
if she was tethered
to the church.
She could possess a person
inside the church, ride out,
and get yanked back
after the kill, so...
And can ghosts
be shot?
This is rock salt.
If we spot her,
it'll slow her down.
Isabella: And as the days passed,
my love for Piero deepened,
as did his belief
in my powers as his muse.
He said he
wanted something from me,
something he could
barely give voice to.
He thought the effect
I had on his work was profound.
He had never
painted so well before.
He asked if he might have
a bit of my blood
to mix into the pigment.
Piero was so afraid
he would hurt me. [ Moans ]
[ Speaking Italian ] I told him, on the contrary,
it was my great joy to do this.
[ Warbling ]
But it wasn't enough.
Ohh!
[ Breathing heavily ]
I told Piero to grind
the flesh, blood, and bone
into the pigment.
I had completely become one
with the painting
and with Piero.
“and with Piero”"
She got to father Delaney.
She's around here somewhere.
We got to get you out of here.
Come on!
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunts loudly ]
[ Grunting ]
The priest
had to die.
He made it his business
to forgive you pigs --
forgive you, when what you do
is unforgivable.
[ Strained ]
Sam, burn the journal!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Sister!
Don't let them!
You are my friend.
[ Screaming ]
[ Chuckles ]
You're --
ooh, you're trucking.
Is that her?
[ Sighs ]
Poetic justice, if you ask me.
For hundreds of years,
those hags made me grovel,
every attempt
to please them futile.
High time someone else
ran in circles, eh?
[ Chuckles ]
Nice touch.
Something I might have
thought of myself.
You see?
We're not
so very different.
What is it
that you want?
[ Sighs ]
Well, Fergus, since you asked,
these friends of yours --
the Winchesters --
I hear they are,
oh, what do you call it, um,
Men of Letters?
Possibly.
I see.
Well, about that --
Listen, we've
been through this.
My relationship with
the Winchesters is my business.
I'll handle them.
I'm not killing them.
All right, deary.
Of course.
Whatever you say.
Dean: Who mixes their blood
and bones into paint?
No woman's
ever done that for me.
[ Chuckles ]
Sam:
Is this you thanking me
for not doing
what you told me to do?
You know, if you
would have burned the journal,
then we wouldn't know
how to kill it, would we?
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, you're welcome.
You know...
You were in that confessional
a long time.
Look, man,
I'm just saying,
I'm your brother, Dean.
If you ever need to talk
about anything with anybody,
you got somebody
right here next to you.
Okay.
I heard what sister Mathias
was saying about, you know,
hiding pain
by taking on a mission,
and I-I know that's
what you're doing a little bit.
And it's okay.
I mean, it's fine. I get it.
I've done it before, too.
But...
I don't buy
for one second
that the Mark
is a terminal diagnosis,
so don't go
making peace with that idea.
There has to be
a way.
There will be a way,
and we will find it.
That's what we do.
So, believe that.
Okay, Sammy.
You want to...
Uh, try that again
like you mean it?
Okay.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man