You ruined my life,
Ollivette.
Crucianti!
[ Screaming ]
Crowley: Is that her?
Rowena:
Poetic justice, if you ask me.
Dean: The Styne family.
Charlie: They've been after me
since I-I dug up
"The Book of the Damned."
All the spells they used
came from a book
of "unspeakable evil."
My family will never stop
looking for that book.
[ Grunts ]
You got to figure a way
to get the Mark of Cain off Dean
before it turns him
back into a demon?
There is a cure for the Mark
in the book.
But it comes at a price.
We got to destroy it.
Bobby: Maybe going behind his back
ain't the best idea.
Sam! Burn it -- now!
And I know it's the life --
doing a little bad
so you can do a lot of good.
Will you help me?
But sometimes
the bad's real bad,
and the good -- it can come
at one hell of a price.
Kill my son.
I'll kill Crowley.
Can you read the book?
Bring me Nadya's codex,
and I'll give you your cure.
We had an agreement.
You want out? Hurry up.
[ Groans ]
[ Knock on door ]
[ Door closes ]
Ah.
You must be Eileen.
Yes. I'm here
for the interview.
Thank you so much
for fitting me in after hours.
As, um, as you can see,
I'm in good health
and my eyesight is 20/20,
which is important, yes?
Because this is
a research study on eyesight?
Mm-hmm.
M-my friends and I
do as many of these
clinical studies as we can
'cause we're all on budgets,
and the money from these things
really helps with college.
Okay.
Everything
seems to be in order.
Okay.
Let's take a peek
at these eyes.
Yes.
Okay.
N-no! No!
No!
No!!
[ Grunts, gagging ]
[ Thuds ]
[ Gags ]
[ Knock on door ]
Everything okay in there?
[ Door handle rattles ]
What's going on?!
Everything okay?
Hey!
? Supernatural 10x21 ?
Angel Heart
Original Air Date on May 6, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Nothing?
You've got nothing?!
Rowena, it's been days!
You said the codex
would crack the code.
I am an artist, Samuel.
These things cannot be rushed.
[ Sighs ]
Perhaps
if I weren't chained up...
I'm really not
at full strength.
Yeah, and you won't be
No witchcraft.
Look, I need the cure
for my brother from the book,
and if you're stalling --
Why on earth
would I stall?!
I want the Mark off your brother
for my own protection!
I want out of these chains
and out of this pit,
and I want you to hold up
your end of the deal
and kill Crowley.
You do remember the deal,
do you not, Samuel?
Believe me, I have no issue
killing Crowley!
The problem is,
the language
Nadya used in the codex
is damn near
indecipherable.
She was a gifted witch
but a selfish pig.
Once she cracked a code,
she then coded its secrets
for herself.
So...
Now we need to break a code
to...break a code?
Quick, aren't you?
Listen,
Dean gets worse every day.
Get this done.
You won't forget
the grocery shopping, will you?
No.
Monroe: Astounding.
Astounding
and disappointing.
There was a time,
Eldon,
when I would call you
our most promising.
You ask your brothers
and your cousins.
But clearly, you have been
spoiled and overindulged,
and the result
is arrogance.
The utter
lack of judgment.
You thought
you'd take time
for a little quickie
with that girl
before you harvested her.
Sir --
And you were discovered
by a witness.
We don't have witnesses!
And left a body behind.
And we certainly
don't leave behind bodies
when we harvest.
The whole key to our success
all these centuries is secrecy.
Daddy...
I've never done
anything like this before.
I haven't been myself...
ever since Jacob died.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
Don't you dare cheapen
the memory of your brother
by using him as an excuse
for your foolishness.
I'm filled with regret,
sir.
I doubt that.
But you will be
if you are cast down
to the lower echelons
of this family,
where you will exchange
your title of son and heir
for lab rat.
I made
this single mistake.
Discipline.
It is all
that holds our life together.
If it unravels,
we are done.
Here's how
you'll redeem yourself.
First, clean up your mess
in Omaha.
Next, you will track down
these Winchesters
who murdered
your brother Jacob,
and who may now have
in their possession
"The Book of the Damned."
It will be done.
Sir?
Uncle Monroe?
Yes, Eli?
I was wondering
if it was best
to put such an important
assignment in Eldon's hands
since his...
[ Chuckles lightly ]
judgment is
so questionable.
That's very bold of you, Eli,
considering your own issues.
My issues, sir?
The mysterious
redheaded girl
that your cousin Jacob
was tracking when he died --
the one
that stole the book --
was that task
not passed on to you?
Have you located her?
I'm trying, sir.
There's still
no trace of her.
Well, if the Winchesters don't
have the book,she's got it.
So if you're so worried
that your cousin will fail,
report in with Eldon
and back his effort.
Now get out.
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Footsteps ]
Wow.
Hey.
Well, you look
like crap on toast.
I just haven't...
really been sleeping well.
[ Sniffs ]
There's a woman
you haven't mentioned?
A woman?
Well, I'm just saying.
You weren't here
when I went to bed last night.
You've been running off
on your own a lot
these past couple weeks.
I do that.
You actually don't.
Dean, we don't always do
the exact same thing
at the exact same time.
Remember when you went off
and snuffed that vampire nest
by yourself?
Have you been
snuffing vamps' nests?
No, I-I...
What is that?
What are you doing?
So, those goons
that were after the book,
the, uh, the Stynes,
well, the one that we killed
said that he had a big family.
So if there's more out there,
I figure we should probably
get to know as much as we can
about them.
And?
Well, there's pretty much
what we do know,
that they screwed
with financial markets,
they helped Hitler
get started,
along with god knows
what else -- probably disco.
[ Chuckles ] But you go back to the 1800s,
and the trail goes dead.
There's nothing in the research,
there's nothing online.
It's like the family
just popped up one day.
Families
don't usually do that.
No, they do not.
Hasn't been
a total waste of time, though.
I think
I caught us a case.
There's a mention online
of a murder in Omaha.
Victim's eyes
were cut out.
Janitor runs in just as the killer
jumps out the window.
That's it?
Well, the window
was on the third story.
Look, man, I'm just trying
to stay busy here, okay?
Unless you have
bigger fish to fry.
No, I-I'm sold.
I'm in.
All right, well,
I'm gonna hit it.
You probably should, too.
We'll leave
first thing in the a.m.
[ Dog barks in distance ]
[ Brakes squeal ]
Hey, Charlie.
Hey. It is you.
Uh, in a...beat-up,
prehistoric subcompact.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
But why
are we meeting here?
I could've come
to the Death Star.
No, no, this is, uh...
this is better, actually.
We'' not gonna be working
in the bunker, so...
Uh-huh.
What is this about,
again?
You were kind of...vague.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay, so, here's the thing --
Dean is not getting any better.
I feel like if we don't
get the Mark off his arm,
it's gonna eat him up.
I get it, but what are we
gonna do about it?
I got ahold of a codex
which is sort of a-a collection
of supernatural
code-breaking tools,
and it should help crack
"The Book of the Damned."
That would be awesome
if the book, you know,
[chuckles]
actually existed.
It does.
Uh, I, um...
[ Clears throat ]
I swapped it out right before
it looked like I burned it.
Okay.
Well, Dean wanted it burned,
so is he pissed?
Of course.
He doesn't know.
Geez! The two of you.
Charlie,
he's not himself.
He's not.
He would try and stop me.
He's given up.
Look, I called in an expert
to -- to use the codex,
but it turns out
it's sort of...encoded also,
so I thought you might help...
move things along faster.
Behind Dean's back.
After Dean told us
the stupid book
would kick our asses
if we mess with it.
I-- is there any part of this
that doesn't reek?
Did I mention
you'll be working
with one of the most dangerous
witches in the world?
[ Sighs ]
I don't know, Sam.
As far as I can tell,
this is...
Our only shot
at saving him.
If we don't take it...
He's gone.
Rowena:
I thought I was clear, Samuel.
I requested more time,
not an assistant.
And I thought
I was clear, Rowena.
Charlie is not
your assistant.
You're hers.
And you studied your craft
where?
Mostly a joint
called m?s java.
It has excellent Wi-Fi.
I have not heard
of this institution,
and I know all the great
global centers of witchcraft.
Makes sense,
'cause I'm not a witch.
I'm a nerd.
And I know all
the great centers of nerddom.
[ Sighs ]
Rowena, are you done
marking your turf?
Listen,
Charlie has tech chops
that'll speed up
cracking Nadya's codex.
You will spot
the ancient curses and spells,
and that'll put this whole mess
in context.
Cass.
Are you in on this,
too?
Hell's bells.
More distractions?
What are you?
Witch or nerd?
Angel.
Beg pardon?
Castiel has,
uh, powers --
spiritual muscle
that'll help safeguard the work.
Safeguard it from what?
You.
I can't be here full time
to referee.
Whoa, whoa.
And I can?
Yes. Please.
Please do this for me.
Well,
what are the rules?
If I'm gonna referee,
I should at least know them.
Quite literal,
aren't you?
Does he know
that the first rule
is don't tell your brother
what we're doing?
Wait --
Dean doesn't know?
Sam,
this never ends well.
That's exactly
what I said.
Okay,
everyone take a breath.
Look, we're up against it,
okay?
And we've all been
up against it before,
and we know there are times
when every choice sucks.
Now, us...lying to Dean...
is the choice
that sucks the least.
We have to
make this work.
Please.
Okay, yeah.
For Dean.
Cass?
Okay.
For Dean.
Barely know the man.
[ Screams ]
[ Whimpers ]
[ Sighs ]
I hope this is important.
I have a perfect game
going.
T-t-there's a problem,
majesty.
Just for once, I wish you trolls
would bring me some good news.
"Sire, Missouri has boils."
Something cheerful.
[ Chuckles ]
It's your majesty's
mother.
What about my mother?
Wh-- uh,
s-she's missing.
What?
[ Grunts ]
You've heard
of killing the messenger?
Don't come back
without news of my mother.
[ Door opens, closes ]
[ Screams ]
Shut up.
[ Groans ]
Nice grouping.
Police told me
no one was allowed in.
That didn't mean
the FBI, right?
And the janitor came in
right after the killing?
Yeah,
he heard screaming --
maybe when her eyeballs
were scooped out.
Janitor saw a man
jump out the window,
run down the alley.
Running?
After, uh...
falling three stories?
That's what
it looked like.
Security footage?
Yeah, sure.
Uh, but just one of them
caught any action.
Out in the alley.
That's the guy
who rented the office.
That's pretty slick
for a three-story drop.
Wait a second.
Can you, uh, play it again?
Yeah.
Keep going.
Okay, freeze there.
Zoom in.
Same ink as the Stynes.
How long
was he renting here?
Uh, just a month.
But I only saw him
a day or so.
Some sort of clinical trial
using student volunteers.
He didn't mention
eyeballs.
Hm. Well, I guess you're gonna
ask about that from now on, huh?
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Excuse me.
[ Ringing continues ]
Listen, you, uh,
remember anything else,
give us a call.
[ Sighs ]
Telemarketer.
[ Door closes ]
You're quite
the chatty Patty.
What'd you tell
those two?
Hardly anything.
Nothing.
I-I've got nothing to say.
[ Groans ]
I don't believe you.
[ Camera clicks ]
[ Sighs ]
Damn it.
That miraculous
machine of yours
hasn't solved everything
by now?
[ Coughing ]
Overrated, I'd say.
I'm using the computer
to find some pattern
in the book's coding
or any synchronicity with
the symbols in Nadya's codex.
Oh.
I'm more old-school.
I read the signs
nature shows me --
the forces that ruled
before there was man.
Wow. Why didn't I
think of that?
Okay, it sounds like
blood sugar is dipping in here.
I got snacks.
When I was human,
I grew very fond
of these pork rinds.
What do you know
about the chick
who wrote
"The Book of the Damned"?
Agnes was a hermit nun...
And as mad as a hatter.
Made it her business
to undo curses.
Like the one
that caused the Mark of Cain.
As in any struggle
between good and evil,
balance is required.
To cure one curse,
Agnes had to know
how to inflict another.
They live side-by-side
in the magic world.
One cannot be
without the other.
Sure, sure.
Like, uh, a binary system.
So, I got to think
like a hermit nun.
[ Chuckles ]
Did I mention
they burned her alive?
"They"?
A cornucopia of curses
and satanic visions
did not go unnoticed
by the church hierarchy.
These men would not abide
a rogue nun.
Poor Agnes.
Ahead of her time.
Much like you and I.
Well...
I actually don't...see
our similarities all that much.
Because you're young and good
and I'm ancient and evil?
Is that it?
What?
Let me tell you
about you --
a difficult and lonely
childhood.
Tragedy, absent parents.
Always outside
the mainstream.
Sexually progressive.
Living in your own head
for solace and direction.
Yeah, but still,
we are pretty different.
I read you
the minute I saw you.
And I'm sure
you're learning
that the line
between good and evil
is quite flexible.
But we part company
when it comes to blind devotion.
Case in point --
the Winchesters.
You've made them
the family you don't have.
Foolish.
Sam and Dean
are like my brothers.
I love them.
I know.
And that steadfast loyalty
will be your undoing, my girl.
[ Chains jingling ]
So, why would the Stynes
be actually up to the eyeballs
in murder?
What's the connection?
Well, when you take
a few Stynes down, more pop up.
I mean,
how many are there?
All I can say is, I'm glad
we burned that damn book.
At least they can't
get their mitts on that.
Yeah.
Uh, what about you?
How you doing?
Oh, you mean the thing?
Yeah.
You know, some dark thoughts,
creepy visions, violent urges.
Same old same old.
I'm happy I got
a murder to focus on, though.
[ Slurps ]
[ Cellphone buzzing ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Cass?
Sam.
No, it's Dean.
What's up?
Nothing.
I'm just, uh...
Just staying in touch.
Like I do.
Something on your mind?
No.
This call is pointless.
My ride's here.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Hey.
The fridge
is picked clean.
Your turn to fly.
I buy.
That's, uh,
that's mine, right?
Hey, uh, you talk to --
talk to Cass recently?
No.
Um, not for a while.
Why?
I was just wondering
what he's up to.
He's got to be
up to something, right?
Ah.
Angel stuff or...
I don't know.
Yeah.
All right,
I vote for pizza.
Crowley: Yes.
[ Squeaking ]
Yes, Rowena is a handful.
Oh, mercy.
Snakes in the bed?
That would
set my teeth on edge.
If I owned a bed.
Or slept...ever.
[ Squeaking ]
Look, I get it.
She's unpleasant.
She's horrible.
She has a messy workstation.
What's the dirt?!
There must be something
that I don't know about her,
something I could hold over her
as a bargaining chip.
[ Squeaking ]
A demon lover?
[ Stammers ]
You don't need
to paint a picture.
Is there anything else?
[ Squeaking ]
Really?
You sure?
[ Squeaking ]
I need a Minion!
We are scouring the planet,
sire, a-around the clock.
We will not rest
until your mother is found.
I should say you aren't.
And I have
another mission for you.
Yes, sir.
Locate this person -- immediately.
I don't care
what it takes.
Fail on pain
of infinite pain.
On it, your majesty.
You're still here.
[ Door opens, closes ]
Surrounded by mediocrity.
[ Wheel clacking ]
It's a wonder
I stay so buoyant.
[ Door closes ]
[ Engine turns off ]
[ Brakes squeal ]
All right,
hold it right there.
[ Car door closes ]
Hey. Hold it.
I said, "hold it."
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Screams ]
Charlie:
I am doing my best,
but with her criticizing,
breathing down my neck,
trying to sign me up
for team witch --
oh, oh, and moaning how
the one good year for music
was 1723 --
I --
I am going crazy.
I know.
No, I mean, she is evil.
She is a wicked witch,
so by definition --
No, no, no, I mean
something bad
is gonna happen here.
Castiel, man,
just spring me for two hours,
one hour --
anyplace quiet.
Dean is my buddy,
and I cannot screw this up,
but -- but my mind is -- is --
it's a wad of gummy worms.
Please.
Dean:
Here's how this works.
You're strong.
I'll give you that.
But you can bleed and hurt
just like the next guy,
so I'm gonna ask questions,
you're gonna give answers,
or it's gonna get crazy
real quick.
Well, I hope
you got some time.
I'm not
the usual breed of cat.
Neither are we.
Did you kill that girl
in Omaha?
Yeah.
So, it's true.
You have the Mark of Cain.
My sympathies.
That's why
you wanted the book --
to remove it.
We wanted the book
because that's where
your power comes from.
See, our family business
is putting guys like you
out of business.
Oh.
It's impressive.
Let me tell you
about my family business.
You're in
way over your heads.
The family is vast --
spread over the world.
And that power
that you mentioned
doesn't come from the book.
It comes
from intelligence and will.
The book facilitates.
Stock market dive,
recession, 9/11 --
any of them ring a bell?
Arab spring.
Didn't even break a sweat.
Okay.
Why?
[ Scoffs ]
Well, you got to be in it
to win it, boys.
You see,
chaos breeds fear.
Fear breeds panic,
and panic breeds desperation,
and there's always profit
to be made from desperation.
You make a big enough mess,
has to get cleaned up.
And we've been in the fix-it
business for 1,000 years,
and business
has never been better.
[ Cellphone buzzing ]
Now, for the last 80 years,
we haven't had the book.
With the book,
we're unstoppable.
[ Clears throat ]
[ Buzzing continues ]
Cass, what's going on?
Make it quick.
The girl you killed --
why take her eyes?
That whole situation --
unfortunate.
We normally never leave a body
when we harvest.
When you what?
It's a family specialty --
bioengineering.
Surgical enhancement.
And I'm not talking
about nose jobs.
See?
Two hearts in here.
Bunch of extra muscle,
especially in the legs.
Every man in the family's
had a little something.
Pretty much
what you'd expect, though,
given the family tree.
The Stynes?
The real family tree.
The name was altered
out of necessity.
You have chanced upon
a lineage
with a long
and proud tradition...
And some
unwanted notoriety.
One of Europe's
oldest families.
The house of...
Frankenstein.
Let me focus.
The greatest witches of history
have sought my counseling.
Yet you spurn me when
I offer myself as collaborator!
Oh, my God! This is --
I don't think
I'm making myself clear.
I've got a --
I've got a situation here.
There's no way
Charlie can go off by herself.
Cass, there are dangerous people
looking for her.
Fine. I'll go with her.
No, you --
You can't leave Rowena alone,
either.
[ Sighs ]
Nothing is getting done.
Then separate them, Cass.
Just do the best you can.
Frankensteins aren't real.
They're made up.
Yeah, of course.
And we never had a family
acquaintance named Mary Shelley
who spent a few nights
in castle Frankenstein
and stumbled upon
our secrets,
and forced us to change our name
and go underground.
So, why didn't Shelley
go public?
She wrote a book.
Doesn't get more public
than that.
Mm.
But no one
believed it to be true,
just like
no one's gonna believe you.
Well, as long as
my brother and me believe,
that's enough.
Yeah, well...
as mighty as I'm sure
your little family is,
mine is a juggernaut.
We're not ordinary men.
We're Spartans.
[ Knife unsheathes ]
But you aren't immortal.
What we are
is expendable.
I go down, there's an army
of replacements behind me.
And where does this army
call home, hm?
Who's big daddy Frankenstein?
Were you here when I mentioned
that we're underground?
There are secrets.
Well, I'm swell
at uncovering secrets.
You give me the book,
and it's conceivable
that we could have
a conversation.
The book?
Mm.
Dude,
we don't have the book.
The book was burned.
The book is protected
by a spell.
It's eternal.
It cannot be destroyed.
Look, Cass,
I got to get back.
Handle this.
I'll be there
as soon as I can.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
What are you doing?
Uh...
Something came up.
What?
It's handled.
Uh, what's going on in there?
Get any more out of him?
Yeah, an earful --
truly.
Let me ask you something.
[ Crash ]
Oh, my God.
He ripped it off.
Alone time?
Why does she need
alone time?
[ Scoffs ]
Bit of a prima Donna,
if you ask me.
[ Vehicle passes ]
The girl is simply
out of her league.
Without me,
the work grinds to a halt.
[ Door closes ]
Rowena.
She needs quiet.
She's under a lot of pressure,
and it doesn't help
that she feels like
she's betraying her friend.
Ohh. Betrayal.
[ Scoffs ]
She'll get over it.
Once she has
children of her own,
she'll know
all about betrayal.
You have a child?
Do I have a child?
The King of Hell.
That's all.
The King.
Crowley is your son?
Well,
that explains a lot.
I'm sure
that was quite a challenge.
Well, back to it, eh?
We're wasting time in here.
I'm gonna...
see how she's doing.
Charlie?
[ Gasping ]
[ Thunder crashing ]
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Ringing ]
[ Click ]
I know where she is.
Now, I can take care of it
for you, if you want.
It'd be my pleasure.
Eldon: No.
[ Inhales sharply ]
I need to handle this.
[ Panting ]
Give me the location.
Well,
you got a pencil?
Just spill.
A dump called
the Blackbird motel.
Registered under the name
Carrie Asimov.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Door closes ]
Hey.
Any sign of him?
Lot of signs --
just no him.
I followed
the blood trail --
which, by the way,
was like the Mississippi --
till it ran dry.
Meaning what?
He bled out?
Meaning
that the trail stopped.
Vanished. Nada.
He sure must have thought
he was gonna win that one,
'cause, phew,
was he Gabby.
Well,
I've been going through
everything we have
on the Frankensteins,
and it's just like
Eldon said.
I mean,
1,000 years of nasty.
They made a ton
mopping up the black plague.
They started
the 100 years war.
You know, I thought, "man,
there's a lot of them Stynes."
You know, it's like, uh,
Alpha-male central.
And then I thought --
and this is key --
I thought, "this is bad,
but it would really blow
if these guys had the book.
At least they don't have
the damn book."
Yeah. Yeah.
At least
the damn book burned.
Right, Sam?
[ Clears throat ]
But then,
Eldon Frankenstein --
he hits me
with this little fun fact.
He says that the book
can't be destroyed.
Says that it can't be
sliced, diced, shredded,
burned, drowned.
Cannot be destroyed.
Ain't that crazy?
Because...
I know
I saw something burn.
[ Cellphone buzzing ]
Sam, you answer that,
so help me...
[ Buzzing continues ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Hey.
[ Thunder crashes ]
Sam, she's gone.
Who's gone?
I've looked everywhere.
Charlie is gone.
[ Thunder crashes ]
Ezekiel -- seven letters.
Seven represents the seeker.
[ Sighs ]
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Okay.
Saints represent
groups of letters
that represent numbers...
that stand for concepts
represented by...
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, wow.
I might be a genius.
[ Pounding on door ]
Eldon: I know you're in here,
miss Asimov.
You have it.
I want it.
I don't
freakin' believe it!
You got Charlie
involved with this again,
and now she's missing?!
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Pounding on door ]
[ Cellphone vibrating ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Charlie, where are you?
Um, a -- a motel --
t-t-the Blackbird.
Sam, someone is here.
T-t-they think
I have the book.
If you have the book,
give it to them.
Charlie has
the damn "Book of the Damned"?!
No, I don't have it.
I just -- I I just --
I have my notes.
Then give them your notes,
Charlie!
Give them the code --
whatever they want!
Charlie, I don't know
what the hell is going on,
but you need
to listen to me.
Give whoever that is whatever
they want. You understand?
Charlie?!
I can't do that, Dean.
So, you had the book
the whole time?
Dean --
lied right to my face.
I thought it was our only chance
to get you free of the Mark,
so I grabbed it.
I made it real clear how I felt.
You ever consider that?
Dean, listen --
And then
you pulled Cass into it.
And Charlie.
Charlie loves you, Dean.
We all love you.
[ Thunder crashes ]
You're gonna give me
what's mine.
Mine and my family's.
[ Tires screech ]
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Thunder crashes ]
[ Gun cocks ]
[ Car door closes ]
[ Thunder crashing ]
Oh, God.
[ Gags ]
Charlie?
[ Thunder crashing ]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man