Sam:
You were a demon.
You still have the mark.
Sooner or later,
that's gonna be an issue.
Jody: My men brought in
a runaway last night.
She's got zero manners, didn't
even thank me for saving her.
Dean: Those vampires stole you.
They're monsters.
You think when the rest of them
find out that you left
that they're just gonna shrug
and cut their losses?
This your family?
Jody: Yes.
How'd they die?
Horribly.
You know
what to do with her?
Jody, I-I've done things.
You don't have to explain.
If you want, I'm here.
Sam:
Is Sheriff Hanscum around?
Man: Sorry. She's out
for the rest of the week.
I already lost 10 pounds!
In -- in one day?
My husband, Doug,
left me last year.
Doug's a dick.
You deserve better.
You betcha.
[ Spray hissing ]
[ Can rattling ]
[ Clank ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Screaming stops ]
[ Thud, squish ]
? Supernatural 10x08 ?
Hibbing 911
Original Air Date on December 2, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ sighs ]
You can get through this.
[ Sighs ]
How old are you?
19.
Get yourself some lunch.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Donna:
Thanks a lot for coming.
Thanks. Here you go.
Have fun!
Hi!
Hiya. Yeah, welcome.
Come on.
Sheriff...
[ Gasps ]
Sheriff Jody Mills,
Sioux Falls.
Okay.
I'm Sheriff Donna Hanscum.
I work out of Stillwater,
but I grew up here,
so you have
any questions --
you know,
best burgers, cheapest gas --
[clicks tongue] just ask.
What's wrong?
Left your smile
back in Sioux Falls?
I left a kid
back in Sioux Falls.
Plus a pile of work.
But when the mayor insists
you go --
You gotta go, yeah.
[ Inhales sharply ] I hear you.
Here.
Have a sucker.
No, thank you.
O-okay.
Doug:
[ Singsong voice ] Donna.
Doug.
Well, aren't you
looking good, huh?
I lost 6 pounds.
Hey!
You're 1/4 of the way there!
Hey, you, uh --
you think you could toss me
a couple extra meal vouchers?
I mean,
since you won't be using them?
Oh.
You are true blue as ever,
Donna, huh?
Doug and I
used to be married.
Got it.
Have fun. [ Laughs ]
Hey.
We good?
Aces.
Yeah, I love the smell
of parchment in the morning.
I mean, how much lore
is even left?
We've got nothing
on the Mark?
Right?
You'd think
these eggheads,
with all the crap
they amassed over the years,
would have actually collected
something important.
Uh, here.
[ Clears throat ]
"He-wolf/she-wolf: A study
in werewolf transgenderism."
600 pages, volume 1.
But, uh,
not something important, like --
I don't know -- maybe
the oldest symbol known to man.
That's not worth our time.
It's not weird enough.
[ Feedback ]
Uh, good morning.
[ Feedback continues ]
Uh, excuse me. If I could
get you all seated, please.
Uh, good morning.
Morning.
I'm, uh, Sheriff Len Cuse,
uh, Hibbing P.D.
I'd like to say first off, uh,
what an honor it is
to have you all here
in Hibbing this year.
It, uh --
[ Siren ringtone plays ]
[ Chuckles ] Sorry.
Sorry. Uh...
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Uh, sorry, folks.
[ Chuckles ]
Uh...
What was I, uh --
Right. Right.
Um, s-seeing as how this is, uh,
m-my first time
hosting one of these things,
Obviously.
I thought I'd like
to try something new.
[ Clears throat ]
Partners.
[ Feedback ]
Uh, f-find -- find an officer
from 50 miles outside
of where you hail from
and be a team this weekend.
Go on, uh, a-and make a friend.
[ Feedback ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Alex,
I know you'll be okay.
You are totally capable
of not throwing a kegger
while I'm gone --
totally, totally capable.
My faith in you
astounds me, too.
I'll call you later.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Oh.
Hi!
Hi.
Looks like
you didn't get a partner.
Looks like.
Well, you got one now.
[ Giggles ]
Hey, Kevin.
Hey, Donna.
[ Laughs ]
Okay,
what did we get?
"Cops vs. Winter:
The snow must go on."
[ Laughs ]
"Establishing a K-9 unit."
Okay.
[ Gasps ] Ooh!
"Preparing for a riot --
why not try it?"
[ Laughs ] Why not?
I don't know.
Hey, Donna.
Yeah?
Hear about the body?
What body?
Yeah, what body?
Sheriff Jody Mills.
Trashmen found it
behind the hardware store
this morning -- eaten.
[ Gasps ] Eaten how?
Like nothing left
but the peach pit, you know?
Any idea what did it?
Coroner's saying
animals out of the woods --
bobcats and whatnot.
No wonder Sheriff Cuse
was so out of sorts back there.
Got this whole mess
to deal with.
Attacks like this common
for the area?
Heck no!
When I lived here,
we kept our critters in check.
Did it leave any tracks --
you know, any hairs?
Not even a claw mark
on the body.
I'll be right back.
Okay. Yeah.
Save ya a seat, Jods.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Chuckles ]
Jody. How's it going?
Uh, you know.
Having the time of my life
at a sheriffs retreat
in Hibbing.
Wow.
Sounds like a blast.
Uh, Dean says hi.
You found him?
Thanks for telling me!
Yeah.
Uh, right. Sorry about that.
[ Clears throat ]
How's he doing?
Good, good.
Yeah, you know?
Uh, you know,
hold on a sec.
I'm gonna put you
on speaker.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Hey, Jody.
How's Alex holding up?
Awesome. Already
head of the cheerleading squad.
Wow. Really?
No. Sam, she smokes grass
under the bleachers.
But at least she's not
luring men to their deaths.
Right.
Listen, this may not be
your kind of thing,
but a body was found here
this morning,
and something had
gone to chow town on it.
Uh, was the throat
ripped out?
Worse.
I'm hearing
that all the flesh
had been eaten
down to the bones.
Any ideas?
Well, it's not a vampire.
Yeah, I-I don't know, Jody.
I-I got nothing.
Jody, um...
We could head that way.
Wouldn't be any trouble at all.
Nah, it's okay. I can handle it.
I promise I'll call if it gets
to be something I can't.
All right.
Well, uh,
enjoy the retreat.
Screw you, Winchester.
[ Laughs ] Talk soon.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
I'm gonna swallow a bag of knives
if I got to keep
looking at this stuff.
Let's --
Jody said she was on top of it, Dean.
Uh-huh.
All right.
Let's take a drive.
Hey.
I'm Sheriff Jody mills.
I want to take a look at the body
they brought in this morning.
Sure.
Soon as you become a member of
the Hibbing police department.
I'm just trying
to help here.
And I'm just trying
to not lose my job.
[ Door opens ]
Hey, stranger.
Hiya, Shelly.
How are the kids?
Ah! Little jerks.
Love them to death.
[ Chuckles ]
Need something?
Oh, I just came
to check out the Vic.
Oh, where's Len at?
He's tied up with the retreat.
Big surprise, right?
But I figure
what's the sense in having
a hotel full of sheriffs
if you can't help out?
Someone's got to get you
a halo or something.
But, um...
What's her deal?
Oh, Sheriff Mills?
Might say she left her manners
back in Sioux Falls.
Ah.
But she's with me.
Oh.
So, what do you say?
Curtains up?
Hold on to your breakfasts.
This one's grisly.
Oofta.
[ Whistles ]
Ate the whole kit and caboodle.
That's for darn sure.
You got
a measuring tape?
Yeah.
Can I see
his personal effects?
[ Locker door opens ]
That string bean
wore these?
Where's the belt?
He wasn't wearing any.
These stayed up
without a belt?
Or...
wild animals stole it.
Jodio.
Check this out.
You know, I've been huntin'
since I could hold a mini rifle.
Seen darn near
every bite in the book,
but I couldn't tell ya
what did the bitin' here.
I was afraid of that.
Meanin'?
Nothing.
Got me stumped, too.
Woman:
Don't go smoking, Howie.
[ Groans ]
Just watch
your "Top Model."
[ Clank ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Metal rattles ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Squishing, thudding ]
[ Screaming continues ]
[ Screaming stops ]
Hiya, Len.
How's that seltzer
treatin' ya?
Oh. [ Chuckles ]
[ Clears throat ]
? All I know ?
Something
I can help you with?
That animal attack last night
sounded real bad, huh?
Yeah, sure was.
What kind of animal
you thinkin' did it, now?
Uh, I don't know.
We got animal control
on it.
And that's it?
Jody Mills,
Sioux Falls.
Graham:
Sheriff Cuse.
We have, uh...
an issue with the...
raffle.
Right.
Excuse me.
I should go see to this.
Uh...
[ Clears throat ]
Enjoy your night,
sheriffs.
He's got about as much I.D.
As  we do -- squat.
You know,
maybe he's right.
Just let animal control
take the lead.
Woman:
Whoo! Push the cart!
I used to put the cans
in his cart.
Are you
really missing much?
Hey...
Honestly, Donna,
I just met the guy, but...
Doug seems
like kind of a dick.
But he was my dick.
I'm gonna go
hit the can --
you know...
where it's less gross.
Woman:
[ Laughs ] Yeah!
Whoo!
Let's keep this to oursel--
Jody: Everything okay?
[ Clears throat ]
Yeah, it's all good.
All good
with the raffle.
Can we get real,
please?
All right,
um, you want real?
Um...
Somebody else turned up dead.
Looks like
another animal attack.
Please,
don't spread that.
We -- we don't want to spoil
everyone's good time.
Or get too many cooks
in the kitchen?
Exactly.
Now, uh, Deputy Graham and I
got to go make a few calls,
uh, so...
try and have a good time,
all right?
Jody: Alex --
Stop.
No! D--
Why do I hear firecrackers?
Hel--
[ sighs ]
So, maybe your life's
not all cupcakes, either.
[ Keys jingle ]
Never said it was.
Uh-oh.
Flyin' the Coop
without me? Again?
No.
No, I get it. I do.
"Take a hint, Donna," right?
It's okay.
There's been
another animal attack.
Shut the front door.
Says who?
I just talked
to Sheriff Cuse.
I was on my way
out of the morgue,
but it's probably
closed by now, anyway. And--
But it'll wait til tomorrow.
Anything I can help with it?
Not unless
you got any gems
on how to handle a teenage girl,
'cause mine is...
Kind of a dick?
[ Chuckles ]
She's got a whole lot more
in there, too.
Really good stuff.
I was 17 once.
Yeah, hair up to here,
attitude up to here.
[ Laughs ]
Why can't I get through
to her?
You let anybody through to you
at that age?
Joey Demoupied.
Drove a motorcycle.
Smelled like...
Mm. Yeah.
[ Chuckles ]
She'll come around.
You did, right?
Eh.
So, fresh corpse,
jerk ex-husband,
out-of-control teen.
Want to get blingo'd
on my minibar
and watch pay-per-view?
[ Chuckles ] Thanks.
[ Laughs ]
I'm gonna crash.
It's been a long day.
[ The band's "The Weight"
plays ]
Don't I know it.
? I pulled into Nazareth ?
? was feelin'
'bout half past dead ?
? I just need someplace ?
? where I can lay my head ?
? Hey, mister, can you tell me ?
? where a man
might find a bed? ?
? He just grinned
and shook my hand ?
? "no" was all he said ?
I said
I could handle it.
Nice to see you, too.
Hey.
Hi.
Okay, I'm headed to the morgue.
You want in?
Uh, we just came from there.
And?
And flesh was eaten
off the second Vic, too.
Anything missing?
His wallet. Why?
Because I think a belt
was missing off the first kid.
A belt? So...what?
We have monsters
eating and then robbing people?
Donna: Jodio,
you take sugar?
No. No sugar.
Okeydokes.
"Jodio"?
It's --
Don't ask.
Wait a second.
Isn't that,
uh, uh, Donna?
Fat-spa Donna.
Right.
You guys
know my stalker?
She nearly blew a case
for us last time.
Yeah, I haven't been able
to shake
that ray of sunshine
since I got here.
She's actually been
pretty helpful,
but, you know,
it's just tough keeping her
out of this nightmare stuff,
you know?
Right. You mind distracting her
while we poke around?
You show up,
and now I'm a babysitter?
Look, she hasn't gotten mixed up
with this crap yet.
Let's just try
to keep it that way.
[ Scoffs ] Fine.
But if she tries to show me
her sticker collection, I'm out.
Agent Frehley?
Agent Criss?
Hey. Sheriff Hanscum.
I thought that was you.
Well, ain't this a kick in
the pants? What dragged you in?
Uh, well, uh...
We can't talk about it.
Oh. Yeah. I hear ya.
Anything I can help with?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh, nothing. [ Clears throat ]
Actually, Sheriff,
I was thinking
you and I could go
check out the gear expo.
What about the morgue?
Well, you know,
like you said,
animal control
will handle that.
Well, if it's cool with you,
it's cool with me.
Great.
Did hear they're packing some
pretty serious heat in there.
Dean: Hey, there.
Agents Criss and Frehley.
Looking for the sheriff.
Of...Hibbing.
[ Chuckles ] That'd be me.
Ah.
Well, we're here
investigating the attacks
over the last
couple nights.
Just wondering
where you're at on that?
On the, uh...
animal attacks?
Yeah.
Graham: Wait, wait, wait.
You telling me the FBI
has got nothing better to do?
Well, we go
where the boss tells us to.
To what --
arrest a bobcat from Hibbing?
Is there a problem?
No.
No, there's no problem.
You ain't the first feds
to roll through here
and come up with nothing.
Sure is cute
to watch you try, though.
Oh, pal,
the FBI doesn't do cute.
Uh, Sheriff Cuse,
we are just hoping
there might be some surveillance
footage of the attacks.
Maybe a traffic camera
caught something.
Right. No. Sorry,
I-I-I don't have a record of it.
[ Clears throat ]
Speaking of, uh...
Can you keep an eye on the expo
for me, uh, deputy?
I got to check in
with the guys at animal control.
Agents,
good to meet you.
Uh...help yourself
to a bear claw.
Well...
Sheriff's lying?
[ Scoffs ] Deputy douche
seems to think so.
All right. I'll go try
and crack the police server.
Maybe something showed up
on surveillance.
Yeah, maybe I'll go
crack the deputy.
Right, but this time,
try to be
a little less defensive
of your "pretend job."
You know,
this badge means something.
I made it at Kinko's.
Yes, you did.
Be proud of that.
Son of a gun.
Uh, officer ladies,
check this one out.
You can take it to lunch,
to the gym,
have your nails done.
She's always
by your side.
How about this puppy?
Oh. Well, it depends.
Think you can handle
a big one?
[ Gun cocks ]
Sigma, right?
10 pounds pull weight.
Cute.
Call this a big one?
[ Gun uncocks ]
Hope you drive
a Porsche.
Doug: Chaz.
If you're trying
to pull the wool over this one,
you got the wrong girl.
Sheriff Hanscum here
is a wolf in sheepskin, right?
[ Laughs ]
Thank you.
Wolves are
majestic creatures.
But save your flattery
for other female people.
Oh. Oh, Sheriff Goodhill.
No. No.
I mean, yeah.
But, you know, we just met.
Cufflinks -- you know how it is.
Cuff what?
Cufflinks!
It's a dating site for cops.
You on it, Donna?
Me? No.
Not quite there yet.
Oh, you still, uh,
getting in date shape, huh? Huh?
It's more like
trying to get through the stuff
on my DVR first.
[ Both laugh ]
Oh, for the love of god.
What is wrong with you?!
You get off
on fat-shaming chicks?
You are so not fat,
by the way.
And you --
you are just a douche.
Uh, okay.
I'll just, uh...
Okay, then.
What the h-e-
double hockey sticks, Jody?
Calling my ex a douche
to his face?
It didn't look like
you were gonna do it!
What would be the point?
We're divorced!
You really think
I'm gonna change him now?
So he gets to treat you like
a doormat forever? Is that it?
How about this?
Till you've actually lost
a husband,
you keep your mouth zipped
about mine.
[ Flesh tearing ]
[ Growling softly ]
Did something happen...
To your husband?
We all have our crosses
to bear, right?
Hey,
I'm sorry if I --
No.
That's fair.
I certainly went there.
You want to talk about it
or --
Not right now.
All right, then.
I'm gonna go
get some air.
Graham: Agent.
Are you looking
for some teeny-weeny handcuffs
to slap on some paws?
[ Chuckles ]
I think we got off
on the wrong foot.
Right.
How's that, exactly?
Well, this investigation
that my partner and I
are here on,
it's -- it's big.
And, uh, we're looking
for some local help --
you know, someone
who's not -- not afraid
to talk shop
with the big boys back in D.C.
Think that might be something
you'd be interested in?
Might be.
What can I do?
Well, first of all,
I'm gonna need you
to be totally straight
with me.
Is there any footage
of the attack -- anything?
[ Sighs ]
Sheriff Cuse
changed the password
on the server yesterday.
It's got the live feed
from the traffic camera
across the street
from where that first Vic
got attacked.
When I went
to go check the footage,
sheriff said
he'd do it himself.
Did he say why?
But, you know,
sheriff's a-a straight shooter.
I'm sure
he had his reasons.
I'm sure he did.
All right, well, I appreciate
the cooperation, Deputy,
and, uh, when I need you,
I'll come find you, okay?
All right.
[ Sighs ]
[ Rustling ]
[ Twig snaps ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Animal attack, my ass.
You seen Sheriff Cuse
around?
Not since the expo.
Yeah, me neither.
How you doing, kiddo?
Me?
Fantastic. Why?
Word 'round the campfire
is you went off the res
a couple months back.
That right?
You and Sam been
passing notes during class?
It's nothing
I can't handle.
Just sayin'.
I make a mean bowl of chowder
if you ever need to talk.
I appreciate that.
Hey.
You got something?
Uh, well,
there was something.
I hacked
into the surveillance server,
but the files
had been deleted.
I thought you said
that sheriff Cuse
was the only one
who had access to those files.
Um, hi.
[ Shakily ] Hi.
Jody,
can we talk a sec?
Alone?
Yeah, we'll go --
we'll go look around.
Okay, first of all, back there,
I was wrong to butt in.
I know it hurt you,
and I'm -- I'm sorry.
What?
Oh. Yeah.
"Quit being a doormat." Yeah.
I hear ya, Jody.
It's okay. We're okay.
Only...
There's something else
I can't quite
wrap my head around.
You ever think
there are things out there --
things that...
don't end up
on the police blotter?
Can you give me
some specifics?
Yeah. Okay.
Uh, well, I was --
I was kinda far away,
so maybe I didn't see it right,
but what I think I saw...
were teeth.
It was Sheriff Cuse.
I saw him standing
over Sheriff Goodhill's body,
and his mouth
was full of...
Shark teeth,
like some kind of...
Monster?
You think I'm crazy.
Not at all.
Did he see you?
No.
I hid -- like a chump.
You really believe me?
Yeah.
So will those guys
from the FBI.
If you say so.
Hey.
Yesterday,
I saw Cuse taking his stuff
into a room
down the hall from mine.
Must have been...304.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
[ Ringing ]
Sam: This is Agent Frehley.
Leave me a message.
[ Beep ]
Sam, Cuse is our guy.
Donna said
she saw him check in to 304.
Hit me back.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
What now?
Just let the locals
handle it?
Oh, trust me --
the locals
should not handle this.
[ Lock clicking ]
Look at
all this sunblock.
You'd think he's
at the Copacabana or somethin'.
I'll explain later.
[ Doorknob rattling ]
[ Gasps ]
What the heck
is that for?!
[ Sighs ]
Sam: Whoa. Whoa.
Got your voicemail.
Sheriff Cuse is a vampire.
She just pulled out a machete.
Donna saw his teeth.
What the cuss?!
A vampire?!
[ Dean clears throat ]
You want
to give her the talk?
Donna: Heck.
Just...Heck.
We good?
Wait. So, when we were
at the weight-loss spa --
Monsters.
Sucking on your fat.
We took care of them.
Aw, geez.
I knew losing 10 pounds that
fast was too good to be true.
Here.
Maybe this is
where sheriff...vampire went.
It could be anything.
What do you got?
Looks like it's an old farm
outside of town.
Could be something.
And it's the only lead
we got.
"We"?
[ Chuckles ]
All due respect, Sheriff,
but vampires
are far more dangerous
than the Johns
you throw in jail.
You're gonna
sit this one out.
Stuff you, Dean!
Or whatever
your real name is.
Hanscum's good.
Jody --
I said she's good.
Okay. All right.
But you're staying back.
We're taking the lead,
okay?
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Car doors open, close ]
[ Trunk door slams ]
If you're gonna swing,
swing hard.
With vamps,
head's gotta roll.
Got it.
Run!
[ Groans ]
[ Coughs ]
[ Hisses ]
Well, hi, there, sunflower.
[ Dean groaning ]
[ Gasps ]
It's all love,
pretty boy.
All of you will
become all of us.
[ Clears throat ]
We won't waste one bit.
Okay, Mufasa, enough
with the "Circle of Life" crap.
You're a vampire.
Mm-hmm.
You're scum.
End of story.
[ Grunts ]
Yeah,
I'm not in the mood.
Wait -- it's not enough
that you kill people.
You've got to rob them,
too?
We scavenge.
We don't sip and go.
We use
every part of the buffalo.
And to think
I gave you lunch money.
But you came
in time for dinner.
Starr, please,
let them go.
I helped you out.
I-I ditched that video
o-of Catfish killing that man.
We didn't want favors,
Len.
We wanted you.
What use am I now?
I don't even kill people.
I-I'm on bagged blood.
Donna:
Uh, I beg your pardon?
I saw you with your vampire face
standing over Sheriff Goodhill.
No, no,
I-I-I found her. I --
I s-smelled her blood.
I-I couldn't help
my --
my fangs.
But I didn't bite.
Well, aren't you a hero.
It's your nature
to eat people.
A vampire who doesn't feed
is like a -- like a...
Tiger eating salad.
We're not gonna stop,
Len.
We'll take down every person
in your sweet, little Hibbing
till you come back
to the nest.
So, what'd you do, Len?
You, uh,
break up Burning Man?
More like Woodstock.
Len found me crying on the curb
after my daddy kicked me out.
I got in Len's van,
and the rest
is wavy gravy.
So, what -- Len's like
your Charlie Manson?
Ohhh.
Charlie couldn't hold a candle
to Len.
He taught us everything.
Yeah, I'm sure it was
all Kombucha and Kumbaya.
Liberating is what it was.
And then, one day, poof!
Len's gone.
Till he landed his photo
in the paper. Stupid.
[ Laughs ]
For running a police retreat,
of all things.
You didn't
just go straight.
You became a damn cop.
[ Laughs ]
Now, that is wild, man.
Are you feeling dirty,
Len?
'Cause we're about to
have ourselves a bloodbath.
Don't you want to know
why I left?
I already know why.
You got boring.
I got a conscience.
Oh?
Prey that begged
for their lives --
I-it was like
even if I used every part,
like I taught you,
I mean, it's still wrong.
So you walked away.
I tried
to protect people.
After so many years
of...gutting them.
That's why I'm here.
I'll join
your bloody caravan...
If it means
you won't kill these people.
We aren't killing anyone.
You are.
[ Chuckles ]
You don't
have to do this.
[ Rope creaking ]
Kiss my ass.
Mm.
We love you, brother.
But we don't know
who you are anymore.
[ Grunts ]
Can't say we didn't try.
Unh!
[ Hisses ]
[ Donna grunts ]
Hakuna matata, lady.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Now, that's what
I'm talking about.
[ Sighs shakily ]
You okay?
Yeah.
Other than feeling
like I want to hurl, sure.
Hey.
I just...chopped off...
a vampire's head.
You were great at that.
Thanks. [ Chuckles ]
You good?
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, for the first
time I've been back,
I didn't feel like
the Mark was pushing me.
First time?
Knowing that these things
are out there
makes the world seem --
I don't know --
bigger...
darker.
All I know is, back there,
killing those vamps...
I felt like me again.
All right.
So, that's...good,
right?
Yeah.
You know,
if you want any pointers
on how to fight
this crazy crap,
I'm willing to fill you in --
you know, what kills what.
I'd like that.
Sam: Okay.
Well,
let's go with that.
[ Car door closes ]
[ Engine turns over ]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man