Wings of Titania,
bear mine eyes aloft
as I bid thee...
Hex bag.
So we're thinking witch?
Yeah. This is old-world
black magic.
We're here for the witch.
Rowena.
Mother?
You did manage
to stay away for 300 years.
There was the unpleasantness
with the grand coven.
It was no environment
for a child!
- So, what did he take?
- Peanut butter and bread.
They sent me
to a boys' home.
Teaches you some discipline
and responsibility, Dean.
Keep you out of trouble.
It's Cain.
As in Cain and Abel?
Lucifer was gonna
make my brother into his pet.
And so I offered a deal --
It's the bloody Mark
of Cain.
So I became a soldier
of Hell --
I can give you the Mark, Dean,
if it's what you truly want.
But you have to know with
the Mark comes a great burden.
What the hell?
Charlie?
We're still connected
physically.
If you hurt her,
you hurt me.
Dean!
I'm so sorry, kiddo.
I forgive you, Dean.
You good?
No.
It wasn't me, man!
I didn't take it!
You keep on coming
and stealing from me!
It was that --
Where's my money?
Where's my money?!
You give me my money!
Swear on my mother,
J.P.,
I see your face in here
again...
I'll kill you.
Like hell.
This is freakin' America, man.
You can't just --
What you looking at?
? Supernatural 10x12 ?
About a Boy
Original Air Date on February 3, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
After Cain killed Abel,
he became a demon.
I felt connected to you
right from the beginning.
You and I
are very much alike.
I can give you the Mark, Dean,
if it's what you truly want.
But when I kill,
I kill for a reason.
I'm nothing like Cain.
Why are you fighting
what you really are?
? Sometimes I sit
and I stare at the rain ?
? isn't rain filled
with sorrow? ?
? Wonder if I'll see my home
again ?
? will it be dry tomorrow? ?
? Time passes softly,
and I'm a day older ?
? but still I'm living
days gone by ?
? ashes to ashes,
the rain's turning colder ?
? finding tomorrow,
the ashes, the rain and I ?
Hey.
Caught a case.
Apparently something
is taking people
and leaving their clothes.
Hmm. About time
this gig got an "R" rating.
All right.
Why don't you check it out?
I'll hold down the fort.
Dean, you haven't
left the bunker in a week.
And?
And you can't just
live the rest of your life
locked up in this room.
I don't know.
I got three hots and a cot.
Could be worse.
Look, I know you're worried
about the Mark.
Yes, Sam. I am.
Between
what I did to Charlie --
Charlie forgave you.
How about
you forgive yourself?
Because I'm not exactly
batting 1,000 here, you know?
Yeah, I do know that,
but staying locked up in here,
sitting on the ground
reading the same lore books
over and over and over again,
it's not helping you.
You need to get back in the game
for your own good.
You can beat this, Dean.
Do you really believe
that?
Yeah, you're damn right
I believe that.
You know,
you also believed
in the Easter Bunny
till you were 12.
No, I didn't.
Look, I was 11.
And a half.
And a half. Right.
So?
Okay.
And then -- then -- then
there was this bright light,
and -- bam --
the dude's just gone.
Nothing left but,
uh...
A cheap suit
and a pair of Florsheims?
Pretty much.
You see anyone else?
No, sir, Officer.
And what about,
uh, a chill?
Or did you smell
any rotten eggs?
What?
No, man. Uh...
I smelled flowers,
though.
You smelled flowers?
What kind of flowers?
Flowery flowers.
Look.
We all know what's
going on here, okay?
Don't say it.
Aliens.
He said it.
Yeah, he did.
Dude was abducted.
Believe me, I know.
May 2003. Those suckers,
they grabbed me,
and they probed me everywhere.
Okay.
Thanks for your time. Yeah.
I'm talking everywhere.
And I mean everywhere.
Okay, okay.
Well, the wheels
just came flying off the bus.
Yeah.
No cold spots means
it probably wasn't a ghost.
And no sulfur
means no demons,
so that leaves us
with what?
Couple of little green dudes
and a bucket of lube?
Or fairies.
Or...Angels.
Ugh. I'd rather have
the little green dudes.
All right, I'll go scope out
J.P.'s place.
You, uh --
you ask around inside.
Or you know what?
We don't have to split up.
No, no, no. It's cool.
I can handle a little 20 questions
with the locals, okay?
You sure?
Yeah, hey, look, it's a dive bar.
It's my comfort zone,
hmm?
All right. Good.
Great.
? It's only
a matter of time ?
? it's only
What can I do you?
Screw it.
I'm gonna believe in myself.
Attaboy.
Give me something dark
and strong.
Hey, did you know that guy
that went missing -- J.P.?
Who's asking?
Just an old pal.
Look, I'm sorry
to hear about what happened.
But...
guy's a lowlife.
That night, I had
to kick his ass out of here
for stealing my tips.
Whatever J.P. got...
Probably had it coming.
Ouch.
? You feel that separation ?
? will put a stop
to all you've seen to ?
? the same old situation ?
? though you struggle
through life ?
? in the end, it defeats you ?
? Oooooh ?
? oooooh ?
J.P. wasn't that bad.
You knew him?
This isn't exactly "Cheers,"
but yeah.
And don't get me wrong,
I would not buy a used car
from the guy.
But he was harmless.
So,
what was his problem?
What wasn't?
You're in here getting stunned
while the sun's still up,
your life's
a regular Charlie Foxtrot.
Trust me.
I'm Dean.
Tina.
There you go.
How do you know
the Royale Motel in Scranton?
My dad, me, and my bro -- we got
snowed in there for a week.
Well, I was there
for about three months
after my father
drank all our money away.
Lived on white rice and tic tacs
until they kicked us out.
Good times.
My dad was always working,
so I came up with
about 101 different ways
to make
macaroni and cheese.
Serious?
Oh, yeah.
Now, add ketchup for spice, hmm?
Uh, tuna, hot dogs,
fluff marshmallow mix.
Ugh!
That sounds disgusting.
Yeah, well, my brother thought
it was exotic.
Well, here's to,
uh, crappy childhoods.
Hey. All right.
Oh.
Oh. Sorry.
I should go.
Uh...
Before you fall hopelessly
in love with me.
You gonna be okay?
I always am.
How we looking?
Not great.
Turns out J.P. was about
three days from getting evicted.
His landlord said the guy
blasted Neil Diamond 24/7
and that his bathroom was,
"like staring
into the Devil's butt."
That's vivid.
And accurate. I saw it.
You saw the John,
or, uh --
Don't.
So, you got anything?
Yeah.
I got, uh, Jack
with two scoops of squat.
I don't know, man.
I think we ought to just
call it a night and, uh...
And what?
Dean? Hello?
Sammy,
I think I got something.
Tina?
What the hell?
Son of a bitch.
Seriously?
Hey.
What's your name?
Dean.
Dean? It's me -- Tina.
What?
Please tell me you know
what the hell is going on.
Honestly,
I'm not sure yet.
Because I left the bar
and then there was this...
A light?
A bright light?
Yes,
and then I was here,
and I thought
this was a nightmare,
but...
Oh, God,
if you're here...
It can't be real.
This doesn't --
I know.
Just try to stay calm, okay?
Stay calm?
I'm a freakin' tween,
and you look like
some One Direction reject.
And we're in some freaky
serial-killer basement.
I can't --
Tina, Tina, just --
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you, okay?
Well, anything else
happen to you.
This is crazy.
How are you so calm?
Practice.
Who's your friend?
I'm not sure.
He doesn't talk.
J.P.?
No!
Hey. Hey!
Don't!
This is freakin' America, man!
You can't do this!
No!
What is it?
Hey, buddy?
Where did that jacket
come from?
My Bar Mitzvah.
It was a magical night.
Yeah, I bet.
Why don't you try it
again?
Dumpster.
Found it by the dumpster.
All right.
Mmm.
They probably poisoned it.
Right.
Obviously.
What do you think
they're doing to J.P.?
Nothing good.
What are you doing?
Getting us out of here.
You know, before...
I thought
you were just another drunk.
I prefer
functional alcoholic.
Seriously, who --
What are you?
That...
is a long-ass story.
Flowers.
Yahtzee.
Get out.
What?
Hurry.
I'll keep him busy.
Screw that.
You're coming with me.
There's no time. Go.
Get help.
Tina --
I know you will.
Help me!
Help me, please!
I need a doctor!
I need a doctor now!
What are you screaming about,
girl?
Yeah?
Hiya, Sammy.
Dean?
Yeah.
W-wait a second.
Y-you're a --
Uh-huh.
How?
No clue.
Some scarface-looking dude,
bright light.
Next thing I know,
I wake up looking like Bieber.
Why would someone turn you
into --
Don't know. don't care.
Hey,
we got any grenades?
What?
Don't -- wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second. Talk to me.
Really, Sam? Now?
I got no grass on the infield,
and a girl's gonna die.
Sorry
if I'm not in a chatty mood.
Look, you wanted me back
in the game.
I'm back in the damn game.
Come on.
Well...
Ma'am, allow me.
Your son is so polite.
Thanks.
Where are we heading?
Tell you on the way.
Okay, okay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait, uh...
Maybe I should drive?
Yeah.
Okay. Seat. Seat. Seat.
Ooh.
Cake. Why would
they give you cake?
Well, don't know.
It wasn't even good cake.
Too dry.
What?
Nothing.
Okay, not nothing.
Look, this is bizarre.
Even for us, Dean.
This is insane.
You -- you're like --
what, you're like 14?
How does it even feel?
Well, I'm me.
I'm -- I'm old me,
but I'm a kid.
It's freakin' weird,
dude.
And...
What?
There was
a Taylor Swift song
on the bus
that I hopped to the motel,
and, uh...
I liked it, Sam.
Liked it a lot.
Okay.
And my voice is weird,
and I've got like nine zits,
and I have zero control
over this.
I mean, it's up. It's down.
It's up for no reason.
That's enough.
Yeah, thanks.
Uh
let's just call it puberty.
Yeah, which sucks.
Again.
Well, listen, I checked out
the alley where you got jumped,
and I found yarrow.
Which means what?
Means we're probably
dealing with a witch.
Yarrow's a flower.
They use it in a ton of spells.
Okay.
We still got some of that
witch-killing crap in the trunk?
Hell, yeah.
So, we'll get you
changed back,
and then
light Sabrina's ass up.
Right?
Uh, yeah, about that.
It turns out, this whole
freak show has an upside.
The Mark is gone.
How?
Well,
I figure if this hoodoo
slammed me back into the body
I had when I was 14 --
You didn't have the Mark
then.
Yeah, and if we reverse
the spell --
then it's gonna come back.
That's what I'm thinking.
So...
Maybe we don't.
Wait a second. Are you saying
you want to stay like this?
No.
No, but...
If it's between being a psycho
rage monster/borderline demon
or a teenager, well...
Really?
Look,
I'm not a fan, either, but...
Sam,
this is problem solved.
And I'm still me.
I can still hunt.
I'm just, you know...
dewier.
Okay, look,
y-you have a point, kind of,
but, dude --
I know.
Some good news, though --
virgin liver.
So, what do you say when
we're done doing our hero thing,
we take her
for a test-drive?
Yeah, sure.
I mean...you can drink again
in, what, like seven years?
That's not funny.
That's kind of funny.
Oh, come on, man.
It's kind of funny.
Looks like someone's home.
Okay. Let's go in
through the basement.
Get Tina out first.
All right.
Still open.
Tina?
All right, let's go.
Dean, I'm way too big
to fit in that.
First time
you ever had to say that, huh?
Big talk coming from the dude
wearing underoos.
Okay, good one.
Here, why don't you go
around back for another way in?
Yeah.
Don't!
Where's the girl?
Upstairs. Alive.
What did you do to us?
Nothing.
I'm no witch.
I just work for one.
Crappy gig.
Where is he?
She.
And she is the worst person
in the world.
Is that so?
I've been with her
for centuries.
Things I've seen her do.
My sister and I,
she made us hurt people,
kill people,
and when
we tried to escape,
she caught us
and tortured me,
and then she made me eat
poor Gretel's heart.
Wait. Witch? Gretel?
What,
are you saying that you're...
Hansel.
My name is Hansel.
Hansel?
And -- and...and Gretel.
Hansel and Gretel,
like the -- like the fable.
Like Brothers Grimm?
It wasn't a fable.
It was based
on a true story.
They just gave it
a happy ending.
Oh, okay.
We get to barbecue
a celebrity. Cool.
You can't kill her.
You're just men.
We're more than that.
We're hunters.
Ah.
Then let me help.
Help?
What's in it for you?
Because if you're going to fry
that candy-coated bitch,
I want in.
You want to help?
Tell me
how to turn him back.
Sam, it can wait.
Tell me how!
The hex bag
that I'm wearing.
It will reverse the spell.
Squeeze it, and you'll return
to your proper age.
Look, we waste the witch,
I give you the cure.
Deal?
Your friend J.P. didn't
have much meat on his bones.
But a good cook works with
the ingredients she's given.
Mmm.
Oh. Wunderbar.
Oh, don't worry, liebchen.
You're too good for soup.
I'm thinking
a nice, sweet chili glaze,
a few hours
roasting in the oven.
And an apple in your mouth.
Hansel.
And pals.
Well, our lost lamb.
I thought we'd
have to go looking for you.
Maybe even abandon
our home sweet home here.
I never dreamt you'd be stupid
enough to come back on your own.
Hansel,
take care of them.
Yeah, he's not exactly
your biggest fan.
Maybe you shouldn't have made
him chow down on his sister.
I never made Hansel
do anything.
Damn it!
They're hunters!
Rumpatur!
Now...who's hungry?
Don't move.
Ooh. Oh, scrawny.
We'll have
to fatten you up.
Don't freakin' touch me.
Oh, I'm going to do
more than that.
Children.
Oh, they're so sweet
and innocent.
And delicious.
You'll see.
When I cook him up,
I'll give you some, hmm?
If you like kids so much,
why not go after kids?
What's with
this whole Fountain of Youth?
Hmm, in the olden days,
if a child went missing --
ah, the young
died all the time.
Now, though, with all your Amber alerts
and your milk cartons,
a person fillets one rug rat,
and people get so angry.
Yeah, I blame Obama.
So, I improvise.
I take adults no one will miss
and give them back their youth.
And then
Kentucky-fry 'em.
It's the only way
I can eat in peace.
So, uh,
is it worth it?
I mean,
word on the street
is people kind of taste
like chicken.
A bit.
European children are more,
uh, free-range, gamier.
Americans, though -- ooh --
they are heaven.
Fattier.
The meat, so finely marbled,
it's almost buttery.
I just can't get enough.
Mmm. Awesome.
No! I am in awe.
This is my first visit
to your country,
and I have to say
god bless the U.S.A.
Oh, so,
you're a tourist.
No.
It's business,
not pleasure.
An old friend
is causing trouble,
and the grand coven
asked me to take care of her.
Poor, stupid Rowena.
Wait. Rowena?
She got red hair,
a thing for ritzy hotels?
How do you know that?
Now you'll burn!
Stay down, boy.
Turn him!
The hell?
No!
That was crazy.
Like...psycho crazy.
And you do this
all the time?
All
the freakin' time.
Not all the time.
So...
Can you turn me back?
The hex bag
went up in flames.
I'm so sorry, Tina.
We may be able to reverse
engineer the spell, though.
Or maybe you don't.
Come again?
I got three ex-husbands,
50 grand in debt,
and not much else.
I was...
kind of a crappy adult.
Maybe I'll do better
this time around.
Get out of town,
get a fresh start.
This is my second chance.
Everybody wants a second chance,
right?
Sure you're gonna be
alright?
Like I told you,
I always am.
Can we at least give you a ride
somewhere?
Give me the keys.
All right, here you go.
It's all the cash we got.
Thanks
for everything.
You stay safe out there,
you hear?
I will.
And hey, we'll always have
the Royale Motel, right?
So...
Grand coven.
Any ideas?
Doesn't sound good.
Well, sounds like
an '80s hair-metal band.
You know, lot of hair spray,
lot of eye shadow,
lot of keytar.
No? Nothing?
Come on, man. I'm painting
a word picture here.
Is it back?
Look, I know
what you're gonna say, okay?
But you were in deep.
I know, I know.
You saved me,
and you saved Tina,
and...you pulled
a Dean Winchester.
Thank you.
Anytime.
Look, man...
Do I wish
the Mark was gone?
Yes, of course.
Absolutely, I do, but...
I wanted you back.
And now here you are,
and you didn't hulk out,
so...
I'll take the win.
As for the rest of it --
the Mark,
everything else...
...we'll figure it out.
We always do.
Damn right.
Let's get out of here.
I'm back, baby.
? Players gonna play, play,
play, play, play ?
? and the haters gonna hate,
hate, hate, hate, hate ?
? baby, I'm just gonna shake,
shake, shake, shake, shake ?
? shake it off, shake it off ?
? heartbreakers gonna break,
break, break, break, break ?
? and the fakers gonna fake,
fake, fake, fake, fake ?
? baby, I'm just gonna shake,
shake, shake, shake, shake ?
? shake it off, shake it off ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man