Who are you?
Name's Cole.
Your older brother,
Dean,
he and I,
we go way back.
And that was the night
that Dean Winchester
murdered my father.
We're talking
heavyweight witchcraft.
Not some new-age,
wiccan water douser, either.
This is old-world
black magic, warts and all.
I hate witches.
They're always spewing
their bodily fluids everywhere.
You know,
it's downright unsanitary.
Hannah: Castiel, it's time
we stopped avoiding the obvious.
Castiel: Hannah,
we can't afford to lose our way.
This mission is everything.
Emotions...Feelings --
they're
dangerous temptations.
[ Panting ]
Ow!
[ Groans ]
Raul.
You better think fast, Tiana,
'cause this looks bad.
I'm sor--
I'll do anything.
I'll come back.
I'll make it up to you.
Just please don't hurt me.
Now...
What kind of message would
that send the other girls, huh?
Aah!!
Oh, Tiana, Tiana.
I'd say I'm sorry
to lose you, but...
There's plenty more
where you came from.
[ Bones crack ]
? Supernatural 10x07 ?
Girls, Girls, Girls
Original Air Date on November 252, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
What? This? Um, cattle deaths
a few towns over?
A demon possibility
or something?
No, it says right there.
It's probably
just 'cause of the drought.
So, what are we
doing here?
Uh, reason's
right on your plate.
Lizardo's porterhouse --
U.S.D.A. prime.
[ Cellphone chiming ]
It's the only place
between Connecticut
and the bunker
you can get a decent steak
under 10 bucks.
Dude, you are blowing up.
Who is that?
Ah, it's just, uh, you know,
these alert thingies.
For what?
You know,
monster...stuff.
Hey, hey. Unh-unh.
No. Give it back.
What? Wh-why?
Because privacy...
And stuff.
Oh, priv--
You're on a dating app?
Yeah, and you know what?
Don't knock it until you try it.
Nice screen name, Dean --
[Deep voice] Impala67.
All right, give it back.
Come on.
[ Normal voice ]
Shaylene, huh?
[ Clears throat ]
Dean, there are like
a million messages here.
Yeah, uh,
check out her pic.
Uh...Oh. Wow. Okay.
Um, okay. She's hot.
But...
"But," what?
But she seems, um...
Kind of...available.
Like, too available.
"Oh, baby, whatever you want.
I'm burning up
just thinking about you."
They get raunchier.
Yeah.
Yeah, I -- I see that.
It's like a, uh --
like a Penthouse letter.
[ Chuckling ] Yeah.
Is that bad?
No, it's not bad, Dean.
It's too good to be true.
I'm sorry, is it --
is it so hard to believe
that an attractive,
red-blooded, American female
could be interested
in someone like me?
You realize there's no guarantee
"Shaylene" is even Shaylene.
I mean, for all you know,
it could be some...
Canadian trucker n-named Bruce.
[ Footsteps approach ]
That look like
a Bruce to you?
We -- we detoured eight hours
so you could get laid?
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, and, uh, you know what?
Lunch is on me.
And, uh...don't wait up.
Excuse me. Hi.
Hey.
Hannah:
It's getting easier.
Isaac came back willingly --
didn't even resist.
There are still
some angels down here,
but the higher-profile rogues
are back.
We find them all --
that's the mission.
Here. Christopher Sherman --
pastor.
Local paper
in Tennessee says
he's working miracles
in his Parish.
Figure of speech?
Perhaps.
The best lead we have.
Until we find something
stronger, we should...
...uh...check it out.
Hannah?
Yes?
What are you doing?
I'm taking a shower.
Um...We don't need
to shower.
I know.
Are you --
Does this bother you?
[ Scoffs ] Bothered?
I...I'm not.
Good.
[ Water running ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Both panting ]
[ Moans ]
I forgot something.
We still need to discuss
my terms.
Oh, like, rules?
Like, sexy rules?
Um, more an issue
of payment.
Oh.
Yeah.
[ Chuckles ]
Sweetie [Chuckles] thought
you figured it out.
I mean, shy of coming out
and saying it,
I thought
I made it pretty obvious.
Yeah, yeah, no.
I-I just, uh...
See, I have this code.
Uh, "No cash for ass."
Oh, well you're
in luck, honey,
'cause I don't want
your money.
All I want from you
is one little thing --
a trifle, really.
I'm listening.
Your soul.
My soul?
[ Chuckles ]
It's nothing, baby.
Who knows what a soul is,
really, if it even exists?
All I know is you say yes,
my guy comes up,
you sign some papers,
and then it's you and me --
good to go.
Mm.
So that's it?
Just...sign over my life.
It's a signature, baby.
What's a little paperwork
compared to
absolute physical bliss?
Well, you make
a strong case.
I love my job.
Do you?
Yeah.
'Cause it doesn't look like
love to me.
[ Clears throat ]
Get the car.
I'll check us out.
[ Door opens ]
Caroline.
Uh...
I -- I put an alert
on your credit card.
Saw a charge here.
I drove all night.
How we doing?
Everybody ready
for a good time?
Okay. John Hancock
right here.
Then we can
get this party started.
Winchesters.
Dean:
She told us everything.
Abduction,
forced prostitution --
it's pretty gnarly,
even for a demon.
She's got her version,
I've got mine.
Liar.
Dean: Let me guess --
she came to you
begging for you
to pimp her out.
Yeah, 'cause
that Harvard degree
was working out
so well for her.
How many girls are there, hmm?
How big is this?
Just me and shay.
He's lying.
There's a brothel.
I heard him on the phone.
They told me what you are --
a demon from hell.
Beats trash
from the street.
[ Scoffs ]
Face it, Missy --
without me,
you would've been dead of drugs
or worse in a year.
Frankly, this little ho
should be thanking me.
Dean: Whoa!
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Stammers ]
Okay.
Well, that just happened.
Yeah,
and he was our best shot
at the location
of the brothel.
Do you have any idea
where it is?
No, but, um...
I saw him give these out
at the bars.
What did you say?
I said, "If you like it so much,
why don't you wear it?"
She won't wear
the clothes you picked.
What should I do?
Gerald,
what do you think?
Don't leave any marks.
[ Door opens ]
Hey, lady, I think
you're in the wrong place.
This is Raul's girls,
isn't it?
Clever name, by the way.
Sorry, but we're not hiring
at the moment.
And, no offense,
but even if we were,
you're a little...old.
Unless you're here
as a customer.
No disrespect to your girls,
but I'd sooner die
than do business of any kind
with filth like you.
You.
[ Gasps, groaning ]
Boss?
[ Retching ]
Ladies, you may want
to stand back.
This will get messy.
Hardly the most appetizing
process in the world,
but killing demons
always makes me hungry.
You coming?
I mean, you're welcome
to stay here.
Fabulous!
Caroline,
you've been gone a year.
Disappeared.
I don't know
what's happened to you,
who's gotten into your head,
but something's going on,
and I'm not walking away
till I know what.
Well, there is a reason,
an answer for all of this.
Th-then tell me.
I can't.
You wouldn't understand.
Then I'm not going
anywhere.
[ Scoffs lightly ]
I waited at the car,
but the desk man said --
Castiel.
This is Joe...
...my husband.
Oh?
Oh.
Who is this guy?
He...Uh...
You saying
you're...together?
What?
Yes.
I left you. For him.
He's the reason.
No.
No, I don't believe it.
This guy? You?
No, there's something...
You're not
that kind of person, okay?
You wouldn't do that.
You couldn't do that.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
[ Door closes ]
[ Door opens ]
[ Scoffs ]
Can't believe somebody
got to kill this Raul tool
before we could.
Check I.D.s.
All right.
Uh, Dean, from the look
and...smell of it, pure demon.
I think this is Raul.
What? Did he
puke himself to death?
Yeah, literally.
Okay, so...
Something went down here.
There was a standoff.
One demon smokes out
and Raul...
What can even
kill a demon like this?
[ Sighs ]
[ Scoffs ]
Apparently...A witch.
[ Mid-tempo
French music playing ]
Uh, ma'am,
why are we here?
I thought you'd be hungry.
I doubt that swine Raul
fed you properly.
Yeah, but...
We don't belong here.
Apologies for
the interruption, ma'am.
That word again.
But I'm afraid
that the bistro des moules
has a very strict
dress code,
a sartorial standard
certain members of your party
fall well short of.
Now can we go?
Stay in your seats.
We're not going anywhere.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
Famalatus.
A Krug '95 --
an excellent vintage.
With our compliments,
of course.
This is awesome.
[ Chuckles ]
How did you do it?
Magic.
Gerald...
A bordello?
You opened a whorehouse
in my name?
Well, technically, the place was
called Raul's girls, but...Yes.
Look,
Raul said that --
Oh, Raul said?
Your decree last month --
soul deals way down
after the war with Abaddon.
Said that you were looking
for proactive
and out-of-the-box strategies
to get numbers back up.
So, you and your half-wit
pal threw me into the sex trade?
I'm evil.
That's just tacky.
We tried
running it past you,
but we were told
you weren't taking meetings,
that you were distracted.
I mean, busy.
Look, this witch
took Raul down like that.
[ Fingers snap ]
Whole operation -- kaput.
I smoked out.
Ran away.
Possessed the nearest meatsuit
I could find.
Apparently so.
Because I thought that
you should know what happened.
Act of aggression like that
didn't seem like something
you could let stand.
Hmm.
Here we go.
Um, so it looks like
in the 18th century,
there were accounts
of demons killed by witchcraft.
Apparently they were
vanquished by a spell
called
defigere et depurgare,
which is Latin for
"to bind and purge."
You think that's the same kind
of spell that took out Raul?
Sounds like it.
But from what I can tell,
that spell hasn't been used
in over 300 years.
And it was only ever known
by one person,
the witch who created it.
That is?
Rowena.
According to
the grand coven,
there are three recognized kinds
of witch in the world.
Most common
are the borrowers --
those who harness
the power of a demon
in order to practice
the art.
Owing to recent experience,
I doubt you'd have
the stomach for that.
Secondly, and rarest of all,
are the naturals --
those who are...
Born with the gift.
You're one of those.
Well [Chuckles]
you are correct.
And what's the third?
The students --
those with no natural ability
who, with enough practice
and training
and a grand coven-approved
mentor to show them the path,
can eke out
a modicum of witchly power.
Will...
You be our mentor?
[ Chuckles ]
Well...I'm about as far
from grand-coven-approved
as it's possible to be.
[ Voice breaking ] They threw me
out many years ago.
Disapproved
of my methods.
Said my magic was
too extreme.
I was forbidden
from using magic,
from taking students,
from forming a coven.
[ Sighs ]
I've been on the run from
those utter fannies ever since.
So, you can't teach us?
Screw the grand coven
and their silly rules.
You two stick with me,
and you can have anything,
do anything you want
whenever you want.
When do we start?
Soon, but not here.
[ Woman gasps ]
Whoops.
I believe that's our cue.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ People shouting ]
Did you do that?
Oh, he'll be fine --
worker's comp and all that.
Are you coming?
Man: Call 911!
[ Breathes deeply ]
I'm not afraid...
'Cause you're a noob.
[ Panting ]
[ Chuckles ] I'm your first.
That's why
you're drawing this out.
'Cause you're studying me.
You're training.
[ Grunting ]
It's gonna take a lot more
than that to make me talk.
Boy, you will talk.
You will talk,
and you will tell me
everything you know about
your buddy Dean Winchester.
At some point, we have to talk
about what happened.
The, uh...
He wouldn't listen,
Castiel.
He wouldn't let me go.
I didn't want to hurt him.
I could've
erased his memories, but...
[Sighs]
It didn't feel right.
I thought if he truly believed
we were together,
he'd give up.
And it worked.
So, why does it feel
so bad?
You did the right thing.
You hurt him,
but you gave him a reason,
something he could use
to move forward
and make sense
of his loss.
I had to take my vessel from
his family -- twice, actually.
Jimmy Novak.
He was a good man.
He was married,
had a daughter...Claire.
And?
And it was difficult,
but necessary.
The mission comes first --
always.
[ Gas nozzle clicks ]
Middle of my shift,
there's Marty falling down,
clutching his head, stroking out
right there on the floor,
sweating, turning red,
like...like...
Like his brains
were boiling?
Was there
anything else unusual?
More unusual
than our head waiter
dropping dead
in front of me?
Before that.
I don't know,
I mean [Chuckles]
I thought getting
two hookers in here
was pretty damn unusual,
but that was before
Marty keeled over.
Uh, two hookers?
Based on what they were
wearing, yeah.
Were they alone?
No. Came in with a lady.
Thank you for your time.
No, that is strange.
All right, I hear you.
Thank you.
Hey.
So, it looks like our witch
was here with two new friends.
Really?
Raul's girls?
What does she want with them?
I don't know. What'd you get
from the Hunter network?
This guy Darrell's
been working a case,
a series of
grisly hotel murders --
one at the Kensington,
another at the Waldorf
in Cleveland --
bodies stabbed,
impaled on the ceiling.
Sounds a little more
homicidal maniac than witchy.
That's what Darrell
thought, too,
until the autopsy
came back.
Actual cause of death --
Let me guess --
boiled brains.
Yeah, same as our waiter.
Well, I'll give this
to the witch --
she's got deep pockets.
The Kensington, the Waldorf,
this restaurant --
that can't be cheap.
Yeah.
Let's get.
Where we going?
Check out every five-star hotel
in the area.
Oh.
What's going on?
I'm sorry, Castiel.
I'm not going with you.
I'm done.
It's hard [Chuckles]
letting go...
of a story, a mission.
But what of the humans
whose lives we sacrifice
in the name
of that mission?
What of them?
We always said the humans
were our original mission.
Maybe it's time, Castiel --
time to put them first.
Where is all this
coming from?
Being on earth, working
with you, I've felt things.
Human things --
passions, hungers.
[ Chuckling ] To shower,
feel water on my skin...
to get closer to you.
But all of that was nothing
compared to what I felt
when I saw him.
Her husband --
his anger and his grief.
And Caroline
was inside of me,
screaming out for him,
for her life back.
These f-feelings,
they aren't for me, for us.
They belong to her.
I know it's time
to step aside.
Goodbye, Castiel.
Caroline, I'm --
Castiel.
I know. [ Chuckles ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Knock on door ]
Okay.
You two ready
for some practice?
Who is it?
Probably
the hotel manager
probably here to complain
that I haven't paid the bill.
You have those spells
I gave you?
Yeah, about that?
I don't read Spanish.
It's Latin.
Phonetics are on the back,
darling.
"Phonetics."
Get ready.
And on my word...
You're in for a world of hurt
when we deliver you to our boss.
What about us?
I'm not going back
to that place.
Operation skank
has been terminated.
The only place you two are going
is the dumpster out back.
[ Gasps ]
Who are
those guys?
Hunters.
Let's get
out of here.
That's not an exit.
Don't worry, ladies.
Our beef's not with you.
We're here for the witch.
Rowena.
Always nice
to be recognized.
Do something --
a spell!
That's
an excellent idea.
Impetus bestiarum.
[ Screaming ]
What did you do to her?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Growls ]
Go! Go!
What'd you do?
What did you do to her?
Attack-dog spell.
We needed a decoy.
But...
But she'll die,
just like the waiter.
Probably.
Few humans are built
to survive magic like that,
and Elle was weak.
[ Sighs ]
But you're not.
I saw it
the second we met.
You're strong.
You're right.
I am.
Occideris ingrat--
Not another word!
Lady, your luck
has just run out.
I'm pretty sure
that's not true.
[ Whistles ]
Pal, we got to work
on your timing.
Drop the gun, Dean-o.
All right, she may not
look like much,
but letting this one go --
big mistake.
Uh-huh.
You heard the boy.
Look, man, I am sorry about
the last time we met, okay?
I'm sorry about
a lot of things.
I'm not the same person
that I was.
You're not a person
at all.
See, I know
all about your kind now.
My kind? Listen --
I'm not a demon
anymore.
So, were you a demon
when you murdered my father?
No.
Then you're still
a monster.
Let's go.
Let...Me...Out!
Look...Whatever she did to you,
you have to fight it.
I...Can't.
[ Screams ]
[ Gun cocks ]
Don't.
[ Banging on door ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
What are you waiting for?
Do it.
[ Sniffs ]
No.
Now, I'm gonna clean
this mess up once and for all.
You're gonna give me
five minutes,
and we're gonna talk.
Get up.
After that...
If you don't like
what you hear...
...you still want me dead,
you take your shot.
What I do...
is hunt monsters.
Your dad, Cole --
your dad was a monster.
Yeah, you say that now,
but last time we fought,
you couldn't even
remember his name.
2003, Nyack, New York,
Ed Trenton.
I was working a case.
Three dead --
livers ripped out and eaten
by your father.
[ Chuckles ]
Livers?
Yeah, I tracked him down
that night to your house.
Well, you say
he was a monster.
What kind of monster
was he?
I don't know.
Never seen that kind before,
never seen it again.
All I know is that
he came home that night
looking to kill --
could've been you,
could've been your mom.
No.
The only reason
that didn't happen
is because I was there
to stop him.
I heard his voice.
It was a human voice,
and he begged you to stop!
It's a ploy.
It's a monster's trick.
I know what you heard,
but know this --
that was not
your father, Cole.
Your father
was already gone.
Put it down.
Sam, put it down!
Cole, it's fine.
Dean?
Put it down!
Cole, hey, right here.
We're talking, okay?
[ Sighs ]
How can I
believe you, huh?
How can I believe you?!
[ Sighs ]
My whole life, I've been...
I get it.
That was your story.
Look, man,
I got one of those, too.
Okay, but those stories
that we tell to keep us going?
Man,
sometimes they blind us.
They take us to dark places --
the kind of place
where I might beat the crap
out of a good man
just for the fun of it.
The people who love me,
they pulled me
back from that edge.
Cole, once you touch
that darkness...
It never goes away.
Now, the truth is...
I'm past saving.
I know
how my story ends.
It's at the edge of a blade
or the barrel of a gun.
So, the question is,
is that gonna be today?
That gonna be that gun?
You've got
a family, Cole.
I heard you on the phone
that night.
I'm guessing
they need you to come back,
and they need you
to come back whole.
[ Sighs ]
[ Knock on door ]
I'm...
Hi.
He say where he's going?
Home.
Rowena?
In the wind.
What you said earlier,
back there,
about being past saving --
were you really --
I was just telling the guy
what he needed to hear.
We better go.
Winchesters showed up.
Alpha team went down.
But Beta team's
working contingency --
Had a perimeter
around the hotel.
We got her.
Right in there --
tortured.
If you'd like,
I could finish her off.
Wipe that ridiculous smile
off your face.
What do you want,
a medal?
A "thank you" for cleaning up
the mess you made?!
Everyone working for me
touched?
Bunch of needy, squalling,
incompetent infants.
The king at last.
King of what? Lilliput?
I mean, I'd heard
you were short, but...
[ Chuckles ]
Well?!
Get to it.
Time for
the coup de grace.
Wee boy, is something
the matter with you?
Cat got your tongue, hmm?
Meow.
Mother?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man