Dean: “The Lore.” Hunters.
Men of Letters.
What a load of crap!
I'm a demon.
Dean: There's no point in trying
to bring your brother back now.
Sam: This isn't even
the real you I'm talking to.
Oh, it's the real me,
all right.
Welcome back, Dean.
How you doing?
I'm good.
But I need to work.
If things go sideways --
I mean, like, an inch --
you gotta give me
the heads-up.
Done.
We got work to do.
What is it -- what --
a-a spirit, demon, what?
This can't be possible.
Dragons, dude.
We're hunting a Djinn.
A freaking genie?
Well, then,
what are you?
I'm a pishtaco.
A fish taco?
It's not a man-droid.
It's a shapeshifter.
Vampire pirates?
Vampirates.
Smurfs?
Fairies.
Fairies?
Nipples?
Come on.
Bitch!
Tulpas require
a ton of psychic energy.
[ As Arnold Schwarzenegger ]
It's not a Tulpa.
It's Calliope.
I think I know
what we're dealing with here.
It's the Stay Puft
marshmallow man.
[ British accent ]
Now, now.
I know
it's a terribly sad day.
Bunny Lacroix
was a good woman,
a fair employer
with a kind heart.
But there is work
to be done.
In less than 24 hours,
the Lacroix family
will descend upon this estate
for the funeral
and the reading of the will,
and it is our duty to make sure
this manor's in tip-top shape.
We owe that much to Bunny.
Colette.
To the master closet.
I'd like you to select
Mrs. Lacroix's wardrobe
for the burial.
Olivia.
Please make sure
all the lavatories are spotless.
Why do I have to --
Now, now.
You're still the new hire.
Colette has seniority.
Chop-chop.
There's no time to waste.
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Footsteps approach ]
[ Gasps ]
But...
Y-you're dead.
[ Whimpering ]
[ Gasps ]
Aah!
Aaaaaaah!
[ Rapid footsteps ]
What have you done?
? Supernatural 10x05 ?
Ask Jeeves
Original Air Date on November 18, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey, yo.
Individually brewed.
Technology, man.
Real men don't drink
out of cups this small.
What is that --
“cinnamon roll”?
It's, uh,
“glazed donut.”
Look, man,
if you don't want it, I --
Nah, it's -- got it.
So, any leads on the scanner
or the...Interweb?
Nothing --
not even a cat up a tree.
So right when we're ready
to jump back into it,
it, uh, goes
radio silence.
Murphy's law.
Well, Murphy's a douche.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, feel like taking a detour
to Connecticut?
What?
Found it
while I was dustbusting.
One of ours?
It's one of Bobby's.
And, in total,
27 messages.
The only one that counts
is from two days ago.
Apparently,
Bobby's been named a beneficiary
in Bunny Lacroix's will.
Bunny Lawho?
Attorney said
she's an heiress,
and Bobby's presence
or next of kin
is being requested
in New Canaan.
I figured we qualify.
How did Bobby know
an heiress?
Bobby had secrets, man.
Like loving on
Tori Spelling.
If he only knew
Dean cheated on her.
Anyway, road trip?
Who knows? Maybe Bobby earned us
some beer money.
[ Engine shuts off ]
Wow.
Think we're
a little underdressed?
I mean, the Fed threads
are in the trunk.
You kidding me?
For once,
we don't have to wear suits.
You're lucky
my waistband's not elastic.
[ Doorbell plays “Fuer Elise” ]
[ Chuckles ]
May I help you?
I'm Sam Winchester.
This is Dean Winchester.
We're here
on behalf of Bobby Singer.
Mr. Singer
won't be coming?
No. He passed away.
Oh, I'm sorry
to hear that.
Uh, condolences
for your loss, too.
Thank you.
Well, you just missed
the funeral,
but the family's relaxing
inside, if you'd like to join.
[ Indistinct conversations,
piano music playing ]
[ Clears throat ]
[ Conversations stop ]
Allow me to introduce
Sam and Dean Winchester.
Sam and Dean Winchester
of the Westchester Winchesters?
U-uh, n-- no.
I don't think there's...
Nah.
...Any relation.
Sorry.
No matter.
You two are...
[ Inhales sharply ]
...adorable.
Oh.
Amber: The pink one.
No. I mean the red one.
I'm Heddy, Bunny's cousin,
and this is my sister, Beverly.
Charmed, I'm sure.
And that's
Bunny's youngest brother,
Stanton --
“Stan” for short.
Come on in, fellas.
Join the mourning.
And his child bride,
Amber.
Go, Stan!
Babe, don't. You're breaking
my concentration.
And then there's Dash.
That's the baby of the family.
He's Bunny's great-nephew --
Harvard business.
How do you guys
know Aunt Bunny?
We, uh --
we -- we -- we didn't
personally know her.
Our -- our surrogate dad,
Bobby Singer, did.
Did.
Bobby? Never heard of him.
[ Chuckles ]
But you can fill us in
over the weekend, huh?
The weekend?
Didn't the attorney
tell you?
Service was today, and the
reading of the will tomorrow.
Oh, but you're welcome
to spend the night.
All the rooms sleep two.
Or three.
[ Smack ]
Okay.
[ Chuckles ]
Where's Colette?
She quit.
Poor dear was so distraught
over Mrs. Lacroix's passing.
Went off
to find herself.
Ashram in India?
Uh, Clown College
in Sarasota.
Mm.
Good choice.
May I have a word with you
in the hall in five minutes?
Sure.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
[ Clears throat ]
So [Clears throat] Sam...
[Chuckles] Tell me...
Do you...work out?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Billiard balls clack ]
[ Snootily ]
Charmed, I'm sure.
[ Normal voice ]
What are these people?
I think
they're called W.A.S.P.S.
What?
[ Clears throat ]
My apologies for being
so oblique back there,
but I'm doing you boys
a favor.
O-okay.
As you know,
Mrs. Lacroix bequeathed
something to your Mr. Singer.
But the reading of the will
isn't until tomorrow,
and I would hate for you
to have to stick around
and be forced to --
well, mingle with the family.
Don't worry, Alfred. We know
which one the shrimp fork is.
Kind of.
Oh, Mr. Winchester.
If you're implying that I don't
think you're good enough,
I-it's quite the contrary.
You're far too good.
The Lacroix family is --
well...
How shall I say this
politely?
...money-grubbing leeches.
What are you talking about?
I thought they were all loaded.
Loaded -- yes.
Rich -- no.
The recession
hit every one of them,
and I'm afraid if they knew
what Bunny left you,
those vultures
would try to stake claim.
And since the attorney
kindly agreed to a hand-off,
you don't have to be subjected
to their scrutiny.
Do you have any idea
how Bunny and Bobby
knew each other?
Not in the slightest.
Um, now,
if there's nothing else,
shall I have Olivia
show you out?
No, no. That's, uh --
we got it. Thanks.
Huh.
Kind of fancy
to leave a guy like Bobby.
[ Chuckles ]
You thinking
what I'm thinking?
If Bunny was banging Bobby,
then maybe these rocks are real.
[ Chuckles ]
What do you mean
it's not real?
The old bag
was rolling in it.
Well, looks like
the old bag's got a soft spot
for fake rubies
and cubic zirconium.
[ Groans ]
This is interesting,
though.
It's a key.
A key to what?
There's one way
to find out --
Ask Jeeves.
Beverly saw you
sexting at dinner.
Bev doesn't know what the hell
she's talking about.
I was texting my mom.
An emoticon
of a peeled banana?
She likes fruit.
Just admit it --
you're cheating.
And you're drunk.
Not to mention paranoid.
Just like Lance.
He was always accusing
poor Bunny of sleeping around.
Because she was.
My sister was nothing
but a two-bit hooker in Chanel!
How dare you.
Your sister's dead.
[ Scoffs ]
What the hell
are you looking at?
Good riddance to you both.
[ Deep voice ] Stanton.
What?!
Amber:
I didn't say anything!
Stanton.
No! Aah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
[ Engine shuts off ]
[ Doorbell plays “Fuer Elise” ]
Everything okay?
Not really.
Yeah.
Thanks.
[ Doors close ]
I presume you gentlemen
left something behind?
I'll check the front closet
for...burlap.
I got news for you,
Mr. Belvedere --
the jacket's canvas.
Uh...
You two were here earlier?
Yeah.
Who wants to know?
Detective Howard,
New Canaan P.D.
Congratulations, boys.
You're now officially
murder suspects.
I'm sorry. What?
Yeah, Bunny Lacroix's brother
Stanton was killed this evening.
His body's
just gone to the morgue.
And you think --
I don't know what to think.
And that's why you two
and anyone else who stepped foot
in this house today
is being detained
for questioning.
Beverly, let go of me!
It's so obvious she's guilty.
You're off your rocker,
old lady.
“Old lady”?! I --
[ chuckles ]
I'm 39.
And you have been
since '03.
How -- how dare you.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but -- but who's guilty?
The town slut, Amber.
She killed Stan.
And what's her motive,
“Murder, She Wrote”?
Oh, everyone knows
that Amber was sleeping around.
She wanted to leave Stan,
but her prenup was ironclad,
so she killed him.
Sounds logical.
Well,
unless you believe
that ridiculous story
that she's been peddling.
“A ghost killed Stanton” --
honestly.
Uh, a-a ghost?
She's claming that Bunny's
late husband, Lance, did it.
Have you ever heard
such a thing?
What a panic!
So stupid.
You're nutty as a squirrel
on those synthetic hormones.
“Nutty”? How appalling of you.
Don't they teach you manners in Harvard?
So, uh...Looks like
we might have a case here.
Vengeful spirit?
Yeah.
Think we can get to the car,
get the EMF?
[ Scoffs ] Not with, uh,
detective friendly.
Not a chance.
Guess we're gonna
have to go old-school.
All right. Cold spots it is.
Yeah.
You stay here, keep an eye on
Mrs. Peacock and Colonel Mustard.
I'll sniff around.
All right.
Heddy: For your information, I already
own a big, beautiful yacht.
Dash: Oh, is that
what you call that thing?
Fine.
It's a mahogany sunfish.
[ Door closes ]
[ Beverly and Heddy
speaking indistinctly ]
Hey.
Got to say, for a family
that just lost two members,
you all...seem fine.
Well, Sam, I'll let you in
on a little family secret.
We don't really
like each other.
[ Chuckles ]
Then again,
what family does?
Mine does.
Uh, for the most part.
It's just my brother and me,
so...
Then you're lucky.
Trust me --
it's a miracle
we've been under the same roof
for 24 hours
and haven't --
Oops.
[ Chuckles ]
My bad.
And, uh, w-why are you so sure
Amber didn't do it?
Because Amber's not a killer.
[ Chuckles ]
She has trouble
using Wi-Fi.
I don't exactly think
she's capable of murder.
[ Clank ]
[ Door creaking ]
And her story
about the ghost?
I don't
believe in ghosts.
That said, if anyone
would come back to haunt,
it's Uncle Lance.
Heard he was
a real bastard.
No one really
mourned his death --
except Aunt Bunny, who became
a recluse after he died.
So, maybe the old goat
has a chip on his shoulder.
Who the hell knows?
[ Footsteps approach ]
Dash...
You're up.
[ Hurried footsteps ]
Dean?
Olivia?
Thank God.
I thought you were him.
Him who?
Phillip -- the Butler.
He locked me in here
because I wouldn't lie
to the detective
about what I saw.
What did you see?
[ Voice breaking ] I saw him
roll Colette's body in a rug.
Clown College Colette?
The Butler killed her?
No, no. He just --
he just hid her.
Then who killed her?
I know
this is gonna sound crazy,
but I saw it
with my own eyes.
Let me guess --
Lance's ghost.
No.
Bunny's.
[ Clock chiming ]
[ Clears throat ]
You know what?
Uh, excuse me.
No, no, stay.
Hey. So?
You seen the butler?
No. Why?
'Cause if anybody has answers,
it's him.
We're dealing with
two vengeful spirits.
Apparently, Aunt Bunny had
a bee in her bonnet, as well.
Uh, husband-and-wife
tag-team killer ghosts?
Well, got to keep
the marriage alive somehow.
The key...
is to a hidden attic.
Why would Bunny want Bobby
to have a key to her attic?
I don't know.
It gets weirder.
I found Olivia and Colette
locked inside.
Clown College Colette?
Yeah, but she ain't studying
balloon animals. She's dead.
Now, what does the butler
have to do with all this?
He's the one
who locked them in there.
Now, I don't know why,
but he's covering
for the spooks.
He's acting like
their Renfield.
All right.
We got to find him.
I'll take upstairs. You take down here.
All right.
Detective Howard:
Sam Winchester?
Where did you
run off to?
Well, well, well.
Mm.
What do we have here?
Whatcha doing snooping
around these halls, hmm?
Uh...
[ Chuckles ]
Up to no good?
Why don't we
get up to no good together?
You know, they say
women just get better with age,
like a fine wine
or -- or cheese.
U-uh, I-I -- uh,
I'm lactose-intolerant, so...
Oh, come on, Sammy.
[ Laughs ]
Don't be coy.
We have got a good 10 minutes
before my interrogation,
and I bet a young buck like you
can do a lot in 10 minutes.
[ Breathing heavily ]
I'm right behind you.
[ Chuckling ]
“Right behind me.” oh.
Could you just give me a hand
with this zipper?
I always have
such a hard time --
[ door creaks ]
Uh, leaky faucet's
down the hall.
Cut the crap, Wadsworth.
What are you doing hiding
dead maids in secret rooms?
I know it all looks
rather...peculiar,
but I can explain.
Dean: So, you hid Colette's body
in the attic
so that she wouldn't
steal Bunny's thunder?
I couldn't stand the thought
of overshadowing
Mrs. Lacroix's funeral
with another death.
She deserved a proper farewell.
I owed it to her.
Well, that's crazy.
No, Mr. Winchester.
That's loyalty.
[ Cellphone vibrates ]
[ Clears throat ]
[ Groans ]
[ Squishing, creaking ]
[ Dialing ]
[ Ringing ]
Sam: Dean.
Sam.
Yeah?
It's no ghost.
What?
It's a shapeshifter.
So, the shifter's
getting its jollies
by impersonating
dead people.
Yeah. First Bunny, then Lance,
now Phillip.
Guess we can rule out
“the Butler did it.”
and the creep just shed,
so now it could be anybody.
Even you.
Or you.
We need to find some silver.
[ Gasps ] Oh, my God!
Hey.
He was like that
when we found him.
[ Panting ]
Who did this?
We don't know yet,
okay?
Now, listen.
Calm down.
I know you think
he was working with ghosts,
but there's something way worse
going on here.
Worse than...
What is going on?
If you want to help,
then help.
Can you do that?
Why do you need
the silverware?
For protection.
Butter knives?
Trust us --
there's a method to our madness.
Can you, uh,
hold this?
Dean.
All right.
Let's do this.
Beverly: No.
No.
[ Sighing ] No.
No! Ugh.
Wait, wait, wait. Go back.
He owned an island.
And a harelip.
Well,
who cares if he's ugly
if you're drinking Mai Tais
in the lap of luxury?
[ Clears throat ]
Hey. Hey, ladies.
Hi.
What are you doing?
Trying to find Beverly
a man.
I've resorted
to fishing online
because the live ones
won't bite.
You mean back there?
I-I was just playing
hard-to-get.
Well, then...
You're a very convincing
actor.
[ Chuckles ]
Come.
Sure.
All right.
[ Chuckles ]
Sit here. Yes.
Ah.
Oh.
Mm. [ Chuckles ]
Boo. I'm feeling
so left out.
Well, then, uh...
Come on in, darling.
Water's warm.
Oh!
Ohhh, yes.
Oh.
[ Sighs ]
[ Doorknob rattling ]
[ Gasps ]
Really?
[ Sighs ]
We...can explain.
Let me guess. You two
got bored last Christmas.
New Canaan clambake,
actually.
We were in line at the buffet,
they ran out of steamers,
one thing led to another,
and, well...
[ Chuckles ]
But we didn't kill
Stanton.
We may be guilty of cheating,
but not murder.
Touch these.
What? Why?
Do it, or I go cards-up
on your whole clambake.
Did...We pass?
Yep.
Don't worry.
Your secret is safe with me.
Come on, you two.
Did you see
how long his fingers were?
There's --
there's just --
first of all, did you see this?
Look how long.
Dean: Should I come back
when you're done?
Oh, he's -- he's --
he's calling to me, so...
And it's all going to hell
right here, right now.
[ Heddy and Beverly
continue talking ]
[ Heddy and Beverly laugh ]
Sorry to interrupt.
Bbbbt.
“Grey gardens” cleared.
Okay, well,
so is Dash and Amber.
They're a thing,
by the way.
Y--
yeah. W.A.S.P.S.
Well,
so, that's everyone.
Except for --
[ Olivia screams ]
[ Both gasp ]
[ Breathing shakily ]
Dean:
Well, we got a floater.
Great.
Yeah, he's a goner.
Drowned in a toilet?
How filthy!
What kind of monster
would do such a thing?
Don't look at me.
I was just trying to pee.
Okay, hold on. Before we start
pointing fingers --
Amber has motive.
She killed the detective
because she knew that it was
just a matter of time
before he figured out
she killed Stan.
Bravo, Rizzoli.
You solved the case.
Want to weigh in, too,
Isles?
I didn't kill Stanton
or the detective,
and I have proof.
Okay, guys --
My alibi
is in this room.
Ooh. Wait for it.
Amber couldn't have killed the detective,
'cause she was with me.
[ Gasps ]
We're in love.
We're...
sleeping together.
I knew it.
Well, then, you have motive, too.
You offed Stan because
you were diddling his wife.
Ohh. The old lady
doth protest too much.
You're only pointing the finger
to distract from your own guilt,
and you probably
got Baby Jane to help.
[ Gasps ]
Well, I never!
I'm leaving!
All right, hang on.
First of all,
who talks like that?
Second of all,
no one's leaving, okay?
Oh, get your hands off me,
young man.
Okay, see,
I don't trust anyone,
and leaving just makes you look guilty.
Ohh.
Dean is right, okay?
We have four corpses now.
Four corpses?
Yes. You can add
Phillip and Colette to the list.
Clown College Colette?
But I thought --
She's dead, all right?
She's dead.
And we can't help you
unless you stop arguing
with one another.
You need to trust us.
Trust you?
[ Scoffs ]
Uh, we don't even
know you.
Look, buddy,
I'm trying to be objective here,
but we've had countless
family functions before,
and even though
we wanted to kill one another,
we never did.
Dash is right. Our get-togethers
never end in murder.
The only thing different
this time around is you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, first of all, whoa.
Whatever
you're suggesting --
You two!
[ Both gasp ]
Let's go.
Don't even think about it.
[ Gun cocks ]
I...hunt pheasant.
Sit tight
until the cops get here.
You don't want
to do this.
We are your best shot
at making it out of here alive.
We're not the bad guys,
Dash.
I beg to differ.
You're wearing flannel.
Hey!
[ Door closes, lock clicks ]
Hey.
Keys.
No, it's locked
from the outside.
Are you kidding me?
[ Grunts ]
Great.
[ Keys clatter ]
“Made in Taiwan.”
freakin' stainless steel.
So that's why no one sizzled?
They're not even real silver?
[ Sighs ]
First, cubic zirconium,
and now this.
No wonder
the rich stay rich.
How we gonna
kill this thing?
You know, we got silver bullets
in the trunk.
Yeah, assuming
we ever make it out of here.
I don't get it. Why would
Sam and Dean want us dead?
Isn't it obvious?
They wanted
our inheritance.
Guess whatever Aunt Bunny
left them wasn't good enough.
For the love of god, Dash,
put down the gun
before you kill someone!
It's okay.
I...Hunt...Pheasant.
Put it down!
[ Gasps ]
I knew those boys
were trailer trash
the moment they rolled up
in that American-made.
Not to mention
homosexuals.
Ugh.
Homosexual murderers.
Like Leopold and Loeb.
Only hotter. mmm.
Oh.
Call the police at once.
Oh, I don't think so.
[ Laughs ]
Excuse me, young lady?
Killer or no killer,
you're still on the clock.
[ Chuckles softly ]
You idiots
couldn't be more wrong --
about everything.
Don't you know if it's not
the butler, it's the maid?
Dean?
You got to see this.
We got played by the maid.
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
Both doors are reinforced.
I'm not the maid.
Well,
that explains the dust.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm Bunny's daughter.
What are you talking about?
Bunny didn't have a child.
Oh, yes, she did --
a very devoted one.
I loved mother
more than anything,
which is more than I can say
for any of you.
Then, where have you been hiding
all these years?
The attic.
Like in the movie.
[ Sighing ] Oh, Amber.
Outside of mother,
Phillip was the only one
at the manor who knew.
So after she died, he took pity on me,
and he let me out.
He told me
to pose as the new maid
so I can hide
in plain sight.
That's why
you killed Colette --
for her job?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Colette was just an accident.
I just wanted to scare her
because I caught her stealing.
Well, that doesn't explain
wanting us dead.
None of us are thieves,
huh?
On, no. You're worse.
Your greed,
your disdain,
your blatant disrespect
for mother --
oh,
you all had it coming!
But...why kill Phillip?
I mean,
if he was on your side...
Because he turned on me.
After Stanton,
he locked me back up.
Lucky for me,
the cute, dumb one let me out.
Gun safe.
Hey.
Try these.
No wonder you were locked away.
You're a monster!
Oh, you have no idea.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Both gasp ]
What in God's name --
Shut up!
[ Gun cocks ]
[ Footsteps approach ]
[ Amber screams ]
Stay here!
Did anyone else
wet themselves?
You don't have
a clear shot.
Neither do you.
Killing you
is the next best thing
to killing Bobby Singer.
What's your beef
with Bobby?
For starters,
he killed my father.
Lance was a shifter?
Lance wasn't my father!
Mother had an affair
with a shifter.
She got pregnant,
told Lance I was his.
He bought it...
Until she brought me back
from the hospital.
My real dad was waiting.
Lance put up a fight, but he was
no match for a shifter.
And just as my dad
was about to take me...
...the hunter
became the hunted.
Bobby.
[ Breathing shakily ]
After Bobby killed my father,
he came after me.
Mother pleaded with him
to spare me.
He agreed --
under one condition.
That she keep you
locked up.
For my safety
and the safety of others.
Mother told the family
she lost the baby.
And she locked me
in the attic.
But she remained devoted to me
until the very end --
even got Bobby to promise
to take care of me
if anything happened to her.
Wait a minute.
Then, Bobby spared you.
You should be grateful.
For what?!
Keeping me locked up
my whole life?
It would have been kinder
to kill me.
Olivia...
You don't
have to do this.
Being a monster
is a choice.
That choice was made for me
a long time ago.
Why haven't you
taken a shot?
Oh.
You don't have
any silver bullets, do you?
[ Gunshot ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Gunshots, casings clink ]
Yes, officer.
Yes,
thank you very much.
Yes, no,
you can't miss it.
Big house on the end
of the street.
All right.
Bye, now.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Guys?
Police are on their way.
What a mess.
[ Chuckles ]
I owe you two an apology.
Don't sweat it.
I mean, you were
just protecting your family,
and...there's nothing wrong
with that.
So, I spoke
to Aunt Bunny's attorney.
He said,
outside from the pendant,
everything was left
to Olivia.
Hey, you know what?
Speaking of that...
...you guys
should keep it.
It's a key
to the attic.
Bobby must have really
meant something to Aunt Bunny.
How can we repay you?
You know what?
Just forget
we were ever here.
[ Chuckles ]
But you saved our lives.
I want everyone to know
what heroes you --
Look, pal, the fact
that we pulled your bacon
out of the fire
is nobody's business.
Okay?
Hey.
I'm serious, Izod.
Put a pin in it.
Or we'll come back
for your preppy ass.
[ Engine turns over ]
Dean, what was that all about
back there?
[ Chuckles ]
What are you
talking about?
I mean...
All those extra shots
after the shifter
was already dead.
What was that?
I don't know.
Target practice?
Come on, man.
I'm serious.
You sure it wasn't...
I don't know, demon residue
or something to do
with the Mark or --
No.
No, none of that.
Right.
[ Sighs ]
Look, man, I got to be honest --
oh, my God, Sam.
It was my first kill
since I've been back.
You know,
I got a little anxious.
I wanted to make sure it was
done right -- plain and simple.
It's --
why am I even
explaining this to you?
[ Bob Seger's “Travelin' Man”
playing ]
Dean, I --
? sometimes at night,
I see their faces ?
? I feel the traces
they've left on my soul ?
? those are the memories
that make me a wealthy soul ?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man