Werewolves that are turned up to
four generations from pure blood
are less feral and can transform
before, during,
and after the lunar cycle.
A human by day,
a freak animal killing machine
by moonlight.
I mean, werewolves are badass.
Best part about it is,
we already know how to
bring these suckers down --
one of these bad boys
right to the heart.
Dean's a demon.
I don't know how you did this,
what kind of black magic stunt
you pulled.
But hear me -- I will
save my brother or die trying.
Stop! It's over, Dean!
There ain't much difference
from what I turned into
to what you already are.
What exactly is that supposed to mean?
I know what you did
when you went looking for me.
Which one of us
is really a monster? Hmm?
You might actually
be worse than me.
We got a whole bunch more
of these to go.
You can make it a lot easier
on yourself.
What the hell are we doing
to him, Cass?
The ritual of
purified blood
is the only treatment I know.
You look worried, fellas.
Welcome back, Dean.
Maybe you should, um,
take some time
before you get back to work,
allow yourself to heal.
? I saw a werewolf with
a Chinese menu in his hand ?
? walkin' through the streets
of Soho in the rain ?
? he was lookin' for a place
called Lee ho fook's ?
? gonna get a big dish
of beef chow mein ?
? aaoooooo!
Werewolves of London ?
I know, right?
? Aaoooooo! ?
? I saw a werewolf
drinking a pi?a colada ?
? at Trader Vic's ?
? and his hair was perfect ?
? little old lady got
mutilated late last night ?
Damn.
Girl after my own heart.
That's the idea, sweetie.
? Aaoooooo! ?
what the hell?
? Werewolves of London ?
? Aaoooooo! ?
? Supernatural 10x04 ?
Paper Moon
Original Air Date on October 28, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey, something I needed
to ask you.
Shoot.
You've been...
Kicked, bit,
scratched, stabbed,
possessed, killed...
And you sprain
your friggin' elbow?
Dude, it was more than
a sprain. All right?
And it was a friggin' demon,
but...
But what?
That sling come with a slice
of crybaby pie on the side?
Please.
How you doing?
Golden, man.
Come on.
Seriously, I'm good.
I am.
You know, we got...
Three more cases of this stuff
on ice in the trunk.
Taking some “we time.”
best decision we ever made.
Here that.
See that thing
in the paper this morning?
Maybe it was an animal kill.
It was three kills,
and it was in the same town,
all within the last month.
Yeah, you're right.
We should call some guys,
have 'em fix it.
Good. Smart.
Done.
Or...
We could be in and out.
It's a milk run.
Right,
because that happens never.
Look, Sam,
what we're doing here,
it's good, okay?
You and me hanging out.
But I need to work.
I need this.
If things go sideways...
I mean, like, an inch,
you gotta give me the heads-up.
Done. You got my word.
Gentlemen.
Well, I'm not gonna lie.
We're damn glad to see you.
You boys must come up
on stuff like this all the time.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
Hell, seen raccoons
in rec rooms
and bears in swimming pools.
But this? You tell me.
Yeah.
Oh. Well, uh...
Where do we start?
What with, uh...Logging.
Ice caps.
Bitcoin. Yeah.
Obama.
You know what? Maybe --
maybe, uh, you could
walk us through the attacks.
Any similarities,
anything weird.
Only thing weird about them
was how similar they were.
Folks torn clean through.
Hearts absent.
Hearts absent as in --
Consumed, most likely.
And there were no witnesses?
Well, the town square attack,
the parking lot...
Those were real late.
But the bar?
Hell, with how jammed
the place was,
you'd think somebody other than
Tommy would've seen something.
And what did he see?
Honestly, not much.
Now Tommy ain't exactly what
we call a reliable witness.
And he's telling
anybody who'll listen
he saw some girl
go out back with Barker,
and she got torn up, too.
So there was a second victim?
Well, sure...
Expect Tommy's a drunk.
There's no body, no D.N.A.,
no blood trail,
no nothing to suggest that.
Give me one sec.
Yeah.
Hearts missing.
Sounds wolfy to me, right?
Yeah. Pretty brazen,
even for a werewolf.
You think it was the girl?
Let's find out.
Yeah, Barker and I
have been raising hell,
chasing tail,
and riding for a long time.
Part of him always knew
when his clock ran out,
it wasn't gonna be pretty.
To go out like that?
By some animal?
Just ain't right.
You mind, uh, you mind
telling us what went down?
It was just another party,
you know?
Barker went out back.
The next thing you know,
everyone's yelling
and screaming,
and he's all torn up.
Now the sheriff mentioned
you thought there might've been
a girl involved.
You think
she was killed, too?
Nope.
So there was no girl?
Couldn't say.
You know we're not cops,
right?
Badge is a badge.
Well, you should also know that
working outdoors the way we do,
we see some --
some pretty weird crap.
Stuff that we can't explain.
I mean, hell, half the stuff,
we wouldn't have
believed it ourselves
had we not seen it together.
Well, you don't have to live
in this town, mister.
You don't have to deal with
the ridicule.
I'm just saying that
crazy might not be half as crazy
as you think.
So if someone were to tell you
they saw a ghost,
you'd...believe that?
Just assume
we believe everything.
Okay, then.
The other night,
I was taking a ride
past the old Sturges farm.
You know,
thinking about the rides
me and Barker used to go on.
I saw her, man.
Saw her who?
The girl.
What, after the attack?
Hell, yeah.
She was just standing there,
all bloody, watching me.
So -- so I turn the hell around,
I-I ran back, thinking,
damn, you know, she --
she's hurt or something.
But...She was just gone.
Like, gone.
Like a ghost.
No, I don't give one red cent
in hell what the cops say.
She was there. She was eaten.
She's a freakin' ghost.
Well...
Ghosts don't shred people
like that.
Yeah, well...
This flea bag,
looks like she ain't done
chowing down
on Sons of Anarchy just yet.
Guess she likes bad boys.
Well, wait'll she gets
a load of us.
Stop ignoring my calls.
Pick up the phone
and call me right now.
This isn't how
it's supposed to go.
Look, I've been down this road
before and I'm not going to...
What?
Kate?
I know who you are.
Congratulations.
After what happened at school,
I thought you'd let me go.
Yeah, well, that was before
you started dropping bodies.
What?
Guy at the bar saw you
before you went all Wolverine
on his buddy.
So...Surprise.
Here we are.
Kate, you said you were
gonna go straight.
What happened?
I guess things change.
Being this...
I tried to be strong,
but the hunger was too much.
Too hard.
It's not like anyone
gave me a handbook
on how to be a werewolf.
Looks like you're doing
a pretty good job so far.
Break some hearts,
then you eat 'em.
I was on my own.
I...evolved.
So that's what you call
killing innocent people?
Whatever you're gonna do,
just...do it.
Hey.
You know what?
Let me do it.
Why?
Because...
I think you should
sit this one out.
What are you talking about?
You're not ready, Dean.
Hello?
Warden, we had another
animal attack over at
the high school gymnasium.
Guy was a security guard.
Same M.O. as the other three.
When?
Deputy said the victim's blood
was still warm
when he got there,
so had to be
less than an hour ago.
Of course. Thank you.
Um, I'll be in touch.
We got a problem.
What, besides, uh,
werewolf Barbie over here?
Yeah.
There was another kill,
across town, just before dark.
Well, how did Kate
get her murder on
and then get back here b--
- You don't think she did it.
- Look... I don't know, man.
But as far as I'm concerned...
Damn it!
All right,
if she's not icing people,
then why play
the big bad wolf?
Maybe she's running
with a pack?
You know,
trying to protect them?
Well,
a hell of a price to pay.
She was about two seconds away
from taking a dirt nap.
What is that?
It's her phone.
Let's see who she was
Booty calling when we pulled up.
Thank you for calling
the Lincoln Motel.
Can I help you?
So what's this about
me not being ready back there?
I'm -- I wasn't...
trying to start something, Dean.
I was just saying, I thought
that was the whole point
of us taking a break.
You know?
Oh, no. No, yeah.
I get that.
And, you know,
there's no worries there.
Okay.
But I gotta ask.
What about you?
What about me, what?
Are you ready?
Why wouldn't I be ready?
Lester.
Lester?
My wife kicked me
to the curb.
We haven't had sex
for four months,
but not that she hasn't
been having plenty.
It is possible that you can
have your revenge.
Who summons me,
and for what purpose?
Lester! don't!
Kill my wife,
and my soul is yours.
Who are you?
Uhh! Ow!
You're a punk-ass demon!
And you work for me now.
Uhh!
You're serious?
This is about Lester?
Um, don't get me wrong.
I'm not --
I'm not -- I'm not trying to
start anything either, okay?
I'm just saying, maybe...
maybe we oughta talk about that.
Okay, expect there's nothing
to talk about.
Okay.
I just figured,
since we're opening up veins
that maybe you'd want
to talk about
the guy who you made
sell his soul.
The guy who you then killed,
right?
I mean, that's the same guy
we're talking about?
I was a demon.
Oh, you were a demon?
Oh, I didn't realize that.
Hey, man, Lester was gonna pay
for that soul shake
sooner or later.
So technically,
it's still on you.
What do you want from me, Dean?
Look, I w--
I'm not happy about it, okay?
But I needed to find you.
So if I had to...
bend a few rules...
Go dark.
Sure. Label it if you want.
Look, man, again,
I'm not complaining, okay?
In fact, I'm doing just
the opposite of complaining.
I...
I just...
You know, between Lester
and the others...
There weren't others.
Okay, either way,
maybe we both needed
that time off.
This is good.
Yeah.  Okay.
All right,
so the, uh, clerk says
a blonde rolled into room 3
just before sunup.
She alone?
He thinks so.
She's on the move.
What's she doing?
Looking for breakfast.
Kate!
It's over.
Oh, god.
Please, don't.
I'll give you anything you want.
Where's Kate?
Who?
You were just
in her motel room.
What? That's my room.
Why were you following
that guy?
Robbie? I-I know him.
I just wanted to surprise him.
Test her.
Test me for what?
No!
Help! Somebody me help!
Just take it easy.
I don't want to die.
Oh! Uhh!
Stop it! Stop it!
don't!
She's my sister.
I lost her.
Kate, why is your sister
a werewolf, huh?
Hey. Hey.
Why?!
Let her talk.
I am!
Then put the gun down.
Why? So she can run again?
Nuh-uh.
She just saved our lives.
My sister is a werewolf
because I turned her into one.
Okay, this is the part
where you help yourself out.
I-I don't care. All right?
I'm sick of the lies.
Let me get this straight.
We let you run
because we take pity on you,
and you turn around
and you start making pups?
You start killing people?!
It's not like that!
I'm no killer.
Well, the way I remember it
from the snuff film
that you left us,
is that you killed
your boyfriend's best friend.
That's because Brian went crazy.
I had no other choice.
Okay, Kate,
if this wasn't you...
That's a big “if.”
Then who was it?
Your sister?
Your sister do this, Kate?
Really?
You almost took a bullet
for her, and you got nothing?
What do you want me to say?
The truth!
Hey, guys. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Can we, uh, take it
somewhere else?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Go grab some coffee,
maybe some bear hearts.
Let's party.
Just so you know,
Brian's the reason
I carry this.
Hey.
I'm just
showing you something.
In case I ever lose it,
like Brian did,
you won't have to kill me.
Yeah, well, saying it and doing
it are two different things.
I'm serious.
And whether
you believe me or not,
I've never hurt anyone
who didn't deserve it.
And I have never, ever
eaten a human heart.
Guess that explains
all the dead chickens
back at the barn.
I eat what I can find,
what people won't miss,
hopefully.
Small game, deer.
I meditate.
Yoga helps.
Yoga?
Okay.
You laugh, but...
I'll pretty much try anything
to keep that side of me
under control.
Well, that is great, Kate.
It really is.
And it's nice to see
that, uh,
this hippie-dippie
new age crap has
had such a positive influence
over your sister.
Tasha...
She's a different story.
After I left school, I was...
Adrift.
Lost.
Not really sure
where to go or...
What to do, so...
I went someplace safe.
I went home.
But...Even though I'd be good,
I started to think about
my family.
How safe were they going
to be?
I was a werewolf.
And then, of course,
there was you two.
What if you showed up and tried
to kill me?
I couldn't risk that.
So I...
walked away.
Never called, never wrote,
just...
Started a new life.
Until one day, I saw a posting
on my sister's Facebook page.
Tasha had been in
a really bad car accident.
The doctors didn't think
she was gonna make it.
We were always so close,
so...
I had to go say good-bye.
Then...
It hit me.
This curse that I had,
that had brought me nothing
but pain and suffering,
could actually finally
maybe do something good.
If I turned Tasha
into a werewolf,
it would heal her wounds,
save her life,
give her a second chance.
So, uh...
I did the unthinkable.
At first, I thought I'd failed,
that...
Even though
werewolves heal quickly,
it was too late for Tasha.
Then she woke up,
not sick anymore, but okay.
Hi. Hey.
Hi.
Tasha had so many questions.
What happened?
How did she get here?
So...
I was straight with her.
The good, the bad, the ugly.
What we were and why we could
never go back home,
and the responsibility we had
to control what we'd become.
I picked you up
from the hospital
I'm gonna take you
someplace safe, okay?
It was a lot to swallow.
But we had each other,
and that felt like enough.
Or...So I thought.
My sister,
she gave in to everything
that I had warned her about.
And...
I knew,
even if I couldn't bring myself
to admit it then...
I knew I was losing her.
So back at the barn,
that was all just an act
to protect Tasha?
She's family.
And, yeah,
worth eating a bullet for.
And she needs me now
more than ever.
This is my mess.
I gotta clean it up.
And how do you plan
on doing that, Kate?
By getting Tasha out of here.
She hasn't listened to you yet.
Why do you think
she's gonna start now?
I don't know, but...
I've gotta try.
Y-you know, we'll go out
into the woods.
We'll drop out
for however long it takes
until she learns
to control this.
Little late for team building,
do you think?
So, what?
I just abandon her?
I did this.
I owe her every chance
to make it right.
What if she never does?
Then I'll take care of it.
You'll take care of it?
You know what that means?
Why don't you ask Brian?
Well, maybe it doesn't have
to come to that.
You know, if you had
shot straight with us
from the get-go,
we might've been able
to help you a lot sooner.
What do you mean?
By curing you both.
Shut up.
Yeah, okay,
or you're welcome.
There is no cure for werewolves.
And for a long time,
that was true,
but we found one.
Now we've got everything
we need on our end.
Okay? But the clock
is tickin',
and we need one more thing --
Tasha.
Unless you wanna do this
without her.
N-no. No.
It's a long drive, but...
I know where to find her.
Dude, what are you doing?
There is no cure.
There's one.
Dean, it's a little more
complicated than that.
Kate and Tasha are monsters,
okay?
Last I checked,
we kill monsters.
Right, but how can you
possibly blame Kate
for fighting for her sister?
We do it all the time.
Well, yeah, and that's
worked wonders for us.
Well, we're still here,
aren't we?
Yeah, but is it right?
I mean, all that you've done for
me, I've still got this Mark.
And we'll figure that out.
We always do.
But you can't take whatever's
happened to us or to you
and -- and dump it
at these girls' feet.
All right, so, what?
You wanna nuance this thing?
Hit me. What's your plan?
Kate?
She's out.
Okay. Then, um...
I gotta tell you something.
I, uh...
I lied about Lester.
What?
There were others.
Other humans?
No. No, no. And --
and I'm sure there were
a few hunters I rubbed --
or I...punched the wrong way,
but...No.
I pretty much saved
my best stuff for the bad guys.
But you gotta
understand something, Dean.
I watched you die.
And I carried you.
I carried your corpse
into your room,
and I put your dead body
on your bed,
and then you just...
Yeah.
I know.
I guess I was hoping
that note would, you know,
fill in the blanks.
“Don't look for me”?
That note?
Yeah, that was
really informative. Thanks.
Yeah.
I...
What?
It's embarrassing, you know?
W-what's embarrassing?
All of it.
You know, the -- the --
that note.
Crowley.
Everything.
Dean, you were a demon.
I was a demon? Oh, thanks.
I didn't -- I didn't realize.
Shut up.
Not to mention,
I never even said “thank you”"
so...
You don't ever have to
say that, not to me.
Well...
Good. Then I guess...
Guess it's all gravy.
Little R&R
and we are back at it.
Hey.
How we doing?
We're getting close.
What is this place?
Ever since Tasha and I
were little,
we've been coming up
to this cabin with our parents.
Now why do you think
Tasha will even be here?
When she because a wolf,
we knew it was gonna be hard,
so we kinda came up
with this escape plan
in case things ever got bad.
So it's a rendezvous spot?
Pretty much.
Now what?
Maybe I should go in first,
explain all this?
Sounds good.
What are doing?!
You son of a bitch!
There is no cure, is there?
I trusted you.
It's not her fault.
It's mine.
She killed people.
Because I did this to her, okay?
So if you want
your pound of flesh, take me.
We'll deal with you later.
But she can be saved!
No.
Tasha's in too deep.
You don't ever come back
from that,
not ever.
Come on, Sammy.
No!
Please!
don't do this!
Don't!
Please, Sam!
Please don't!
I can't believe
my own sister betrayed me.
Yeah, expect...she didn't.
You're not gonna shoot me.
And why is that?
Sam.
Drop the gun, or Dreamreat here
gets his mind blown.
Don't do it, Sam. Uhh!
Well...Sammy?
Tasha!
What did --
who are these people?
Brandon. Travis.
I turned them.
They're our new family.
Yeah, you're a regular
psycho Brady Bunch.
Hey!
No!
You've always had
crappy taste in guys.
Tasha, we can talk about this.
They were gonna kill me.
And now
you're protecting them?
No. I'm protecting you.
Yeah. I'm good. Thanks.
So here's how it's gonna be.
You can walk away
or you can join my pack.
I'm not walking away.
Then prove
you got what it takes.
Eat his heart out.
Kate.
You don't have to do this.
No one's talking to you,
Paul Bunyan.
So?
No.
Take them. Have some fun.
Oh, and I want a heart to-go.
Put it in a doggie bag.
On your knees!
Wow. Well,
I'm awfully flat--uhh!
Ohh! Uhh!
T., I can help you
get better.
Oh, I am better.
And smarter and stronger
and awesome.
I'm a freakin' superhero.
Who kills innocent people?
No, that's not you.
You were a good kid.
I was weak and scared.
I let people
walk all over me --
mom, dad,
friends, boyfriends,
you.
But I'm not weak anymore.
And I'm not scared.
I'm scary.
I was trying to give you
a second chance.
You wouldn't have been...
normal,
but we would've had
each other.
We still can.
But I'm not gonna
spend my life on the run
from people like
Mary-Kate and Ashley out there.
We're strong, Kate.
We can go anywhere we want.
We do anything we want.
And of anyone gets
in our way...
You don't have to be alone
anymore.
We can do this together.
You okay?
I've been better.
These guys, huh?
Can you believe 'em?
Yeah, a couple of minor leaguers.
Yo!
You're dead.
You don't get to talk.
In fact --
uhh!
Uhh!
Well,
welcome to the majors, boys.
Kate...
We're gonna be good, okay?
We're gonna be great.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
So we going after her?
I don't know, Dean.
But you gotta admit,
when push came to kill,
she did good.
Yeah.
So maybe it's a good thing
you didn't shoot her.
Really? You're gonna Monday
morning quarterback this thing?
If you got an itch
to scratch...
Dean, look,
we both jumped on this case.
I agree.
Equal parts blame there.
But the whole idea behind
laying low was to rest,
to...try and deal with
everything we --
everything you went through.
Maybe we jumped back in
too fast.
I mean, Dean,
you were a demon.
You still have the Mark.
Didn't you ever wanna
talk about it?
Talk about it?
Talk about it how?
Come on, man.
I am coming on, Sam.
Look, I know what happened.
Okay? I was there.
Remember?
I'm not trying to get by it.
I just...
That's not what
this was about.
Then what is this about?
About gettin'
back in the saddle. Okay?
Doing something good,
not stewing in my own crap.
And what if you're not ready?
Well, I'll give you
one thing.
Pretty damned good
at getaways.
Yeah.
Well, I decided that living
was better than being dead.
For what it's worth,
thank you.
At the end of the day,
she was your sister.
No. She wasn't.
Listen to me, Kate.
You keep moving,
keep your nose clean,
and we can stop meeting
like this.
I hear ya.
And I will,
but I'm not gonna promise,
'cause...
Yeah.
See you around, kid.
I sure as hell hope not.
Let's say you're right.
About what?
Everything.
Maybe I'm not ready
to hunt.
But I am just trying to
do the right thing, man,
'cause I'm so sick and tired
of doing the wrong one.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man