What's your sin?
I was a horrible mother.
Crowley: You are shamelessly
sucking up so that I'll free you
so you can run amok and gum up
my operation once again.
Who is there left
for you to trust?
You and I
are very much alike.
Yeah, except I didn't kill
my brother.
The Mark can be transferred
to someone who's worthy.
But make me a promise
first.
When I call you,
use the Blade on me.
Dean: Don't you think that if Cain
knew how to remove the Mark,
he would have done it,
like, centuries ago?
I'm done
trying to find a cure, Sammy.
Dean, Cass is so close.
Maybe Cass is
onto something with Cain --
but the answer
is not out there.
It's with me.
So, I'm gonna fight it
till I can't fight it
anymore.
[ Bangs on cell door ]
Lights out in five.
Hey, any mail?
Oh, the usual --
postcards
from anti-penalty folk,
proposals
from your lady admirers.
You said
you were done with those.
Hey, how's your wife,
by the way -- Amanda?
That's her name,
isn't it?
You know I killed
an Amanda once?
My fourth.
I'd do your wife the same,
buddy,
only slower.
Two weeks from Tuesday,
Tommy.
Yeah.
Let's do it!
Let's do it now,
tonight!
[ Beeping, bell ringing ]
[ Ringing stops ]
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Buzzer ]
Tolliver giving you
the usual grief?
[ Chuckles ]
Nothing new.
[ Electricity crackling ]
[ Chain rattles ]
[ Electricity crackling,
chain rattling ]
I can't wait
till he's gone.
[ Electricity crackles ]
Who the hell are you?
How'd you get in here?!
I've gone by many names
in this life.
The father of murder
is one of them.
[ Breathing heavily ]
And by the state's count,
you've taken six lives yourself,
Tommy.
Although by my count,
it's nine.
Oh, come on.
You aren't one of those
“it wasn't me” type fellas,
are you?
Because I know
you're a killer,
just like me.
Yeah, I did it.
Honesty.
That's good.
That's the spirit!
Ugh!
[ Groaning ]
Now, I bet you're wondering
what I'm doing here.
Did I come to punish you
or save you?
Well...
The truth is, Tommy...
I'm here to do both.
[ Gasps, gurgles ]
? Supernatural 10x14 ?
The Executioner's Song
Original Air Date on February 17, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Dean: The Zodiac?
Sam: Seven victims.
Dahmer?
17.
That's some freaky stuff, man.
It's a whole new side of you.
It's called true crime, Dean.
It's a hobby.
No. Bass fishing, needlepoint --
that's a hobby, okay?
Collecting
serial-killer stats --
that's --
that is an illness.
[ Chuckles ]
Get your badge.
Yeah.
[ Intercom buzzes ]
Man: Hello, gentlemen.
State the nature of your visit.
From the office
of the Inspector General.
Got an appointment
with the warden.
Thank you.
Parking is to the left.
Look for
visitor parking only.
Dean: All right,
so what are the stats
on this, uh,
vanishing act here?
Tommy Tolliver was convicted
of six murders back in '09,
but those are
just the ones that stuck.
According to the news,
he escaped from a locked cell
on death row,
this inexplicable,
Houdini-esque escape.
So what are we thinking?
Some sort of
a mass-murdering magician?
Yeah,
or a teleporting demon
or a who knows what that
can walk through Supermax walls.
Could be in our wheelhouse.
[ Scoffs ]
Yeah, your wheelhouse.
“Hobby.”
[ bell ringing,
cell door unlocks ]
[ Indistinct conversations]
[ Sighs ]
Warden Skeiff?
Uh, Inspectors Moore
and Ranaldo.
We spoke on the phone.
Yeah.
Welcome to death row.
Have a look.
But good luck finding anything
out of TDJC compliance.
Sam: So, why don't you tell me
what happened?
[ Warbling ] The night
Tolliver disappeared,
our little ship was running
as tight as ever,
and I got documentation
to prove it.
Do you stand by
what the press is saying --
locked cell,
no security breach,
no guard misconduct?
Which press?
Mainstream media
is calling for my head,
said I was
grossly incompetent.
But the tabloids,
they're saying --
They're saying
it's magic [Scoffs]
That Tommy pulled off
some dark miracle to escape.
You saying
you believe that?
I'm saying there was
some kind of magician
on the block last night,
but it wasn't Tommy.
That's right before
Tolliver vanished.
Was that a brownout?
That was my thought,
but then...
Is it one of the guards?
Nope.
But I don't know who he is,
how he got in,
or how he and Tolliver
got out.
Can you zoom in on that?
Can and have.
Too dark to make out
much of anything.
Do it.
Freeze it.
Blow it up.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Gonna answer that?
Not at this moment.
[ Ringing continues ]
You're wasting your time.
I told you,
I don't know where he is.
Me and Cain ain't friends.
He kills demons.
Low-level guys like me
keep our distance.
You sure about that?
[ Sizzling ]
All right!
All right.
[ Breathing heavily ]
He's been seen,
past few months,
making passes
through Bogg's marsh,
one county over.
No one knows why,
what for.
Like I said,
we keep our distance.
And that's all you know.
Yes.
Yes, I swear.
Okay.
Aaaaah!
Demon: 86 last quarter,
while I only get credit for 48.
A-and I was working
with Alban
on nearly all
of those soul jobs.
[ Game beeping ]
If you don't arrive at a point
within the next 10 seconds,
so help me, I'll --
As a crossroads demon,
I have received less credit
than I am due
for soul collections...
...my king.
So you're looking
for a promotion?
No. I'm just asking...
I'm merely suggesting
that I get credit
for the work that I did
beside Alban.
Equal credit
for equal work.
Fine.
You can have your credit.
Thank you.
The wee man! Ugh!
Mother,
you have, uh, an opinion
you'd like to share
with the room?
Oh, no.
Private thought,
nothing to do with you
or the affairs of the court.
[ Sighs ]
It's just
not what I would do.
Oh, enlighten us all.
What would you do?
This demon asks you
to equalize credit
for his and another's work --
split the baby,
if you will.
Well [Laughs] then I would
well and truly split the baby.
I'd cut this puling, pathetic,
greed-grubbing git in two,
literally,
then I'd nail
his bloody halves
to the doors of the court --
a reminder to all
not to waste the king's time.
Whiners beget whiners.
You can't reward
behavior like that --
why I never gave in when you
asked for sweeties as a child,
no matter how much you cried.
Well, you were a very...
chunky child, darling.
Bit of a bloater.
That's enough.
What'll it be, sir?
Let's do...
What she said.
Wha...
N-no, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
Come on!
[ Screams ]
That's my boy.
So?
[ Groans ]
Cass is still not answering.
Great. Well, I have been looking
into Tommy Tolliver,
seeing if I can figure out
why Cain went to the trouble
of springing him.
And?
Still pretty unclear.
I did find this blotter
out of Orlando
about his dad,
Leon Tolliver.
Uh, like father, like son.
Convicted felon, fresh warrant
for an assault charge,
but he's gone missing,
hasn't been seen in a week.
You think
the two are connected?
I mean, the police just assumed
he fled the warrant,
but if Cain took Tommy,
it might not be a coincidence.
So, what, Cain's got a vendetta
against the entire family?
Maybe.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
It's Cass.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Hey, where you at?
Illinois.
Hey, Cass, we got a lead.
Cain abducted
a Texas death row inmate
named Tommy Tolliver.
He's dead.
What?
How do you know?
Call it an educated guess.
Cain has been very busy.
Okay, where are you?
We'll come to you.
[ Rustling ]
I'll call you back.
Hello, Castiel.
What have you done?
These bodies?
Just cleaning up a mess I made
a long time ago.
Cain,
I know what you were.
But you'd resisted
for so long.
What can I say?
I got the taste back.
With Abaddon's army
gunning for me,
I had to
take up arms again,
and I liked how it felt.
Those were demons.
These...
[ Sighs ]
Humans.
Eh, the Mark thirsts
for all kinds.
This is a massacre.
Yes.
And soon
it'll be a genocide.
My children,
my whole poisoned issue.
A lot of them out there
right now --
killers,
fighters, thieves,
some more peaceful
than others.
But they still carry it --
the disease.
If the Mark wants blood,
I'll give it mine.
You'll kill them all?
You are Adam and Eve's
firstborn.
Your descendents
are Legion.
At most,
I'm culling...1 in 10.
Of everyone.
I've got time.
How's Dean, by the way?
I hear he did good,
took Abaddon down.
He's not well.
Even with
the First Blade hidden,
Dean is losing his fight
against the Mark.
If we don't find a cure --
There is no cure.
I'm living proof of that.
But don't worry about Dean.
I'll get to him,
in due time.
Sorry, Castiel.
You're not on my list.
Crowley...
Long day.
I'm sure you must be tired.
But I've had a wee idea.
Yes?
The name Olivette
means little to you.
A high-ranking member
of the grand coven,
the one who led the charge
against me.
Really, it's a grudge.
I won't even deny it.
But she's just come back
to the states,
and I thought if you,
in your kingly beneficence,
would be so kind
as to assist me,
now would be an excellent time
to strike.
Well done, Mother.
Next time
you run a long con,
let more than a few hours
of suspicious,
entirely uncharacteristic
usefulness pass
before making your ask.
You think I had
an ulterior motive,
that I've been
manipulating you?
You couldn't be
more transparent.
[ Laughs ] Well, duh!
Of course
I was manipulating you!
I am your mother,
after all.
Manipulation's
who we are.
Oh.
My wee sausage,
what matter is it
that I had a motive?
We had fun today,
didn't we?
It was fine.
We could have more.
Get out of this dump,
a break from
these foul-smelling suck-ups,
flex our muscles
in the real world
and in the process take out
a miserable, old witch
who's been standing in my way
for centuries.
What do you say?
[ Sighs ]
I'm sorry I couldn't bring
better news, Dean.
It's not your fault,
Cass.
Sam: Thank you.
All right, the sheriff gave me
a few more names,
some preliminary I.D.s
on the bodies.
And?
And it seems to fit Cass' story.
I mean, there's no way to tell
the relation to Cain, obviously,
but he's wiping out entire
families, one after another.
[ Sighs ] So who's next?
Is he done with the Tollivers?
Uh, I think so.
I mean, Leon didn't have any siblings
or any other children I can see,
and Tommy was never married,
so I...
Oh, come on.
Damn it.
What?
Tommy did have a son,
estranged,
who lives with his mother
in Ohio,
uh, Austin Reynolds,
12 years old.
Is the kid still alive?
As of an hour ago, yeah.
He updated his status.
But, I mean, come on.
It's a kid.
You don't really think
Cain would --
Yes, he would.
There were old men
in those graves, Sam, women.
I mean, you heard Cass.
It's a fire sale.
Everyone must go.
Where you going?
We know
where Cain's gonna be.
The kid's in danger.
Okay, so what, we track him down
to Ohio, and then what?
Then I'll do
what I have to do.
I'll kill Cain.
When he gave me the Mark,
Cain said
that this day would come,
that after I killed Abaddon,
I would have to come
and put him down.
Great. So you're taking orders
from a madman.
No, he wasn't mad then.
Cain resisted the Mark
for a long time,
then I came, kicking up trouble
about the Blade.
I sent him down this path.
This is on me.
It doesn't mean you have to be
the one to go after him.
Yes, it does.
And there's only one thing
that can kill him.
The Blade.
[ Gun cocks ]
Dean's right.
Dean, wielding the Blade
against Cain himself...
...win or lose,
you may never come back
from that fight.
I know.
I'll need a demon force
to get us past her security.
2 units of 10
should suffice.
Once we're inside,
we'll want to throw her
off guard,
mess with her head
a little bit.
So I thought...
Rune of Amaranth.
Illusion work. Smart.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Chuckles ]
Excuse me.
I'll be right back.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't --
Dean: Cain's back.
He's gone dark,
and I need the Blade.
Why would I do that
for you?
Because you have
as much reason
to want Cain off the board
as anyone.
Cain has a kill list,
and you're on it.
What do you say, Crowley?
You in?
Yes.
Good. I'll text you
the location.
Once she's well flustered,
I've got
an especially nasty spell
to finish her off with.
Mother,
it's not happening.
What?
Not today.
Where are you going?
Something's come up.
Olivette can wait.
This can't.
Is that
what I think it is?!
Not that it's
any of your business.
Let me guess.
Bringing it to your wee pal,
the Winchester boy.
You'd give that
to the one person
who can harness its power
against you.
He's a threat to you!
We've a common enemy,
a bigger threat.
Well, if he's not a threat
to your life,
he's certainly a threat
to your credibility.
We've talked about what
this does to your reputation.
We are not having
this conversation.
Consorting with hunters!
Oh, me. Oh, my.
You honestly believe
that they're your friends,
that they care about you?!
[ Insects chirping ]
Kid here?
Castiel: He's nearby.
Upstairs in the barn.
He's playing with
a basketball.
Cain will strike soon.
Maybe tonight, maybe tomorrow,
but soon.
And when he does --
yeah, I got it.
You charge in
with the Blade solo.
And the kid?
What, we just watch and wait
until Cain attacks?
I thought this was
a rescue mission.
We save the kid
after Cain shows.
We know what Cain's after.
That's our only advantage.
We want to trap Cain,
we use it.
A 12-year-old as bait.
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
Crowley: Neither can I.
What's the matter,
Crowley?
You suddenly grow
a conscience?
Too good to put a minor
in danger?
Don't give a damn
about the kid.
I'm talking about
the risk to us.
There is no us.
You're here for one reason.
That's to hand me the Blade.
Yeah, about that.
Seeing as this is shaping up
to be one of those,
uh, two-step capture then kill
kind of deals,
I think
your buddies would agree
it's better to keep the Blade
out of your hands
until we've got Cain
sewn up,
just to be safe.
Now, back to this plan
of yours.
[ Rock 'n' roll music playing ]
So...
If this works
and we capture Cain,
then what?
We'll cross that bridge
when we c--
if we come to it.
You know last week,
when I said that I would go down
swinging when the time came?
I meant that
I was at peace with that.
I just didn't realize
the time would come so soon,
you know, like right now.
I'm scared, Sam.
? ...down in Mexico ?
? got hitched
in the house of gin ?
? my hangover will never end ?
[ Hinges squeak, door closes ]
[ Music stops ]
Someone there?
[ Rustling ]
Hello, Austin.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to kill you.
Castiel: No, you won't.
Run!
You can't stop me.
[ Groans ]
[ Banging on door ]
[ Rustling ]
Don't.
Please don't.
Illusion spell.
Oh, yeah.
The real Austin is long gone.
18th-century magic.
If I had to hazard a guess,
Rune of Amaranth.
Good eye.
Something I picked up
from my mother.
Well, I know you fear me.
I can only assume...
Oh. Clever.
Won't hold me for long,
you know.
It won't need to.
Cass, hey, you okay?
I'm fine.
It worked?
Yeah.
My turn.
Dean, look,
we want to help.
No.
No, with you in the ring,
it'd just be a liability.
Dean?
I'd be too worried about
what he could do to you...
Or what I could.
Plus,
I need you three out here
to take out
whatever comes out of there.
And I'm serious.
I mean whatever comes out.
Happily.
What guarantee do I have
that you'll give it back
when you're done?
If I survive
and I come out of there
and I don't give it back,
you'll all have a much bigger
problem on your hands.
[ Warbling ]
Dean?
I'm good.
Hello, Dean.
At a loss for words,
my son?
Allow me.
This is the part where
you tell me it's not too late
and I can lay down arms,
abandon my mission.
“We don't have to fight”.
I'll spare us
the formalities.
You're past talking down.
Cain,
you're fully mental.
Oh, I prefer to think
I've finally gotten clear.
When I made my bargain
with Lucifer,
killed Abel,
I released a stain
upon the earth,
a stain deeper
and far more lasting
than mere precedence.
Your bloodline's tainted,
so you say.
So I know.
Not all killers
are my descendants,
and not all my descendants
are killers,
but enough are,
enough for me to know
that extinguishing them
is the least I owe this world.
Can you honestly tell me
that humanity's not better off
with fewer Tommys
and fewer Leons...
Fewer yous?
And what about the kid?
He could go either way.
I prefer to be thorough.
How's it feel, Dean,
holding the Blade again?
It feels like
a means to an end.
Then do it.
[ Coughs ]
That seems a bit weaker
than I would expect from you
with the Blade.
I think you can do better.
Unless...
You're holding back.
What is it, Dean?
Do you think if you hold back
just enough, you won't succumb,
that you'll leave this fight
the same as you entered?!
Look to my example, boy!
There is no resisting the Mark
or the Blade.
There is only remission
and relapse!
[ Coughs ]
You told me
that this day would come.
that I would have to kill you.
Is that so?
I'm afraid you've misunderstood
my intentions here, Dean.
When your pet angel
found my burial site,
I thought about ending him
and swatting him like a fly.
But then
I thought about you.
Your biggest weakness,
the thing I noticed
the moment I met you,
your courage,
your reckless bravado.
I let him go,
knowing that he would
report back to you,
knowing you would bring
into battle
the one thing
that can kill me,
I truly want.
[ Sizzling ]
Oh, it's been too long.
That old feeling
makes me wonder
how I ever had the strength
to resist.
[ Gasping ]
This may be hard
to believe
in light of what
I'm about to do to you,
but I care about you,
Dean.
I truly do.
But I know
I'm doing you a favor.
I'm saving you.
Saving me from what?
From your fate.
Has it never occurred
to you?
Have you never
mused upon the fact
that you're living my life
in reverse?
My story began
when I killed my brother,
and that's where your story
inevitably will end.
No. Never.
It's called the Mark of Cain
for a reason!
First --
first, you'd kill Crowley.
There'd be some strange,
mixed feelings on that one,
but you'd have your reason.
You'd get it done,
no remorse.
And then you'd kill the angel,
Castiel.
Now, that one --
that I suspect
would hurt something awful.
And then!
[ Groans ]
Then would come the murder
you'd never survive,
the one that would
finally turn you
into as much of a savage
as it did me.
No.
Your brother, Sam.
The only thing standing
between you and that destiny
is this Blade.
You're welcome, my son.
[ Groans ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
What's the matter?
Tell me
I don't have to do this.
Tell me that you'll stop.
Tell me that you can stop!
I will never stop.
[ Grunts ]
[ Blade plunges ]
[ Thunder rumbles ]
Dean?
Dean, the Blade.
You lied to me.
It's not the first time
today.
Cain's list --
you weren't on it.
Hey, hey, hey.
You did it.
Dean, you did it.
[ Sighs ]
Rowena: Fergus...
I don't want to hear it,
the “I told you sos,” not now.
What are you doing?
What's it look like?
I'm leaving.
Another
petty manipulation.
No.
Then what, mother?
What do you want from me?!
You can't understand
my disappointment...
or my pride.
[ Voice breaking ]
You don't know this,
but after I left you,
after I was forced to leave you,
I heard of your death --
your mortal death.
[ Sniffles ]
I thought you were
gone to me forever.
Then,
hundreds of years later
and thousands
of miles away,
I find you,
the King of Hell,
and not by luck
or accident.
You made that happen
all by yourself.
You're not a mother.
You can't know what
that pride felt like,
how huge it was.
But can you try to imagine,
for me?
Now do you understand
why it breaks my heart
to see what a colossal numb nut
you've become?!
You've got the crown,
but you're no ruler,
not really!
A sad, bored, wee boy
on the throne
who'll flop ass-up
the second those Winchesters --
hunters who'd as soon see you
dead as have you to tea --
ask you to.
[ Scoffs ]
You're no king,
not anymore.
You're their bitch.
Dean, um, you know,
what you did back there,
it was incredible.
You know, if you can do that
without losing yourself,
that's cause for hope,
even without a cure.
Yeah.
Maybe.
So, where's the Blade?
Somewhere safe.
Good.
Well, if you guys
will excuse me,
I think I am gonna go sleep
for about four days.
Of course.
How is he?
Sam?
Cass...
Dean's in trouble.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man