? Carry on, my wayward son ?
? there'll be peace
when you are done ?
? lay your weary head to rest ?
? Don't you cry no more ?
I will save my brother
or die trying.
It's the Mark of Cain.
It's just a curse.
It can be removed.
You're their bitch.
Get out.
"The Book of the Damned"
is a spell book
for creating or undoing
any kind of damnation
there is.
I think this is in code.
Rowena:
Bring me Nadya's codex,
and I'll break this text
right open.
? Once I rose above the noise
and confusion ?
? just to get a glimpse
beyond this illusion ?
Dean is not getting
any better.
if we don't get the mark off
his arm, it's gonna eat him up.
? I was soaring ever higher ?
? But I flew too high ?
Castiel: My grace,
it's been restored.
? Though my eyes could see
I still was a blind man ?
Find me a cure for my brother.
Then I'll kill Crowley.
? I still was a mad man ?
Thank you, Sam...
? I hear the voices when I'm dreaming ?
...For reminding me who I really am.
Crowley: There must be something
that I don't know about her,
something I could hold over her
as a bargaining chip.
? Carry on, my wayward son ?
Rowena: She's cracked the code.
? There'll be peace
when you are done ?
Charlie?
? Lay your weary head to rest ?
I don't want
to have to hurt you.
? don't you cry no more ?
Dean: I don't think that's gonna be a problem.
Anything?
12 voicemails.
LoJack on the Impala
has clearly been disabled.
So a big heaping scoop
of nothing.
We need Rowena to hold up
her end of the bargain -- now.
What?
[ Sighs ] Nothing.
It's -- it's just
if she removes the Mark
using
"The Book of the Damned"...
What of the consequences?
Which are what?
Dean said --
Dean guessed!
[ Sighs ]
Guess.
What are we
supposed to do, huh?
Just sit on our asses,
do nothing?
No. We find Dean.
And then what?!
The only thing that stopped
Cain was death.
Do you want to kill Dean?
Because I don't.
And the only way I know
how to save my brother
is to cure the Mark.
And, yes, I know
there will be consequences,
but not you, not Dean --
not anybody can tell me
what those consequences are.
So I'm not gonna let my brother
d-destroy himself on a guess.
[ Sighs ]
We save Dean.
[ Horn blares in distance ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Cellphone chimes ]
[ Groans ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Ahh.
[ Breathing heavily ]
I'm good.
[ Sniffs ]
? Supernatural 10x23 ?
Brother's Keeper
Original Air Date on May 20, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ train whistle blares
in distance ]
Rose McKinley.
[ Police radio chatter ]
Raised up
about three miles from here.
Nice parents,
God-fearin' folk.
Well, they let her leave the
house looking like a whore.
Whoa.
Why don't you tell me
what you really think, Agent?
Oh, I'm sorry, Sheriff.
My bad.
Let me tell you
how we work out here, son.
That right there could be
the whore of Babylon --
wouldn't make
no difference at all.
'Cause all I see is
somebody's little girl.
And I feel like a real jerk
suggesting otherwise, Sheriff.
My apologies.
Good luck crackin' the case
with your eyes shut.
You worked some pretty
dark stuff in your day,
haven't you, Agent?
Must've left
quite a mark.
Oh, you have no idea.
[ Sighs ]
Your partner's
a piece of work, Agent.
Rudy:
Yeah, ain't he, though?
Dean-o!
Welcome to the party.
The hell you doing here,
Rudy?
Ah, you know, just a thing
I got for dead girls.
[ Chuckles ]
Just -- just workin'
a gang of fang, you know?
Just like you.
Yeah,
not today you're not.
I'm gonna need you
to take a walk on this one.
Uh, okay, except, uh --
except I called you,
so, uh, if anybody's walking,
it's --
Oh, you called me?
No, no. You begged me.
Just like Tuscaloosa,
just like Old Lyme,
we both know you're playing
dress-up out here,
and it's just a matter of time
before you get yourself killed.
So why don't you
take that walk
and let the real hunters
do the work?
Sheriff: Agents!
New deal.
Rose wasn't alone
when she disappeared.
Friend named Crystal Thorrson
was with her,
and Crystal is still AWOL.
I'm heading over
to interview the parents.
How about we agree
you boys sit this one out?
You know something?
Life's too short...
Partner.
You know, I don't know what
crawled up your ass today,
but frankly,
I don't care.
Regards to your brother.
Hello, boys.
Just in time for tea --
u-unless something on your mind?
Five things, actually.
[ Gun cocks ]
Hollow tips filled
with witch-killing brew.
How exciting for you.
Your NRA will be beside
themselves with pride.
No more games, Rowena.
Do the spell now.
Or what exactly?
Come on, Samuel!
You and I both know
that's nothing but a bluff.
Charlie may have
cracked the codex,
but who's going to read it
if I'm gone?
Not to mention
handling the ingredients,
getting the measurements
just right --
unless, of course,
either of you
have spent years of your life
studying with the greats,
mastering the intricacies
of high witchcraft?
But forgive me.
Maybe you have.
I know you're upset.
We all are.
Poor Dean.
Let's just have
a nice wee cup of tea...
and negotiate.
[ Gun uncocks ]
What do you want?
[ Chuckling ] Oh, well,
we know what I wanted.
Soiled the sheets
on that one, didn't we?
Let's talk about
what I'll take --
my freedom guaranteed
and the codex.
Sam, you can't be --
Do you know which spell?
I do.
Sam.
This is a mistake.
Rose and Crystal
were friends since...
forever it seems.
Uh, you think that Crystal
could still be in danger?
We do, Mrs. McKinley, and
the fastest way to find Crystal
is to find out
who did this to Rose.
Did you notice any change
in her behavior recently --
uh, new friends,
a new boyfriend, maybe a crush?
Rose was...a shy girl.
But...you think she might know
who did this to her?
In Rose's case,
she not only knew the person,
but, uh, she was trying
to have intercourse with them.
So I'm just trying to figure out
whether it was a boyfriend
or whether it was just
some random roll in the hay.
No.
Uh, there were no relations
that we're aware of.
No relations at all.
What the hell is this, Agent?
I'm just doing my job,
Mr. McKinley.
By suggesting
my daughter was a slut?
I'll admit
that thought crossed my mind.
Then I came here,
and I smelled the deceit
and the beatings and the shame
that pervade this home.
And you know what?
I don't blame Rose anymore.
You shut your face right now.
No wonder she put on that skank outfit
and went out there
looking for validation,
right into the arms
of the monster that killed her.
Joe, who did this?
[ Screams ]
No! Joe!
Who did this?
[ Grunts ] Stop!
Joe.
[ Gun cocks ]
Who did this?
[ Crying ]
I don't know.
[ Sobbing ]
I don't know!
[ Gun cocks ]
Whoa.
What?
Crystal,
she's still...
Why?
[ Breathing heavily ]
There were these guys
living out by Cross Creek,
said they were [ Gun uncocks ]
rehabbing a cabin out there.
Mostly,
I think they just wanted
a place
to drink and meet girls.
And Crystal and your sister
knew these guys?
But you couldn't be bothered
to tell the cops that
when your sister
turned up dead?
I was sort of the one
who brought them out there
in the first place.
"Sumsu mimma ezebu
ilu ma ikkibu Lu."
"S-something made by God,
but forbidden to man."
Forbidden?
The forbidden fruit?
[ Chuckles ]
No.
The actual apple
is the first ingredient?
"Sumsu mimma ezebu Lu,"
da-da, da-da, da-da.
Okay, uh, what's next?
"Something made by man,
but forbidden by God."
Okay, well, God forbade
false idols, right?
The Golden Calf.
Wasn't that destroyed?
"Sumsu mimma sen arramu."
Great.
[ Clears throat ]
What's
the third ingredient?
Oh.
What?
The third ingredient,
it's impossible.
What is it?
Loosely translated --
my heart.
It's not impossible
at all.
Not my literal heart,
feathers.
Something I love, the spell
calls for me to kill it.
A sacrifice.
Precisely.
The book will grant
freedom from the curse,
but it wants something in return.
Well, then give it.
Bring me something I love,
I'll kill it.
I want my freedom too much
to make a fuss over that.
The -- the problem is,
I don't love anything.
What about Crowley?
Happy to kill him.
Let's not call it love.
I don't believe you.
Everyone loves something.
Woman: Oskar!
Oskar!
Czas Na kolacje!
Polish boy. Oskar.
I'm sorry. Oskar?
You saw Oskar?
Who is he?
Who was he?
Uh, a peasant boy -- his family
helped me through some difficulties,
300 years ago.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Rudy. What's up?
Rudy: Wish I could say
it was good news, Sam.
I just bumped into Dean
working a fangbanger
case in Superior.
Dean's in Nebraska,
w-working a case?
Yeah, my case.
And, uh...
He's not playing well
with others.
Yeah, Dean's not exactly
in the best place right now.
You know what?
Do me a favor.
Just text me the details,
would you?
All right.
Whatever you need.
Okay. Thanks.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
What's going on?
Cass, take this.
It's Dean's hair.
You need it for the spell.
Cass, I need you
to do this for me.
Make the spell happen
whatever it takes, please.
[ Sniffs ]
[ Snarls ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
Dean-o,
uh, this is Reggie.
We're just gonna talk,
all right?
And -- and come
to an understanding.
Back your ass
out of the room, mister,
and leave the blade.
Yeah.
No.
Rudy, walk away.
No, D-- no, d-Dean-o,
just do
what he says, okay?
He's not gonna kill you.
You're his insurance,
all right?
Now man the hell up
and walk away.
Oh, I will kill him,
friend.
You keep yappin',
I will.
Do it.
Dean!
Back up.
Do it.
D-don't test me.
Dean, stop!
You don't have
the guts.
[ Shouts ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Screams ]
[ Screaming, crying ]
What did you do?!
You're Crystal, right?
Yeah, well...
I just rescued you.
He --
you could've talked.
You just...
You're welcome.
[ Police radio chatter ]
Crystal:
He just let him die.
Just let him die.
Agent.
Maybe you can tell me what in
the hell is going on here.
The way the girl outside
tells it
is one of your boys came
in hot, got his partner killed,
then went
some kind of samurai
on that son of a bitch
over there.
[ Muffled ]
I knew that boy...
[ Sighs ]
Who summons anymore?
Couldn't you call?
You're not
in my contacts list.
What?
I need your assistance
to help cure Dean
of the Mark.
What's the expression
I gave at the office?
Maybe I'd feel
a little different
if Sam Winchester hadn't
just tried to bloody kill me!
I'm afraid "no" is not
an acceptable answer.
Or what?
Or...
That's right.
Burn those eyes blue.
Spread those broken wings
and destroy me!
Or...Do it my way.
Right.
Now beg.
What?
Blast me, or beg.
Crowley.
King!
King.
If you --
if you would --
if you would be
so kind...
The three ingredients
on this list.
"Forbidden fruit."
Well, for starters,
it's a Quince, you dummy,
not an apple.
No problem.
"Golden Calf"...
Or what's left of it --
check.
"Something Rowena loves"?
I would've thought
it would've been you, but...
Spare me.
I've lived it.
[ Paper rustles ]
[ Chuckles ]
Well...
I'm in.
[ Sighs ]
[ Knock on door ]
Dean, it's me.
[ Grunts ]
[ Electricity crackles ]
Te nunc invoco, mortem.
Te in mea potestate defixi.
[ Rumbling ]
Nunc et in aeternum.
Don't tell me
that's queso.
Yeah -- yes.
Queso and, uh,
taquitos, tamales.
Homemade
by yours truly.
All with the bad fat.
[ Sniffing ]
Consider it an offering.
For?
I want you to kill me.
What I find
truly fascinating, Dean...
[ Smacks lips ] mmm.
That's good.
...is that
you and I both know
that I've been burned
by you Winchesters before,
yet you still call.
Yeah, I know,
but not this time, okay?
No games,
no second thoughts.
I know you know
what this is.
what it can do.
I've tried
to fight it.
to beat it on my own.
And I-I can't.
I got no moves left --
except you.
Well, I never thought
I'd see the day.
My goodness.
Dean Winchester
has tipped over his king.
But I won't kill you,
Dean.
You're death.
And that Mark on your arm
is the First Curse.
Nothing can kill you.
Okay, well, forget killing me.
Can you get rid of it?
I could.
But...
Creatio ex nihilo --
God created the earth
out of nothing --
or so your Sunday-school teacher
would have you believe.
What, so
Genesis is a lie, eh?
Shocker.
Before there was light,
before there was God
and the archangels,
there wasn't nothing.
There was the Darkness,
a horribly destructive,
amoral force
that was beaten back
by God and his archangels
in a terrible war.
God locked the Darkness away
where it could do no harm,
and he created a Mark that would
serve as both lock and key,
which he entrusted to his
most valued Lieutenant, Lucifer.
But the Mark began
to assert its own will,
revealed itself as a curse,
and began to corrupt.
Lucifer
became jealous of man.
God banished Lucifer
to Hell.
Lucifer passed the Mark
to Cain,
who passed the Mark
to you,
the proverbial
finger in the dike.
Well, that is just
fan-friggin-tastic, isn't it?
So I could
remove the Mark,
but only if
you will share it with another
to ensure
that the lock remains unbroken
and the Darkness
remains banned.
I'm not doing that...
not to anyone.
What if I told you I could
relocate you somewhere far away,
not even
on this earth,
where you
would still be alive,
but no longer a danger
to yourself or to others?
[ Cellphone ringing ]
Sam: Dean.
I gave it a shot,
Sammy.
Listen to me --
whatever you're doing,
whatever you've done,
please...
[ Chuckles softly ]
Hell, I even worked a case.
I gave everything I had
to beat this thing down.
I saw. I saw Rudy.
Well, then, you saw
what I did.
No, that wasn't you.
Sure as hell
felt like me.
Brother, I'm done.
No. No, you're not.
Dean.
Grab a pen.
It's time to say goodbye.
Get you a refill,
Jimmy.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Dishes clatter ]
Fancy a story?
You?
What did you do?
A long, long time ago,
there once lived
an evil bitch -- sorry, witch --
who was forced to flee her home
and her only son
because she was,
well, horrible.
Starving and homeless,
she threw herself upon the mercy
of a peasant Polish family
who took her in,
fed her,
and nursed her
back to full strength.
This was a kindness
she had never known.
She was particularly taken
by their 8-year-old son
who, apparently,
she grew to love.
Mm.
How do you know
all this?
A hamster told me.
Tragically...
...the boy was terminally ill
and soon to die.
But before
the witch departed,
she gave the boy
and his family
the only thanks
that made sense.
She cured the boy
with one spell
and cast another that would take
root once he was full-grown.
That lying, manipulative
whore mother of mine
gave you immortality,
didn't she...Oskar?
[ Door opens ]
Hey.
Dean: Sam.
What is this?
We need to talk.
Whatever you are thinking
of doing, don't.
There is another way.
You don't need to go with him.
You don't need to die!
Funny you say that.
Truth is, when I left,
I thought the only way out
was my death.
Well, I was wrong, Sam.
It's yours.
What?
He's gonna...
Gonna send you
into outer space?
No, well, he didn't
say outer space.
This is madness,
Dean!
Far from it,
I'm afraid.
No one's asking you.
Hear him out!
Our conundrum
is simple, Sam.
Your brother
cannot be killed,
and the Mark
cannot be destroyed,
not without inciting
a far greater evil
than any of us
have ever known.
What evil?
The Darkness.
What the hell is that?
Well,
what does it sound like?
Does it sound
like a good thing?
Even if I remove Dean
from the playing field,
we're still left with you,
loyal, dogged Sam,
who I suspect
will never rest
until he sets his brother
free --
will never rest until
his brother is free of the Mark,
which simply
cannot happen,
lest the Darkness
be set free.
Then there was that time
you stood me up.
You traded my life.
I'm willing to live
with this thing forever,
as long as I know
that I and it
will never hurt
another living thing.
This isn't you.
[ Chuckling ]
This doesn't make any sense.
No,
it makes perfect sense
if you stop thinking about
yourself for one damn minute!
Death:
It's for the greater good.
Once you consider that,
this makes
all the sense in the world.
Crowley:
Why the long faces?
Oh. Let me guess.
Mother showed you
her "mustn't touch it" again.
Do you have
the ingredients?
The Quince cost me
a major I.O.U.
with
a Palestinian warlock.
The gold from the calf --
well, let's just say
I'll be hanged
under certain
sexual-deviancy laws
if I ever show my face
in Jordan again.
And the third?
Ah, yes.
All my long life,
I wondered what I'd done
to deserve a mother
who refused to show love.
I pained over it.
I built my bloody kingdom
on top of it.
Then one day,
epiphany struck.
My mother was incapable
of loving anything.
For the first time
in hundreds of years,
I felt free.
And then you showed up
in my dungeon,
we communed,
and I began to realize
you weren't incapable of love.
You're incapable
of loving me.
Goodness, Fergus, save it
for the stage, why don't you?
I mean,
fabulous speech,
but you put yourself
on far too high a pedestal.
The fact remains I do not,
will not,
and have not
loved anything ever.
[ Sighs ]
You were saying?
Dean: Remember when
we were in that church,
making Crowley human,
about to close
the Gates of Hell?
Well,
you sure as hell
were ready to die
for the greater good then.
Yeah, and, Dean,
you pulled me back.
And I was wrong.
You were right, Sam.
You knew that this world would
be better without us in it.
No, no, no,
wait a second.
You're twisting my words here,
Dean.
Why? Because we --
we track evil and kill it?
The family business?
Is that it?
Look at the tape, Sam.
Evil tracks us.
And it nukes everything
in our vicinity --
our family,
our friends.
It's time we put a proper name
to what we really are
and we deal with it.
Wait a second.
We are not evil.
Listen...
We're far from perfect,
but we are good.
That thing on your arm
is evil,
but not you, not me.
I let Rudy die.
How was that not evil?
I know
what I am, Sam.
But who were you
when you --
when you drove that man
to sell his soul...
Or when
you bullied Charlie
into
getting herself killed?
And to what end?
A-a good end?
A just end?
To remove the Mark no matter
what the consequences?
Sam,
how is that not evil?
I have this thing
on my arm,
and you're willing to let
the Darkness into the world.
You were also willing
to summon death
to make sure you could
never do any more harm.
You summoned me
because you knew
I would do anything
to protect you.
That's not evil,
Dean.
That's not
an evil man.
That is a good man
crying to be heard,
searching for...
some other way.
No, there is
no other way, Sam.
I'm sorry.
Good.
Fight.
This is ridiculous.
Do you love this man?
Rowena, is it true?
'Course it's true.
Say hello, Oskar.
Rowena.
[ Voice breaking ]
Even for you, Fergus,
this is a new low --
a cruel, shameful,
disgusting low.
It's only cruel if you
actually go through with it.
Though...
...who's the cruel one then?
Aah! Aah!
Ohh!
Okay.
That's enough.
Hey, that's enough.
[ Breathing heavily ]
You'll never, ever
hear me say
that you -- the real you --
is anything but good.
[ Coughs ]
[ Spits ]
But you're right.
Before you hurt...
anyone else,
you have to be stopped
at any cost.
I understand.
[ Exhales deeply ]
Do it.
[ Clears throat ]
Please.
Do me the honor.
[ Inhales deeply ]
[ Exhales deeply ]
Close your eyes.
Sammy,
close your eyes.
Wait.
Take these.
And one day,
when you
find your way back...
Let these
be your guide.
And they can
help you remember
what it was
to be good...
...what it was to love.
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Sighs ]
It's for family
you must proceed, Dean.
To be what you are,
to become what you've become
is a stain
on their memory.
Do it.
Or I will.
[ Exhales sharply ]
Forgive me.
You've grown so big.
Not too big to give your old
auntie Rowena a hug I hope.
Hope
I haven't hurt you.
[ Voice breaking ] Don't
think about that one moment.
Everything's fine,
Oskar.
Everything's fine.
Nobody's
hurting anybody.
Goodbye,
my sweet wee boy.
[ Gurgles ]
[ Sobs ]
Ab manu dei...
Ab manu hominis.
[ Sam grunts ]
You okay?
I'll live.
You?
Fantastic.
I think
I just killed death.
Ab cruore cordis
Mei adfusuro in aeternum.
Tolle maledictionem
tuam ab hoc viro.
[ Thunder rumbles ]
That sound right
to you?
[ Electricity crackling ]
Aah!
[ Grunting ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Coughs ] Ah.
[ Metal clatter ]
Manete!
[ Grunts ]
What is this?
This is impossible.
You're not
powerful enough.
To what?
Control the likes of a
bored king and a wayward angel?
[ Chuckles ]
Impetus bestiarum.
[ Groaning ]
I'm afraid, Fergus,
that in all your long life,
you've never seen what a real
witch can do with real magic.
I'm
terrifically pleased
it's the last thing
you'll ever see.
Dele malum hoc.
[ Snarling ]
Castiel.
Don't.
[ Growls ]
Do not.
[ Snarling ]
Don't!
[ Grunts ]
Please!
This is good.
Dean, this is good.
[ Door closes ]
The -- the Mark
is off your arm.
Nothing crazy happened.
You get your baby back.
Yeah.
I'm sure everything's
perfectly fine.
[ Electricity crackling ]
What?
What did death
call this?
The Darkness.
[ Rumbling ]
Get in the car.
Yeah.
Let's go, let's go!
Dean.
[ Roaring ]
Dean!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man