The Mark of Cain
never lets its host die easy.
It's just a curse.
It can be removed.
This is Purgatory.
Dean: There was something about
being there.
Most days felt like
360-degree combat.
[ Benny growls ]
Dean: It felt pure.
Cuthbert Sinclair.
He was named "Master of spells."
Sam: His work
got a little crazy.
The leadership called it
"eccentric and irresponsible."
We're done.
So you're choosing the Winchesters?
I'm choosing me.
The Book of the Damned
is a spellbook
for creating or undoing any kind
of damnation there is.
We translate this thing,
I think we can get
the Mark of Cain off you, Dean.
I don't trust you,
but I need help.
I need the Mark of Cain
off of my brother.
Something tells me
you can crack this book.
The only question is,
will you help me?
Shall we discuss terms?
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Newspaper thuds ]
[ Cartoon playing on TV ]
[ Turns off TV ]
Hey!
Get lost.
My show just started.
You have a record player
in your room.
Dad's speakers are better.
Tough luck.
?
I need the laundry started.
The workmen have finally...
[ Turns off TV ] Left for the day,
and I have my hands full with dinner.
And please, none of
your Betty Friedan stuff.
It's not fair.
Look, I always get stuck
with the hard chores
just 'cause I'm the girl.
Yeah? Well, tough luck.
[ Boy chuckles ]
Man: The house is great, Ted.
It's a bit of a fixer,
but it's a real beaut.
[ Todd Rundgren's
"I Saw the Light" playing ]
It was caught in some
ownership muddle for years.
But finally hit the market,
and I leapt.
? It was late last night ?
? I was feeling
something wasn't right ?
? there was not
another soul in sight ?
? only you, only you ?
? so we walked along ?
? though I knew there was
something wrong ?
Woman: Don't spend all day
down there!
? So strong ?
? about you, ooh, ooh ?
[ Loud thud ]
? Then you gazed up at me ?
? and the answer was
plain to see ?
? 'cause I saw ?
? the light in your eyes ?
? in your eyes... ?
[ Clank ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Loud boom ]
? 'Cause I couldn't ever love
no one ?
? or so I said ?
? but my feelings for you ?
? were just something
I never knew ?
? till I saw the light... ?
[ Songs fades out ]
[ Dog barking, birds chirping
in distance ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Sizzling ]
[ Closes door ]
[ Sizzling continues ]
Mom?
Dad, where's mom?
[ Gasping ]
Mom?
[ Needle scratching, static crackling ]
Brad?
Uhh!
[ Gasps ]
[ Wood creaks ]
Aah!
Mom?
Mom!
Everything's
gonna be okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Everything's...
Gonna be just fine.
? Supernatural 10x19 ?
The Werther Project
Original Air Date on April 22, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[ bell dings ]
[ Country music playing ]
There's only one thing
you could possibly do for me
that I can't,
at least presently,
do for myself.
Kill my son.
?
He's expecting it from me.
Already has his stinking minions
on high alert.
And if you're wondering how
a mother can get to the point
of wanting her own son --
No, I'm really not.
I'll do it.
I'll kill Crowley.
First things first --
can you read the book?
Of course I can.
I'm likely
the only witch alive
who can understand
such old, dark magic.
?
Just not in its present form.
[ Bell dings ]
Drink's on me.
Hey. You're not going
anywhere, pal.
I'm your mortal enemy.
I've tried to kill you
and your brother --
your brother as recently
as last month.
You wouldn't have come to me
if I wasn't your last resort.
You're desperate. [ Laughs ]
You can stop pretending
you're not.
[ Cell phone vibrating ]
[ Beep ]
So rude.
?
Now...I can't read the book
in its present form,
but there is someone
who could.
Nadya. Grand coven witch.
Where do I find her?
You don't. She's dead.
Long ago.
Murdered for her life's work.
[ Inhales sharply ]
Her decryption formulas,
her codex...
That you can find.
Bring me Nadya's codex,
and I'll...
Break this text right open
and give you your cure.
Where do I look?
If I were you,
I'd start at home.
Who do you think
murdered Nadya
and stole the codex
in the first place?
The Men of Letters.
[ Whack, crunch ]
?
[ Splashes water ]
Ha ha!
Jackpot.
Dean!
Hey.
What happened? What is this?
I know, right?
Six vamps. Solo.
[ Closes refrigerator ] I think  that's
gotta be a personal best.
[ Taps can ]
[ Can fizzes ]
You couldn't have waited?!
For what?
Oh, come on, man.
I can handle it.
I did handle it.
What if you couldn't?
But I did.
It's done.
Come on, man. It's the only way
I can take the edge off.
I'm sorry. I don't always like
to wait around for you,
especially with you looking
at me like that all the time.
Look at you like what?
Like that.
Like I'm some sort of
a-a-a diseased killer puppy.
You know what, man?
I'm sweaty and I'm covered
in vamp juice.
Can we just
talk about this later?
I'd like to get back to
the bunker, get my buzz on,
and, uh, you know,
pass out watching
"Speed 2: Cruise Control."
[ Hits arm ]
[ Grunts ]
We cool?
Cool.
?
[ Canister clatters ]
[ Knob clicks ]
[ Whirring ]
Man: Please, let come to order.
Men of Letters
meeting minutes --
May 16, 1956.
On the matter of
Cuthbert Sinclair expulsion.
Man: This is hardly
your first offence, Cuthbert.
You've been cited for
disciplinary infractions
seven times
in the course of your tenure.
This...enchanted vault
of yours,
this...
"Werther box."
A warding so potent it achieves
a theoretical rate of...
In your own words,
"98% lethality."
Extreme measures
were warranted.
The coven's desperate
to get the codex back.
The Werther box works.
All too well, I'd say.
Working in secret,
embarking on this project
without oversight...
you left two fellow
Men of Letters vulnerable
to your most potent magics.
Fletcher and Martinez were
members in good standing.
Fletcher chanced upon the box
and died in two hours.
Martinez heroically tried
to shut it down.
We found him dead on the floor
beside the box,
his wrists cut.
I already apologized
for that accident.
I refuse to do so again.
Why are you all
so small-minded?
Hmm?
We were brought here
to do great things.
To take risks,
to bring the fight to
the monsters of this world --
and yet, to a man,
you choose instead
to moulder in these stacks.
You are not men.
You're librarians.
Nothing more.
Before we rule
on what is to be done
with you,
I'm prepared to give you
a chance to secure our leniency.
Tell us how to shut it down.
The box is still in St. Louis
with the codex.
It's still a danger.
Let me tell you what you can do
with your leniency, Markham.
[ Inhales deeply ]
You know,
I saw the writing on the wall.
I knew you cowards would
shut this project down,
which is why I built it
the way I did.
There is only one way to silence
the Werther for good.
Let's just say Martinez was
on the right track.
I doubt you lot have the guts,
but you're welcome
to die trying.
Markham, would you have us
keep trying?
The box is to be interred
and guarded where it stands,
in perpetuity.
Bury it.
[ Knob clicks ]
[ Cell phone rings ]
[ Inhales sharply and groans ]
[ Ring ]
[ Grunting ]
It's a bit early.
[ Ring ]
I'm over 300 years old.
Beauty sleep
isn't optional.
I've been looking into the, uh,
thing we discussed.
So I got a lead,
but it's guarded by
a violent enchantment
I need a spell to...
break the spell.
The Cabirian invocation.
Easy to obtain.
Good all-purpose disenchantment.
Great. Thanks.
Uh, but...
It's not recommended
for amateurs.
In inexperienced hands,
the invocation has a way
of fizzling out.
I could come.
You might need me.
I'll take my chances. Thanks.
[ Scoffs ]
Whoa!
Woman: Bad idea.
I-I can explain.
Yeah, don't bother.
You got three choices --
get arrested,
get your bits blown off,
or get back.
Yeah, all right. I think
I'll, uh, think get back.
Sorry.
Attaboy.
Yep. [ Exhales sharply ]
[ Flaps lips ]
[ Car door opens ]
[ Groans ] Hey ya, Sammy.
How's the case?
What are you doing here?
Well, it looks like I, uh,
I'm here to save your sac.
[ Chuckles ]
Look, you were right. Okay?
I shouldn't have gone off solo
like I did.
It was stupid.
And?
And selfish.
It was a douche move.
If you're doing this case by
yourself to teach me a lesson,
you don't have to, okay?
How'd you find me?
Ah! [ Chuckles ]
I, uh...
[ Paper crinkles ]
Took an etching
off your notepad.
Then I decided to
take a crack
at the, uh,
St. Louis suicide house.
So you know about it?
I got the basics from Google.
The family moves into
a long-vacant house.
Uh, one week later,
three of 'em dead
by their own hands.
Whole family wiped out
except for the daughter,
which the house is still
under her name.
I'm figuring she's the one who
nearly unmanned you back there.
But see,
here's what I don't get.
I mean, a cold case
is one thing, but...
this is subzero.
I mean, there's nothing
even in our wheelhouse,
unless you know something
I don't.
Yeah. Um...
[ Clears throat ]
That "long-vacant home"
used to be a Men of Letters
chapter house.
Sam: Remember Magnus?
You mean
the dickwad ex-Men of Letters
that tried to make a zoo exhibit
out of me? Yeah.
Before he was expelled,
he built Werther,
a magical box
with a deadly alarm system.
Werther is buried
somewhere in that house.
It was supposed to have
been guarded,
but I'm guessing that plan
went out the window
when Abaddon massacred
the entire membership in '58.
And then the house
stayed in limbo
until some lucky family
bought it.
Werther's a time bomb
and it needs to be defused.
Not only is this
in our wheelhouse,
it's our responsibility.
Our responsibility?
We're Men of Letters.
It's our legacy.
Well, hey, if you say
this is a case...
[ Claps hands ]
I'm in,
if you'll have me.
What did I say?!
I...Aah!
[ Cocks gun ]
You're not...
Fella tried to...
What do you want?
You saw him?
Oh, tell me you did.
I'm sorry, but my name is --
is Dwight Twilley.
I'm with
the neighborhood watch.
We're -- we're looking into
a few recent break-ins.
And if you saw the guy
and you -- y-you could
give a description,
it would be mighty helpful.
If I could -- if I could just
have a minute
of your...
[ Voice rises ] Time?
[ Clears throat ]
[ Door closes ]
Uh...
Tall white fella.
Ah.
Pretty hair.
Mm-hmm.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Lock clicks ]
It's a nice house
you have here, uh...
Suzie.
Suzie. You live alone?
Just me and Gus.
Gus?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Kettle whistling ]
[ Whistling slows down ]
Dean: So all alone
in this big house, huh?
Must get lonely,
even with, uh, Gus.
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, well,
I'm used to alone.
No, no. I'm fine, thanks.
Been alone here since, uh...
'80?
After my family died,
my aunt Pauline moved in.
She took care of me,
raised me for a few years.
Then, well...
[ Loud clattering ]
[ Sam grunts ]
So, uh,
what -- what happened?
To your aunt?
Well...
I told her not to go
in the basement.
No one goes in the basement.
What's in the basement, Suzie?
[ Block thuds and scrapes ]
[ Bowl clatters ]
Ma'am, you okay?
[ Cocks gun ]
Oh! Whoa! Suzie.
My social skills may be rusty,
but I'm no idiot.
Doorbell hasn't rung
in months,
and two visitors in one hour?
One breaking in,
and the other asking all sorts
of q-questions about --
I told you, I was from
the neighborhood watch. I --
Yeah, yeah,
neighborhood watch. Right.
Boy, you seen this house?
There's only one thing in here
worth gettin' at,
and it sure as hell
ain't me.
Okay.
You came for the box.
[ Flame whooshes ]
Purificare la magia.
Whoever left that
Godforsaken thing down there...
I knew someday,
someone would come for it.
I swore
never to let that happen.
He's downstairs,
isn't -- isn't he?
He's my brother.
And we're here to help you.
You call him up here.
Now!
You call him up here!
Dean: Okay. Sam!
Sammy!
[ Whispers ]
Purificare la magia.
She wants you up here now!
[ Breathing deeply ]
[ Clank ]
[ Loud boom ]
No. No!
Get out!
Out! Out!
You bastards!
Okay. Okay.
You let it out!
[ Panting ]
[ Inhales sharply,
exhales deeply ]
[ Running footsteps ]
Dean!
[ Breathing deeply ]
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Take it easy.
You have any idea
what you've done?!
Put the gun down.
We can talk about this, okay?
What's that?
Hey, Suzie. You miss me?
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with her?
I don't know.
Stay back.
Stay back!
[ Chambers bullet ]
Go.
[ Glass shatters ]
Come on, Suze. That any way
to treat your family?
[ Continues
breathing heavily ]
[ Chambers bullet ]
[ Vase shatters ]
[ Whimpers ]
Hello, Suzie.
[ Gasps ]
[ Groaning ] Oh!
[ Continues breathing heavily ]
What are you doing, huh?
You don't have a plan.
You don't have a defense.
No.
You did this to us.
You let it out.
We died while you slept.
[ Gasps ]
Suzie: No! [ Sobs ]
Suzie!
No!
[ Growls ]
Suzie?
Suzie: Please! No! Stop!
Stop! [ Whimpering ]
[ Doorknob rattles ]
Suzie!
[ Pounds on door ]
Suzie, let me in!
I can help you!
[ Continues whimpering ]
Sam: Suzie, it's not real!
You don't have to be sad.
And you don't have to
be alone.
Sam: Suzie, please!
Not anymore.
Suzie! Hey, let me in.
I can help you, okay?
[ Sobs ] Oh, please, no.
Suzie?!
Dean!
[ Whoosh ]
Sam?!
[ Gunshot, thud ]
Suzie?!
[ Growls ]
Crap.
Boo.
Survived 40 years
in this house,
keeping that thing
on lockdown,
and one visit
from a putz like you...
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm so sorry.
Lot of good "sorry" does me.
Look at me.
Look...At...Me.
There she is.
First casualty of
your misguided mission.
But what's another human life
to you?
Anything's worth it,
as long as you two
make it out alive.
And how's that search going?
Any closer to a cure?
This isn't real.
You're not real.
[ Gasps ] You think Dean's the wild card,
the loose cannon.
But don't you see?
Making deals with witches,
opening Pandora's box
down there?
You're the reckless one.
You'll do anything
to keep clinging to
that doomed brother
of yours.
How many more will die,
Sammy?
You know it.
You have to be stopped!
And the only one
who can stop you is you!
Do it, Sammy!
End this farce
once and for all!
Vanesce!
Told you you'd need me.
How did you find me?
Same way I just saved you --
magic.
Had a feeling you might
be in over your head.
Yeah, well,
you can't be here.
If Dean sees you...
Dean?
Sam?
Hey. Hey.
What are you doing?
[ Growls ]
Uhh!
[ Snarls ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Panting ]
Hey, chief.
[ Chuckles ]
No. No, it can't be you.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
[ Claps hands ]
Wake up!
Dean, whatever you're seeing,
it's not real!
Real enough to him.
What are you doing?!
He can't see me, Sam.
Yeah, he's too far gone.
Can you wake him up?
I only brought enough
dispelling magic for one.
Maybe if you'd told me
we'd have company...
There is no "we."
Fine.
Take this all on by yourself.
But the odds are
totally stacked against you.
You're not real.
Oh, the spell's got
its hooks in deep.
If you want him woken up...
[ Snaps fingers ]
You're gonna have to rip this
enchantment out by the root.
The box.
If we can figure out
the fail-safe,
we can break the spell
and get the codex.
Suzie's hallucinations
drove her to suicide.
Same thing happened
to her family.
Werther's illusions tried to do
the same thing to me.
And so?
So I can't leave Dean alone
like this.
Well, then... [ chuckles ]
We'll just have to tie up
the bonny lad.
[ Whispers ] Could be fun.
Come on, Dean. How long
you gonna keep this up?
The silent treatment
for me?
We got so much
to catch up on.
Hey, look, it's good
to see you, okay? It is.
But like I said,
you ain't Benny.
I'm not?
Well, shoot.
Hey, I'm bummed out, too,
but you are just a figment,
okay?
You're --
you're subconscious junk
my brain's throwing up
to distract me
from getting back to reality.
"Figment"? "Junk"?
Well, I'll try
not to be offended.
Why not trust me?
I've gotten you
outta here before.
Besides, if all I am
is your "subconscious junk,"
well, then how can I
lead you wrong?
[ Chuckles ]
Well, how about that?
A perfect circle.
Don't look at me, chief.
You chose the way.
[ Rope and wood creaking ]
Here it is. There's some
kind of inscription.
It's some kind of cursive,
but the light source has dimmed.
[ Sighs ] I know what I've said
about your kind,
but...oh.
The man who came up with this?
The craftsmanship of the box,
the sadism of the spellwork...
It's all so...
deliciously baroque.
All right, come on.
[ Whoosh ]
Inluminia.
[ Chuckles ] Well,
now that is just creepy.
Benny -- whoever you are --
I need to get out of here.
"Need" and "want" are two
different things, ain't they?
It's all a figment, right?
You, me, left, right.
But no matter which way
you turn,
you keep ending up here.
You gotta wonder --
why this figment?
Why this place?
What are you saying?
Nothing
you don't already know.
This is where you wanna be --
your happy place.
And you don't really
wanna leave.
Rowena: "Arcam confutare..."
"To silence the box..."
Mm.
"Sitim restinguere..."
"Slake its thirst..."
"Sanguine nostrum."
"With...the blood
of our own."
That's it?
"The blood of its own..."
What?
"The blood of our own."
Men of Letters blood.
Legacy blood.
My blood.
Oh.
Remember what you said to me
when we first met?
About the purity
of this place?
Dean, slow down.
Dean, stop.
Listen.
[ Snarling in distance ]
This?
This place, you don't have to
go looking for a fight.
All you have to is be still
for one moment,
and that fight
will come to you.
That's why
you're here, Dean.
That's the purity
you crave --
killing with no consequence.
No, Benny,
I don't wanna fight anymore.
I'm tired of fightin'.
The Mark ain't.
So...can't leave.
Don't wanna stay.
Bit of a bind, ain't it?
Good thing there's always
a third way out.
You can't tell me you haven't
been thinking about it.
That ain't gonna happen,
ever.
Come on, Dean.
I know you can see it.
The purity, the honor.
There's no honor in that.
What, you just wanna wait
for the Mark to reclaim you?
Go out swinging, die topside,
then what?
Maybe kill a few humans?
Kill Cass? Kill your brother?
Yeah, that's mighty honorable!
Benny, shut up!
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
I forgot...
About your plan.
You gonna get Sam and Cass
to put you down?
You really think they're gonna
keep that agreement? Come on.
Dean, let's say they do.
Do you think they will ever
recover from that?
[ Whispers ]
It will ruin them.
This little backup plan
of yours,
I know you've been thinking
about it for a time.
[ Whispers ] I know
it's been gnawin' at you.
You can't leave that job
to them.
You're right.
[ Grunts ]
[ Wood cracks ]
Benny: Out there?
You're sleeping.
You make the right choice
in here,
you'll sleep forever,
and you won't ever
hurt anyone ever again.
No one needs to know, Dean.
What happens in Purgatory,
stays in Purgatory.
[ Grunts ]
[ Bottle shatters ]
[ Clicks ]
How do you know
this will work?
I don't.
[ Groans ]
[ Bowl clatters ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Groans ]
[ Clank ]
Hey.
[ Cogs clicking and whirring ]
[ Rowena chuckles ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Whispers ] It's working.
I always did love it here.
It's as good a place as any
to call it a day, huh?
[ Breathing shallowly ]
Slow down.
Right. Okay.
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ Clicking and whirring
slow down ]
No, no, no.
[ Exhales sharply ]
It wants more, Sam.
It wants it all.
The codex...
Path to the cure.
It's in there.
If it wants more,
it'll get more.
[ Bowl clatters ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Groans ]
[ Knife clanks ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Clicking and whirring
speed up ]
I'd do it.
If I really had to,
I would.
But the real Benny
would never let me.
We already covered that,
chief.
It's not me.
You know what else
won't let me?
This thing on my arm.
For better or worse,
the Mark...
it wants me alive.
[ Squish ]
[ Grunts ]
Thanks, pal,
but no thanks.
[ Whoosh ]
It's opening, Sammy!
[ Inhales deeply ]
It's nearly there!
[ Blood continues dripping ]
[ Grunts
and exhales sharply ]
Sam!
Hey! Hey. Hey.
[ Groans ]
Sammy, whatever you're seeing,
it's -- it's a trick.
Okay? It's not real!
Dean? [ Ragged breathing ]
Yeah.
Hey. No.
No. Hey! Hey!
[ Groans ]
[ Smack ]
[ Grunts ]
Get away from me!
No, don't! Don't!
[ Grunts ] It's the only way.
[ Knife clanks ]
It needs legacy blood...
No.
Enough to take a life.
Yeah, well...
It doesn't have to come from
just one legacy, does it? [ Grunting ]
Uhh! [ Groans ]
It needs more blood,
it can have mine. [ Groans ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Knife clanks ]
[ Clicking and whirring
speed up ]
[ Clicking and whirring stop,
door unlocks ]
Oh, well.
[ Whoosh ]
[ Breathing deeply ]
[ Click ]
[ Creaks ]
[ Exhaling sharply ]
[ Door closes ]
Sam: [ Strained voice ]
Overkill, don't you think?
I mean, we broke the spell.
The box is just a box.
[ Sledgehammer thuds ]
Well, now it's scrap metal.
[ Groans ]
You okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
You road ready?
I'll be fine.
That says something,
doesn't it?
Werther splits us up
in there.
Within an hour, we,'re both
on the brink of death?
Sorry about yesterday,
going rogue on you like that.
You know what, Dean?
Don't apologize. I...
[ Scoffs ]
I think that makes us even.
The universe is trying to
tell us something
we both should already know.
We're stronger together than apart.
[ Pats arm ]
Mnh.
Now what could possibly be
so valuable
that it takes a spell that nasty
to protect it, huh?
[ Grunts ]
No idea.
Whatever it is,
we'll keep it safe.
[ Starts engine ]
[ Door closes ]
Well, hello, cowboy.
Oh, you've got it!
[ Whispers ] Oh!
[ Gasps ]
[ Exhales sharply ]
Is it enough?
To what?
To translate the book.
Find a cure for the Mark.
Oh, aye. [ Chuckles ]
Good.
[ Shackle clicks ]
Wh--
[ click ]
What in the hell is this?!
Insurance.
Comfortable?
We had an agreement, giant.
[ Chain rattles ]
The agreement stands.
You will decrypt
the book of the damned
and find me a cure
for my brother.
And that is all you will get
from the book.
[ Chain rattling ] I'll burn the book,
then I'll kill Crowley.
[ Click ]
But until then...
I'm your slave?
You can't -- you can't just
leave me here.
You want out? Hurry up.
Get to work.
Ugh! You big bampot!
[ Chain rattles ]
Uhh! [ Inhales deeply ]
[ Door opens and closes ]
[ Exhales ]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man