- Are you in love with her?
- Whoa! No, shut up, Dad.
What?
No, I either go as me
or I'm not going at all.
No! Fuck off! Moron.
You can't... you can't deny me
for ever, you know.
Well, denied, mate!
It was the lung transplant. I've got
the power to fuck powers out of people.
(RUDY SCREAMS)
Aah! Oh!
(SOBS)
Whoa! Whoa! I need to talk to you!
It's about a jumper!
(RUDY GRUNTS)
Morning, Finlay!
(REGGAE PLAYS)
Oh, come on!
That's... that's fuckin' it!
RUDY: He's fucked off!
He's left me!
Rudy 2's buggered off and left me!
Where's he gone?
Shit, I don't know. He's been gone
for a couple of days now.
I thought he might come back in the night,
but he's not.
He's never been out of me
this long before.
- Are they my trousers?
- Yeah. Shit. I'm sorry.
I was going to ask if I could borrow
some clothes, because I've run out!
What are you gonna do?
Fuck, I'm not gonna do nothing.
If he wants go off and do his own thing,
that's his decision.
Good riddance. That's what I say.
Frigging free at last!
- Thank fuck almighty, I'm free at last.
- Don't...
- (MUTTERS)
- Stop it.
(it THE RAPTURE'. Echoes)
# The city breathing, the people churning
The conversating
# The price is what?
# The conversating, this place is heaven
# And if you see them... #
David Simmonds, right, now,
he was a kid at our school. He had a tail.
It was like a useless flap of skin
at the base of his spine.
And one day
he had the bloody tail removed.
And now I know how he feels.
To losing your tail, guys.
Let's get them in there.
But he was part of the gang.
For fuck's sake!
He was Scrappy-Doc to your Scooby.
You're Shaggy. Obviously.
Urn... which one am I?
- Velma.
- Velma?
- Mm.
- With the glasses?
- Fuck off.
What if he's killed himself?
Why... why the fuck
would he have killed himself, Finn?
He didn't mean to.
Satsuma in the mouth.
Dog collar on. Bit tighter, bit tighter.
Fuck's sake!
I'll piss off and I'll frigging celebrate
by myself, shall I?
Fuck you.
Fuck".you.
Have a nice evening.
That is a really pale arse.
OTHERS: Eurgh.
What the fuck, guys?
- Aah!
- OK.
Christ sake! Why am I not in bed?
Morning.
Morning! Ah!
This is... this is Rudy 2's fault! I cannot
be expected to look after meself!
I've only just worked out
them screw-top lids
on them aspirin bottles.
OK. How about you just put some pants on
first, then we'll talk about it?
Mate, running out of bog roll
is one fucking thing.
This is bang out of order.
(WHEEL SQUEAKS)
It makes my blood boil.
I mean, there's a municipal recycling
facility two minutes down the road.
It's just scum.
Sick, inhuman scum.
We kill people.
Frequently.
Yeah.
Well, there's honor in killing people.
There's no honor in fly-tipping,
is there?
(BANG)
Hey!
Check this guy out.
- Is he all right?
- RUDY: You all right, mate?
How you doing?
Oh, he looks friendly, doesn't he?
How you doing? You all right, mate?
Oh, shit! He's a big huggy.
Two sugars. Milk and two sugars.
Milk and two sugars! Get the man
a cup of tea immediately bef...
Oh, my fucking God.
It's him! It's Rudy 2!
Where have you been?
Who's done this to you?
ALEX: Are we absolutely sure it's him?
Are you fucking kidding me, man? Look!
He's got to be about 80. Maybe even more.
Do you remember what happened to you?
Oh.
- It's you.
- Yeah.
Always liked you.
It's raining. Your hair's so pretty...
when it's wet.
Jesus Christ.
The man's a fucking vegetable.
I tell you what's happened here.
The storm.
This will be something to do
with the storm.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- ALEX: You think so?
- FINN: Mm-hm.
Well, thanks for the heads-up,
Miss Marple.
Maybe it's something to do
with that superpower support group
he's been going to.
RUDY: So, what does he need
with a support group, anyway?
Talking about your feelings,
that's the first sign of weakness.
You want to bottle
that stuff up inside you,
until it becomes one solid mass
of anger and resentment.
- That's what my Uncle Peter did.
- (PHONE RINGS)
Admittedly, he drank himself to death,
but that's not the... point.
Hello?
He's hungry-
Gammon and egg,
and fish and...
He wants gammon.
Well, I don't know.
Get him some from a vending machine?
OK, hurry up.
You need to be the one
dealing with this, not me.
Oh...
- Guys, this is it.
- Right.
What's the plan?
The plan is... we go in there
and we ask 'em which one
turned Rudy 2 into an old man.
- Shit plan.
- Is it?
If Rudy 2's a regular at this group,
they're going to think you're him.
Go undercover, pretend to be him and
whoever did it'll be surprised to see you.
They'll give themselves away.
That is genius. Here's what I need, right?
I need a beard. I need some glasses.
I need a pipe. I want a cloak.
Get me a staff of some kind.
You need to look like Rudy 2, otherwise
they're not gonna think you're him.
This guy, eight GCSEs.
Let's go undercover.
Rudy 2. How are you doing?
I would imagine you're...
quite surprised to see me, guy.
Not really. Urn...
you always come on a Tuesday.
Let's just say that old habits... die hard.
Old... habits.
- I'm Finn.
- Nice to meet you. Hi.
Oh, don't worry about me.
I'm just here for the biscuits.
Cheers.
So, what's your power?
- Teleke...
- Milky nipples.
"Hm?
' M'"'Y nipples.
Cos every time he tells a lie,
he just expresses milk from his nipples.
It's ridiculous,
and he's very embarrassed about it.
Now, you're going to have to excuse us,
cos we do have other people
we need to speak to.
Finlay.
What was all that
with the fucking milky nipples?
What was the plan, Finn?
Can you remember it?
The plan was, we don't tell anyone
what our real powers are.
That was nothing to do with the plan.
Was it not?
- No!
- Now, listen to me, dude, seriously.
Someone here knows something
about Rudy 2. I suggest we just split up.
Yeah, I think we should just... Fuck off.
(CRUNCHING)
Why is there a turtle by the biscuits?
He turns up every week.
It's someone with a power.
There's someone inside of there?
Yeah.
His name's Mark.
All right, mate?
You don't have to be embarrassed.
About your, um... your power.
How about you? What's... what's your power?
Me? Oh.
It's, er... it's complicated.
I don't really like to talk about it.
It's all right. You don't have to,
if you don't want to.
The thing is, other people
make certain assumptions about my...
(CLEARS THROAT)... sexuality, and...
What, they... they think you're gay?
Yeah, yeah. I... I guess they do.
And... are... are you gay?
No!
- (CLICK)
- (ELECTRICAL HUM)
(SIGHS)
Now you know.
Fuck off!
You're... you're literally
trapped in the closet?
(CHUCKLES) How funny's that?
And also very serious.
Quietly poignant.
Yeah.
Actually, I've got a friend
who can take powers.
How does he take powers? How does it work?
I'll let him fill you in on the details.
Ah. You're gonna love him.
His name's Alex.
He's on community service.
Great.
Miss Marple? The prick.
- (WHISPERS) Hey.
- (WHISPERS) Fucking hell.
(CLICKS FINGERS) That's her.
She's old, he's old.
I'm going undercover, man.
- This is it.
- OK, wait.
Ooh, er... OK, everyone's here.
Let's make a start.
Shit.
- Hi, Rudy 2.
- Yeah. All right, you.
Urn... Rudy 2. Last time,
you were telling us about Rudy 1.
Was I?
I don't... I... I don't remember.
OK, well, you were telling us
you were embarrassed by his behaviour.
You feel betrayed that he hasn't
introduced you to your parents.
Just... let's just let someone else
have a turn, shall we, mate?
What about him over there?
He looks like he's got issues, don't he?
(CLEARS THROAT)
You... you were saying that
at times you're ashamed of him,
that he makes you feel ashamed.
Just fucking move on!
For fuck's sake, man!
Ha.
(CHUCKLES)
It melted all over the seats.
Sorry? What did?
My dad's car with the leather seats.
We were goin' to t'seaside
and chocolate melted all over the seats,
but he wasn't angry.
He just bought me another one.
Fuck! What the fuck are you doing, talking
shit about me behind my fucking back?
You're ashamed? You're fucking ashamed?
- You fucking shambles!
- What the? Get off him!
- Fucking mug.
- Get off!
You're all right. You're OK.
Come on, dude! This way.
Oh...
- What is he wearing?
- What? They're nice shorts, them.
Trainers? What, he's going
for a kick-about in the park, is he?
I don't care what he does.
He can do what he wants!
Guys. There's someone
I'd like you to meet.
- (OTHERS GASP)
- Eurgh!
I found him at the group last night.
- There's a person in there.
- JESS: Sorry? Hang on.
You found a turtle,
and you just thought that
you'd pick him up and take him home?
You abducted a turtle?
- Well, technically, it's a tortoise.
- (FINN CLEARS THROAT)
Guess who followed the evil old woman
home from the support group
and got her address?
This guy did! Genius.
The lad's a frigging genius.
Eight GCSEs. English, Maths and French.
Where's he gone, then?
- Who? Gone?
- Shit!
RUDY: Oi!
Mate, what you doing?
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Idiot. Where you going? It's this way.
- You moron... Oh, Christ.
- And who the fuck might this be?
- Er...
- What's the matter? Cat got your tongue?
Aaah!
Argh! Argh!
Oh!
Aren't you going to introduce us?
Shit, I don't know who he is.
He's nothing to do with me.
He's my grandad.
Men like this fought in wars,
cheek by jowl,
belly-down, crawling through the mud,
the blood, and the fear. And for what?
Eh?
Boys with hair straighteners.
Girls in jeggings,
with their flabby arses hanging out!
It was my very real privilege
to have met you, sir.
(SIGHS)
You need to step up!
He is your responsibility!
Oh, fine! Fine. I'll sort... I'll sort it.
Fuck!
Right, just get you in here.
Perfect. Look at this place.
Just...
(GRUNTS)... just get you sat down there.
There we go.
And what do we have in here?
Look at that.
What a lucky fella! There you go.
Cornetto, chair.
It's like the frigging Ritz in here.
Have fun. Don't eat it all at once.
See you in a bit.
(DOOR CREAKS)
Are you Alex?
Your mate said you'd take my power.
What mate?
- Your mate with the milky nipples.
- (DISTANT DOG BARKS)
- What? Sorry?
- He was short.
Oh, Finn. You monkey-faced fuck.
Er... look, no of fence, mate,
but I don't really do blokes.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means I'm not into having sex with men.
- What, you think I'm gay?
- I don't really care what you are.
Look, I'm not gay!
This is it. Her name's Maggie.
All right, Maggie.
It's time to pay
the fucking piper, biatch.
Bosh!
- What are you doing?
- Well, I thought it was part of the plan!
We could have just knocked.
It's too late to frigging knock now,
Finlay, for crying out loud!
Is it too late to knock?
Shit, I'm just gonna knock, man,
see what she's saying.
You-hoe'?
Here she comes. What do I say?
Say sorry.
All right, love?
Why did you break my door?
Because I....
I thought you'd fallen... over...
...and broken your hip.
Well, you can fix that lock
when you've helped me with my jigsaw.
Oh... God.
I have a cat.
She may try to drink from your nipples.
- What are you doing?
- It just fucking won't fit.
You need to find the edges first,
work from the outside in.
- Basic puzzling.
- Oh, just...
fuck the jigsaw, man.
I'm going undercover.
- I'm going to see what she knows.
- OK.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
(SIGHS) So... Maggie.
I suppose you're...
quite surprised to see me.
Aren't you?
It's Wednesday.
You always come Wednesday.
- Hands.
- (TUTS AND SIGHS)
Oh...
So...
how's that awful Rudy 1 treating you?
He's not awful. He's just...
he's a bit misunderstood, that's all.
You should leave him.
I'm sick of telling you.
Well, maybe he needs me.
And perhaps it's time
he learnt to look after himself.
Well, with all due respect,
perhaps it's time you minded
your own fucking beeswax, Margaret.
I don't think I care
for your tone today, Rudy 2.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have sworn.
Bedroom.
There's a ball of pale pink.
Well, go on.
(TUTS AND SIGHS)
Yes.
All four corners.
Huh.
They all mean something.
Who knows what?
They'll find out eventually.
Who Will?
The people on the jumpers.
It's their future.
- (SNORTS)
- You'd better be going.
Don't you usually meet up with Tim
on a Wednesday?
Oh! Tim! Course I do!
Tim... Tim. Tim waits for no man,
as it t'were.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
- Seriously, though.
I've mislaid my old Filofax. Can't
remember. Where exactly do I meet Tim?
FINN: She knits the future. It's not
exactly your classic superpower, is it?
Hey.
I need to talk to you.
Oh.
(CLEARS THROAT) So...
Tim? I suppose you're, er...
quite surprised to see me.
Give us a minute.
Stay. Where you going, dude? Stay there.
Tim? Tim?
- It happened again.
- Hm?
I woke up this morning and I found this.
Oh, for fuck... Do you?
What? Fucking gun!
I don't know where it came from,
but it can't be good.
Help me.
Just please tell me what to do.
All right, instead of me telling you
what I think you should do,
maybe you should tell me
what you think you should do, Tim.
I need to snap the band.
Remind myself that this is real.
That it's not a game.
Cool. Well, then, just snap it.
You snap the band,
remind yourself it's real and...
Well, what, dude?
What?
What's the matter, dude? You're getting
a little bit twitchy there, dude.
Let's not get that out...
For fuck's sake, put it away.
They'll ring the fucking police.
- (GUN COCKS)
- No, no, no, no, no! For fuck...
Snap the band, dude! Put it away!
Fucking snap the band, Tim.
Snap the fucking band!
Snap the fucking band.
Put the fucking gun in the bag.
Dude, put the fucking gun in the bag.
For Christ's sake, Tim! Shit!
- (SIGHS)
- Thanks.
Oh! You're welcome.
You're a good friend.
You're not so bad yourself.
Finlay, dude, drink that shit up.
Why the fuck does he help these people?
And he doesn't even go on about it,
he doesn't tell anyone.
I... I gave 20p to Cancer Research.
I'm still going on about it.
- Are you all right?
- There's something I need to do.
- I'll call you later.
- OK.
RUDY: Here he is.
The silver fox, where...
Shit!
You locked him in a fucking cupboard!
Huh. Well, technically,
that's not a cupboard.
That's a bloody storeroom, innit?
No, this isn't a fucking joke.
It was only five minutes while I was...
I was taking care of everything. So...
I don't care if it's for five minutes
while you go for a piss.
All right. Jesus Christ,
I'm fucking sorry, like.
Look at him! Look at him!
This is not a joke!
This is not some minor inconvenience
to your day!
It's not some random old man!
He's Rudy 2 and he's a part of you!
All right.
(WHISPERS) Shit.
I'm sorry, man. Oh, shit, I'm sorry.
Oh, no, it's all right.
Don't be sad.
Oh, I'm tired.
Go and get some bloody shut-eye.
I'll go and get our dinner.
We'll watch it in front of the TV, yeah?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
(SNIFFS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
It's me.
- Mr Johnson.
- You.
You came back.
Look at you.
I didn't mean for it to happen like this.
I love her.
I've waited my whole life
to feel this way...
...and now I've got her,
I... I can't just let her go again.
I'm so sorry.
- Goodbye, Rudy 2.
- Help me.
Help me. Help me! Help me!
He's here! Help me!
Help me!
Are you all right, mate?
He was here! He was here!
- Who was here? Calm down.
- He was here! He was here!
- He's still here! He's still here!
- Calm down. Who was in here?
(GASPS)
My tea. I wanted my tea.
Oh, Christ.
It's all right, mate. I'm here now.
I'm here now and I won't leave you.
Now, then, until I can figure out
how to get him back to normal,
we're all gonna take turns helping,
so I've drawn out a simple rota system.
That's colour-coded and handwritten.
Laminated. Nice touch.
Thank you.
In here we have boiled sweets.
They're for you, dude.
TV guide. You'll note I've ringed
all the relevant programmes.
Diagnosis Murder, snooker,
Cash In The Attic, and Bargain Hunt.
(SLAPS MAGAZINE)
This fine figure of a man has looked after
me more times than I care to remember,
and I tell you something else,
he'd have done the same
for each and every one of you,
because he's a bloody good bloke.
Now, we've got a lot to do.
So I think we should get on it.
Let's do this. Come on, guys.
(REGGAE PLAYS)
# Well, I heard about the good news
that happened last night
# Oh, yeah, and it brings out joy... #
(SNAP)
#...And happiness gone deep inside
# Oh, yeah
# Yes, I'm glad
I'm glad of some good news
# That's happened last night
# So don't you marvel
# These things must come to pass... #
Um... Alex, will you do me a quick favour?
Will you fuck my tortoise?
Urn... just give me a minute
to think about... that.
(SNIFFS) Er... actually,
I don't need a full minute. It's a no.
It's a man and his name's Mark.
He's trapped in here and he can't get out.
- That is really tragic.
- Mm.
But I'm still not fucking your tortoise.
You have no idea, do you?
I found out what my power is
and it's totally useless.
There's nothing I can do to help anyone.
But you... you can make a difference.
You're the only one out of us
who can actually change people's lives.
And what are you doing about it? Nothing.
It's just sat there in your pants.
Use your power, Alex.
Help people.
Be a superhero.
Fuck the tortoise, Alex.
Right! Here we go, look,
clean clothes. You're gonna be beating
'em off with a shitty stick, you are.
There you go. All right, let's get...
What the frigging hell are you wearing?
My jumper. Maggie made it for me.
He was cold. I found it under the sofa.
That's fucking me! That's me!
I'm fucking flying! Look!
- What are you talking about?
- It's the future.
That is me, that.
I fucking knew... I knew it!
Oh, it's just a jumper.
This woman, she knits the future.
That is us, look.
All right.
How comes there's only four of us?
Well, she's had to miss Finn out,
obviously.
No-one can knit
that fucking small, can they?
(LAUGHS)
Let's get him... let's get him
ready for bed. Hands in the air.
Whoo-hoo!
Let me just sort your collar out.
Right, let's get this off. Are you ready?
Where's he gone? Where's he gone?
Oh, my God, where's he gone? There he is.
- Right.
- Oh, tell him about the chocolate.
What chocolate?
The leather seats.
You were going to the seaside.
Chocolate all over seats.
Me dad's car with the leather seats.
Oh, shut up, man. No-one
wants to hear about that. It's boring.
No. I like it.
It was a... a Curly Wurly.
And I put it in my back pocket
of my... of my shorts.
And I sat on it all the way from home
until the motorway.
That were a bloody brilliant holiday!
I can't...
D'you know, I forgot about that.
Er... I buried me tank on t'beach.
The fucking... the tank.
I got... I loved that tank.
I got it for my birthday, didn't I?
Me mam and dad,
they dug up the whole beach,
but they couldn't find it.
15 years later, they went back,
didn't they, to the same beach?
Oh, aye.
They were eating their sandwiches...
...and there was a boy.
He was making a hole.
(TUTS) They found my tank.
I got my bloody tank back.
(SIGHS)
Do you want to watch TV?
- Er... yeah. Yeah, all right, then.
- Yeah? Good.
I'll get the crisps, shall I? All right?
(BOTTLES CLINK)
The irony is
that for me to take your power,
and for you to stop
being trapped in closets,
we need to have anal sex.
Mm.
Just so we're clear, am I fucking you
because you're not gay
and you're just sick of having your power?
Or am I fucking you because you are gay
and you just don't want anyone
to know about it?
It's a head-scratcher.
It's my dad.
He won't accept me.
Well, then, he's a dick.
He's the one who needs helping, not you.
I should go.
I don't suppose
you'd fancy a drink some time?
DAVID ATTENBOROUGH ON TV:
And though their mating is now over,
the male will often begin
to review his amorous...
- Eurgh. What you doing?
- Noth... nothing.
Shit. I'm sorry. I just thought...
I thought it was his neck.
- Oh.
...picking fleas and tics out of his fur
and so...
Right, come on, you, buggerlugs, drink up.
Homes Under The Hammer
is about to start. Let's have it.
Come on.
We don't want to miss that, do we?
- What are you doing, man?
- I think he's having a heart attack.
What do we do? Fuck!
Somebody help!
- Somebody help!
- Breathe!
Jesus fucking Christ! What do we do?
Stand back.
- Are you a doctor?
- I'm an electrician.
He's not fucking breathing!
Clear!
Oh, shit.
RUDY: Are you all right, mate?
JESS: Are you all right?
- Are you all right?
- He is.
It's all right, man, I'm here now.
It's all right, bud.
- Yeah, you're all right.
- Thanks. Thank you.
Get him up.
Finn's with him. He's gone off to sleep.
(SIGHS)
He's gonna die, isn't he?
Not... not now.
Soon.
And I'm going to be all on my own.
Who's going to look after me
when I get like that?
Maybe you'll meet someone,
settle down, have kids.
Like a normal person.
Who'd want to settle down with me?
Hm?
When my grandad got old,
we found him a home.
He was happy there.
Maybe it's the best thing for him.
For everyone.
They'll look after him.
You can visit him when you like.
Yeah.
Will you come with us?
Of course I will.
All we need now is get you a bloody TV.
Couple of posters.
It's a fucking bachelor pad. That's what
this... Look at this. En suite.
Cheeky wee in the sink.
And if you fancy a ham and avocado
sandwich at four in the morning,
you got your room service there,
cheeky tug.
- (RUDY CHUCKLES)
- He came. He... he came to see me.
Oi, listen to me.
I'll come and see you.
I'm gonna be here so often, you're gonna
be sick of the friggin' sight of me.
I'll see you soon.
Yeah?
All right?
Let's just get away. We'll go somewhere.
- Start again.
- (LAUGHS) Where?
I don't know. Anywhere.
There's too many memories for me here.
Or...
...how about
we don't go anywhere...
and we just go for a drink instead?
(CHUCKLES)
I went back to your group.
No-one knows anything.
Shit, I'm... I'm sorry, man. I tried.
You know, but then I went
to Mum and Dad's house
and I've got you a present.
(GRUNTS)
Eh?
Oh, yes.
They dug up the whole beach.
They were having their sandwiches...
They did.
I want you to have it, yeah?
You? I wasn't expecting to see you.
Really? Why? Sorry, why might that be?
Mr Johnson isn't here any more. He's gone.
I'm sorry, I just... I seem
to have mislaid the old Filofax.
Which Mr Johnson do you mean?
Cos I help a few on a regular basis,
that's all, so...
Len Johnson. I'm really worried about him.
We've tried all the hospitals,
but there's no sign of him.
- Thanks.
- Hm.
(WOMAN SINGS ARIA)
(WHEEZING)
It's OK.
There's no need to panic.
We're going to be together.
Me and Naomi.
I know you'd be happy for us.
But I can't risk you ruining everything.
(HE GROANS)
(MUFFLED GROANS)
(MUFFLED MOANS)
What the fuck are you doing to him, man?
He's my friend.
My power. I can swap ages with people.
Rudy 2 used to let me switch with him
for an hour a week
just to give me a break
from being an old man.
(GASPS)
I loved her from the minute I saw her.
(SNIFFS) Naomi.
She was my nurse.
I never got married. I...
...never found my true love... until now.
What if I was to tell her
what you've been doing?
What if I showed her the photo of you?
Cos then she'd see you
for what you really are.
Please don't tell her.
- You all right, mate?
- (COUGHS)
It's all right, mate.
(COUGHS)
It's all right, it's all right.
Do it.
Do it or I'll tell her everything.
Take his hand. It's all right.
Come on.
All right, pal. There.
You're all right.
Now then,
I believe a thanks is in order,
innit, young man? Ha-ha-ha!
You locked me in a cupboard.
No, it wasn't a cupboard,
it was a storeroom,
and I wiped your arse
and I gave you butterscotch
and I let you watch the friggin' snooker.
- I don't like the snooker.
- You ungrateful fucker!
- Nah, I'm only kidding. You did great.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
I'm going now, mate. See you on Friday.
(KISSES)
Hey, come on. Give over, you soft shite.
Come here, come on, welcome home.
(CHUCKLES)
So...
about that gay guy
that you hooked me up with.
- Oh! Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
I just wanted to say thanks.
It felt good helping somebody.
You know, I think this is what
I'm supposed to do with my power.
You know, be like a... a proper hero.
And all thanks to you, eh?
Yeah, pleasure.
So, hang on. Now you're into
helping people, would you?
No. I won't shag your tortoise.
Morning, Mark. Did you sleep well?
(WHISPERS) See you later.
- You all right?
- Mm.
Oh!
Is it weird that I miss him?
It was nice having someone to look after.
No, I don't think it's weird.
Do you know what?
If I wasn't such a total fuck-up, I'd...
I'd probably ask you out for a drink
and you'd say yeah
because, well, I wouldn't be the mess
that stands before you now.
I'd be... I'd be someone different,
you know, someone...
...you know, someone good.
And we'd end up having
this really amazing time together and...
I dunno, we might even end up
as boyfriend and girlfriend.
(CHUCKLES)
And it wouldn't end up with me
just fucking it up all the time
and you thinking I'm a total cunt.
It wouldn't be like that at all.
It'd be nice.
And we'd be happy... together
and, I don't know, fucking hell, one day
we might even get a dog or something.
(SHE CHUCKLES)
Huh.
All right, then.
All right, then, what?
You just asked me out for a drink
and I said yes.
Yeah.
Huh.
Sam. Sam.
I wanna show you something.
Is that me?
Yeah. I think so. Huh!
And this girl down here
with the lightning bolts.
I had an heart attack. She saved my life.
Who's that on top of the building?
- I don't know.
- Maybe it's you.
What if we all become superheroes?
Huh!
I mean like, you know, proper...
superheroes.
Maybe it's our destiny.
#...l saw you
# So cruelly you kissed me
# Your lips a magic world
# Your sky all hung with jewels
# The killing moon
# Will come too soon
# Fate
# Up against your will
# You give yourself to him... #
- (BEEP)
- I think it was my friend Lia.
Lia?
I... I think she did something to me.
- What do you do?
- Probation worker.
I... Oh, my God.
Just don't talk to me. I'm... I'm a twat.
I'm... I'm Lia.
It was you, wasn't it?
Can I just? Let me just say, in my...
- let me just say in my defence...
- Aaah!
JESS:It's her.
She's downloaded into Alex.
Oh!
Girls, girls, girls, girls, girls!
I think he's gone.