Jess, I...
Jess.
It's Alex.
They're giving him a lung transplant.
- Shit.
- I tell you now.
You don't want to be getting
a transplant round here.
Hi. How are you? OK?
Good. You're Alex, right?
I'm not being funny,
but you have to have sex with me.
I've only just got out of surgery.
You need to leave.
We're just talking.
Get him out of here.
Please! You have to fuck me!
Call security!
Think about it! Think about it!
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
OK. Bye.
Alex is out of surgery.
He's going to be OK.
Ah! Get in, mate! Well done.
I tell you now, I never
doubted it for a second.
The handsome barman lives.
Come on. Dude, you need
to pay up right now.
That's 20 of your English pounds.
Fucking pygmy.
Let's have it, come on.
You... you put money on him dying?
Yeah!
No! No. What kind of person
do you think I am?
You said it would be funny
if they chopped his cock off
during the operation.
There's something very wrong
with you. Oh, Finn.
Honestly.
Well, I'm glad he didn't die. I am.
But I will say this.
He may have a new lung,
but you can't replace
his cheating heart.
Twat.
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Scouts, dude! Yes! You're Scouts.
These were the happiest and
the proudest days of my life.
Look at 'em!
You were in the Scouts?
That should never have been allowed.
I swore... I swore a solemn oath to,
you know, to obey the Scout Law,
to do my best, to do my duty to God
and Her lovely majestic
Majesty the Queen.
Huh. Lived by a code.
I were like a samurai warrior.
Yeah, that's... that's you all over.
And then... and then
they cast me out.
Why were you cast out?
I don't want to talk about it.
I will say this.
A Scout is meant to walk an
impossible line
between his love of scouting
and his raging hormones
in the first flushes
of sexual adventure.
There are girls!
You're a girl! Shit!
That's an unnatural abomination.
This is not how Baden-Powell intended it!
Take that uniform off!
You look like a dick!
Shit.
Is he still staring?
He's really staring.
He's gone.
Look at 'em. Scouts... Scouts
is a time for boys to be boys.
You know, the... the first time
I masturbated. Scouts.
The first time I ever saw
another boy's penis. Scouts.
First time I touched
First time another boy
touched my penis.
Scouts? It was in Scouts!
It was in Scouts. Happy,
sunlit days is what they were.
Oh, my God. Look at this tramp.
Hi.
Ahem. Hi. Ahem! Hi.
What the fuck was that?
Shame on you, Finley!
You've got a visitor.
Handsome barman! Here he is.
How you diddling, mate?
Eh? I've brought you
some grapes and that.
I haven't brought you any grapes.
How's Jess?
She's dead.
She's not really dead.
I was just trying
to make you feel better.
So...
she didn't want to come and see me?
Yes, she did.
She wanted to come, but she...
She hates my guts, doesn't she?
She doesn't hate your guts, man.
Well, maybe. I don't know. She...
Do you... do you know what, man?
Who could ever possibly
understand the inner workings...
They've got little
fickle minds, mate.
My dad, he used to say to me,
you know, he used to say,
"Rudy, women are very much
like tractors."
Which I have never understood.
I think it's something, really,
to do with potatoes.
That's what it is. Shit.
They're just not like men,
seriously.
Hi.
What's this badge for?
Fire safety.
I know who to call
if there's a fire, then.
You should call the Fire Service,
activate the fire alarm and leave
by the nearest emergency exit.
Right, yeah. Good... good to know.
You know, always... be prepared.
What about this one?
Global Conservation.
First aid. Road safety.
This one here is for fucking.
Really? They...
they give badges for that?
No.
Yeah, I know.
Because of health and safety...
..and AIDS.
Have you ever fucked a Scout before?
Have I?
That would be a... a no.
No, I haven't.
I...I fingered a Girl Guide, though.
Do you mind if I tie you up?
You are full of surprises. Go for it.
I hate to sound like my dad,
but are you over 16?
I'm 18. Ah.
What type of knot are you using?
A double constrictor knot,
almost impossible to get out of.
Ooh, good choice.
OK. Now lie down.
Right there.
He's ready.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
Oh, shit.
- Hi.
- Oh!
Shit. Do you want tell me
what the fuck is going on?
You are to become one of us.
A Scout? Can't I just
fill in a membership form?
You are to become an agent of Satan.
And if I say no?
Oh, shit. Shit.
Then I'll cut out your heart
and burn it in hellfire.
Is that a chicken?
Oh, you... you've got the wrong guy.
I'd make a terrible agent of Satan.
I'm... I'm lazy, and...
and disorganised,
and ask anyone who knows me,
I'm... I'm shit.
Ecce Satanas meo...
sicut ego et ipse regnabit Dominus
super terram
meam tenebris...
Jesus! Fuck!
You killed the chicken!
Lucifer habitabunt in te!
Aah! Aah!
Aah.
You should see his scar.
Dude looks like Action Man.
What an handsome barman!
You've seen him?
Of course I've bloody seen him.
We're best mates. Some people say...
..we look like brothers. Ahem!
You're best mates? Mm-hm.
Really? Erm... what's his surname?
Kagi... Kagillima.
Kagillima?
It's... it's...
it's Wong... Smith.
Wong-Smith?
I know. It's ridiculous, innit?
So, you know how the handsome
barman saved your life?
Does that cancel him out
shagging that girl?
Cos it feels about the same to me.
Why are you so interested?
Because if you stop seeing him,
he'll just... he'll leave, won't he?
He'll wander from town to town
like The Littlest Hobo.
And, Jess, I don't know whether my fragile
heart could ever take any more of...
You're not going to believe
what's just happened to me.
Were you bent over double again,
sucking yourself off,
bit of pollen's gone up your nose,
you've sneezed,
you've bit the tip off your penis...
No!
Oh, come on.
? Gonna throw it back to you
? By now you should've somehow... ?
? Realised what you gotta do
? I don't believe that
anybody feels the way I do
? About you now. ?
Yeah.
They don't look
like agents of Satan.
Of course they don't look
Agents of Satan never look
like agents of Satan, do they?
Mm.
You don't believe me, do you?
You think it's all just a desperately
sad and lonely cry for attention.
Yeah, well, I told them you were
capable of anything, mate, so...
Oh, when you come in tied up,
covered in chicken blood...
What's that? Chicken blood?
Hm?
It was Finley.
What? It was Finley.
Oh.
Have you been running
an illegal slaughterhouse
in my community centre?
No.
If I find out you have been
supplying local restaurants
and kebab houses with dodgy meat...
You won't, cos I haven't.
Then we don't have a problem, do we?
No. No.
? You're my wonderwall... ?
Pussy.
Hi. It's me.
How do you know where I live?
So, I guess I kind of followed
you home from the hospital.
Don't freak out. Look, I don't know
what your problem is. I don't care.
So, can you just piss off?
Oh, fuck! Oh!
Fuck!
The door slamming like that.
It wasn't an accident.
Well, it was, but it was me.
I've got this power.
I cause accidents. It's a nightmare.
Neil said he could make it stop.
Who's Neil?
You've got his lung.
They transplanted it into you.
He had this power. He could fuck
other people's powers out of them.
He was going to fuck my power
out of me. Is that what he told you?
He was after a shag.
I've spoken to people he helped.
He took their power.
His power's been
transplanted into you.
Is this a wind-up?
Did Jess put you up to this?
It's a test, isn't it?
And if I shag you then I fail.
Well. Ha!
Good try. Because
it's not going to happen.
Seriously.
Take a hint.
The catch on the
dishwasher door broke.
I tripped over it,
fell on a potato peeler.
The handle of a mug of tea
snapped off as I was drinking it.
Jesus.
There was a loose paving slab
at the top of a flight of steps.
I don't even remember
what all these are.
That's just a birthmark.
I've got money. I'll pay you.
I don't... I don't want your money.
You cheated on me,
and I can't forgive you for that.
Maybe I should be able
to get over it because
I really fucking like you,
but I can't.
We were together and
you shagged her,
and I really fucking
hate you for that,
but then you go and get yourself
stabbed for me and you save my life.
Why did you shag her?
Why would you do that?
Because now I have to end it with
you and that is really fucking hard!
Say something, then, you dick.
I promise...
it is not what you think.
Oh, my God. No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No. It's not like that.
You unbelievable fucking twat!
You just made it so much easier!
It's a power thing, Jess!
Please can we fuck now?
You're not helping!
Well.
Look who it is.
Yeah, well, look who it is...
right back at you.
Have you seen this?
I'm going to have a scar.
You were trying to convert me
into an agent of Satan.
You don't have to worry
about that any more.
I'm going to rip out your heart
and shove it up your arse.
Rudy!
Guys, a little help!
Seriously?
Whoa!
Who's laughing now?
Hoc cecidit angelus devorabit vos!
Rudy!
Resident in tua anima, mea tenebris
emergere reget hoc mundo!
Fuck off! Fuck off!
Lucifer reget hoc mundo,
ego reget huius mundi pro aeterno!
You've killed the Scout leader.
See, I told you he
was trying to ki...
Ah. What's wrong with you?
She dared me to swallow
my full Cornetto in one go, man.
It's given me the worse brain...
I thought I were going
to die for a minute.
We got you one.
Ooh. Thanks.
Hey, monkey boy, you done good
there. From wankster...
..to... to gangster.
That's a G. Yeah.
We should probably bury him.
I'll get the shovels. Ah.
Loop it over once.
Twice.
Left over right.
Through the rabbit hole.
Bastard!
I just thought...
For God's sake.
What?
Fucking what?
What are you staring at?
What, you never seen a grown man in
his childhood Scout uniform before?
You need to get out more, pal.
Just take that.
What's this? What am I looking at?
It's a support group.
It's for people with powers.
And I think we should...
I think we should go.
Do you?
Well, yeah, it's a...
it's a good opportunity to...
for us to talk about our situation.
Bastard!
...in a... in a non-judgmental,
confidential environment.
What situation?
There is no situation, dude.
There's absolutely
nothing to see here!
I just think... I think we need to
talk about our future, together.
And I just... I thought you might
want to be with me while we do it.
For crying out loud!
Look at Finley, eh?
Look at him. Frigging
confident and flirtatious.
Dibs on that bloody fragrant
blonde he's talking to.
Why are you telling us?
It's not who you tell.
It's the act of saying it out loud
that makes it legally binding.
I don't make the bloody rules,
love, but I will abide by them.
Shit.
Mm? Here he is!
Handsome barman. Ali G in the house.
See what I did there?
Dude, see what... Cos your name's...
Cos your name's Alex.
I just put a G on it.
It's not what you think.
Seriously. I'm not interested.
Yeah, but I didn't even shag her.
Oh, no way. He's done it again!
Mongrel. Look here.
Can we please do this somewhere else?
Do what somewhere else?
She found him shagging
another girl. That's twice now.
Why am I not surprised?
Seriously. Don't.
Oh, am... am I supposed to be scared?
Finn!
Are you scared now?
Fuck off, you little prick!
Finlay? What are you doing with
the handsome barman? Put him down!
Stop it! Stop it!
He will always shit on you,
cos that's who he is.
He can't help himself.
You need to wake up
and smell the arsehole.
Hey!
Hey! I thought of a good reason
why you should fuck me!
There's definitely
something going on with Finn.
Oh, yeah, I think he's
going through puberty.
You know, it's a very
confusing time for any young man.
I thought you said you were going to
talk to him. And I did.
What did he say? Well, I had to wait
for the right moment, you know.
I sat him down,
just put my arm around him.
We just sat there for a moment,
bit of quiet contemplation, one man,
another substantially smaller man.
And?
He went, "I'm fine. I'm good."
So, we're actually no closer
to knowing why Finn was
behaving like a total psycho?
Oh, for God's sake, Jess.
When a man wants to talk to you,
you're going to see
his lips moving like this.
And when he doesn't, he's in...
in his special quiet place,
a shed of the mind.
Hello. Welcome to the group.
Take a seat.
Why don't you tell us who you are
and a little bit about your power?
Erm...
I'm Rudy.
Well, Rudy Two.
And I was created by the storm.
I suppose you could say...
..I'm the living embodiment
of a split personality disorder.
Hi, Rudy Two.
Hiya.
Hi.
Look, I... I don't even know
if I've got this bloke's power.
There's only one way to find out.
Slip it up there.
Do we have to have full sex?
I don't know if coming on my tits
is really going to cut it.
I just don't want to hurt you.
I'm so stuffed full of painkillers
I won't feel a thing.
This is a chance to use
your cock for good.
What's the story
with you and that girl?
I messed up. I cheated on her.
You still like her?
Yeah.
So, why did you cheat on her?
Can we talk about something else?
Whatever you like.
I fucking hate guys like you.
Oh, do you want me to stop?
Cos there's plenty of
girls I can fuck
that don't look like
a big bag of shit and blood.
Sorry.
I shouldn't have said anything.
No, I... I can't do this.
Please. I'm sorry.
How do we know when it's worked?
I don't know.
Oh, Jesus.
Are you coming?
No, it's, er... mm, it's something
else. What the fuck is that?
Oh.
Thank you.
Well, Barbara...
Rudy?
All right, Finn? Is this
a dream? You look taller.
I've got something for you.
Oh! Is it a present?
You'll see.
A present for my birthday!
It's a surprise.
Is it Scalextric?
I bloody love Scalextric!
Take me to it!
Take me... take me to it.
Hey. Oh.
Yeah.
I like what you've done here, the
chicken and the candles and stuff.
I don't even know what this is.
I can see you've gone to a lot
of trouble, dude, but I just...
Shit, man, I kind of had my heart
set on Scalextric a little bit.
Ecce Satanas meo...
Hey.
..sicut ego et ipse regnabit
meam tenebris.
What, are we speaking French, eh?
Je m'appelle Rudy!
Dude, j'habite la community centre.
Finn?
What the fuck?
Finn's the devil.
Or... or at least an agent of Satan,
or whatever they call themselves.
That's why he's been
acting so weird.
When he killed that, erm...
Scout leader guy, I... I don't...
I...I don't know, I think
something...
I think happened to him.
Finn?
No. He's too short to be the devil.
You're bleeding.
Mm.
I've got my period.
What are you hiding
behind your back?
Nothing.
It's a dead chicken.
You're one of them.
Do you want to know something?
You're next.
Hiya, Jess.
I know what you are.
I'm just a cheeky little Scouser.
Eh? Eh?
Eh? Calm down! Calm down!
You're the devil.
The devil.
What's she like?
She's hilarious.
So funny. You're funny.
She's... she's one of you!
You've converted her!
No.
It's all in that pretty
little head of yours.
Oh, fuck it, fuck it, fuck it!
Shitting hell.
Chickens are fed, dude. So...
I meant... monkeys.
Shit. Shit! Fuck!
That's bad.
I, er... I haven't had sex with
anyone. I've just been in the shower.
Believe it or not, the world
does not revolve around your cock!
Bit harsh.
So, what are you going to do?
I don't know. I can't go back to the
community centre. I can't go home.
They'll be looking for me.
Well, um... you know, you can...
You can stay here
tonight if... if you want.
My friends have been turned into
agents of Satan,
and you're coming on to me?
You are unbelievable!
I can't do anything right
by you, can I?
Oh! That's hot coffee!
It's warm coffee.
Jessica.
It's Rudy. He's one of them.
It's... it's Rudy Two.
Are you in there? Rudy One's
turned into an agent of Satan.
I just... I just don't
know what to do.
I thought you might be in there
with the handsome barman.
Jess?
You all right?
So, Finn's got this book
on satanic rites,
and it says the only way
to drive Satan out of anybody
is to douse them in holy water
and you've got to...
You've got to read
this little passage here.
That's great, only
I'm fresh out of holy water.
Well, I went to the church
on the way here, so...
Sprite? No.
No, it's holy water. I
filled it up from the font, guys,
on the way here.
Finn and Rudy said they were going
to the bar later on tonight, so...
I suppose you want me to help you?
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm thinking about getting
a raven as a pet.
What?
I feel stupid asking.
Is it that raven to replace me?
Bros before hoes... and ravens.
You're flippin' cool, Finn.
Do you know that?
You're not going in
there on your own.
If I go on my own,
Finn will let me get close to him.
She's right.
Do you know how to use this?
Bullets come out of this end?
Hiya, Jess.
Can I talk to you alone?
Yeah, course. Step into my office.
It's not really an office.
It's... it's the bar.
Drink?
Uh!
Get back. Stay back!
Let the Holy Cross be my light.
Let not the dragon be my guide.
Step back, impure spirit.
What you offer me is evil.
I exorcise you in the name
of our Lord Jesus Christ.
I free you from
the snares of the devil.
Get thee back, Satan! Get thee back,
Satan! Get thee back, Satan!
That's brilliant, innit?
"Get thee back, Satan!
Get thee back, Satan!"
Holy water?
It's Sprite.
This isn't you. This is me.
I'm just improved. Version 2.0.
Version 2.0 is a dick.
I like the original.
Didn't want to fuck me,
though, did you? Don't.
You'll come round.
First I'm going to cut off Alex from
the bar's cock and feed it to him.
Don't come any closer.
Or what? You're going to shoot me
in my cute and monkey-ish
little face?
Go on, then.
Do it.
Shoot me.
Do it!
I'm really sorry.
About what?
I'm one of them.
Ow! What was that?
Ooh!
Uh. Oh.
Oh!
How fucking cool is that?
It is very cool.
I'm going to call him Nigel.
Big mistake, my friend.
Isn't it a bit weird
that we're agents of Satan
but we're still
on community service?
We'll burn the probation worker
at the stake after lunch.
There's something
I want to show you first.
What is it?
Let me see.
You did all this for me?
Just because I'm Satan's
chief agent on earth,
doesn't mean I can't be romantic.
I love you.
I always have.
And now I'm going to fuck you
and make you a bride of Satan.
Look forward to it.
Oh!
Mm! Mm, mm!
I'm doing this for you.
It was the lung transplant.
I've got the power to
fuck powers out of people.
Look, I know you can't forgive me
for shagging that girl.
And I'm not asking you to.
And I could say that it will
never happen again, but it would.
There's always going to
be some other girl.
I hate myself for what I
did to you and I'm sorry.
But now I've got the chance
to... to use my cock for good.
And I want to save you.
I'm doing this for you.
I'm sorry.
Is that what I think it is?
Sorry.
You fucked me?
Do you think I enjoyed it?
Probably.
I was shagging the devil out of you.
And it was the only way.
And I was doing it for her.
Hiya, Jess.
Mm.
Ooh.
This is for you.
But you... Hang on.
How kind. What... what is it?
I knit the future.
Ah.
Thanks.
So, these people here in these
orange jump suits, is that us?
I think so.
Are we going to become
proper superheroes?
Ah!
Did you get community service
for fucking him up the arse
or breaking into
the community centre?
Breaking and entering.
Breaking and entering
his sphincter. Boom!
We all know what happened!
I think we're all mature enough to
brush it under the carpet,
as far as it will go.
Not just under the carpet -
under the underlay under the carpet.
Where things go when there's
no need to speak about them
or think about them ever again.
So, how comes he didn't
take your telekinesis?
I guess it's last in, first out.
Of his sphincter! Boom!
I thought we weren't
going to talk about it?
Sorry. Sorry.
Eugh!
What? I just... Shit, man.
I don't know. I keep thinking
about you and him. It's horrid.
Oh, for... What happened to
brushing it under the underlay
under the carpet?
I live in the flat below, Finn,
and I've drilled
an hole in the ceiling.
I can see everything, mate, every...
Horrible.
Like a frigging
giant shagging a dwarf.
Boom.
Oh, shit! It's my dad!
Dude, your mum and dad
are proper going for it.
That's not my mum!
Please, don't.
I will find you and I will hurt you.
Mum has a right to know
what's going on here.
I won't do it!
So, there's this stuff going
on with our parents, and...
..he won't let me in.
He won't listen to me.
Why don't you just leave him
the fuck alone, yeah?
I'm going to shank you!
He's burning her clothes.
Why's he burning her clothes?
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.