Should I compare thee
to a summer's day?
Thou art more lovely.
You're laughing at that?
I am allowed to laugh.
It's him! It's Rudy 2!
Stand back!
Are you a doctor?
I'm an electrician.
There's someone inside
of there?
Yeah.
It's someone with a power.
All right, mate.
Who's that on top of the
building?
Maybe it's you.
What if we all become
superheroes?
Oh!
What you doing?
Noth... Nothing.
Shit, I'm sorry, I just...
I thought it was his neck.
Leah?
I can hear you.
I know you're in there.
Leah!
I know something
happened to you in the storm.
Something happened to me, too.
I've been going to this group...
It's for people like us.
You don't have to
go through it on your own.
We could go together.
I miss hanging out with you.
Call me.
Leah?
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
From man-to-smaller-man,
you're never going to get over this
childish infatuation with Jess
until you find a girl who looks up
at you with little puppy-dog eyes
and says the words, "Your tiny little cock
tastes like marmalade, Finlay."
Now, look at her - she looks
like a fun girl. Eh? Lady Marmalade!
Some people say tears
are the best form of lubricant.
No-one says that.
Oh...
Ow!
Sorry. I'm so...
Lubricant!
It's the best form of lubricant.
Better than tears...
marmalade.
Because it's more
lubricating...
Just fuck off!
Tea?
Hope it starts soon -
got work to do.
Bloody paperwork - never
stops, eh?
I know.
What d'you do?
Probation worker.
Oh, my God, I'm... I'm so
sorry.
Oh, my God.
I was just going to clean the biscuit off.
I kind of splattered ya.
O-OK.
I don't usually spit tea and
biscuits in a girl's face.
Unless she's asking for it.
I'm not saying...
you were asking for it...
No. No means no.
And that's coming from a guy
who gets told no a lot.
I mean, it's not like I'm out
there, forcing myself on girls.
I don't know what the fuck
is wrong with me.
I'm really sorry. Just don't talk
to me.
I'm... I'm a twat.
I'm Leah.
Finn.
I'm Finn.
Oh!
Pick'n'mix! You've been holding out
on me, Finlay.
Little bastard.
I know what you're doing.
Just a minute!
This is about Jess, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about you taking Finn to
the support group to hit on girls
so you don't feel so guilty
about your feelings for Jess.
Well, I refute that.
Or at least, I think I do.
What does "refute" mean?
It means you don't accept
something.
Yeah, well, I refute that.
What if I was to tell Finn why you're
so keen on him getting a girlfriend?
Don't, you can't. I really like
Jess...
Just stay away from the
support group, please.
Fine, I will! I'll stay away from
your ridiculous support group, pal.
Oi, I'm still the boss of you,
pal.
I refute that.
Oh, do you? Well,
when I learn how to fly, I'm going
to soar like a friggin' eagle.
And I'm gonna take a massive shit on
your head from a very great height.
It isn't you on the jumper.
You don't know that!
It's very difficult getting
a good likeness in wool.
I will not let you screw up
the future for all of us.
Gah, whatever.
Refuted!
I refute you, sir!
Do you think I should go over and
put a good word in for him?
What are you going to say?
I could tell her about
his strangely weighty balls.
They're like... hairy apples.
Are you Alex?
Yeah.
I was told you can help me.
With my power.
What's the problem?
I turn things inside out.
Hm.
That doesn't seem that bad.
It's good for doing the laundry.
And transgender surgery.
I turned my cat inside out.
OK...
Why don't we go somewhere
a bit quieter?
OK.
So what's your power?
What?
Your power.
Why were you at the support
group? Oh...
Er... I have super hearing.
That's so cool.
What?
I said, "That's so cool."
I said it quietly, because you
can... Right.
It's not always on.
It gets too loud.
OK.
So, what about you?
What's your power?
I can move
other stuff, too. Not just lager.
Shit! Shit, I'm sorry.
I-I should go.
Do you want me to walk
you home?
Sorry.
Sorry. Just let it air dry.
Not it. The trousers.
Let them air dry.
Shall we...?
Oh!
..Hi.
Do you... like apples?
Er... yeah.
You are gonna love his balls.
Well, I hope everything works out
for you. Sorry about your cat.
Oh, never mind.
We were just...
We can probably guess, actually.
We don't need... any photos...
Videos.
Well... Have a good night.
Having a great night anyway,
already.
Alex.
From the bar.
Can't keep it in his pants for more
than two seconds. It's a sickness.
A disease.
Can I get your number?
Sure, yeah.
I'll call you. OK.
Is anyone going to the bar tonight?
I work there.
I wasn't talking to you.
I'll go with you.
Whatever.
Sure, I'll go for a drink.
Yeah. Oh, oh... Shit, I can't.
No, I met this girl at the support
group last night.
Leah. Yeah, we really, really
connected.
Went out afterwards for a drink...
They saw me.
So... this whole thing
about going for a drink is so you
can tell us about this girl.
No.
No! I was...
I was just interested in what your
plans were for tonight.
Excuse me!
Oh...!
Something on your mind?
You're on my mind. You are.
You've cast a spell.
I can't eat, I can't sleep
and I can't shit,
without that
popping into me head!
Well, um, I hate to mess up your
well-established routine of eating,
sleeping and shitting, so...
Do you want meet up later
and talk about it?
Yeah.
OK. Well, it's a date.
Grr, you're a witch.
You're a beautiful friggin' witch.
You know that?
Hiya.
Hi?
Don't worry, I'm...
not going to spit tea and
biscuits in your face.
Unless you want me to?
Sorry, do I know you?
Good one!
What?
Oh, I see.
You like to play games.
Well, you'd better watch yourself.
Because if you wanna play,
then you're playing...
..with a player.
I've got no idea
what you're talking about.
Or who you are.
Of course you don't.
..Game on.
Do me a favour?
I'd love to.
Stay the fuck away from me!
So, do you want to talk about
what's going on with us?
Yeah, I do.
Right, now, when it comes to
Finlay, there is no "us".
Honestly, I'll just deny I even
know you.
"Jess? Who's Jess? Is she that
Chinese fella with a bit of a limp?"
So we can't just be honest
about it?
Of course we can be honest!
We can be honest about it.
That's my middle name -
Rudy Honest Geoffrey Wade.
You go first.
I like you.
Whoa!
.Which is really weird, because you
can be such a total dick.
Hey, whoa! Well, I refute that.
That's...
That is refuted.
If you want to start seeing me,
I'm not going to sneak around.
We have to tell Finn.
Or we could just not tell him.
Bingo.
If you...
want to be with me,
then we have to tell Finn.
I don't know, isn't there, like, a
middle ground where we just...
where we don't tell him?
Just...
Yeah, all right. I'll tell him.
Man-to-smaller-man, I'm just going
to have a word with him.
It's not a problem. Oh!
Ugh!
Finlay's here!
Finlay's here.
Women.
Where?!
I'm saying.
One minute, you're...
spitting tea and biscuits in their
face and they're being all coy and shy
and the next minute, they're
acting like they don't even know you.
I'm done with this bullshit.
Wahey, where's he going?
Come here.
You mean, like, done with all
women? Everywhere?
Jesus, man - women are beautiful.
They've got lovely little...
..shapely eyebrows,
smell of pain au chocolat...
Who are you talking about?
What?
Talking about me mum.
She stinks of pastry.
Absolutely hums of the stuff.
It's probably her hormones,
I don't know.
Right.
It's Jess.
Ah.
She's the only girl for me.
Now listen, between me and you,
don't say anything, I just...
I think Jess might be a bit of a
cunt.
Whoa, you can't say that!
Why not?
Because she's perfect.
Yeah, she is perfect, mate.
She is.
She's perfection.
Eurgh!
Oh, God's sake!
So what are you gonna do?
Are you going to tell Finn
about your feelings for Jess?
Are you out of your friggin'
mind?
There is only one thing I can do.
Gah!
Finlay?
Check your messages.
Might find a little... present
there.
What is it?
Check it out. Enjoy.
Gah!
Is she taking a shit?
She's taking the Mother
Teresa of all shits, dude.
Her face is all contorted -
what the fuck?
I know!
It's enough to put you off her,
isn't it?
Eurgh, I can't watch...
Oh, my God!
Consider yourself cured
of your childish infatuation.
Why have you sent me a
video of Jess taking a shit?
Eh?
Yeah, I got one of those, too.
I thought it was one of those
e-greeting cards.
Are you fucking kidding?
Gah!
Shit!
Morning!
Morning.
Good... good morning,
Jessica.
What the fuck are you doing?
That's my phone!
Yeah, I know, I've only gone
and bloody liberated you,
freed you from the tyrannies
of friggin' texting.
You're free now. Just take off
your shackles, get rid of them,
throw it in there.
? Free-ee, Nelson Mandela
? Shoes too small to fit his
feet... ?
He should have gone to Clarks - they
do a bit of a wider fit, don't they?
You're paying for a new phone.
What d'you mean, you don't have
insurance? Bloody hell.
Well, some people might call
that a bit irresponsible.
Know what I mean?
Not me, I think it's adorable.
I call it adorable.
I call it not having a fucking
phone.
Adorable!
Fuck!
What the fuck are you doing?
So suddenly, you know me again?
Oi - you need to see this.
Yeah, I know.
It's all over the internet.
No! Fuck!
The shit's hit the fan, Finlay.
By fan, I mean fuckin' World
Wide Web.
I'll see you later.
Where are you going?
To see Leah.
The girl I met at the support
group.
You are? That's brilliant.
Get gone. Go on.
You know, I saw him coming out of
the bar with her the other night
and she looked like she
pissed herself.
Or maybe her vagina had
become so moist, it just...
..soaked through her clothing?
And when has that ever
happened?
Summer 2006, Lisa King.
Her vagina so moist,
it was like a...
..gently bubbling brook
on a beautiful spring day.
Hi.
Hi...
Who are you?
Where am I?
You're in my flat.
I found you unconscious in
the corridor.
I think you must have been in
an accident.
Shit!
I don't know what happened.
You're OK.
That's the main thing.
Do I know you?
No!
But it's weird, because I feel like I
know you, too.
I-I should go.
You don't have to!
Stay, if you like.
Do you want a beer?
I... I've got to get back,
I'm on community service.
Stay. We'll have some pizza.
D'you like Chinese food?
Anything you want.
I...I'd love to.
Honestly, I would, but I've got things
to do, you know, like litter to pick up.
There's everything we need right
here! We don't have to go anywhere.
..OK.
This has been fun, you know...
whatever... this is.
I'll see you around.
Don't.
You've had your fun, the party's
over and I'm leaving.
Fuck off! No!
Wh...?
D'you wanna tell me what's
going on?
We're in a virtual world.
I had us converted into
electronic signals.
We're just a long stream
of ones and zeros.
Here's a question.
Why the fuck would you do that?!
I like you.
You don't even know me!
It's me.
Leah.
The other night?
At the support group?
You spat biscuit in me face!
That was me.
I was... downloaded into my
friend's body.
OK.
I don't want to get heavy with
you,
but I'm done with all your little
computer games, OK?
I want out.
Game over!
I thought you liked me.
Well, call me old-fashioned, but
you kind of blew it when you turned me
into a string of ones and zeros
and kept me prisoner in a
virtual bedsit.
It's better this way!
I hate it out there.
You're a fucking nutter!
Just great - perfect.
I-I finally meet a girl that I
really... Oh!
What?
Nothin'.
You just need some time
to get your head around it.
I've got me head round it.
Yeah, I think I have.
Er, I want out!
I know we can be happy!
Where are you going?
You can't keep me in here!
Let me go!
You can't do this!
It was really weird, because
I was walking across the estate
and people were looking at me...
..and laughing.
It's happened three times now.
This one guy was really staring at
me with this big smirk on his face.
Oh, honestly! Bloody hell.
What a strange and unpredictable
world we all bloody live in.
My office.
Now. Yep.
I want to tell you a story...
OK.
This story involves a young man who
developed an affection for another
young man.
When the young man could
repress his feelings no longer,
he made a video...
..expressing his desires
via the medium of poetry.
And the young man sent the
video by electronic mail,
or e-mail, as it was to become
known.
Five minutes later,
there was a ping in his inbox
and then another...
and then another.
It transpires that the other young
man did not share his feelings...
He found the poem amusing,
so he shared it with
everyone he knew
who shared it with everyone
they knew and so on and so forth.
And the young man was understandably
upset by this cruel rejection,
so confronted the
object of his desires
in a deserted
underground car park.
And with tears
streaming down his face...
..he recited the poem again...
..as he beat the other
young man to a bloody pulp.
Do you see my point?
Not really.
Perhaps this will help you.
Gah!
Korean mash-up.
Gah-gah-gah Uh! Uh!
Hnn, hnn, hnn, hnn...
Why is there a video of me
shitting on the internet?
What d'you mean?
Making toilet on the internet?
Damn you, Bill Gates!
That's out of order, man.
Can't believe it.
It was you, wasn't it?
Can I just... Let me just say...
Let me just say in me defence...
Look, we've all made
bloody mistakes.
Aaaah!
Fucking 'ell! Jess!
What the fuck?! Jess!
Ow!
Jesus fucking Christ!
Argh!
I brought you some pizza.
You think you can just win me over
with a few slices of pizza?
Pathetic!
I'll come back later.
Whoa, wait...
What kind of pizza is it?
Hawaiian.
You're the one who wanted to
come and talk about our issues,
which, for the record, are
all in your weak little mind.
But that is before I realised
how important this group is.
Do you know, honestly, you are like
a bull with an 'ard-on in a china shop,
it's ridiculous.
Is this about Jess?
I just... I don't know what to do...
You try and do the good thing,
the right thing, the noble thing,
and what d'you have to show for it?
A friggin' broken 'eart
and a ruptured testicle.
Hm.
I'll see you later.
Brilliant.
Fuck me.
All right?
Don't ever let your testicles
get viciously beaten
with a wooden broom handle.
I'll keep that in mind.
Do.
So I hear you and Finn
were in the bar the other night,
it was all getting a little bit Lisa King
in the crotch department, wasn't it?
Eh?
The brook does bubbleth over.
I don't know what you're talking
about. Of course you don't know.
A lady doesn't speak of such
matters.
Was Madame satisfied?
No, really, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I'm talking about Madame.
And Master Finlay,
I presume he's to be found
in a pool of his own
bodily fluids somewhere.
Who's Finlay? For God's sake,
Finlay is the small,
well-intentioned monkey-ish
little fellow. You...
You are L...
You're Leah, aren't you?
Oh, I get it. I'm sorry.
You're embarrassed.
And deeply ashamed.
Just wink three times and I'll know.
It wasn't me.
I think it was my friend, Leah.
I think she did something to me.
Look, in a couple of days,
everybody is going to be going crazy
about a new video of a...
of a dancing cat, or...
Or the grizzly bear
chasing the dwarf!
It's a classic, his little legs...!
Anyway, my point is,
no-one remembers it.
You obviously remember it.
I think you looked
rather cute, actually,
your face all screwed up
and contorted.
Will you please just
shut the fuck up?!
Guys! No! Stop!
Can I just say, in my defence...
No, you f...! Don't!
Not the testicles!
For God's sake!
I think Finn's in trouble.
So... how does
this girl's power work?
Well, I don't know.
Her mate seems to think
it's something to do with computers
and friggin' inserting yourself
into people.
I don't really understand it, but
she has got our little monkey man
and I, for one, will not
let him be experimented on.
Unless she's dressing him up, man,
like one of them chimps
in the PG Tip adverts,
then colour me amused.
Can I just say, in my defence...?
Oh, my God!
Finn?
Oh, shit!
She's fucking killed him!
Finn,
I never had a chance to
tell you, dude, it was me!
I stole the birthday money
from your gran,
but I were only borrowing it, dude!
I were going to pay you back!
He's got a pulse,
he's still alive.
He doesn't need to know about the birthday
money from his gran, it was only 20 quid.
He's in here.
She's got him on a memory stick.
It's good pizza.
I'm glad you like it.
This doesn't mean I want to stay
here.
It's not even real.
It's just ones and zeros.
This isn't even real tinned
pineapple, is it?
When was the last time
you left your flat?
The day of the storm.
Wow!
You really need to get out more.
Really!
I used to go out.
Gradually, I just...
stopped.
Everything's easier online.
You chat to who you want to chat to,
you decide you don't like them,
one click and they're gone.
You never have to see 'em again.
They take the piss.
Click.
They act like a dick. Click.
You embarrass yourself... Click.
See, it's not like being out there,
you're in control.
If it works for you, great.
'I like it out there.
'You stay here and click away,
because I'm going to be on my way.'
We can be happy in here, I know
we can. We've everything we need.
If you're so happy,
then why were you
at the support group?
Why were you there if...
you didn't want help?
If this is so great,
why were you there?
Why were you there?
Because I'm lonely!
Of course you're lonely.
You never leave your flat.
You tell her, Finn.
You soft twat.
Shut up, this is good.
'Life is just passing you by.'
Real life.
And yeah, it's shit sometimes.
But you need the shit
to appreciate the good things.
Like...
the first time you meet
a girl you fancy.
That...
shy little flutter.
I had that when I met you.
At the support group,
I asked you for a drink.
That wasn't even me.
It was.
It was you, it was your
personality.
You're prettier than
your friend, anyway.
I'm... I'm not saying, like,
she's a munter...
or...
You're prettier.
We could give it a try,
out there.
I like ya. You're just saying that
so I let you go.
You'll leave and you'll
never come back. No!
If you like me, you can
stay in here with me.
No, no! No!
Finlay!
Let him go!
Right...
Shit!
I'm all out of brilliant ideas.
You don't know what you're missing.
Five foot four-and-a-quarter
inches of sheer magnificence.
No.
No!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Quick, quick, quick!
He's in.
Where's the memory stick?
I've got it.
His phone!
OK, so how are we going to get Finn
out of here and into his body?
Well...
Guys, luckily for young Finlay
down here,
one of us has a masters
degree in computer science.
Yeah, but you don't actually have a
masters degree in computer science,
do you? You have a fake certificate
that you printed off the internet.
It this about the shitting? Because
seriously... For fuck's sake.
Hello?
That was refreshingly easy.
I think we're getting better
at this stuff, guys.
Why don't I take him home with me
and then I can look after him
while we all figure out what
we're going to do?
You? You want to look after him?
What are you gonna do with him?
Give him a bath.
Scented candles.
Everyone likes a scented candle.
Mm-hm.
Yeah, and, um, you can drive him
home in your new car,
can't you?
Yeah.
Have you got a new car?
Am I on the insurance? Oh, my God!
Let's get a caravan.
Give me the memory stick.
We'll get on the ferry, we'll just go
to France, load up with baguettes,
just fucking drive, guys,
you know what I mean?
It's her.
She's downloaded into Alex.
Look, we can be together...
I can make him happy.
Handsome Barman, dude, seriously.
Are you in there at all?
Argh!
Gimme the memory stick.
Don't make me hurt you.
OK.
Jesus Christ!
Go, go, go!
Whoa!
What's happening? Ssh!
He's talking to the caretaker.
The most noble of all professions.
Argh!
He's fucking head-butted him!
Do one!
Shit!
It's a dead end!
I think he's gone. Argh!
Well... nailed to the floor.
That's a first.
Speak for yourself.
School play, Crucifixion
re-enactment gone badly awry.
Hi.
Help!
Hi!
Hello? Hi!
Oh!
You're electro girl,
me doppelganger's looking for you.
He wants to speak to you
about a jumper or something.
What are you doing?
I... I know it's a big ask,
but is there any chance at all
that you could pull these
nails out of us?
I'm...
on my way to a job, so...
"I'm on my way to a job."
That's what the Good Samaritan said
to Jesus when he found him
nailed to the Cross,
but do you know what?
He friggin' un-nailed him
and then he said, "Do you want to
kip in me stable with that donkey
"from... Bethlehem?"
And Jesus said...
Do you know what he said? He went,
"Oh, cheers, mate.
See that water over there?
"I'm gonna turn that into wine.
"And fish."
You really know your Bible,
don't you?
Me faith's very important to me.
For fuck's sake.
Whoa, careful, careful, careful.
Come with me.
Don't. You can do this!
I'll be with you.
Come on.
Don't worry,
there's nothing to be scared of.
Nobody's going to hurt you.
Get off my monkey, you crazy bitch!
Leave her alone!
What happened?
She has been inserting herself
into you, dude,
and not in a fucking
"I'm not gay,
"I just want to know how it feels"
kind of way, neither.
I'll handle this.
I think you'll find
she's already been handled.
By me.
In there.
Can I just say in my defence...
Just don't, just stop!
Jess! Please, just...
There are things
I need to tell you and I just...
You need to listen.
The business with the defecation,
perhaps that was an error of...
No, it was,
it was an error of judgment
on my part,
but my motives,
they were true and bloody noble.
Watching you defecate your guts out,
it didn't put me off you at all.
At all!
There is no greater test
of a man's feelings.
I have seen you turn shit-ugly.
But...
But to me, it was shit beautiful.
You are...
You're a beautiful shitter.
What?
Hang on, hang on.
It's not just a one-off thing,
is it? I mean...
You are going to be my girlfriend,
aren't you?
I'll be your girlfriend.
Yeah? Yeah.
Oh...
Um...
I... I'm sorry... Um...
Last week, you shocked me
and you restarted my heart.
I didn't look like this,
I was an 80-year-old man,
I had senile dementia.
That was you?
Yeah, I just... I didn't get chance
to say thank you or anything and...
Thank you.
Ooh! No, can I just...?
I'm sorry to bother you,
it's about a jumper.
Are you some kind of
knitwear salesman?
I've seen the future.
And I think it might be your future.
So what happens to me?
I think you become
a proper superhero.
It's a support group for terminally
ill young people.
I'm one of their care assistants.
It's not fucking fair.
What can you do?
Yes!
Fuck you, you fucking loser!
Holding someone, it...
It makes me feel alive.
What's going on?
I don't know what's going
on with him.
I've got something for you.
Yeah?
This has been a good day.
Yeah, it has been a good day.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.