Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
If I do happen to find her,
you'll get your reward money.
- Oh, shit.
- Who's that?
Federal marshal.
Dexter Morgan, what the hell
are you doing here?
Arlene's a friend.
We met through Hannah.
It's not safe for you to go back
to the hotel.
- You need something private.
- What the fuck?
It's only for a couple
of nights.
Couple of nights?
That's it.
Sorry I'm not Deb.
She's always accusing me
of comparing you to her.
Welcome back to Homicide,
detective.
I just need some time
to think about it.
Take all the time you need.
There's no life for me here
in Florida.
I can have a life somewhere else
far away from here--
in Argentina.
Maybe we all can.
Yes. Me, you, and Harrison
are gonna move to Argentina.
Zach's killer is related
to you.
The brain surgeon is related
I had two sons,
Daniel and Richard.
- My older son...Daniel....
- He killed Richard.
Then we put Daniel into
a mental health institute.
That guy Cassie was dating...
Daniel Vogel is Oliver Saxon.
Suppose you do find him,
Dexter.
What are you going to do?
He's murdered four
innocent people,
and he killed Jack Hamilton.
He's my son.
He got away.
That's why I'm here,
to warn you.
I think it best,
from here on out,
that I handle this myself.
Vogel is on her own,
and so am I.
I'll kill Saxon
and leave Miami forever.
So now do you believe me?
Yes.
Feels good to cook
for you again.
It reminds me of what
it was like to be your mother.
You think fixing breakfast
makes you my mother again?
- No.
- You gave up the privilege
a long time ago.
Daniel, whatever mistakes
I've made in the past,
I wan to make it up to you.
I can help you.
Help me how?
I can arrange
for the care you need.
The care I need?
I will never
be locked up again.
I have contacts
at the best facilities.
Like the last one
you sent me to?
Do you know what that was like?
Day after day wondering when
you'd finally come to visit,
only to realize
that the answer was never!
Daniel, I couldn't.
You'd killed Richard.
That was your fault!
You ignored me.
All you ever cared about
was Richard.
You never tried to help me.
I was young, inexperienced.
I didn't know how to help you.
But you sure as hell knew how
to help Dexter Morgan.
You taught him how to deal
with his condition.
You gave him everything
you denied me.
While I was rotting away,
you gave him a life.
I know that.
I do.
It was a horrible mistake.
I was your son.
I needed you.
- Please...
- Please what?
Let me help you.
I'm sorry for everything
I've done.
I truly, truly am.
I wish I could believe you.
Hannah.
Hey, Harrison.
Oh, I missed you.
Aw.
Hey, soon you'll be able
to spend
all the time you want with her,
but right now, Hannah and I need
to have a grown-up talk.
- Okay, bud?
- Okay.
So...
- some potentially good news.
- Yeah?
Deputy marshal Clayton
stopped by my place.
It seems like he's backing off
on his search for you.
Oh, that's a huge relief.
Even so, he managed to get
your face all over the news.
You still need to lay low.
So how am I gonna
get out of Miami?
Well, no one's looking
for a woman
traveling with her husband
and child.
I'm thinking the three of us
could leave together.
I like the sound of that.
There's still so much to do.
I've gotta tell Batista
I'm leaving...
get Harrison out of school,
see Astor and Cody
one more time.
I need to list my condo,
sell my boat, my car.
Deb can help out
with all that stuff.
Wow.
We're really gonna do it.
Yeah.
We're moving to Argentina.
God, that was always
such a fantasy
I never thought that
it would actually happen.
Otherwise I would have
learned Spanish.
We'll learn together.
We'll be leaving soon.
I have to kill Saxon first.
Oh, so you are gonna
go through with it.
I have to.
Vogel's not thinking clearly.
She doesn't seem to realize
she's in danger.
I feel like I need
to protect her.
You feel like you need to?
Yeah.
- What?
- It's just...
when it comes to you
and killing,
feelings never enter
the equation.
She needs me to protect her.
Hey! Stay off
aunt Deb's treadmill.
But it's fun.
No, it's not for kids.
Hey, come here.
I want to hear all about
what you've been doing
for the last eight months.
Okay.
- Hi, Aunt Deb.
- Hi.
- Come on.
- Can we talk?
What the hell is Harrison
doing with Hannah?
Deputy marshal
pulled off the detail.
It's not safe for Harrison
to be at the apartment
as long as Saxon's
still out there.
Okay, then I'll watch him,
but he shouldn't be with her.
That's not fuckin' fair to him.
Deb, I have to
tell you something.
What?
Harrison and I are
leaving soon.
What do you mean
you're leaving?
- You're leaving where?
- Leaving Miami...
with Hannah.
What are you talking about?
We're moving to Argentina.
Are you kidding?
You know how stupid
that sounds?
Deb--
You're gonna take
your fuckin' son,
move to another country
with a wanted fugitive?
Have you fuckin'
thought this through?
Deb, I have.
We want to have
a life together.
I wish there was a different
way, but there's not.
We need to leave the country,
start someplace new.
You act like this
doesn't even affect me.
I know it does.
Well, then, that's a really
selfish decision on your part.
We'll still see each other.
I'll...come up here,
and you can visit.
Okay, I'll look you up
the next time I'm in Argentina.
Deb, I'm sorry.
This is hard for me too.
- Hey. How was your day?
- Long.
Aww.
Well, I had a really good day.
Not only am I about
to graduate,
but I got a recruitment letter
from Greenwood Academy.
- A therapist position.
- What's Greenwood Academy?
It's a very well respected
special-needs school in Atlanta.
They want to set up
an interview.
That's fuckin' great.
When you going?
I'm not.
What do you mean?
Why not?
Joey, I'm not moving
to Atlanta when you're here.
I'll find something in Miami.
I'm just so flattered
that they're interested.
Jamie, I-I would feel
like shit
if I was the cause
of you missing out
on a great opportunity.
You shouldn't.
This is my decision.
All I'm saying is, you know,
you should do what's best
for your career.
What about us?
Don't worry about us, you know?
We'll...make it work.
Be right back.
I'm gonna go grab a drink.
- Evelyn.
- Tom.
Please.
Everything okay?
Yes, fine.
A little over-worked, so...
Mm. Thanks for coming in
this morning.
As I said, it's kind
of a sensitive matter.
It's about one
of your patients.
Zach Hamilton.
As I'm sure you're aware,
he's gone missing.
Yes. I was hoping he'd
turned up by now.
He hasn't.
And I promised his parents
that I would look into it
personally.
But I'm afraid I've hit
a dead end.
Tom, you know that
I'm not at liberty
to discuss my patients.
Come on, Evelyn,
I'm trying to help this kid.
Now, he lived at home.
How was his relationship
with his parents?
Like anyone his age.
Did he say anything
about trying to get away?
He talk about any friends,
maybe a special girl?
Was he into drugs?
Gambling?
- Was he suicidal?
- I don't know.
Look, I know you understand
better than anyone
what it's like to lose a child.
Not knowing is even worse.
Imagine how the Hamiltons
must feel.
I wish I could help,
but I just don't know anymore.
I'm sorry, but I have
another appointment.
Saxon killed his brother
when he was only 14.
Killed seven more in the fire
when he was 17.
How many more since then?
He's lived in a dozen cities
across two continents.
Never been arrested.
Never leaves a trace.
Is he the perfect psychopath
I once was?
- Dr. Vogel.
- Dexter.
Can we talk?
What are you doing here?
Tom wanted to question me
about Zach.
Well, of course,
I couldn't tell him anything.
But I feel horrid
keeping Zach's death
from the Hamiltons.
And we both know that Zach's
killer is still out there.
Understand, Evelyn,
you are in danger.
Well, you don't have to worry.
My son isn't gonna harm me.
- How do you know that?
- I just do.
Have you been
in contact with him?
I saw him.
When?
We had breakfast yesterday.
Where is he now?
I have no idea.
- Evelyn...
- It's the truth.
He--he was angry and he
stormed out of the house.
I don't know whether I'll
ever see him again.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you want to kill him.
And I don't want that
to happen.
I can't turn my back
on him again.
What is there you can
do for him?
Well...
first, I can establish trust.
I wasn't a good mother to him
when he was a child.
I need to win him over.
And then...
well, eventually, hopefully...
I'll get him back
into a facility.
And how many more
innocent people will he kill
before you do that,
before he kills you?
If you won't protect yourself,
I need to do it.
I don't want you
to protect me, Dexter.
I don't want you to be a hero.
- Evelyn, I have to--
- Please!
Don't use me as an excuse
for killing Daniel.
She doesn't want my help.
So do I just walk away
from this?
We could leave
for Argentina tonight.
Dexter, you don't want
to leave this unfinished.
I don't even know
how to find him.
You always find a way.
If you don't kill Saxon,
her life is at risk.
Crime scene.
You can send it back, you know.
It's not the salad.
So you asked me here
to watch me eat?
You can't tell
anybody this, okay?
Dexter is leaving Miami.
Why?
He's quitting?
He and Harrison are gonna
take the rest of the year
and travel.
Fuckin'-a.
Good for him...or not.
I don't know if he's ever
coming back, you know.
I mean, I get wanting
a change, but--
Sometimes, you know,
when things don't feel right,
changing it up is better
for everyone involved.
Not better for me.
He's my brother.
I don't want him to leave.
I understand, but maybe
you should think about
what's best for him.
Look, when I left New York,
it was one toughest things
I ever did,
leaving my friends and family.
But as it turns out,
finally being on my own
was the best thing
I ever did for myself.
Batista gave me my badge back.
Fuckin'-a, that's great.
Or not.
It's good. It's good.
I've wanted to come back
for a long time.
You tell Elway?
Not yet.
You know what
this means, right?
You and me, side by side.
Just like old times.
Seriously?
It's a crime scene.
Gotta go.
No, I got it, I got it.
Okay.
Next one's on me...partner.
Nothing will change
after I'm gone.
Blood will continue to pool,
I just won't be here
to photograph it.
The guy was hit pretty hard.
Major head wounds,
lots of broken bones,
internal injuries.
Road rage.
The guy on the bike wouldn't
get out of the way,
gave him the finger,
so the driver ran him over.
Lieutenant, can I get a word?
Sure.
Hey, Dex.
I didn't know
I had to work today.
Why would you think that?
Because it's Saturday.
Are you high?
You're high, aren't you?
I can smell it on you.
Go home.
- Dad...
- We'll talk about this later.
Go!
And stop smoking pot.
You have every right
to tell me what to do at work,
but you have no right
to tell me what to do at home.
Well, that's... that's...
that's a huge shock, Dexter.
I know it seems like
it's out of the blue,
but after Rita's death...
And with the job,
I've just had enough death
in my life for a while.
I need a break, so...
this is my notice.
You need this, don't you?
I wish you nothing
but the best.
Thank you.
I'd like
to keep this between us.
I'd like to let other people
know myself, Jamie included.
She's gonna take it hard.
You know,
she really loves Harrison.
He loves her too.
Anyway, she's moving on
herself.
New job soon.
Maybe this'll make it easier.
I'll miss you, bro.
Hey, listen,
if you change your mind,
you always have a home here.
Got it.
He said, "I'm too big for a nap,"
and then he went right to sleep.
Cute.
So are you any closer
in your search for Saxon?
Not really.
I don't know much about him.
He moves around a lot.
I guess he figures if you stay
in one place too long...
Eventually you get caught.
I wish we could just leave.
Yeah, me too, but I know
that you have
to protect Dr. Vogel.
Actually,
she doesn't want me to.
Then why are you doing this?
Because it's what I do.
It's... who I am.
It's all I know.
Dexter, you're more than that.
Am I?
You think that when
we move to Argentina
that... it's possible
for you and me
to have a fresh start?
Yes.
Well, then, the sooner
you kill Saxon,
the sooner we can get there.
Vogel is the key.
I'm sure he'll go for her.
But I can't just sit
and watch her.
Especially if she figures out
that you're watching her.
That can make things worse.
I need to find him, but
maybe I don't need Vogel.
Just her computer.
I want you to see something.
Get in.
I'm not gonna hurt you...
Mom.
Trust me, if I wanted you dead,
I wouldn't be holding
this door.
Do you recognize this
from the video I sent you?
This is where you kill
your victims.
Why did you bring me here?
To help you understand.
Have a seat.
Don't worry, I wiped it
down after every, uh...
Well...
This room is more than
what you think it is.
It's a reminder.
Of what?
Of where you sent me.
I've made it look exactly like
what they called
our "treatment" room.
When I would refuse
to take my meds,
the doctors would strap me down
into a chair like this...
and they would force
the meds down.
And that was usually
the highlight of my day.
You can see why
I caused that fire.
I can see why you'd do anything
to get out
of a place like this.
You said before
that you wanted to help me.
Yes.
I'd like that.
Most facilities aren't like this, Daniel.
I could put you someplace where
you'd be very comfortable...
I could see you every day.
I want you to help me
like you helped Dexter.
I want you to show me how
to exist free in the world
just the way I am.
Yes, I can.
Daniel, I can't help you
to murder innocent people.
If you care about me,
the way you say you do,
you'll figure out a way to make this work.
I wanna be someone you can love.
I'm asking you as your son...
please help me.
All right, I'll find a way.
What about Dexter?
He's still after me.
I'll talk to Dexter.
Don't make the same mistake
you made with Richard.
Choose right this time.
Choose me.
I'll get Dexter to understand.
Do you think that's possible?
I'll make it possible.
I want this, Daniel.
I want to be your mother again.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Vogel told me where she keeps a
spare key in case of an emergency.
I think protecting her
from her deranged son qualifies.
Saxon installed spyware
on her computer.
Thing is, that can go
both ways.
So if Saxon can see
Vogel's computer...
then I can see Saxon's.
So what are you looking for?
Something, anything
that can give me an edge.
What's this?
That's the video
he sent to Vogel.
And this one's from last week.
- No, don't!
- Zach.
No, no!
What are you doing? No!
Dexter, if something happens
to Evelyn,
it will haunt you forever.
You can't just
run off to Argentina
and escape who you are.
I'm not trying
to escape anything.
So you'll post
a job listing next week?
Great. Listen, I just don't
need any forensic tech.
I need the best out there.
He's filling some big shoes.
I appreciate it.
Sorry, deputy.
How can I help you?
Just came by to let you know
none of our leads
on Hannah McKay panned out.
You know, when the trail
goes cold at this point,
the subject either
was never here,
or skipped town pretty fast.
What does that mean?
It means the case is back
to low priority.
All right.
Thanks for the heads up.
I couldn't help overhearing.
You said you're looking
for a new forensic tech.
- You know someone?
- No, I'm just curious--
Who's leaving?
It's not Dexter Morgan, is it?
Close the door.
He hasn't told any
of his friends yet,
so this is on the QT,
but yes, Dexter's moving on.
Oh, he got a better job, huh?
No, he's going to travel,
spend time with his son.
- Really?
- Yeah. I can't say I blame him.
Hey, babe.
How was your day?
Okay.
You working?
Yeah, I'm just
sending out resumes.
I'm almost done though.
Hey, um...
can we talk for a sec?
Okay.
I feel like an asshole,
but I gotta be honest with you.
Okay, so...
be honest.
It's not working out
between us, is it?
- Is that a question?
- No.
It's--
I'm sorry.
Then why did you let me
move in here?
I mean, why wait until now,
Joey?
I hoped it would
make things better.
I don't know what else to say.
Ugh, I am so stupid to think
you would ever get over Deb.
It's got nothing
to do with Deb.
I thought you wanted
to be honest with me.
I am.
This is on me.
She's got nothing
to do with it.
Joey, see, that is
what hurts the most.
You just keep lying about it.
I'm not lying, Jamie.
Okay, you know what?
Don't worry.
I'm gonna move my stuff
outta here as soon as I can,
so you're free to not
go back to Deb.
Jamie--
Bye.
Hey.
- I don't want to intrude.
- Well, it's your house.
It's your family.
It's your family too.
I want you and Harrison
to be happy.
So...how do you feel
about us leaving?
Scared.
My whole family's moving.
Scared?
You've always been there.
I don't know what my life
looks like without you.
Well, maybe it looks better.
Really?
Hanging out
with two serial killers--
does it get better than that?
So you see my point.
I don't know.
Better or worse...
you've always been there.
Moving on without you
feels like jumping off a cliff.
I know what you mean.
What?
Will you?
Hey, look who's here.
Hi.
- Hi. Just checking in.
- All is well here.
Harrison's playing outside
with Deb.
- Oh, good.
- You doing okay?
Yeah, I just wanted
to hear your voice.
I have to go.
- Evelyn.
- Dexter.
I was hoping we could talk.
Okay.
I've been rethinking
what I said earlier,
and I fear I was being
too judgmental.
I think it's possible that
you and Hannah
could have a relationship.
- Really?
- And I think moving far away,
beginning anew might be
the best thing for you.
Moving far away?
Is that the important part?
You mentioned Argentina?
That could be a good place.
Why do you want me to leave?
Dexter, I think
there's hope for Daniel.
I don't think he likes killing.
I could help him,
but I'm not going to get
that chance if you kill him.
So just leave, please.
Leave Miami.
You don't think
he likes killing?
He says he wants my help.
Let me show you how much
he doesn't like killing.
No, don't--aah!
No...
That's Zach's head
he's sawing into.
Oh...
There's no hope
for him, Evelyn.
This is the same person
who killed your younger son.
He will never change.
I'm sorry.
So what now?
You know what needs to happen.
Otherwise, he'll go on killing.
Where is he now?
He said he would
call me tonight.
Set up a meeting
with him tonight.
Someplace public...safe.
Call me and let me know where.
I'll follow him
and take it from there.
Just please don't
let him suffer.
I won't.
Debra Morgan.
Do I know you?
Deputy U.S. Marshal
Max Clayton.
And this is Harrison.
- Hey, buddy.
- Hi.
You guys have met?
Over at his dad's, yeah.
Harrison, why don't you
go inside.
- I'll be there in a minute.
- Okay.
Elway gave me your address.
I thought it better
we talk in person.
Okay.
Look, I'm worried
about your brother.
Dexter? Why?
It's probably nothing,
but it just struck me as odd
that he's leaving town
at the exact time
Hannah McKay is rumored
to be here.
How do you know he's leaving?
Uh, overheard at the station.
Maybe it's nothing, but...
are he and Arlene Shram
a couple?
I don't know. I don't keep up
with his dating life.
Okay, it's just I know
he used to have a relationship
with Hannah McKay.
What if he still does?
- Then he's a fuckin' idiot.
- That's what I'm afraid of.
I know I'm going out
on a limb here,
but what if these two
somehow reconnected?
I mean, his life
could be at risk.
- His son's too.
- Dexter wouldn't do that.
I hope not.
I don't need to tell you
what a dangerous person
Hannah McKay is.
You know more about her
than I do.
If Dexter were dating
Hannah McKay,
I would fuckin' know about it.
Maybe he'd keep it from you.
Who knows?
I mean, men do stupid things
for beautiful women.
Logic just flies
out the window.
Well, I appreciate
your concern,
but that's not
what's happening here.
Dexter's burned out,
that's why he's leaving.
Okay. Thank you.
I respect your opinion.
Here's my card.
Call me if you think
of anything.
Okay, will do.
Hey.
You guys hungry?
- Yeah!
- Hey, go clean up, Harrison.
Is everything okay?
Not really.
Something happen?
Deputy Marshal Clayton
happened.
He was just questioning me
on the beach.
I thought that Dexter said
that Clayton was backing off.
Somehow he found out
that Dexter's leaving,
and it tweaked him.
He thinks Dexter's
helping you hide.
Oh, God.
I covered for both of you,
but you have got
to stay hidden until you leave.
Of course. Yes.
Oh...
thank you for protecting me...
again.
Who knew I'd be so good at it?
We'll all be out of here soon.
I know.
- I-I have lunch.
- No, thanks.
I have someplace I need to be.
- Hey.
- Can we talk?
- Nothing to talk about.
I know why you're here.
I'll have your last check drawn.
I was gonna give you two weeks.
Don't want your two weeks.
I still have friends
in Miami Metro, they said
you were going back.
Well, shouldn't we talk
about this?
I went out of my way
to make this work.
I put up with your bullshit.
The more I gave,
the more you pushed back.
It's quite clear to me
you were never gonna work out.
Well, I'm sorry.
I really appreciate the job...
and everything
that you've done for me.
Don't mention it.
Let--let's just, uh...
Okay.
I'm gonna go pack up my office.
I'll have security do that.
They'll deliver it
to your house.
And all the case files
are mine, of course.
Including those
on Hannah McKay.
- Good luck to you.
- Yeah, you too.
Harrison, remember
what your dad said.
That's not a toy.
But Aunt Deb does it
all the time.
Harrison, please listen.
I am.
Ow!
Harrison!
- Ow! Ow!
- Honey, it's gonna be okay.
- Ow.
- I know it hurts.
I know it hurts.
It's gonna be okay.
Ow. Ow...
- Here, hold that.
- Ow.
Dexter Morgan.
Dexter, call me.
We're gonna have to
take you somewhere
and get you patched up.
- What happened?
- He fell and hit his chin.
It's a pretty deep cut.
It won't stop bleeding.
I'll let the doctor know.
Are you the mother?
- Are you the mother?
- Uh, yes.
I'm just waiting for his father
to call me back.
- Fill this out.
- Okay.
And wait for us
to call his name.
Okay.
Thank you.
Harrison,
you're being so brave.
I can't wait to tell your dad.
Harrison Morgan?
Uh, yeah.
Here.
Been a while
since we've been here.
- Choir director.
- Long time ago.
Saxon's first victim.
And his last victims.
It's also been a while since
you've used victims' pictures.
He needs to see what he's done.
That was always
very important to you.
People get what they deserve.
At least they should.
I've come a long way.
It feels like
I'm a different person
from the last time
I was in third room.
You're still you, Dexter.
I hope you realize that.
Why wouldn't I?
I just don't want you to have
any unrealistic expectations
about whatever happens next.
I know exactly
what happens next.
I kill Saxon.
And then Hannah
and Harrison and I
get on a plane
and start our new lives.
- Hey, Jamie.
- Go fuck yourself.
- What?
- Debra, come on in.
I'm ready to come back
if you'll have me.
"If I'll have you"?
Are you sure about this?
You're not fooling me?
Uh, I don't think so.
Well, in that case, hallelujah.
Can you start today?
I was thinking more like
a week or two.
Of course.
Loose ends.
Yeah, something like that.
Whenever you're ready,
I'm ready.
- It's funny, though.
- What?
You coming back
as Dexter's leaving.
- He told you?
- Yeah.
And don't worry about Jamie.
- What was that?
- Oh, you don't know?
Quinn just ended things
with her--stupid idiot.
- He did?
- And so, you know,
Jamie kind of blames you.
Yeah, I get that.
Yeah, she thinks Quinn is
still in love with you
or something like that.
I didn't want to know
the details.
I'll let you have at him first.
We need to talk.
- I just did what--
- Not here.
Did you break up with her
because of me?
No.
Yes.
I mean, no and yes.
Don't get all mad.
Your face gets all red
when you get mad.
No, it doesn't.
What the fuck happened?
It's not complicated.
I wasn't happy.
I mean, I was okay,
but I kinda knew
I was never gonna marry her.
Probably would have
ended it soon anyway,
even if what happened
between you and I didn't happen.
Nothing happened.
We shared a kiss.
That's not a reason to fuckin'
break up with somebody.
You're not hearing me.
I probably would have
broke up with Jamie, but
what happened between you and I
just made it clear that
I shouldn't be with her anymore.
- Got it?
- Yes.
So yeah, to be
completely honest,
I still have feelings for you,
but I don't expect anything
from you.
- Why not?
- I didn't think you wanted--
I still have feelings
for you, stupid.
I didn't change, I just--
I wasn't sure that I saw
a future for us.
What about now?
I don't know.
I mean, I used to--
I used to feel like something
was holding me back, but now--
now I just--shh!
Are you sure it was
Hannah McKay
- you saw earlier today?
- Yeah.
I'd seen her picture
on the news.
She brought in her son.
He had a cut on his chin.
Hannah McKay doesn't have
any children.
- Are you sure this is her?
- Well, I think so.
What was her boy's name?
His name was Harrison Morgan,
and she sure acted
like he was her own.
I fell on my chin.
Yeah, how many stitches are
holding that chin together?
- Six.
- Wow. I bet that hurt.
Yeah, but Harrison
was very brave.
I even got a lollipop.
Can I go play now?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks for taking care of him.
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
I feel awful.
I can't believe
I wasn't here for you.
You went out in public.
You put yourself in jeopardy
because I was setting up
the kill room.
- Dex, you didn't know.
- It doesn't matter.
I'm trying to save
Dr. Vogel
when I should be taking care
of you and Harrison.
We're okay, really.
It's fine.
- But there is one other thing.
- What?
- That deputy marshal came by.
- Here?
He talked to Deb. I think
she put him off, but still,
we can't stay here
for much longer.
I know.
Evelyn?
Dexter, he's here.
Here? Where's here?
At my house.
He called me.
Said he was a couple
of blocks away.
No, that wasn't the plan.
You were supposed to meet him
someplace in public.
Someplace safe.
It's the last time
I'm ever going to see him.
I wanted a private
good-bye.
It's not a good idea.
- That's him now.
- Evelyn?
What?
I have to go.
- Well, be careful.
- I will.
Dexter, go!
What if the marshal comes back?
He's not coming back.
It's Evelyn who needs you
right now.
I should stay here with Hannah.
This is exactly
what Vogel warned you about.
You're trying to live
in two different worlds,
and it's got you paralyzed.
I'm not paralyzed.
I'm making a choice.
Son, you're choosing
to be afraid,
because for the first time
in your life,
you think you've got
something to lose.
Is that who you want to be?
Oh. That's all right.
I'm getting old.
My aim isn't as good
as it used to be.
Why'd you want
to see me tonight?
I just thought it would be
nice for us to talk...
about normal things.
Unlike the other couple
of times.
Hmm. Of course.
- What's wrong?
- Wrong?
- You seem tense.
- No.
No, not at all.
I'm very comfortable.
Maybe a little tired...
under the circumstances.
Is there something
you want to tell me?
I just wanted to see you.
Guess I'm sounding like
a mother already...
constantly wanting
her son around.
You know...
when you see as many people die
as I have,
you know when they're afraid.
What are you afraid of, mother?
He's still here.
- Hello, Dexter.
- What do you want? Where--
Don't move.
I want to show you something.
Don't touch her.
Mother chose
the wrong son, again.
Evelyn?
Oh, no, no, no.
No...
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com