Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Dexter...
- You can't kill me.
- Why?
Because I don't fit
Harry's code.
Trust me when I say that
there's a place
in this world for your son.
You're perfect.
How can you still say that
when you know
what I've done to Deb?
Uhh!
I shot the wrong person
in that trailer.
Why'd you save me?
Why didn't you let me drown?
I couldn't imagine my life
without you in it.
I'm glad to see
that you two have managed
to find your way
back to each other.
Well, the family
that kills together...
Zach's killer is
related to you.
The Brain Surgeon...
is related to you.
Daniel.
He's going by the name
of Oliver Saxon.
- What are you going to do?
- What do you think?
He's my son.
- I still have feelings for you.
- I just--
Remember me?
Where do you think you'll go?
I haven't decided.
Argentina.
Me, you, and Harrison
are gonna move to Argentina.
I've got a line
on Hannah McKay,
but I'm gonna need your help
reeling her in.
But he's on to you,
and you gotta move fast.
I tried to get an earlier
flight, but it's booked solid
'cause of the storm.
I have a proposal.
We walk away.
You went out of your way to
kill your mother in front of me,
and you just expect me
to forget?
Evelyn?
This is usually
my favorite moment, the kill.
Now, I don't even
wanna be here.
Hey, Deb, change of plans.
Go get on a plane.
Last site someone
visited on this computer
was for an Aero Sudamerica.
I'm gonna tail the Morgans,
see if they'll lead me to her.
Aah! Aah!
What the fuck is going on here?
Help me, please!
- Unh!
- Agh!
Don't move.
I used to live my life
at night,
in the shadow
of my Dark Passenger.
But, over the years,
my eyes adjusted,
and I could see.
And now, what's in focus
is my future.
Bright.
Brighter than it's ever been.
This is Detective Debra Morgan.
I've been shot.
Are we almost there?
It's, uh, Gate 209.
Just a couple more.
I want some Oreos.
There'll be food on the plane.
Come on, you promised
to help me count.
- 210.
- There you go.
I always thought
that if I ever left Miami,
I'd be running for my life...
not running towards a new one.
211!
Ladies and gentlemen,
we'll begin boarding
Flight 691 to Rio de Janeiro
in a few moments.
To ensure an on-time departure
we ask that you have
your tickets and passports
ready for the attendant.
Where's Hannah?
- Hannah?
- Hey, where are you?
I'm at the gate.
Where are you?
I'm in the ladies' room, Dex.
Elway is in the boarding area.
Come here, buddy.
Attention passengers.
We now begin pre-boarding
for Aero Sudamerica
Flight 691 to Rio de Janeiro.
He didn't see me.
Did he see you?
No, I don't think so.
He's got a clear view
of the jetway.
He must have bought a ticket
to get through security.
We won't be able to board
without being spotted.
And he's right between
you and the exit.
Dex, I just heard them.
Our plane is boarding
right now.
Stay where you are.
I'll call you right back.
Okay.
Hey...
you want some Oreos?
Yay!
Come on.
Why don't you grab something
for the flight?
- Nothing too big.
- Okay.
The storm is coming fast...
At this time,
we'll now be boarding
all passengers
in business class.
All passengers, stand by...
Hey, excuse me.
Hi. I have tickets
on this flight.
I'm a forensic analyst
with Miami Metro.
- Yes?
- I don't want to tell you
how to do your job,
but I just saw a guy
drop that bag under that chair
and then just walk away.
I thought maybe he forgot it,
but it really looked
like he left it there
on purpose.
Did you see where he went?
Yeah, he's, uh...
right over there, on the phone.
I know
it's probably nothing, but...
like they say, "If you see
something, say something."
Thanks.
Security, this is Casey
at Gate 211.
There's a Caucasian male...
Deputy Marshal,
it's Elway again.
Third message.
I'm still at the airport.
I still think Hannah McKay's
trying to leave the country.
Call me back
as soon as you can.
Thank you.
- Sir...
- Oh, that's okay.
- You can stack that.
- Airport security.
Need you to come with us,
please.
What?
What happened?
Just got to ask you
a few questions.
What the hell is this about?
I'm gonna miss my flight.
Sir, I need you
to do what I ask.
This way.
You gotta be fuckin'
kidding me.
Hey.
Okay, the coast is clear.
- Elway's gone.
- Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
- due to a security concern...
- Let's go see Hannah.
...it is necessary at this time
for all passengers
- to exit the boarding area...
- Clear this area right now.
What did you do?
Put Elway
on the no-fly list.
Unfortunately,
now we're not flying either.
Come on, bud.
All right, let's move her.
Stabbed in the heart.
Pretty quick.
His gun is missing too.
We're going to assume
Saxon still has it.
I'm calling your brother.
No, he's leaving with Harrison.
If you tell him what happened,
he'll stay.
- Deb--
- I swear to fucking God,
I'm not getting on that
ambulance if you call him.
Okay.
I'm gonna ride with you
to the hospital.
No problem, sir.
For once, do not argue with me.
I'm in the ambulance.
That's it.
You're such a fuckin' asshole.
Yeah, he signed it.
He's inside.
I'll meet you at the hospital.
I'm right behind you.
Miami Central,
this is Rescue 6.
We're transporting
Lieutenant Debra Morgan...
- You're all right.
- Hurts like a motherfucker.
Ooh.
I really hate getting shot.
You need to stop that.
Uhh!
I really thought that was it.
I thought I was gonna die.
No.
You're gonna live forever.
Ah!
I thought maybe I was
getting what I deserved.
What you deserve?
Why would you think that?
I've done shit
I'm not proud of.
Stuff I can't take back.
Think I haven't done shit
I'm not proud of?
It's not the same.
I know.
You went through a bad time.
But I fucked up too, Deb.
A lot.
But I think we get
to make up for it, you know?
Uhh.
How?
You do enough good
in the world,
it sort of cancels out the bad.
I think I would need
to save a busload of nuns
or something.
You're a good person.
A lot better than most.
Now that you're back
on the force,
you're gonna have
a million chances
to do good.
Maybe even save that
busload of nuns.
If they're like the ones
I had in school,
let 'em go.
Come here.
Hey.
I'm gonna be right here, okay?
We both are.
Her vitals are stable.
- Let's get her into surgery.
- I love you, Joey.
What's that?
So?
She's on her way
to surgery now.
She took one in the gut.
We don't know
how bad it is yet.
Where's Dexter?
Deb asked us not to call him.
She what?
She says he's on
a trip with Harrison.
She didn't want to worry him,
but I say screw that.
- He's gotta know.
- Damn right he's gotta know.
Due to
a possible security concern,
we are evacuating the terminal.
It's Matthews.
Hello?
Dexter, Saxon escaped
after shooting Debra.
No.
Well, thank you for telling me.
I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
It's Debra.
What?
Come on, bud.
Saxon shot her and got away.
Is she okay?
She's in the hospital
getting ready
to go into surgery.
Is Aunt Deb sick?
Uh, just a little.
But the doctors
are fixing her up right now.
We need to go to her.
I'll take you back
to the hotel.
We should fly
into a different country.
They're only gonna
hold Elway for so long,
and you know he's gonna
hit all the flights to Rio.
There may not be
any more flights, Dexter.
I heard people saying
that they were
going to close the airport
to wait out the storm.
We should leave
from another city.
See what you can find online.
Well, what about you?
- I'll join you when I can.
- But--
Don't worry.
We'll make this work.
One bag of ice
and one gallon of water.
- Can I get one more?
- Only one bag.
Ohh!
- Hi, Jamie!
- Hey, Harrison.
So tell me all about
your adventures...
How is she?
Still in surgery.
Yeah, we were unable
to speak to the doctor
before she went in.
Your sister's tough.
Just like your old man was.
Yeah, Dex.
She's gonna pull through.
Due to severe weather...
This is Deputy
U.S. Marshal Clayton.
Please leave your name
and number after the beep.
Clayton, it's Elway.
Again.
Look, I don't know
where the hell you are.
But I'll tell you this,
McKay's still in town.
With all the flights canceled,
I'm sure she's looking
for another way out of here.
I put the word out
to all of my contacts,
and I'll tell you this--
with what I pay these people,
if she walks through a hotel
lobby, a car rental agency,
a bus, a train station,
I'm gonna hear about that shit.
All right...I'll try you
at your field office,
see if I can get you there.
U.S. Marshal's service.
How may I direct your call?
Yeah, this is Jacob Elway.
Listen, I've been working
an investigation
with Deputy Marshal Clayton.
I've been trying like hell--
I guess you haven't
heard the news, sir.
What?
Clayton was involved
in a shooting.
I'm afraid he was killed
in the line of duty.
Why aren't you in Argentina?
Why do you think?
I told them not to call you.
Well, I'm glad they did.
How come we never went hiking
when we were kids?
Hiking?
Climbing.
Mountains.
Hiking.
I don't know--
'cause it's hard
to find a mountain in Florida?
There are mountains
in South America.
All over the place.
Why are you
looking at me like that?
Or is that just your face?
Uhh.
I should never have
left Saxon alive.
It's not your fault.
Clayton fucked everything up.
Bad luck.
No, it's more than that.
Ever since you found out
who I am...
I've screwed up your life, Deb.
It's not yours
to screw up, Dexter.
I am responsible for my life.
Do you hear me?
I don't want you to feel guilty
about this.
I don't want you to feel
guilty about anything.
You hear me?
You were meant to be happy,
so you need to go
fuckin' be happy.
Okay.
Hello there.
Dr. Kruper.
Uh, Dexter.
I'm Debra's brother.
Ah, nice to meet you.
Okay, just gonna
check your stomach.
So how are you feeling
otherwise?
I wanna go hiking.
I wouldn't recommend that
for at least a few hours.
How is she?
That bullet
bounced around quite a bit.
But it missed hitting
anything important.
You are very lucky.
So she's gonna be all right?
There is a lot of recovery
time ahead.
But...I'd say
we're looking pretty good.
I'm optimistic.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
I bet Hannah loves Argentina.
Pretty blonde,
lots of attention.
Just her thing.
Hannah didn't make the flight.
Elway was there,
and we had to lose him.
That's my fault, Dex.
I put him on her.
That rat-face fuck.
I'm--
I'm sorry.
No, don't start
blaming yourself.
Coming from Mr. "I Screwed Up
Your Life, Deb."
I need to find another way
for Hannah to get
out of the country.
I'm thinking of sending
Harrison with her now,
and meeting up with them
after you get out
and Saxon is taken care of.
You heard the doctor.
I'm fine.
You should go.
We'll get Saxon.
- No.
- Dex, we'll get him.
Your life is waiting on you.
You should leave.
Deb...
The next word I want
to hear you say is good-bye.
Say it already,
or I'll crawl out of this bed
and kick your fuckin' ass.
Good-bye.
I'll see you soon.
How's Aunt Deb?
Can see her?
Ah, she needs to rest.
But she's gonna visit us
real soon.
Hey, did you know that
this is the hospital
where you were born?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Right down there.
It's the first time I saw you.
I was with Aunt Deb.
Holy fuckin' shit.
There's another Morgan now.
- Yeah.
- Congratulations.
You're a father.
Yeah, and you're an aunt.
Jesus.
Did you and Rita
land on a name yet?
Harrison.
Dad would love that.
"Harrison."
I wanna hold him.
Which one is yours?
I, um...
That's your son.
Do you want to hold him?
- Yeah, I wanna hold him.
- Uh, he's sleeping.
Let him sleep.
He has his whole
fuckin' life to sleep.
He's so small.
Don't worry.
He'll grow.
How does it feel
to be a father?
I have no idea.
Everything's gonna
be different now.
I know.
Hey, thanks for your call.
No problem.
How's Debra?
The doctor's optimistic.
That's good to hear.
Listen, Dexter,
if there's anything I can do...
Well, I'm probably
being paranoid, but...
Saxon is still out there.
You think you could put
a couple of unis on her room?
I'm already on it.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Hey.
Hey, I just heard about Deb.
What happened?
Uh, it's a long story.
I don't really
have time to go into it.
You in a hurry to get back
to Hannah McKay?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
That's why Clayton
was following Deb.
He figured she was helping you
and Hannah leave the country.
And if that's true,
I guess you know
you're partially responsible
for his death.
Just stay away from me.
Storm's comin', buddy.
And it's gonna be real hard
to find a way out.
Don't go down with her, Dexter.
Son of a bitch.
The National Hurricane Center
is reporting that Laura
is now just east of Cuba,
with sustained winds topping
100 miles per hour.
If it keeps on this
current course,
it could hit the keys
by sundown.
Shh. It's okay.
Shh. Hey.
It's okay.
Hey, we're closed.
Only reason I'm here
is to keep the animals calm to--
Stitch me up.
Okay.
Okay, I'll do
whatever you need.
Miami's entire coast
is being evacuated,
so we can use all the craziness
to get out of here
without being spotted again.
They're lining up
evacuation buses.
The bus?
Yeah, the highways
are parking lots,
but the buses
have their own lanes,
so we can take one
all the way up to Jacksonville
and fly out from there.
We'd better leave
for the bus station soon
if we're gonna make it on time.
What is it?
Nothing.
It's a good plan.
You're still worried
about Deb, aren't you?
The doctor said
she's out of danger.
Hey, we can, uh...
we can stick around--you know,
ride out the storm here.
It's not safe
with Elway on the hunt.
You need to get out of here,
the faster the better.
Well, I could, uh,
I could leave now
and you could meet me there.
I could even
take Harrison with me.
Or I could, um, go alone.
No, I have no problem
with you taking Harrison.
I'd be happy to know
that he's with you.
It's just that I don't
want to lose you again.
Even if it's just
for a couple of days.
Hurry up.
Almost finished.
One more stitch.
Please.
Just...go.
I won't say anything to anyone.
Special report
about one of Miami's finest,
Debra Morgan.
That's her.
I'm here
at Miami Central Hospital
where a detective with
Miami Metro Homicide
is recovering from surgery
after having been shot.
We have learned that a deputy
marshal died on the scene.
The suspect, Oliver Saxon,
is still at large
and may have carjacked
a blue pickup truck.
If you have any information
about the whereabouts...
Get your car keys.
We're taking a drive.
Can't you just let me go?
Do what I said...
and you won't get hurt.
Alright, keep moving,
no pushing.
Oh, no, it's okay.
You want me to carry that?
Yeah. Wait.
Come here.
All right, everyone,
please keep moving the line.
It's Saxon.
He's still out there.
I can't leave
until he's caught,
until...Debra is safe.
I'm sorry.
Sir, you need
to get back in line.
It's, okay, I--
I understand.
Here.
Take Harrison.
I'll meet you down there.
You sure?
Yeah.
He'll be safer with you.
Take this.
It's just water, snacks.
A few essentials.
Call me from the airport
as soon as you know
that you made your flight.
I will.
Harrison...
you're gonna leave with Hannah.
You're not coming with us?
No, of course I am.
I just forgot a few things
I need to take care of.
As soon as I do,
I'll meet you there.
I promise.
I'm gonna miss you.
It's just for a little while.
It'll be fun.
We're all going to
this really cool place,
and you're gonna
get there first, okay?
Now, I want you to mind Hannah.
You do what she says.
You know what, daddy?
What?
I love Hannah.
So do I.
See you in Buenos Aires.
We'll be waiting.
This is the final boarding call
for Mockingbird Bus 24
to Tallahassee.
Come on, Harrison.
I'll check on Deb,
and then I'll deal with Saxon.
This is the hospital.
I've done everything
you've asked.
I just wanna go home.
So this is it?
I promise.
I don't say a word to anyone.
No, I know.
We need a doctor over her!
He's choking.
I need a suction canister.
Right away.
Doctor?
Jesus.
His tongue.
It's been cut out.
Let's get him to the O.R.
My God, why would anyone
cut his tongue out?
All eyes on the victim.
The perfect distraction.
Saxon.
At this time, ask all visitors
to make their way
towards the exit
in the north wing.
All surgical staff report
to their current assignments.
Drop it.
We got this, Dex.
Quinn?
Dex, I...
Where's Deb?
I don't know.
Something went wrong.
There was a...problem,
and they rushed her to the ICU.
What happened?
They're working on her now.
Um...sh-she stopped
breathing.
Mr. Morgan, I'm afraid
I don't have good news.
There were complications.
What kind of complications?
We think a clot formed
during surgery
that triggered a major stroke.
Debra's brain was deprived
of oxygen for a period of time.
What do you mean?
I thought you said
she was gonna be fine.
I had hoped so.
I'm very sorry.
Is she going to recover?
It's possible that
she could breathe on her own,
but she won't be able to eat
without a feeding tube,
and, according
to the brain scans,
she won't be able
to think, reason,
or even know that you're there.
Now, uh, we've intubated her,
and I've lowered
her body temperature
so that we can preserve
as much brain function
as possible.
You don't know Deb.
She'll, uh--
she'll pull through this.
You hear about miracles
all the time.
Well, that's just it,
I'm afraid.
It would be a miracle.
I've never seen a miracle.
Hello, Harrison.
Ohh.
He's so fuckin' small.
I'll have to watch what I say
around you, little man.
Don't you want
to hold your son?
You won't break him.
Okay.
Talk to him.
Hello, Harrison.
See? He knows you.
I don't know how to do this.
Just keep his head up.
No, I mean everything.
How to be a father,
how to take care of him.
You'll be great.
How do you know?
'Cause you've always
taken care of me.
I have?
Ever since we were little.
Don't you remember
the monsters?
Uh, no.
Every time mom would
turn off the lights,
they'd be running
all over the walls.
And I couldn't fuckin'
go to sleep
'cause I thought they were gonna
eat me or something.
I don't remember.
They were the shadows.
You came in and explained it
in your dorky little voice.
You were like, "Oh, it's just
the absence of light, Deb."
I don't even know
why I remember that,
but I do.
And even then,
you stayed in my room
and slept on the floor
by my bed.
You made me feel
so fuckin' safe.
You were always
taking care of me.
I know you're gonna
be a great father,
because you've always been
a great big brother.
You really believe that?
With all my heart.
You were so wrong, Deb.
Tell me about Argentina.
Well, uh...
they have their own special
kind of cowboys.
They're called gauchos.
Maybe you'll get to meet one.
You know what else they have?
Penguins.
I like penguins.
But not just in a zoo,
they're wild ones,
kind of roaming around.
'Cause Argentina is close
to the South Pole,
which is where Santa Claus
has his summer home, and...
and...because
he's on vacation,
he's always in a good mood.
So he says yes to everything.
Who knew you'd be
so good with kids, huh?
How did you find me?
One of my contacts
finally came through.
Look, let's be civil
about this, all right?
No need to upset Harrison.
All right, everyone,
please take your seats.
We're going out now.
Next stop, Daytona.
So this is what's gonna happen.
We're gonna sit here quietly
until we get to Daytona.
Then we're gonna very calmly
get off the bus.
I'm gonna drive us
to the marshal's field office.
I'm gonna turn you in,
and I'm gonna hand Harrison
over to Child
Protective Services.
And I'm gonna collect
what's turning out to be
a very hard-earned reward.
Dex, we're gonna nail
this asshole to the wall.
I promise you...
for Deb.
Oliver Saxon.
Or would you prefer to be
called by your given name,
Daniel Vogel?
You know, there are several
ways we can do this.
Given that we have footage
of you killing other people,
it would be
in your best interest
to cooperate.
It's up to my lawyer
how cooperative I am.
Are you sure?
Because if you have any hope
of staying out
of the electric chair,
you should probably
start talking.
Just fuckin' admit it.
You killed Cassie,
you killed Clayton.
And you shot Deb.
How did you hurt your arm?
This?
It's just a scratch.
No.
Deb's a good shot.
Who's Deb?
Fuck you! You--
you fuckin' shot her!
And you left her there to die!
Just like you killed
your own mother,
and you left her to die,
you fuckin' piece of shit!
Quinn. Out.
I'd like to, uh,
speak to my attorney, please.
You know, he was right
about one thing.
You are a fuckin' piece
of shit.
Batista and Quinn will be able
to make a case against Saxon.
I could leave now for Argentina
and let the State of Florida
kill him.
Folks, we will be arriving
at the Daytona station
momentarily.
After a short stop,
we will proceed on
to Tallahassee.
Anyone making a connection
to Jacksonville
should disembark and proceed
to boarding bay three.
Hey, hey.
I'm just getting some tea.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you want some?
How stupid do you think I am?
Here's what's gonna happen.
The horse tranquilizer
I just gave you
is gonna kick in
in about eight seconds.
You're gonna asleep
for a couple of hours
and wake up in Tallahassee
with a slight headache,
feeling humiliated and cranky.
Come on, sweetie.
It's time to go.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hi, I'm here to do a GSR test
on...Oliver Saxon?
Sign in, please.
Would you like
an officer with you?
No, I'm good.
Hit this button if you need us.
Got it.
I wish I could
blame you for everything.
For what you did to my sister.
But I know it's all my fault.
Should have walked away.
You know, what you've actually
done is opened my eyes.
Forced me to look at myself.
And what do you see?
A trail of blood
and body parts.
What a pretty picture.
In one, sharp moment
you took away this...
foolish dream that I could
have a happy life.
Is that why you're here?
Tell me all this?
No, I'm here to kill you
with that pen.
You all right?
He tried to kill me.
Dexter.
Help me out here.
What--what were you doing
with Saxon?
I went in to do a GSR test.
But you don't even
work here anymore.
How are we gonna
to explain this?
I'm officially here
till the end of the week.
Okay, but why would you
personally do this test?
After what he did to Deb...
It's exactly because
of what he did to Deb
that I went in there.
I wanted to make sure everything
was handled perfectly--
by the book, no mistakes.
And I wanted to look him
in the eye.
Okay.
I get that.
It's obviously
self-defense.
Yeah.
We got everything we need.
I'm glad he's dead.
Wish I could have
done it myself.
You should go, Dex.
I know that you have
a lot to deal with.
Yes.
Hey...
I'm praying for her.
As much as I may have
pretended otherwise,
for so long, all I wanted
was to be like other people.
To feel what they felt.
But now that I do,
I just want it to stop.
Attention all staff
and hospital personnel,
the National Hurricane Center...
Uh, sir...
just so you know,
all patients in the south wing
are being moved.
We have to consolidate
space and power.
At 150 miles per hour.
It has been elevated
to category 3.
At this time,
all staff must report
to their preassigned station.
I would change everything
if I could.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
But I can't
leave you like this.
I'm your big brother.
I love you, Deb.
- Dexter.
- Hey, where are you?
At the airport, about to board.
We're gonna make it.
That's great.
Where are you?
I'm still in Miami.
But I'm gonna be leaving soon.
I can't believe
this is actually gonna happen.
You know, I think,
once we get there,
we should start
making our way south.
They have 3,000 miles
of coastline.
We can just keep going
until we find the perfect spot,
or maybe some penguins.
That sounds great.
I am so happy right now, Dex.
Me too.
Do you wanna talk to Harrison?
Please.
Okay, here.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hi, Harrison.
I just want to tell you
one last time
that I love you.
I love you too.
I want you to remember that
every single day
until I see you again.
Daddy loves you.
Okay.
Bye.
I destroy everyone I love.
And I can't let that happen
to Hannah,
to Harrison.
I have to protect them from me.
Good morning, Miami.
Hurricane Laura has passed
and everything is going
back to normal.
There is no longer any threat.
Hurricane Laura
is slowly dissipating
over the Atlantic.
She is heading south...
The majority of destruction
is along the harbor.
There have been some reports...
The cleanup has begun
as the city returns to normal
with coast guard teams going
as far north as Daytona Beach
- and as far south...
- Cutter 6, go ahead
and turn to your 1:00.
There's something there.
I can't make it out.
Give me a time.
Stopping in five seconds.
- Okay, I think we got a visual.
- Copy that.
Turning northwest.
We've surveyed the wreckage.
There doesn't appear
to be any survivors.
We're heading back.
Batista.
This is
the U.S. Coast Guard.
We just wanted to call
and report the wreckage
of Dexter Morgan's boat.
Dexter?
Hey, uh, how about we go
get some ice cream, yeah?
- Okay.
- Yeah. Come on.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com