? Dexter 8x07 ?
Dress Code
Original Air Date on August 11, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Previously on Dexter...
It's no accident
that Zach Hamilton is here.
He's drawn to blood,
like me.
And the arterial spurting here
indicates
that the killer severed
the carotid artery
with the first stab.
I'm promoting Miller
to sergeant.
Are you fucking
kidding me?
You actually made me
want this,
and now you're gonna
take it away.
I just did
a little research on you.
You checked into me...
Like a criminal.
Hey, Niki--
- Dexter, this is Oliver.
Oliver, Dexter.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you too.
Zach Hamilton
killed Norma Rivera.
He deserves to die.
Isn't that a little intolerant
coming from you?
What if you were
to teach Zach the code?
Maybe it's time to see
if the experiment
will work.
What possibly makes you think
Zach could be taught the code?
I see something in him.
Why were you going
to kill your father?
Because he's killing
my mother.
She's drinking herself to death
because of him.
You killed
because you want to kill.
You should just go ahead
and kill me.
Why?
'Cause if you don't,
then I will do it again.
I can't help it.
Am I ready to be
a spiritual father?
Hey, are you okay?
- I don't feel so good.
- Deb?
Hello, Dexter.
Remember me?
Hello?
Dexter?
I was just about to leave you
another message.
Where have you been
all morning?
The last thing
I remember is...
Hannah.
Is everything all right?
Not if Hannah got to Deb.
I can't really talk now.
I just thought you should know
that Zach Hamilton called.
I'm so glad you decided
not to kill him, Dexter.
I have to go.
Deb, are you okay?
Dex, where the fuck are you?
Just a sec.
I'm outside of Kendall.
Are you alone?
Why wouldn't I be?
W-why are you
on the other side of town?
I need you to come
pick me up.
Are you okay to drive?
I think so.
I mean, who the fuck knows?
I...Woke up on the floor,
feeling like shit.
You were gone.
What the--
what the fuck is happening?
Just come pick me up.
I'll text you the location.
We'll talk when you get here.
Hannah drugged us,
left me stranded
in the middle of nowhere.
If she's come back because she
wants one or both of us dead,
then why are we both
still here?
It was Hannah,
wasn't it?
It was.
I saw her
before I blacked out,
but then I woke up here.
She must have
drugged our food.
If Hannah poisoned us,
why didn't she kill us?
Who the fuck knows,
Dexter?
Maybe we were supposed
to eat more.
Or maybe she just wants
to let us know she's out there.
Maybe this was just
the beginning.
If we were normal people,
Dexter,
we would go
to the U.S. Marshal Service.
We can't do that.
She knows everything about me.
Yeah, but she
didn't talk about you
the last time
she was arrested.
Because she was
in love with me.
Drugging me and leaving me
on the side of the road
might suggest
that's changed.
So what the fuck
are we supposed to do?
There are
traffic surveillance cameras.
She had
to have passed them.
I'll put in a request
for the footage,
get a license plate.
I thought this part
of my life was over.
So did I.
The moment I asked you
to kill her
was the moment that I started
to lose myself,
and I'm just starting
to get back.
I don't want
to deal with this.
I want her gone.
Deb, I'll take care of this.
I promise.
Hannah--just thinking about her
throws me off course.
I have to put in a request
for the traffic footage.
Zach, what are you
doing here?
You were supposed to meet me
at 10:00 this morning.
I've been waiting
all day.
- You could have been followed.
- By who?
Oh, Detective Quinn?
No, he's pretty easy to lose.
But one day, he'll be there
when you don't expect him.
Don't ever come
to my home again.
- I just wanted to talk to you--
- ever.
We can't be seen
in public together.
Do you understand?
That's your first lesson.
Okay. Jesus.
I'm--I'm sorry.
It's just--
I-I spoke to Dr. Vogel,
and she--
What exactly
did she tell you?
That you have this, like,
way of living that...
A-allows you to do what--
what you and I
have in common,
and--
and that might be something
that I can do too.
I mean, fuck,
I have so many questions.
And I'll answer them
as best I can.
Are you gonna help me
be like you?
Don't even pretend.
Hi, Dexter.
Going
for a little night swim.
Enjoy.
Who's she?
- That's my neighbor.
- She's cute.
Yes, she's cute.
You need to go home.
When are we
gonna talk about--
I'll call you.
Look, something has come up
that I have to deal with.
My day job,
which is something
you need to get.
Why?
I have money.
You're a weird guy
who lives with his mom.
You might as well be
wearing a sign.
Look, all I'm saying is
that you need
to have
some kind of cover life,
something that makes you
look ordinary.
Yeah, right, yeah.
I get it, yeah.
Zach, I understand
what you're going through.
I will help you
with this.
Okay.
Thanks.
Not a single sighting
since she disappeared?
Thank you.
Motherfuck.
What you doing?
Nothing.
Why do you look
like you just got caught?
Come on,
what are you doing back here?
You looking at porn over here
or something?
- No.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Company computer.
Will you-
And I am the boss.
Hannah McKay.
Wayne Randall's girlfriend,
right?
Got arrested a while back
for something,
then somehow slipped away?
Why you--
why you looking her up?
None of your goddamn business.
Will you fucking back off?
- Jesus, relax.
- No, I'm seri--
you come in here
all the time
and invade
my personal space,
standing so close,
trying to flirt.
You're fucking
making me uncomfortable.
I didn't come in here
to flirt, okay?
I just came in here to see
if you wanted me
to pick you up something
for lunch, that's it.
I'm all set.
Are we done?
Yeah.
Yeah, we're done.
You know what?
We're not done, actually.
See, Deb, you came to me
six months ago,
an emotional wreck,
saying you just quit the force
and you needed a job.
I gave you that job.
I gave you good pay,
good benefits.
I didn't ask
a lot of questions.
I put up with a lot
of weird shit from you
because you're good
at your job
and because I'm a nice guy.
So I'm really, really sorry
if this cramps your style,
but next time, maybe you want
to try a little gratitude
instead of always being
such a fucking bitch.
Now we're done.
There she is.
Vista Marina car rentals.
Vista marina car rentals.
This is Stacy.
How may I help you?
Hi, Stacy.
This is Detective Cooper
over at Miami Metro.
My badge number is
143634.
We're investigating
a hit and run.
We think somebody
who rented one of your vans
might have been
a witness,
so I was hoping to get
some information over the phone.
I can fax you over a copy
of the warrant, if you'd like.
Oh, I'll just get it for you.
Do you have the license plate?
Yes, I do.
It's, uh, GLV43951.
The name on that account
is Maggie Castner.
The local address is
slip 23, Vista Marina.
Thank you, Stacy.
Want the phone number?
Yes,
that would be helpful.
813398-2723.
You may have found her.
If so,
a little too easily.
You think
she wants to be found?
I think she wants
to destroy our lives,
mine and Debra's both.
Debra's very fragile
right now.
Even the threat
of Hannah coming after her
could derail all the progress
she's making.
I won't let that happen.
So what's your plan?
Slip 23.
You have her number.
You could call.
I don't want to let her know
I've found her yet.
Why do you seem
less scared than excited?
Because Hannah
doesn't scare me.
Maybe you need
to rethink that.
They all look
like nice apartments,
but I think you should work
things out with your brother.
Angel and I
are gonna be fine.
I've just had it
with the whole "big brother
ruling over the roost" routine.
And the thing is...
What?
Well, just,
most of these places,
I have to sign
a one-year lease,
and I wasn't sure
about...
About what?
Okay, I'm definitely not
pushing you, okay?
I'm just trying
to be practical here.
If our relationship
keeps moving forward,
we might want to eventually get
a place together.
Yeah, eventually.
You don't have to decide now.
It's just something
to think about.
Yeah, I'll totally think
about it.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
I-I blew that whole thing
out of proportion, I think.
I just felt like
you were trying
to, like, get rid of me
with a check.
I was just trying to be
a good, you know, father.
That was really sweet
of you.
But it's my problem,
and I want
to take care of it.
Well, I can respect that.
So we're cool?
Cool.
How about you and I
do dinner tonight?
I can't.
I have to work
right after class.
You know,
pay off the debts.
Wow, well,
good for you.
Where are you working?
It's a sports bar
called Lucky Pete's.
I can, uh, call you, though,
when I'm free.
We can get together.
Okay.
Sounds great.
The Hannah McKay I know
hated the ocean.
But it does make
for an easy escape
into international waters.
Brave of her to be walking
around Miami like that.
Or maybe she's found someone
to protect her.
- May I help you?
- I'm just meeting some friends.
I'm sorry, sir.
Members only.
Oh, but I'm a friend of--
Even so, sir,
we have a strict dress code.
Call it a night,
Dexter.
You don't want to go in there.
I do want to go in there.
It's their territory.
You'll be
at a disadvantage.
I need to know
what she's up to.
Dexter.
Is your father a member
at the Red Coral Club?
Yeah.
It's full of old farts in suits.
Why?
Can you get me in there?
Tonight?
Yeah.
Sure.
Good to see you,
Mr. Hamilton.
So what are we doing here?
Looking for someone.
I thought we weren't
supposed to be seen together.
This is different.
You know her?
That's my ex-girlfriend.
Nice.
Who's the guy?
I'm gonna find out.
All right,you keep an.
You text me
when he's coming back.
Got it.
Hannah.
It's Maggie now.
You shouldn't be here,
Dexter.
Well, I'm not leaving
until you tell me
why you drugged me and left me
on the side of the road.
Well,
after what you did to me,
I'm not sure
that you get to ask questions.
But here I am,
asking.
What are you doing
back in Miami?
Well, I was
about to enjoy a Martini.
You should probably leave,
though,
before my husband returns.
Your husband?
You're married
to that guy?
Yes.
I'm very lucky.
Yeah, well, he seems rich.
You were always
a pragmatist.
Well, the money's nice,
I have to admit, but...
He has other talents.
Miles is
the adventurous type.
What are you doing here,
Hannah?
My husband will be back
any minute,
and it's probably
in your best interest
that he not see us
together.
Well, I told you,
I'm not leaving
until you tell me
why you did what you did to me.
I see
you've made a friend.
This is my husband,
Miles Castner.
Dexter Morgan.
Maggie has told me
about you.
Oh?
How you were
her boyfriend,
until you betrayed her,
turning her in
to the police.
Quite a predicament
you left her in.
Shall we finish
our drinks?
I think it's time
for us to go.
Well,
that's an excellent idea.
Make sure Mr. Morgan is given
whatever he needs.
Didn't you get
my texts?
I warned you
that guy was coming.
I know.
So why didn't you
walk away?
I mean, I watched him.
I stayed on him.
I didn't fuck up in there.
I screwed up, not you.
You did exactly
as I asked you to.
So what now?
Nothing.
I'll call you.
We'll talk tomorrow.
So that guy,
are we--
are you gonna
kill him?
I only kill people
who deserve it.
You here,
'cause something
sure ain't right.
While them orphans
was camping in the woods,
something gave them
a proper fright.
Miles Castner
made his fortune
in international casinos.
He has the power
and the reach
to get Hannah
a new name, new passport,
but if she's as happy
as she seems in her new life,
then why is she here,
messing with mine?
Miles Castner--
what kind of name
is Miles, anyway?
Don't be a chump, zoomer!
Ain't no such thing as...
- Hey.
Hey.
Hello.
Harrison, hello.
That's it?
I remember
when I used to get a hug.
Even I don't matter
when rastamouse is on.
I checked in
with Marshals, FBI,
fucking Homeland Security.
There hasn't been a single
sighting of Hannah McKay.
I'm hoping
you've had better luck.
Yeah.
I found her.
She's married.
Well, there's someone
for everyone, I guess.
I hope he's sleeping
with one eye open.
What's her married name?
The guy she's married to
is worth $700 million.
He owns casinos.
The name, Dex.
Castner.
Miles Castner.
They're staying
on his yacht.
I don't know what they're doing
in Miami.
Maybe he has business here
or something.
But he seems to know
who she is,
even knows
about her and me.
And she...
Seems to like him,
or maybe she just
feels obligated to him.
I doubt Hannah McKay
feels obligated to anyone.
It's got
to be operational.
She needs
a cover life.
It's not like
it's a real marriage.
She can't actually
love this guy.
Oh, my God.
You're still in love
with her, aren't you?
What?
No.
She's probably trying
to kill me.
Trust me,
no one knows
what it's like
to fall in love
with the wrong person
more than I do.
But you better get
your fucking head on straight.
She is everything
that is wrong with our lives.
She is a vortex.
She is a black hole.
She sucks everything
into her being,
leaving nothing behind.
We have got to get her
out of our lives.
I'm working on a plan.
Are you sure
you can be objective?
One little toss
of Hannah's pretty blonde hair,
and you turn
into a fucking moron.
Hannah?
Hannah is here?
Both of you?
Jesus.
Really?
Deb, I'm on top of it.
I'm gonna figure out
exactly what she's up to.
Are you?
Where is Hannah?
Right now,
she's on a very big boat
with her husband.
Niki?
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I came here
to see you.
I didn't realize
this place was a breastaurant.
I mean, it is a sports bar.
It's just topless.
And I make
really good money here.
Are you really okay
doing this?
Yeah, it's not the best job
in the world,
but it's also not forever.
I'm fine with it.
I can tell
that you're not.
Me?
Oh.
Look, I go to places like this
all the time.
- See?
- I--
look, I've stared
at a million boobs.
But until now,
I never considered them
to be...
daughter boobs.
Daughter boobs?
Well, come on.
You know what I mean.
Guy, hey.
Her face is up here, okay?
Come on.
It's so sweet
that you care.
I'm just gonna stay here
until something better
comes along, okay?
Yeah, I'll, uh--
I'll let you do your thing.
Do you want to have dinner
on my next free night?
Yeah.
That's great.
It actually makes sense,
in a way,
that Dexter would have been
involved with another killer.
- Well, she's back.
- Mm.
And she poisoned us.
Who knows what the fuck else
she has planned?
What does Dexter say?
He's trying to figure out
what else she's up to,
but I'm afraid he's thinking
with the wrong head right now.
You're concerned
for your safety.
And for Dexter's.
Let's take a step back.
From what you've told me,
if she wanted to kill you,
you'd be dead by now.
Well, maybe she just wants
to prove
that she has control,
that she can kill us
whenever she wants to.
It's a very unsettling
feeling, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
So what is it
you'd like to do?
I would like to take her
to Marshal Services
and have her
the fuck arrested.
- But Hannah knows too much.
- Yeah.
But at least
I wouldn't have to worry
about what might or might not be
in my morning coffee.
When the brain surgeon
was out there,
a threat to me,
I-I could hardly sleep.
I trusted Dexter
to solve the problem,
and he did.
And if I can't?
Before you take matters
into your own hands,
be sure to consider all the
consequences of those actions.
The husband is a complication
I don't need.
I have to get Hannah alone,
in a situation I control.
Have you done the blood work
on the triple in Lummus Park?
Not yet.
There's the prints on the
pesticide bottle still to run
and the decomp
over in Coconut Grove
we still have to process.
Yep.
Whew, we could use
an extra set of hands, right?
Someone lower level,
an extra warm body
to offset all the cold ones.
Don't you think?
I mean, at least to make a dent
in the paperwork.
Sure, I guess.
Excellent idea.
Zach...
What's he doing here?
Quinn.
Okay.
My client requests
that you cease and desist
this 24-hour watch
you have on him.
He requests it.
I'd like you
to back the fuck off.
You took these photos,
Zach?
Yeah, and those
are just the best ones.
Quinn, do you have
anything to say?
Yeah, I think
the kid's guilty.
I'll answer for you,
Detective Quinn.
On behalf
of the entire department,
I can assure you
that we will--
well, how did you
put it, Zach?
"Back the fuck down."
- "Off."
- Yeah that too.
Right,
Detective Quinn?
- Right.
- That's right.
Gentlemen,
let me show you out.
What the fuck
were you thinking?
That rich asshole
is walking around, free.
We have nothing
on this kid.
That's why I was
following him.
Yeah, if this was
any other case,
I would personally sign off
on the overtime.
But this one...
Let it go.
That's an order.
By the way, me and Jamie
are moving in together.
You're what?
You're doing what?
Hey, uh,
you got a minute?
Uh, make it fast.
Okay, well, Dexter and I
are buried in that glass box.
We need an assistant.
I don't know about that.
Wait, hold on,
we've been under budget
the last three quarters.
It was Dexter's idea.
Okay.
Part-time.
You're one hell
of a lieutenant.
The photos
we a nice touch.
Thanks.
I thought so.
Well,
now he's off my tail.
We can get down
to business.
Find someone to...
You know.
Eventually.
What do you mean,
"eventually"?
I mean...
Long before my father taught me
how to do what I do,
he taught me
how not to do it.
Why would I want
to not do it?
Timing is everything.
One thing
you need to learn--
the first thing
that I had to learn--
is to wait.
Control your urges.
Channel them appropriately.
Dexter, I can't wait.
I can't control it.
Yes, you can.
You're gonna get your chance,
Zach, I promise.
But the only way I've survived
as long as I have
is by being careful.
I'm gonna teach you
how to do that.
And then?
And then you'll be able
to do what I do
and get away with it.
What do you want?
I saw you
with your son.
Maggie never mentioned him.
Hard to picture her
as the family type.
There's nothing going on
between Hannah and me.
Good.
Then listen.
I'd sooner see her in prison
than lose her.
Do you understand?
Because I could call
a few people
and ruin your life.
And being a family man,
I'm sure
that's not what you'd want.
People are so impatient.
Dexter,
what are you doing?
This is something you don't want
to get in the middle of.
He said he'd sooner see her
in prison than lose her.
If that's what he thinks
this is about,
she's the one in danger.
I thought you were going
to find out
if Hannah was a threat
to you and Debra,
not if Miles was a threat
to Hannah.
Why can't I do both?
Your flowers.
That's the thing
about plants.
You don't look after 'em,
they die.
So...What's up?
Miles just confronted me
at a gas station.
God.
He likes to be dramatic.
Is he a threat?
A "chop you up and toss you
in the ocean" kind of threat?
No.
But he could
make your life miserable,
have people look into you
and follow you around 24/7.
He sounds
like a great guy.
And you're really
in a position to judge?
Why did you marry him?
Because he was there
when you weren't.
I needed him, Dexter.
I met him
a few years ago
when I did some flowers for him
at an event,
and he found
my background intriguing.
I could tell that he had
a bit of a crush on me,
so when I made my little escape
and when I had nothing
and when I was desperate,
I knew that he could give me
a whole new life,
a new identity,
money.
Plus, he makes me happy.
Bullshit.
If you're so damn happy,
what are you doing
back here?
Why did you
drug Debra and me?
You know,
I think you should go.
No, answer me.
I wanted to make sure
that you weren't gonna
put me in jail.
I had to see
if you would come to me.
Because it doesn't matter why
anymore.
I changed my mind.
About what?
I wanted you
to kill Miles for me.
You what?
He's possessive
and controlling
and obsessed with me
to the point
where he follows me
everywhere.
I might as well be
in prison.
If I were to try
and leave him,
he would--
he would just turn me in.
Why haven't you dealt
with this in your usual way?
Because his family
already thought
that I was some kind
of gold digger
when we got married.
If he was gonna
drop dead suddenly,
for no reason,
I would be the first person
that they would turn to.
And once the cops get
a good look at me--
You wanted me
to make him disappear.
I thought you might feel
like you owed me.
- Owed you?
- You didn't have to turn me in.
You ruined my life.
I did-
You know, it doesn't even
matter anymore,
because like I said,
I changed my mind.
And this is my problem,
and I'm gonna find
a way to deal with it.
Why did you
change your mind?
Because the moment that
I saw you there, unconscious,
I realized that,
despite the shitty way
that it all ended,
you were it
for me, Dexter.
I've never felt that way
about anyone before or since.
You're the only person
that I can be that honest with.
And I didn't want
to ruin that
by manipulating you
into doing something
that might be bad
for you.
It was the same
for me.
No, just leave it
at that.
I have to go before Miles
finds out where I've gone.
- Hannah...
- Good-bye.
Hey.
Um, can I borrow that
high-tech G.P.S. tracker thingy
that you have?
Please?
Yeah.
Being nice
when you need something, huh?
I'm not surprised.
Sorry
that I overreacted earlier.
I know
that you're interested.
You act like you are.
But, Jake, you don't want
to get involved with me.
You have no idea
who I really am.
I just want a chance
to find out.
Can I help you?
Is that your car?
Um, it--
it's my brother's car.
I think I left my sunglasses
in the passenger seat,
and he's not answering
his phone.
Your brother is...
Dexter Morgan.
He lives in the building.
Oh.
Oh, you're Dexter's sister.
I'm Cassie, his neighbor.
Debra.
Oh, fuck, you're Cassie
who went out with him, right?
Really?
He mentioned me?
You look surprised.
I am.
I, uh, I guess I figured
he thought
I was the worst date ever.
He didn't exactly
follow up.
But he's always nice to me
when I see him.
He's kind of impossible
to read.
Yeah,
that would be Dexter.
Oh, okay, good, I was starting
to think it was me.
Nope,
definitely not you.
Hey, um,
since I've got you here,
what's his deal?
Jamie seems to think
he's not over his ex-girlfriend,
which totally makes him
more attractive to me,
'cause apparently, I have
a thing for unavailable men.
Sorry.
That was an overshare.
That's all right.
I get it.
It's so crazy, right?
I meet
this totally nice guy
who's completely
into me,
and I'm still hung up
on the mysterious man next door
who hasn't called.
I don't know you...
At all, actually.
But you seem
like a normal girl, you know?
If I were you,
I would probably stick
with the guy
that's obviously interested.
Trust me,
Dexter is not a mystery
that you want to solve.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sorry about all that.
It's all right.
Have a good one.
See you.
- Hey!
- Hey.
You could've come inside.
I just got your text.
Oh, well,
you know,
I think I've seen enough
of that place, you know.
So...
What brings you by?
I wanted
to let you know
that a lab assistant position
just opened up at Miami Metro,
and it's yours
if you want it.
What does it pay?
$13.75 an hour,
plus dental.
I make a lot more money
than that here.
You did say that
this wasn't your first choice
as a line of work.
Yeah.
I figured
you'd jump at the chance
for a future that didn't
include pole dancing.
I'm not gonna
be a stripper, Dad.
Whoa.
Hey, it just slipped out.
That's okay.
Well, listen,
just do me a favor.
Just think about it,
okay?
I think it would be good
for the both of us.
Okay.
All right.
- Bye.
Well, that's probably best
for all involved.
Two psychopaths together--
never a good mix.
Hannah's not a psychopath.
She has feelings.
I'll have to take
your word for that.
Anyway, I called you
over here tonight
because I'm concerned
about Zach.
He came to me today
in a very agitated state.
I know, I didn't let him
kill his father,
and now he's feeling the urge
more than ever.
And how do you plan
to handle it?
I was ten years old
when Harry told me
what my future would be.
I didn't kill
until I was 19.
Zach can wait.
He just doesn't know
he can.
- Apples and oranges, Dexter.
- Sorry?
You thought you had no choice
but to wait
because your father
told you to.
But you were just a boy
who'd never taken a human life.
- Zach has already killed.
- Don't get me wrong.
I'm glad you took him
off your table.
But the moment you did,
Zach became
your responsibility.
He's relying on you,
Dexter.
You need to take this
very seriously.
Hi, you've reached
Zach Hamilton.
Please leave a message.
Hey, Zach.
It's Dexter.
Let's meet tomorrow afternoon,
2:00 p.m.
I'll come
to your studio.
It's good
that Hannah's leaving.
I have enough on my plate
trying to turn a young killer
into...
Someone like me.
Miles knows that Hannah and I
saw each other yesterday.
If Miles
will do this to me,
what will he do
to her?
So who are you tracking?
I'm just kidding,
obviously.
I don't want
to invade your privacy.
I just want to see
if you need anything.
No, I'm good.
Okay.
Jake.
I know I can be
kind of a dick sometimes.
You don't deserve that.
It's okay,
most people think
I'm a dick too,
so I guess we're even.
This past year
hasn't been my best.
The truth is,
I wouldn't be surviving it
if it weren't for you,
so thank you.
You're welcome.
Dexter?
Come on, what the fuck?
Dexter!
It looks
like he's not home.
Can I give him
a message?
Yeah.
Fuck him.
Hey, babe.
Good hunting?
Yeah, I found
a couple dresses.
I think
you'll really like them.
Nice.
I'm guessing today's shopping
went better than yesterday's.
- About the same.
- Really?
That's surprising,
considering there probably isn't
much of a selection
at your old greenhouse.
What are you
talking about?
You were
with your friend...
Dexter Morgan.
Well, he a--
he asked to see me.
He wanted to make sure
that I was all right
after you confronted him,
and I told him
that everything was fine,
that we were
very happy together,
end of story.
Don't lie to me.
I know the truth.
Oh, Miles, I told you,
I don't care about him anymore.
So you won't be
too upset then.
About what?
About what
yesterday's excursion
is going
to cost your friend.
Miles,
that's unnecessary.
- You've made it necessary.
- No, please, don't hurt him.
"Don't hurt him"?
Why, because you love him?
No, I promise you.
I'm not ever gonna
see him again.
He's the reason
you insisted...
- Stop it.
- On coming with me to Miami,
returning to a place where...
- Ouch!
- You're a wanted criminal.
Miles, ow!
He's the unfinished business
you mentioned.
I want you to know
I forgive you.
We're going
to make a new beginning.
I've already told the crew
we're leaving tonight.
We'll sail up the coast,
then cross the Atlantic,
just the two of us,
for the rest of our lives.
That's how much
I care about you.
No, Miles.
Stop it, please.
You'll never have
to leave this boat.
Stop
I've given you everything!
You belong to me.
No, stop it.
Get off me!
I-I tried to run,
but...
He just grabbed me.
I didn't mean for it
to happen this way.
Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
We need bleach, bags,
something to cut with--
an Axe or a saw
or something like that.
You think
you can get me those things
without letting the crew know
that anything's wrong?
Yeah, I think so.
Yes.
Wait, you need
to change.
- All right.
- Hannah.
It's gonna be okay.
I'll take care
of everything.
I believe you.
So that's how
you make people disappear.
Give or take a plastic room
and a kill table, yeah.
Yeah, I remember
that part.
Do you ever wish
that you had followed through?
With killing me?
No.
Ever wish you had?
I was never going
to kill you, Dexter.
It's just--
well, I knew I couldn't
live with Miles for much longer,
and...
Unlike you, I don't
actually enjoy any of this.
So what's next?
I told the crew
that Miles was going
to New York
for a few days,
so that should
buy me some time.
What's wrong?
I have to go
to a crime scene...
At my apartment building.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know.
I have to go.
Please don't leave town
before we talk again.
I won't.
This could be
my apartment.
Cassie.
Dexter?
W-what happened?
I don't know.
I just got here.
Cassie and I,
we were supposed
to have a date tonight.
I'm sorry.
I know you were friends.
You okay to work this?
Yeah.
What do you see?
She was bludgeoned.
See those marks
on her neck?
Someone held her down
and beat her to death.
God.
Norma Rivera
was bludgeoned.
Is it possible
Zach did this
when I was
with Hannah?
Harry was
a good teacher to me
because he
was normal, human.
But can anything good come
from putting
two killers together,
whether it be
student and teacher
or whatever
Hannah and I have?
Or will it always end
the same way,
like this?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man