? Dexter 8x09 ?
Make Your Own Kind of Music
Original Air Date on August 25, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Previously on Dexter...
I should be focused on
who bludgeoned Cassie and why.
But instead,
ever since Hannah came back
into my orbit,
she's all I can think about.
Have you seen that kid
around Cassie?
I don't know him.
I'm sorry.
Joey, my friend was murdered.
Once they catch the killer,
you're not gonna have
to be scared anymore, okay?
You know if it were Deb
asking you to stay,
you wouldn't
even put up a fight.
She'd want to catch the killer
as bad as I do.
Sorry I'm not Deb.
I think Hannah McKay
is back in Miami.
Are you interested or not?
Very.
What are you doing here?
I came here for her.
Who the fuck are you?
I don't wanna know.
I don't want to
know anything else ever.
She's your problem now.
I can't go to jail, Hannah.
Lose my kids again?
I couldn't take it.
We've always stuck together.
That's not gonna change now,
is it?
I found your blood
underneath Cassie's fingernails.
Zach had nothing to do
with Cassie's murder.
So how did my blood
end up there?
Your plane leaves at 8:00.
27 minutes later
you'll land in Nassau.
From there, where you go
is up to you.
Where do you think you'll go?
I haven't decided.
Argentina?
Every contact leaves a trace.
But the changes--they're never
what we anticipate.
I believe Hannah McKay
was just in Miami
going under the alias
of Maggie Castner.
Stay with me.
I just want to stay here
with you.
I know, but you can't.
Dexter, I'm so sorry
about Zach.
I know how much he meant
to you.
I need to see Dr. Vogel
and figure out our next move.
You should stay here,
inside, out of view.
But I have to see Arlene
this afternoon after her shift.
Why?
It's not safe for me
to draw money
out of Maggie Castner's
bank account anymore.
The only money I have is
what I've been sending away
to Arlene to hold for me.
And I'm gonna need
that money to...
Start a new life.
Okay.
"Be careful."
I know.
Actually I was gonna say,
"I love you."
I love you too.
Poor child.
I'm gonna have to find a way
to let the family know.
Just give me a little time
before Miami Metro
gets brought in.
I will.
This is the song
that was playing
when I found Zach's body.
Do you know it?
Yes, of course.
I used to play it all the time.
Still do.
Does it mean anything?
It's just a pleasant song.
But possibly some of my patients
heard me playing it.
? They may try and sell ya ?
There are some signs
of a struggle.
They fought here.
This table was out of place.
But whoever did this
cleaned up after himself.
There's no blood.
I wish I could understand
what this is all about,
why he's doing this.
I mean, it's clearly not simply
to frighten me.
He's trying to send a message.
But what is the message?
I don't care
what his message is.
He killed Zach.
He broke into my apartment
and dumped his body there.
What if Harrison
had been home?
I will find who did this,
and I will kill him.
I'm sure you will, Dexter.
But you need
to remain focused.
I am focused.
Blood.
He missed it.
And a few hairs pulled out
by the roots.
There's a big fingerprint
in the middle of it all.
Zach's, most likely.
Almost like
it was put there deliberately.
Zach learned from me.
He knew the importance of DNA.
It's possible
that he ripped these hairs
from whoever attacked him
and stuck them there
for me to find.
If this is a clue,
as you said,
then Zach acted
with extraordinary calm,
rational thought.
Yes.
Something I'm not sure
you're doing right now, Dexter.
What?
Your desire
to avenge Zach's death,
that's an emotional response,
possibly fueled by having to
say good-bye to Hannah.
I didn't say good-bye to her.
How do you mean?
We're going to make
a life together.
Dexter, how?
I don't know.
We'll figure it out.
Over the time
I've spent with you,
I've come to realize
that you're not
the perfect psychopath
I thought you were.
You have a depth of emotion
I never thought possible.
It's true.
I'll find the brain surgeon.
And I'll kill him.
But once I do I'm gonna
focus on a life with Hannah.
I think you
misunderstood my point.
Straddling two worlds
as you are, it's dangerous.
Killers cannot have
a full emotional life.
I think you
underestimate me.
So this is Maggie Castner's
passport photo.
That's Hannah McKay's.
I won't even ask
how you got those.
Good. Please don't.
They look
pretty much the same.
Have you had contact?
I have not.
Her boat left
for St. Kitt's yesterday,
but I don't think
she was on it.
What makes you think that?
Just a hunch.
A lot of good that does me.
What about her husband?
Supposedly in New York City,
but there's no record of
his jet ever landing there,
much less taking off from here,
so...don't know.
All right, then.
I'll look into this.
There's, uh...
There's one more thing.
I'd actually like to be a part
of the team on this one.
Thanks, but the Marshal Service
doesn't really take on partners.
- I understand, but--
- If I do happen to find her
you'll get your reward money.
Fair enough.
All right.
Deb.
Hey.
I saw you from my car and I--
I had this moment
where it was
just like old times.
Tell me you're here
to see me.
Quinn, actually.
I meant what I said
the other day.
We'd love you
to come back with us.
I just don't think
Matthews would go for it.
He was pissed that I left
so abruptly.
You never know, Deb.
I'll leave you two be.
Thanks for coming.
I need to, uh,
ask you for a favor.
Yeah. Anything.
I think I know
who Cassie's killer is,
but Matthews asked me
to lay off.
The guy's from
this rich fuckin' family.
So I was wondering if you could
look into him for me.
Sure. This all you have?
Yup. His info.
Social, address,
his name's Zach Hamilton.
Kid's a fucking serial killer
in the making.
I think Cassie's
the second person he killed.
Yeah, I will--
I'll get right on it.
I'm gonna go
say hello to Dexter.
The sooner I can
identify Zach's killer
the sooner I can
be done with all this
and get back to Hannah.
Excuse me,
you can't go in there.
Sorry.
Who the fuck are you?
Hey, hey, hold it.
Deb, this is
my daughter Niki.
Niki, this is
former Lieutenant Debra Morgan.
Oh, shit. Sorry.
My dad says that
you're, like, a total rock star.
Why'd you leave?
She's a curious one.
Come on.
Let's go see someone else.
Nice to meet you.
What the fuck are you doing
with Zach Hamilton?
Quinn called.
He thinks Zach killed Cassie.
I thought so too,
but I checked it out.
Zach didn't.
What was Zach doing
with you and Hannah in the keys?
Serial killers convention?
I was helping
Dr. Vogel out.
I don't know why I even
ask you these questions.
No one else knows.
Zach's dead.
Now I know.
I don't want to know,
'cause now I'm gonna have to
explain how I know.
Kind of, yes.
I was thinking
about coming back here.
About being a detective again,
doing something good
for a change.
But it'll just lead me
into another fucked up
situation, won't it?
A familial match.
...to Dr. Evelyn Vogel?
What?
The hairs we found
in Zach's studio--
I ran a mitochondrial DNA
match on them.
It tests a person's mother line.
Yeah, I'm aware of this test.
Well, it's a direct
match to you.
Zach's killer
is related to you.
The brain surgeon
But how is that possible?
I have no family.
Well, not anymore.
Anymore.
Well, I was married
and I had two sons.
Daniel and Richard.
And now?
They're gone.
What happened to them?
One day I found Richard--
he was my youngest--
at the bottom
of our swimming pool, dead.
At first I thought
it was an accident.
He wasn't a strong swimmer.
Then I realized the truth.
My older son Daniel,
he...
He killed Richard.
Yes.
Daniel was--
Daniel was highly intelligent.
But he was
also very troubled.
Oh, it was
much more than that.
He was devoid of empathy,
had a complete lack of fear,
of the sense
of right and wrong.
He was a psychopath.
Realizing this and wanting to
find a way to help Daniel
led me into this field.
I failed Daniel, I--
I was never
able to treat him.
Maybe that's one reason
I was so determined to help you.
This is Daniel.
My husband and I covered up his
involvement in Richard's death.
Said it was an accident,
and...
Then we put Daniel
into a mental health institute.
He was only 14.
- Here in Miami?
- No.
No, I sent him
back to England.
Three years later
he was dead.
How?
A fire broke out in the wing
where Daniel was living.
Some idiot nurse
had left the door locked
to take a coffee break.
The children
couldn't get out.
Seven of them perished.
One of them was Daniel.
Did you see the body?
No. My husband did.
He was horribly burned.
If it was his body.
That's preposterous,
Dexter.
He can't be alive.
You said yourself
he's highly intelligent.
Could've faked his death.
But after all these years...
Why would he do
these terrible things now?
The brain cores.
Do they mean
anything to you?
Well...
Well, even as a child,
Daniel was...
aware that he lacked empathy
and how I felt about it.
It's possible he boxed some up
and left it at my door.
Daniel Vogel would be
in his mid-40s.
Anybody. Nobody.
That guy Cassie was dating.
He was interviewed that night.
Oliver Saxon.
Is it possible
this is Vogel's son?
Daniel Vogel
is Oliver Saxon.
You created
half a dozen fake I.D.s.
He could've done the same.
The easiest way is to assume
the identity of a dead person.
Oliver Saxon,
death certificate.
The guy's a fake.
Doesn't mean
he's your brain surgeon.
I need to get
a DNA sample from him.
Dexter, this is
Deputy Marshal Clayton.
He's here on a tip that
Hannah McKay is back in Miami.
Uh, sorry if I don't
seem glad to meet you.
This is kind of a shock.
I guess that means
you haven't talked to her.
Why would I?
I told him
that you dated Hannah
before you turned her in
for the Sal Price murders.
Wasn't the smoothest
breakup.
I guess not.
And that makes you a target.
Frankly,
the Hannah McKay I knew
would be too smart to risk
coming back to Miami.
Could be.
Look, I got no definite
information she's here.
I'm just
following up on a tip.
Yeah, but until
we know for sure,
I think we should put unis
on you just till this plays out.
That's the last thing I need
while I'm trying
to help Hannah stay hidden.
On the other hand, the brain
surgeon's still out there.
And he knows where I live.
Yeah, but I don't
need unis to watch me,
just my apartment and my son
when he goes to school.
Don't worry. We're gonna
watch Harrison like a hawk.
Deputy Marshal Clayton...
How do you plan to find Hannah
even if she is here?
Well, I'm getting her picture
out with the local media
asking anyone to call us
if they spot her.
'Kay.
But if by some chance
she decides
you two need
to talk things over,
be sure and give me a call,
won't you?
Of course.
Believe me, I want her
behind bars as much as you do.
Okay.
This is exactly
what Vogel warned you about.
Trying to straddle
both worlds.
You should be following up
on Saxon right now.
Let Hannah handle
her own problems.
I can do both.
Hey.
Have you gone
to see Arlene yet?
No, I was
just about to leave.
Don't. I just had
a federal marshal in my office.
They know you're here.
Oh, God.
You can't go to Arlene's.
You need to lay low.
Dexter, I can't start
a new life without that money.
- I can give you money.
- $1/2 million?
Well, no.
Look, I'll drive you, I'm not
letting you go by yourself.
Okay, but hurry.
This marshal
changes everything.
We can never
be together here.
I know.
What are we gonna do?
Let's get your money,
and we'll figure that out later.
You were right.
The hotel manager in Key West
positively I.D. Ed Zach.
He was down there
when she was killed.
Where the fuck do you
get your information from?
I have my sources.
Wish I had your sources.
Thought I had
this one nailed.
Well, you're at square one.
You've been there before.
You'll close it.
Just after the whole
Sergeant Dick dance, you know,
I feel like I got
something to prove.
You're a good cop, Joe,
you don't have to
prove anything to anybody.
Then there's Jamie,
you know,
I kind of want
to solve it for her.
She was really close
to Cassie.
Yeah.
And I just haven't
been there for her lately.
What do you mean?
I thought she moved in.
I mean, like, emotionally.
Come on, since when
are you Mr. Sensitive?
Fuck you, okay?
God.
It pours right out of you.
You know,
she's always accusing me
of comparing you to her.
Oh. Um...
Well, I mean, I can't really
advise you on that.
Puts me in
an awkward position.
Why is that?
Because of our history,
asshole.
I mean, history is history,
right?
Jamie knew Cassie
better than anyone,
so maybe you should
question her again.
Maybe something'll turn up.
She's just been a wreck
about the whole thing.
It's kind of hard
to walk the line
between caring boyfriend
and hard-nosed cop.
I'll talk to her.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Be fun to play cop again.
That'd be great. Thanks.
You can buy me lunch.
And two fuckin' desserts.
This is a nice place.
Yeah, I found that
when you're a fugitive
asking somebody to hold
$1/2 million for you,
incentives are helpful.
So Arlene gets a cut?
She gets what she needs
to keep the kids off welfare,
and I get--
the Bank of Arlene.
Exactly.
- Hey, babe.
- Hey, Arlene.
Aren't you
the asshole who turned her in?
- That would be me.
- Long story.
Can we come in?
Yeah.
So now we're
back together, huh?
How's that gonna work out?
We're figuring it out.
I told the kids
there's snakes in here
so they wouldn't go near it.
There you go.
Oh, shit.
Who's that?
Federal marshal.
Stay here. I'll handle this.
You answer the door.
Come with me.
Like you've got
nothing to hide.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm Deputy
Marshal Clayton.
You mind if I ask you
a few questions?
Uh, yeah.
Dexter Morgan.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Arlene's a friend.
We met through Hannah.
Really, now?
Yeah, I just stopped by
to tell her what you told me,
that Hannah might be
back in Miami.
Yeah, I gotta keep
an extra eye on the kids.
Looks like you, uh,
recently changed your address.
It seems like a step up.
Better school district.
It says here you work part
time waiting tables at Denny's.
That's right.
That won't buy you
a doll's house,
let alone pay the rent
on this place.
You sure you haven't
gotten any help
from your friend
Hannah McKay,
who just happened
to have married a man
worth over $1/2 billion?
Didn't even know
she was married.
It says here
you got a record.
Do you have any idea
how many years
aiding and abetting
a fugitive will buy you?
Look, I'm the one
who's been...
helping out Arlene.
Now I see
what you two really bonded over.
You sure can pick 'em.
Listen, do me a favor.
Either of you hear from
your old friend Hannah McKay,
you give me a call.
- Of course.
- Yeah, we will.
Hey, Deb.
Dexter's not here.
I know,
I was just driving by
and I wanted to say hello
to the little man.
Oh.
Look, Aunt Deb,
I can write my name.
That's awesome.
I am so sorry about Cassie.
You doing okay
working here and everything?
Honestly, no.
Not really.
I mean, the cops are watching
the place, which helps.
She have a lot of friends?
Yeah.
She's pretty popular.
Everyone's just in shock,
you know?
Especially Oliver.
Who's that?
This guy Cassie was dating.
Were they dating
for a long time?
Just a couple weeks.
I guess it was love
at first sight.
At least for him.
What do you mean,
"for him"?
Between us, I think
Cassie was actually gonna
break it off with Oliver,
but then he was all,
"we should go to
the Bahamas for a week."
Bahamas after
two weeks of dating?
Yeah, he just kept
pushing her into it.
He would not take no
for an answer.
You weren't a fan of his,
I take it.
Sometimes I just thought
he could be a little clingy.
But he was great to Cassie.
Hey, we should all
have someone
who worships us
like that, right?
When was the trip to
the Bahamas supposed to happen?
This week, I think.
Hey.
Quinn, it's me.
I just talked to Jamie.
I think we need
to revisit the boyfriend.
Oliver Saxon.
So you think Clayton
bought your little story?
I'm not sure.
Either way, he's got
your photo all over Miami.
It's not safe for you
to go back to the hotel.
You need something private.
Yeah, but where?
I do know of one place.
Something tells me it's
the last place I'll want to go.
Debra's, if I can
talk her into it.
I was right.
I can't think of a better
option, can you?
Unfortunately, I can't.
You mind answering
a few more questions?
Anything I can do
to help find
the guy who did this
to Cassie.
This must be
really hard on you.
The last few days
have been a nightmare.
I still can't even
believe it.
I just wish
I had time to breathe.
I'm so busy at work.
In fact, I'm already late
for an appointment.
This won't take long.
What is it you do,
exactly?
Building inspections.
And that's where you were
at the time
of Cassie's death?
Yes.
You're welcome to take
a look at my workbook.
I was in Sunny Isles,
inspecting a new condo.
Just a few minutes
away from here.
Yes.
You must be pretty busy,
huh?
I'm booked wall to wall
for the next few weeks.
Oh, really?
I thought you and Cassie
were planning a trip
to the Bahamas.
How were you gonna
work that in?
I...
guess that was
a little crazy.
Cassie kept pushing for it,
and I didn't want
to disappoint her.
Oh, it was her idea?
Yeah.
She really wanted
a romantic getaway.
Seems a little fast,
don't you think?
After a few weeks of dating.
I know it's hard
for most people to understand,
but we had
something special.
And we both knew it.
Look, I'm really sorry,
you guys.
I've got to get going.
Maybe we can
pick this up later?
Yeah, no.
We'll come back another time.
That would be great.
Thanks.
He lied to us.
About what?
Jamie said that whole Bahamas
thing was his idea.
It was a way for Cassie
not to dump him.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean
he's a killer, you know.
I mean, he just could be
fuckin' obsessed with her.
Yeah, well, it wouldn't
hurt to look into it.
You know, look a little deeper
into his alibi.
I'll get on that.
Feel that?
What?
Us, you know,
working together again.
It's nice, you know?
Yeah, I mean,
it's a lot better
than doing background checks
for elway.
- Yeah.
- I forgot how much I like it.
Shit.
Ah...I'm sorry.
I don't know why I did that.
Let's just pretend
you didn't.
- Okay.
What the fuck?
Sorry, we let ourselves in.
You two should talk alone.
I need a place
where Hannah can stay.
And you want that to be
my place?
There's a federal marshall
after her.
He knows she's in Miami.
He's gonna do everything
he can to find her.
It's the only move
I could think of.
To bring Hannah
to my house?
I know.
It's only for
a couple of nights.
Just...
Until I can get her
out of Miami.
Please?
A couple of nights,
that's it.
Thank you.
You could also thank me
for getting Quinn
off Zach's trail.
How?
Simple. Get him
to focus on the boyfriend.
Oliver Saxon.
Saxon?
You think he did it?
Well, he's a damn good
suspect.
Quinn and I
talked to him today.
If Saxon thinks
the police are onto him,
he'll know
that I'm onto him.
You should stay away
from Saxon, Deb.
He could be more dangerous
than you think.
What are you
talking about?
I can't go into it
right now,
but please just...
do as I ask.
I knew going back
to the force
would put me in
a fucked-up situation.
Here it is,
ahead of schedule.
He's all yours.
You'll be okay here?
Sure.
We'll just hang.
If Deb and Quinn
did anything to spook Saxon,
I have to act fast.
I'm too late.
He's already moved out.
But if this has his DNA,
I can check it against the hairs
I found at Zach's studio.
Here you go.
Are we going to see
Hannah?
Hannah? Why?
I saw her on TV.
They said people
are looking for her.
Is she in trouble?
No, she's fine.
Hannah's...
just popular.
You miss her?
Yeah.
I liked playing with her.
She was nice.
I wish she could
be my mom.
It's a match.
Saxon is Vogel's son.
Daniel.
He's going by the name
of Oliver Saxon.
He was dating my neighbor
until he killed her
in her apartment
two doors down from mine.
Do you have any idea
where he is?
No, he cleared out
of his place.
He could be anywhere
right now.
Suppose you do find him,
Dexter.
What are you going to do?
What do you think?
I don't know
how I feel about that.
He's murdered
four innocent people,
and he killed
Zach Hamilton.
He's my son.
There's nothing
you can do for him.
I can--I can try
putting him back
into a safe facility
where he can't hurt himself
or anyone else.
I'm not going to let you
kill him, Dexter.
I'm sorry.
You brought me into this.
Because I didn't know
who he was then.
Try and understand,
my youngest son is gone forever.
Maybe I have a second chance
with Daniel?
You really believe that?
You have a son.
Wouldn't you believe it?
This second chance she wants
could get us both killed.
But, for her own sake,
I have to tell her
what she wants to hear.
Fine, we'll do it
your way.
Just...
Help me find him.
Is there a way
to reach out to him?
I don't know.
Think.
The Mama Cass song
that he left playing
in your apartment...
What about it?
One of the few happy memories
I have with Daniel
was when he was a little boy,
and every Saturday,
I'd take him
to the King's Bay Cafe
in the marina.
There was a juke box there.
And Daniel would
always play that song.
Maybe it's more
than a happy memory.
Maybe it's an invitation.
King's Bay Cafe.
It's still there.
Saxon's been one step
ahead of us this whole time.
We know he stole
your computer files.
But how could he have known
about Zach Hamilton?
We met him after that.
The detailed notes that
you keep on your computer...
Yes?
I think Saxon's
been monitoring your laptop.
It wouldn't be hard.
You just need
the right spyware.
We can use this.
Write an entry
in your journal
saying that you're going
to the King's Bay Cafe
tomorrow morning.
And you think he'll read it
and go there?
Well, you said yourself
he's been trying
to send you a message.
He wants to see you.
I don't like
deceiving Vogel.
But if it's the only way
to get to Saxon...
You had no choice, Dex.
You had to lie to her.
I just
can't believe Vogel
still thinks her son
can be helped.
Well, it's not that crazy.
After everything
he's done.
You would want to
help Harrison, wouldn't you?
Vogel pretty much
made the same point.
She's right.
I mean, look at what
your own father did
to protect you.
Right or not,
Saxon needs to be stopped.
I'm putting him
on my table.
And how is Vogel
going to feel about that?
I can't worry
about it now.
At least she'll be alive.
Well, you'll
figure it out.
I'm glad you're here.
I want to be able
to keep being here
for you, Dex.
But?
But there's no life
for me here in Florida.
We both know it.
I can have a life
somewhere else
far away from here...
in Argentina.
Maybe we all can.
You and Harrison
could meet me there.
We can start over.
It would be hard on Harrison
to uproot his whole life.
At first, it might be,
but sometimes
change is a good thing.
Sometimes it can--
yes.
Me, you, and Harrison...
We're gonna move
to Argentina.
We'll make it work, Dex.
I can give my notice
at Miami Metro,
say I'm burnt out.
I'm taking Harrison
to travel for a while.
Only Debra
will know the truth.
Lieutenant.
Have you heard anything
on the whereabouts
of Zach Hamilton?
Zach Hamilton?
You made it pretty clear
that we back away from him.
I just got a call
from his parents.
They haven't heard from him
in days.
Did they file
a missing persons report?
They just did.
Look...in case he does
turn up,
I want to be
the first to know.
I'll make sure of it.
Deb, thanks for coming in.
Yeah. What's up?
Welcome back
to homicide, Detective.
You'll earn your way back up.
You don't know how happy
this makes me feel.
It's like the family
coming together again.
We gotta celebrate.
Yeah.
What?
It's all happening so fast.
And?
Would you rather
it happened slow?
I just...
need some time...
to think about it.
What's there
to think about?
Thought this
is what you wanted?
It is.
I mean, I thought it was.
I don't get it.
I just need a little time,
you know.
Take all the time
you need.
Hey...
Hold on to this.
Hey.
I, uh, tried
getting in touch with Saxon,
but, uh, he's not
answering his phone.
And, uh, went by his place.
He cleared out.
Shit.
Yeah.
At least we're on
the right track.
Yeah.
Good luck with that.
Deb...
I, uh, wouldn't have
gotten this far without you.
I'm glad I could help.
You cleaned.
A little.
Well, I hope I can
still find shit.
I used to know
where everything was.
Hungry?
Are you kidding?
Totally fair.
Well, I am gonna eat,
and I made enough
for you too.
You going back?
How the fuck
can I go back?
My brother's
a serial killer.
And I have another one
hiding out in my house,
eating salad.
Sorry.
It was stupid to think
that I could go back.
Well, I know a lot
about wanting things
that you can't have.
I wish,
somewhere along the line,
I'd learned to take no
for an answer.
Would have made my life
a lot easier.
But you didn't?
I'll take that one.
Fine.
Well, it's just who I am.
And, uh...
something tells me
that you might
be kind of the same way.
Maybe that's the one thing
we have in common.
I can't believe
I'm eating food you made.
It's not bad, though, right?
No.
Mm.
All right, two-minute warning,
Harrison.
Swim lessons are calling.
Almost done.
Sorry about this police
protection business.
No, it's good.
I'm actually glad
that they're here.
I mean, if Hannah
were to stop by,
poor Harrison would
probably run right to her.
He's not the only one.
Dexter,
hope I'm not intruding.
No, not at all.
Come in.
All right.
What can I do for you?
Just checking in and making
sure everything's okay.
Yeah, everything's fine.
Well, good to hear.
I'm thinking
the Hannah McKay threat
has pretty much died down.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah, I mean,
if she was here,
I'm pretty sure she's gone.
So I'm gonna recommend we pull
off your protective detail.
Okay.
All right.
And what's your name?
- Harrison.
Wow.
Is this your family?
Mmhmm.
Is this your daddy?
That's you, right?
Mmhmm.
Now, who's the pretty lady?
That's my mom.
Your mom?
Hey, why don't you go
grab your towel, bud?
Swing time.
Come on, let's go,
little shark man.
He lost his mother
when he was just a baby.
I think drawing her helps him
feel closer to her.
Sure.
Well, we really do
need to get going, uh...
Thanks for checking in.
All right, take care.
Hey, you got a sec?
Sure.
Closing the door.
That's never a good sign.
So Hannah McKay
dated your brother, huh?
You didn't think to mention
that to me at all?
Thought never
crossed your mind?
I didn't think
it was important.
What else are you not
telling me?
I don't know,
but if I told you--
Drop the bullshit, Morgan.
What happened in the Keys?
You see her?
No.
I don't believe you.
'Cause you either saw her,
or your brother told you
to lay off--
Well, what if he did?
What does it even matter?
Oh, I'll give you
250,000 reasons why.
But, clearly, you and I
have different priorities.
My brother?
Yeah. We do.
You know, after all the things
that I've done for you,
I find it hard to believe
that you could do this.
I really do.
And maybe you need
to ask yourself
if this is the right job
for you.
And if not, why don't you
get the fuck out?
'Cause I could
use the office space
for somebody
that gives a shit.
Oh, Dexter.
Sorry, I...
know I'm early.
I'd make you some coffee,
but I only have tea.
That'll do.
I warn you, it's strong.
I need all the help
I can get this morning.
Thanks.
Just so we're clear,
I'm meeting up with Daniel,
and I'll lead him
out of the cafe,
where you will sedate him.
And--and we'll take him
to a facility.
Every time
I close my eyes,
I-I still see his face.
- Daniel.
- Yes.
Now to learn
that he's alive
is just too good
to accept.
It is hard to believe.
But another part of me
knows it's true.
And I'm going to see him.
My son.
My little boy.
He still exists.
No--no matter
what he's done.
Uhh!
I thought
one of Hannah's potions
would be gentler
than my needle.
Now Vogel will never
have to face
what her son has become.
Can I get a cup
of coffee please?
I'll bring that
right over.
Here you go.
? nobody can tell ya ?
Hey, Lucy.
Hi.
? There's only one song
worth singin' ?
? nobody can tell ya ?
He's played that song
three times.
When is he gonna give up?
I'll follow him until I find
a quiet place to grab him.
For Vogel's own good,
it's time I killed
the messenger.
Saxon must have
spotted you.
He's good at this.
He might think Vogel
sent you, Dexter.
He could going to her house
right now.
You've reached
Dr. Evelyn Vogel.
I'm not available
at this time.
Please leave a message.
Evelyn!
You drugged me.
You have every right
to be upset,
but I was only trying
to protect you.
Where's Daniel?
He got away.
That's why I'm here.
To warn you.
Well, I consider myself
warned.
And I think it best
from here on out
that I handle this myself.
It's not safe.
Or smart.
I appreciate your concern,
and I'm grateful
for everything you've done.
But this
is a family matter.
You once called yourself
my spiritual mother.
Doesn't that
make us family?
Well, after what happened
this morning, Dexter,
how can I trust you?
Well, trust me or not,
I'm going to take care
of Daniel.
Your safety and mine
depend on it.
And after that,
I'm on my way with Hannah.
- On your way?
- I'm leaving Miami with her.
We're going away together
with Harrison.
You know that won't
end well.
And you trusting Daniel,
that he's not gonna
hurt anyone again--
how will that end?
Leave this alone, Dexter.
Vogel thinks I'm unique,
caught between two worlds--
my humanity
and my darkness.
Maybe I always will be,
but I can't imagine
a life without Hannah
in either one.
After this morning,
I won't have to.
Vogel is on her own,
and so am I.
I'll kill Saxon
and leave Miami forever.
So now do you believe me?
Yes.
You didn't send him.
Are you hungry?
How about
a little breakfast?
Okay.
Mom.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man