You high, popo?
A cop with a sense of humor.
You can check the cop car.
Also check his personal car, work, home.
Foreman, get out!
Am I the only one who finds this funny?
You stole my article.
I wouldn't do that.
We're not friends, we're colleagues.
Ow! Son of a bitch!
Now we're both exposed.
I'm gonna die.
You die, I die. It's not gonna happen.
Time of death, 12:26 P.M.
I need a bone saw.
- I'm sorry. I wish I could.
- You said you
I just want a little tiny slice of
this guy's brain, that's all I need.
Just enough to tell me
what's killing Foreman.
A thin slice of Joe's brain could
also cause a public health crisis.
It's not a good idea to scream "fire"
every time somebody lights a match.
Don't downplay this, House.
You put both of them
in isolation for a reason.
Joe's death elevates this
situation to a biosafety level three.
Ooh, level three.
You should call Jack Bauer.
I called the CDC.
Well, tell them
I'll be really, really careful.
We don't have the proper equipment
for you to be really, really careful.
You can do whatever you want to
Foreman, but the CDC will do this autopsy.
Whatever. The point is, we'll be
lucky to get results in three days.
I told them how urgent this is.
And they told you?
We'll have the results in three days.
Aw, that's a shame.
Because Foreman will never get to know
what it was. He'll be dead in 36 hours.
Maybe this is a toxin.
Maybe it's not contagious at all,
and you're killing Foreman
because of a maybe.
Well, you have 36 hours
to figure out which one it is.
Foreman. Come here, fast.
What's going on?
When are they doing the autopsy?
You're doing it. Now.
You ever study how they used
to do ice pick lobotomies?
I read about it in
med school. Why would I--
shove an ice pick into the eye
socket. Just above the tear duct.
Bang it a couple of times with
a hammer, get a sample.
What's going on, man?
Foreman, you can't do it.
You'll be in violation of--
- Can't do the time if you're not alive.
- You.
I need you to suit up.
Get that equipment away
from Dr. Foreman.
Take your time, guys.
Why don't you just tell him
to go slow? Won't be your fault.
Foreman.
We don't even know what kind
of contagion we're dealing with.
Which is why we need
to chop into the guy's head.
- It's dangerous.
- Not to you, Foreman.
There are other ways
to diagnose you.
Yeah? You have the answer?
Foreman, do it now.
I am warning you, do not--
What are you doing?
That didn't feel right.
He's blind.
He thinks he can see.
Same as the cop.
I need something
to bag the sample.
Forget it. You just
biopsied a mattress.
No,no,no.I'm fine.
House, there's the sample.
Get it, test it.
You gotta test that sample!
Apparently I was
optimistic about the 36 hours.
Intractable, unbearable
pain is up next.
Sure you don't want to reconsider
that whole autopsy thing?
-=House=-
Season 2 Episode 21
Physically, his eyes are fine.
Problem's isolated to his brain.
Damage to the occipital lobe extends
from the primary visual cortex--
Should we test him for
bacterial meningitis?
If it was meningitis,
we'd all be sick.
- His CSF could show signs
- That would be pointless.
We already did a brain biopsy.
It was negative.
Toxic mold?
If it was toxic mold, I'd be sick.
How do we know you're not sick?
Do I seem happy to you?
Never.
It was funny.
Well, let's assume
it's not blood-borne.
If you start cracking jokes,
we can re-assess.
In the meantime, stay away from
people and animals that you care about.
Guillian-Barre?
Neither of them had any sort of paralysis.
Joe could have died before the
paralysis had a chance to present.
**What about arbovirus?
Start treatment.
For Arbovirus?
You think our Jersey beat cop
has been spending a lot of
time exploring deep, dark Africa?
Treatment for everything.
Likely or unlikely. If you
can think of it, treat for it.
Mixing that many meds will
create all sorts of toxic interactions.
We'll box his liver, trash his kidneys.
There's got to be a better way.
Of course there's a better way!
It's that body sitting in the room
with him that Cuddy won't let us touch.
Bacterials, virals, toxins, fungals,
parasites. It's got to be one of them.
Where are you going?
To see if I can find
another brain to biopsy.
We're going to lock Joe up
downstairs until the CDC gets here.
Foreman, you can't see.
Right.
House wants to start you on
some meds. They're in the airlock.
For what?
Leading candidate is toxic mold.
Is Cameron sick?
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
You're casting your net a little
wider than toxic mold, aren't you?
Guillian-Barre is also on the table.
This is an oval shape...
has either an L or a 7.
I'm guessing an L. Levofloxacin,
because you can't rule out bacteria.
Eight, zero, zero. That's the dosage
for the acylovir in case it's viral.
Square...no,
more like a rhombus.
That's fluconazole for fungus.
There's about eight
others here. You--
You're treating me for everything.
You have no idea what I've got.
House thinks this is
the best course of action.
House is desperate.
House is never desperate.
Something we give you will work.
Yeah, we should start
treating all patients this way.
When they get sick,
they just take everything.
It's better than doing nothing.
Hello?
I'm at the cop's place.
I need to retrace your steps.
You don't think the "treat him for
everything" approach is enough?
Where did you start your search?
The kitchen.
You will tell me everything
you did, everything you touched.
If you went to the john,
I want to know when and why.
I started with samples
from the mold in his sink.
What next?
That's it. Then I left.
What do we do now?
Wait for Steve McQueen
to get giddy.
Excellent plan.
Hey, dad.
It's Eric. I'm not
doing too good.
How's Foreman?
You're accessing a webcam?
Cuddy's shower.
Are you a fan of the Brazilian? I--
Is that your kitchen?
Well, obviously I
couldn't bring him here.
He's been exposed to
whatever Foreman's got.
You infected Steve?
Why didn't you just get
a rat from the pet store?
Because...I needed one
with a clean medical history.
Who knows what kind of
antibiotics they give those rats?
So this is your plan? Just sit
here and watch your rat all day?
Well, it shouldn't take long.
Got the AC blasting,
I soaked the floor of his cage...
as soon as he gets sick,
I do an autopsy.
As soon as he's dead.
Right after he gets sick, there's a good
chance he'll get hit in the head with a...
cane-shaped object.
Normally you just use
your patients as lab rats.
It's a nice change.
First symptom is euphoria.
How do you know if a rat's euphoric?
He doesn't usually climb on his
water bottle like that, does he?
the seizures only seem to happen
when she's in her car seat.
She starts to rock and grunt.
She responsive?
No, no, it's like she's in a zone.
And her abdominal
muscles become dystonic.
Big word.
Someone's been on the interweb.
I looked up a few articles on epilepsy.
You know, there's actually some
really great youth soccer leagues,
that would cater specifically
to her special needs,and...
I think it might explain why she's
been having a hard time in preschool.
Let's confirm your diagnosis
before you have her held back.
Strobing lights and high-pitched
sounds can provoke a seizure.
You're a goof.
Takes one to know one, loser.
Wait, that means I'm a loser.
Scratch that.
These episodes.
She get sweaty afterwards?
Soaking wet.
And does she seem
upset by them, or just tired?
No, she kind of thinks it's funny.
You mix rocking, grunting, sweating,
and dystonia with concerned parents,
and you get an amateur
diagnosis of epilepsy.
In actuality, all your little girl is doing
is saying "yoo hoo" to the "hoo hoo".
She's what?
Marching the penguin.
Ya-ya-ing the sisterhood.
Finding Nemo.
That was funny.
It's called gratification disorder.
Sort of a misnomer.
If one was unable to gratify oneself,
that would be a disorder.
Are you saying she's masturbating?
I was trying to be discreet.
There's a child in the room.
Oh, this is horrifying.
Epilepsy is horrifying.
Teach your girl about privacy
and she'll be fine. Here you go.
Thank you.
One afternoon, and you're on pace to set
the record for most patients seen in a month.
You're upset that I'm doing clinic hours?
Wow, that is so like
rain on your wedding day.
For the past three hours, I have been on
the phone with the CDC, while you are--
Yeah, how's that going,
by the way?
They promised to expedite--
Tough to do an autopsy when they
haven't even picked up the body.
It's tough to treat your patient when
you're not even on the same floor.
Go. Clinic is covered.
I go watch the meds drip into his IV,
you think that'll make the
treatment work faster?
Go to your office.
Play with your ball.
Write on your whiteboard.
Insult your team.
Do whatever it is that you do
to figure things out.
Feeling guilty?
It's not too late to change
your mind. Go call the CDC.
Tell 'em you were just joshing.
Keep avoiding Foreman's
ase until he dies.
Then I'll drown in guilt.
Feeling any better?
How are you doing?
I'm not the patient.
Is your sed rate elevated?
No.
So far,it looks like I lucked out.
Cameron.
Looks like you left
a tourniquet on the bed.
You can see again?
The treatment's working.
The question is, which treatment?
We'll start weaning him off one at a
time. Which one do we start with?
I don't care if you do it alphabetically.
Just stay on top of his vision.
First sign of regression means
we've taken him off the wrong one.
The latest blood work.
Foreman's amylase and lipase
levels are three times normal.
Pancreas is failing.
A toxic side effect of his meds.
Philosophical question.
How do you want to die?
Old age.
Your choice is currently between 4 hours
from now and 14 hours from now.
So I'm assuming that
means you want the latter.
The cocktail's working.
My vision's almost
completely restored.
The meds are curing
what's in your head,
but they're trashing your pancreas.
That's why you're puking and
you can't stand up without screaming.
So lower the dosages.
Less stress on my pancreas,
still battle the infection.
Lower dosages will still be toxic.
I don't care!
I can handle the pain
of the pancreatitis.
I don't think you can handle
life without a pancreas.
We keep you on these meds,
you'll spend the last four hours
of your life being able to see.
Take you off, you'll go blind again.
But it'll give us time to figure
out what's eating your brain.
Fine.
What do we do next?
Eric?
Dad?
Yeah, you two can
get caught up later.
Sir, I need you to come with me.
House.
Uh...what is this?
He isn't a what, he's a who.
They even have the right to vote now.
Rodney Foreman, Cuddy.
Cuddy, Rodney Foreman.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.
This is Foreman's dad.
Yeah, I got that.
And Dr. Cuddy, here, is
the Dean of Medicine.
Remember that cool autopsy
I was telling you about,
the one that would
save your son's life?
She's the one can give
us the green light to do it.
I understand you don't
want them to do it.
Dr. House didn't
seem to know why.
Mr. Foreman, I am doing
everything I can to get the CDC--
Won't be soon enough.
And my decision to follow
public health safety protocols
Oh, don't blame the rules.
Don't want to hang this
on policy and protocol.
I'm well aware that it may cost your
son his life, just as I am well aware
that my decision has a devastating
effect on family and friends
Without having them
paraded in front of me.
Your son has an unknown,
contagious, deadly infection.
If we don't contain it here, even
more people could be at risk.
And I am capable of empathizing
with those people too
without having them
paraded in front of me.
I understand.
What's wrong with your hand?
It's--it's called a muscle contraction.
I thought this thing was in your brain.
It is. It just means the infection's
moved to the primary motor cortex,
which controls the muscles.
Aren't you glad you sent
me to med school?
Does it hurt?
No.
Is it gonna?
The--the other guy...
he didn't seem to
suffer too much, he--
just went in his sleep.
Steve still acting normal?
No sign of contractures.
They got the cop's body
in a locked,airtight bag.
And a guard on the door.
These feds are
seriously paranoid.
He hasn't gotten up
to pee in hours. He's due.
You haven't sprinkled
senokot granules on his doughnut?
His bowels would
open up like the Red Sea.
He wouldn't eat the doughnut.
Have you seriously been
down here for hours?
No.
I had to pee a couple times.
You've got to stop
blaming Cuddy for this.
Given that it is her fault,
that seems appropriate.
That part is her fault.
The part where somebody
wasted his time in the basement,
plotting the overthrow of a
government agency, that one's on you.
The only think I can do is think.
I can pretty much do that anywhere.
As long as no one's bugging me.
Did you call your brother?
No.
Did you?
It's not a big deal.
I sure would have liked
to see Mom, though.
You know she
can't travel anymore.
You tell her?
Why?
Just upset her for a while.
Then she wouldn't
remember for a while.
Think she should know?
She's lost a lot of who she was.
She can't deal
with something like this.
And you can?
I still know you're
going to a better place.
It's easy for you, isn't it?
As long as you believe I'm going
to a better place, dying ain't so bad.
I don't want you to be afraid.
If I'm not afraid of dying, what the
hell should I be afraid of, Dad?
I thought you believed.
I did.
I'm not so sure anymore.
I'm going to pray for you, son.
I suggest you do the same.
Field of vision is regressing.
And he's reached an
eight on the pain scale.
The disease pattern is following
the exact course as Joe's.
Only it's moving
much faster in Foreman.
Good! It's an anomaly.
Anomalies tell us things. Why is this
moving faster in Foreman? What's different?
Could be a different
strain of the same disease?
Right--we were wasting all this
time looking for an unknown disease.
We should have been looking for a
different strain of an unknown disease.
Joe's a cop.
He's into physical fitness,
he could have had...
a more powerful immune system,
stronger metabolism.
Foreman's black.
What?
How long have you been
sitting on this information?
Lupus, gout, glaucoma,
osteoarthritis, hypertension, diabetes,
stop me any time, they all affect
black people more than whites.
Check everything.
Bacterials, fungals,
toxins, parasites.
Look for anything with a
documented racial disparity.
Wait.
The rat's showing symptoms?
No.
He's completely healthy.
Maybe that's the difference
between Foreman and the cop.
How are you feeling?
Why are you here?
Because you're a friend.
And I should be here.
I'm sorry House used my
dad to try and manipulate you.
You've got integrity, you aren't
going to change your mind
just because you're
confronted by my father.
Thank you.
Just like I'm not
going to forgive you
just because you come
by here and ask how I'm feeling.
You know I've had no choice.
Of course you had a choice!
Regulations are clear.
And the punishment for
violating those regulations!
Is it death?
Because frankly, I'm okay if
you get a fine, a suspension--
hell, you can spend a couple
of years in jail if it saves my life!
You're dying too fast.
Couldn't agree more.
Hey, Cuddy.
Having a nice visit?
What's that?
Legionel--legionella pneumophila.
And why are you carrying
a vial of it around with you?
Foreman was perfectly
healthy before he got this infection.
Our cop wasn't.
He had legionnaire's disease.
Our cop didn't turn into brain
food until we cured the legionella.
Legionella slowed down the disease.
Why would that happen?
No idea.I just know that it did.
So you want to infect Foreman?
Gonna tattle to the CDC?
Meds can't help me,
but a disease can?
Forget it! Just take the pain
away and put me under.
If I put you under,
I can't monitor your pain.
If I can't monitor your pain,
I won't know if the legionella's working.
I'm not consenting to you giving me--
What was that?
I wish there could have been
a puff of smoke or something.
Would've been
much more dramatic.
Keep your slippers on.
Wouldn't want
you to cut your foot.
Do you feel any better?
I can't breathe. I'm dizzy.
And I can barely hear anything over
the sounds of my lungs crackling.
That's the legionella.
You figure that out
from the symptoms,
or from the vial of stuff
tossed in my room?
I'm trying to be professional here.
There's no reason to be nasty.
- I'm in pain.
- So is House.
And he's a delight.
He doesn't try to kill his colleagues.
You can remove the thermometer now.
It's down almost a whole degree.
How's the pain?
Great.
This is the good kind.
How bad is it
compared to an hour ago?
No worse.
The legionella helping?
Yeah.
Good.--Not great.
Didn't fix anything,
it just slowed it down.
The point was to give Steve a
little more time to get sick.
What are you going to
do if he never gets sick?
Brilliant.
Cameron,what type of illnesses
affect humans, but not rats?
Why are you asking me that?
Because I'm sure that you spent the first
12 years of your life dreaming of being a vet.
The rat is not getting sick.
Cameron is not getting sick.
Sorry.
It's okay, it's not your fault.
Presumably, you're still healthy because
whatever it is, is not bloodborne.
Steve has no excuse. He did
everything that Foreman did.
Some bacterial infections
don't infect rats.
Foreman tested negative for every bacterial
infection that would affect his brain.
And what infections could he be
positive for, but test negative for?
When we test for infections,
we look for antibodies.
But what if the patient is infected,
but has no antibodies?
What if the body is not
fighting the infection?
Why would--
I asked first.
Let's start with the what.
We'll deal with the why later.
If the body doesn't recognize the infection,
our tests come back negative,
and the disease rampages
through the body unstopped.
Exactly like the cop and
exactly like Foreman.
And what if the patient was then
exposed to a second infection?
Like legionella?
The body would recognize that
infection, increase the white count,
send in the troops to start fighting,
and the initial infection would
get caught in the crossfire.
So the question becomes,
what type of bacterial infection
affects humans but not rats,
and the human body would
be unlikely to recognize?
The answer is Listeria.
I'm starting you on Apogen.
So you're basing this theory
on the test being negative
and your rat being healthy?
And the fact that
Legionnaire's is helping you.
But the medicine you want
to give me will put an end to that.
Yeah.
And if it's not Listeria, all the Apogen
will do is cure the Legionnaire's Disease
and put whatever is killing
me back into overdrive.
Stop asking me questions based
on the premise that I'm wrong.
The antibiotics are in the airlock.
I think the first biopsy
didn't give us the answer
because you didn't go deep enough.
I want you to do a
white matter brain biopsy.
Absolutely.
Don't blame you.
The world is such a complicated place
if you've got higher reasoning skills.
I'm often jealous of small
animals and retarded children.
Take the antibiotics.
There can be minimal
damage if it's done right.
If the surgeons drill where
I tell them to drill.
One slip--you could spend the rest of your life not
being able to keep your drool in your mouth.
I'd rather be disabled than dead.
Sure, I make it look oh so sexy.
It's actually not as
glamorous as you might think.
The biopsy will tell us
for sure what's wrong.
The antibiotics could
do the same thing.
Could, not will.
We try it, we see.
The antibiotics will bring back the pain.
Pain makes us
make bad decisions.
Fear of pain...is almost
as big a motivator.
Look,we still have time.
I will do that biopsy if I have to.
But not a moment before.
Start Foreman on IV antibiotics.
Where's his dad?
Where are you supposed to
be when your son is dying?
He's not with him.
He's in the chapel.
I started your son on
a new course of treatment.
If it works, he'll get better.
If it doesn't, he won't.
While he's not getting better,
he's going to experience
so much pain
that we'll have to put him
in a chemically-induced coma
while we figure out what to do next.
My son says you're
a manipulative bastard.
It's a pet name.
I call him Dr. Bling.
I assume you're here for a reason.
What do you want from me?
When your son is in a coma,
You're the one who's going to have to
make the medical decisions for him.
Oh, whatever you decide is fine.
You don't care what I do?
I'm not a doctor. What do I know?
Except what Eric tells me.
He says you're the best
doctor he's ever worked with.
I need your help.
There's nothing I can give you for the pain.
I want to be put out.
I can have a nurse in here in five minutes.
No. Want some help.
I might not come back.
I've never done a will.
I'll call a lawyer for you.
I want you to be my medical proxy.
All the things that piss me
off about you in House's office--
You're too emotional, too caring,
too cautious--
they're all good things on this floor.
- Your dad is
- No.
- He cares about you.
- So do you.
I can't do this.
We expect family members to make
decisions about their loved ones
after a ten-minute briefing
that we're agonizing over even
with years of medical experience.
That's from my article.
I'm sorry, Allison.
I shouldn't have stolen your article.
I shouldn't have exposed you.
You were a friend.
I need to know that we're okay.
No.
I'll be your proxy,
but we're not okay.
You're scared you're dying. And that's
the only reason you want to set things right.
We're going to get you better first,
and then, if you still want
to apologize, I'll be around.
I'll call that lawyer.
Any improvement?
Well,as far as we can tell,
the only thing the antibiotics
are treating is the legionella.
I think we need to consider
alternate theories.
Like what?
We do the biopsy. We--
give the antibiotics more time.
There is no more time. The
pain is almost unbearable already.
So he's almost in unbearable
pain. He's not almost dead.
Which means we have more time.
Mr. Foreman?
We need to put your son in a coma.
You should be there.
It's a medical procedure, right?
Yeah.
But once we put him out,
if--if we don't solve this,
he won't wake up.
What should I say?
Should I talk to him like
it's going to be...okay?
Or should I be saying good-bye?
I need to know what
people say when--
Just tell him you love him.
Hey,son.
Hey, dad.
It's going to be okay.
You don't know that.
I know.
You don't.
I don't want to miss you.
I love you too, Dad.
Hey.
It's gonna to be okay.
- Can we do this now?
- Yeah,of course.
I accept your apology.
Why weren't you with Foreman?
I hang out in the basement,
you rag on me.
I stay in my office,
Honkey just can't buy a break.
Do the biopsy.
Based on the cop's progression, I
figure he's got about another four hours--
You figure?
You're playing Russian roulette,
but the gun's pointed at him.
No, cutting open his
head is what's dangerous.
Oh, it's dangerous.
Well, what would people think?
The reason you don't see patients
is because if you know them,
- you'll give a crap about them.
- I know you.
If you give a crap, you stop
making outrageous calls.
If this was any other patient,
you'd have damned the risk and
cut their head open a long time ago.
He's out. The EEG shows
he's still in pain.
The antibiotics have had more than
enough time. We're doing the brain biopsy.
Not unless you people can't come up
with something clever in the next three hours.
Now. We're doing it now.
- Who died and made you boss?
- Foreman.
It's legal.
He's out of his mind.
Yesterday he was giggling
about a hole in a guy's head.
Then hire a lawyer and challenge it.
In the meantime, Cameron's in charge.
Why would he sign that?
It's nothing personal, Mr. Foreman.
My son doesn't trust me.
How exactly is that not personal?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You're talking about this man's son.
- You're denying him the right to be a part of
- Oh, shut up, House.
If you want to do the biopsy,
do the biopsy.
If House tries to interfere, let me
know and I will take care of it.
Yeah. You're a hero.
If it wasn't for you, we'd be cutting into
a dead guy's head instead of Foreman's.
Sorry.
Thanks.
- That was great!
- It was rude and unnecessary.
Yeah.
Go away.
Give me time.
- We're out of time.
- An hour.
What does "out of time" mean?
His O2 stats are 94 right now.
His lungs are about 90. The danger
of fatal arrhythmia doesn't increase.
So what? There's no point in waiting.
You were right. We should be
cutting into a corpse's head.
Yeah,we should be, except the
CDC's got the cop's body--
There's got to be other bodies.
You think this thing
has killed other people?
No.
That apartment was a dump.
Just because Steve McQueen didn't get sick
doesn't mean some other vermin didn't.
You give me an hour. I go
back there, I find a dead animal,
I cut its head open
instead of Foreman's.
Foreman's already
on 100% oxygen.
Once his O2 seds hit 90,
I can't wait any longer.
Where's your suit?
Either you'll find the answer,
or I'll find the answer.
Doesn't matter.
Prep the drill.
We gotta be ready to
go if we get the signal.
92.
I found a blind bird.
Great.
How fast can you get it in here?
I'll know in about 30 seconds.
You better have the bird.
The surgical team's in place.
I screwed up.
How can you not
capture a blind bird?
That's not what I meant.
I screwed up the
first time through this place.
Foreman told you everywhere he went.
It's not where, it's when.
He came here early afternoon.
Me and Steve came through two
hours too late. You were six hours early.
It's the water. The irrigation
system only pumps--
House, I tested the water.
The water's clean.
House.
We tested the wrong water.
He stole cable, he stole
fertilizer, and he stole water.
It's riddled with Naegleria.
I know.
You already did the biopsy.
I thought I had no choice.
How's my son?
He has primary amebic
meningoencephalitis.
It's a parasite that goes through
the nose and migrates into the brain,
where it feeds on brain cells.
The Legionella attacked the parasite.
That's why the disease slowed down.
Is it treatable?
We started him on an antiparasitic,
and the amoebas will
clear out of his system.
And he'll be okay?
Then--then we'll wean
him out of the coma--
will he be okay?
There'll be no lasting
damage from the parasite.
But the surgery?
We don't know.
How are you feeling?
Can you talk?
I don't feel anything.
Are you numb?
No,I--I mean...
I don't feel any pain.
Keep your head still.
Follow my finger.
I'm okay.
Your breath stinks.
And you're peeing into a bag.
What are our names?
You did the biopsy?
Thank you.
Names?
Cameron.
My dad.
And the manipulative bastard.
You remembered.
How you doing, Dad?
Great.
Relieved. Great.
What did I have?
Naegleria.
Biopsy showed the amoeba.
CDC autopsy eventually found the amoeba.
And House found it in the
water on the cop's roof.
Wiggle your left toes.
Wait, wait.
You went back
and she did the biopsy?
Your left toes, Foreman.
I just did.
No, you didn't.
He can't move his toes?
He can move them.
Raise your right arm.
What?