Ugh. I think I'm gonna puke.
Not on this dress.
I'm serious.
Kate Moss was doing this at 13.
You have two years on her.
Yeah, that's what I like to see.
You got this.
Next show, you're bride.
Did Austin just offer you bride?
It wasn't a real offer, Dad.
He was just being nice.
These shoes are gonna
be impossible to walk in.
You've done this
a hundred times before,
all right?
The runway's just
a little bit longer here.
One of the girls said
Madonna's in the front row.
Sweetie, sweetie,
hey, come on, come on.
You gonna be able
to do this? Hmm?
All right, come here, come here.
Here, hold this.
The doctor gave me these
for anxiety, all right.
It'll calm you down. Here.
Come on, it's okay.
Austin:
Where's Alex?
Alex, you're up!
Go, go, go, go!
Knock 'em out.
Are you okay?
Aah!
Alex!
2x13 - Skin Deep
Original Airdate (FOX):  20 February-2006
"Desire" by Ryan Adams
# Two hearts fading
like a flower #
# And all this waiting
for the power #
# For some answer
to this fire #
# Sinking slowly #
# The water's higher #
# Mmm, desire #
# Desire #
# With no secrets #
# No obsession #
# This time I'm speeding
with no direction #
# Without a reason #
# What is this fire #
# Burning slowly #
# My one and only #
# Mmm, desire #
# Desire #
Wilson:
How'd you get here?
By osmosis.
No helmet?
Didn't seem like riding weather.
And the fact that you can
barely stand upright had
nothing to do with it?
- Infarctions hurt.
That's what they do.
- House!
Worsening pain could
actually be a good thing.
Means the nerves
might be regenerating.
Could be good,
could be bad.
Thanks for the differential.
Any other options?
Have you ever
considered a career
as a motivational speaker?
- Why don't you
check out some rehab?
- I did the rehab thing.
One session.
And you didn't even
finish that session.
The guy wanted me
to visualize the healing.
I can do that home.
At least let me
get you an MRI.
It's a very simple equation.
More pain, more pills.
Teenage supermodel.
Presented with double vision,
sudden aggressive behavior,
cataplexy--
You had me
at teenage supermodel.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Wow. You should be a model.
Are you really 15?
Who are you?
I'll be the one
saving her life today.
Assuming she's dying.
Who are you?
He's my father.
Any idea
what's wrong with her?
Well, from the looks of it,
not a single thing.
Probably should stop staring
and check out the file.
So, what set off the brawl?
She stand in your light?
I didn't even know her.
I didn't know
what happened.
Look, I know some models
are notorious for hissy fits.
But Alex, I've never
even seen her get angry.
Even when she was a kid
she was--
I'm sure she was
delightful in her youth.
And then you passed out.
I was passed out,
but I wasn't.
I knew what was going on,
but I couldn't move or talk.
Yeah, that sounds
like a medical thing.
It's called cataplexy.
Cat fight and cataplexy
on the catwalk. Cool.
How much
were you drinking?
She only had
one sip of champagne.
Forget it. We'll find out
from the tox screen.
All right, look.
I gave her a valium.
Do you think
that's what did this?
No. How long have
you had the sweats?
- A couple of days.
- Any other complaints?
Uh, my stomach's
been bothering me.
And I've been feeling
a little nauseous.
O kay.
Here's how this works.
My lackeys will be by shortly to
draw some blood, collect some urine,
any other fluids you got.
They'll do some other
doctorly stuff.
And we'll be in touch.
Since when do you
voluntarily go see patients?
- Have you seen her?
- She's 15.
Yeah, but there's
something about her.
Something in her eyes.
A kind of maturity.
Yeah, yeah. She's an old soul.
This is creepy even for you.
She's a fashion model
on the cover of magazines.
They hold her up
as the sexual ideal,
but the law says we can't
touch her for three more years.
How hypocritical is that?
Did the history reveal anything,
oh, I don't know, medically relevant?
History, right.
I  knew I was forgetting something.
You should do one of those
while you're running the labs
and the tox screen.
Labs show valium
and heroin in her urine.
A supermodel on smack.
Shocker.
Oh, Alex. I expected
so much more from you.
Heroin chic is
so five years ago.
Okay.
Let's start crossing out
withdrawal symptoms.
A positive test means
she tried it once.
Doesn't mean she's an addict.
She's only 15.
There's no age limit
on addiction.
He's right.
She's never menstruated.
Sounds like a symptom
of drug addiction to me.
Or bulimia. Or her age.
Some girls don't start
till their mid to late teens.
Evidence to the contrary.
The rounded hips.
The perfectly sculpted,
bountiful breasts.
Chase:
Implants.
I've seen some of her photos.
They've grown dramatically
since last summer.
Symptomatic of turning 14.
Two clinic hours says
that those love apples are
handcrafted by God.
Whoa! I thought
you didn't believe in God.
I do now.
You're on.
Could we talk about her health
instead of her breasts?
It could be relevant.
Come on, Cameron.
There's nothing
to be ashamed of.
Many women develop breasts--
No, I'm fine.
Even if she is an addict,
a lot of her symptoms--
the cataplexy, the violence--
they could be neurological.
We chalk this up to drugs,
we could be releasing her
with Juvenile MS or Parkinson's or--
So detox her.
Fine. We'll set her up on a program.
They'll wean her onto the methadone--
And in four weeks
we'll know you're right.
Or we'll know that Cameron's right,
and the pretty girl will do Milan
next Fall in a wheelchair.
Put her in a coma and
pump her full of naltrexone.
Cut the four weeks to one night.
The lab reports show that
your daughter had heroin
in her system.
Were you aware
of her drug use?
No.
We think she's suffering
from withdrawal symptoms.
Detoxing generally
takes several weeks.
The danger is that
if the drugs are masking
some of other illness,
it could worsen
before we've weaned her off
of the heroin.
Well, how much worse?
We don't know because
we don't know what's wrong.
There is a rapid
detox procedure.
We flush her system
with an opioid antagonist.
It'll end her addiction overnight.
But the process is dangerous
because we have to induce a coma.
It also means that if she ever relapses,
there's a good chance she'll overdose
because her body won't react to the drug.
So either way I'm--
I'm risking her life.
Do you have to tell her
how dangerous it is?
Is it dangerous?
There are certain risks.
We've gone over them
with your father.
And he's not worried?
He's your dad.
He's always gonna worry.
But he knows we're gonna
take good care of you.
Oh. Everything's starting to hurt.
My legs.
Heroin withdrawal is
an extremely painful process.
But we're gonna put you to sleep.
You won't feel a thing.
Promise?
I promise.
It was a pretty
stupid thing to do, huh?
Getting hooked on drugs?
Yeah, not the best move
you've ever made.
Alex:
I just--I thought
it would be fun.
C hase:
You don't have to
explain to us.
A lot of the other girls were--
When you wake up,
you'll feel a lot better.
[Monitor starts beeping]
Nurse. Nurse!
You son of a bitch!
You killed her.
- She's not dead.
- She had a heart attack.
She's stable now.
The anesthesia--
Get her out of that coma.
Don't think so.
Stop this. All right,
I-I don't consent anymore.
I want to do the slow detox.
Did you ever get a paper cut?
A really nasty one
between the fingers?
Multiply that by about a billion
and it'll just barely approach
the kind of suffering she'll experience
if we wake her right now.
We're committed to this.
She's out till morning.
Go get a book.
I haven't slept in weeks.
Because my teeth hurt.
Dentist couldn't find any cavities.
And I'm getting these headaches.
Oh, poor you.
I think I'm going crazy.
And my stomach.
I roll out of bed,
and I want to puke.
I take it your married.
You must be psychic.
You must be witty.
When's she due?
- How'd you know she was--
- Because I'm doing her.
You've got Couvade Syndrome.
Which is just
a fancy way of saying
you should stop whining.
Millions of women
have got the same thing.
They're not bugging me.
You're suffering from
sympathetic pregnancy.
Gotta go. People dying.
The whole circle of life thing.
- It's all in my head?
- Nope. It's all in your hormones.
Good  news is
no one's gonna lecture you
if you smoke and get drunk.
Shouldn't she be awake by now?
It's only been a half an hour
since we stopped the medicine.
Well, you said that's
how long it would take.
I said it would take
about half an hour.
Well, couldn't this
mean something--
So far, it means nothing.
She had a heart attack.
She could have brain damage.
She could have something--
She's opening her eyes.
Alex? You okay?
Can you hear me?
Hmm.
I got the cute doctor.
Huh. Do you feel any pain?
Good. Let us know
if anything changes.
If your stomach
doesn't feel right, anything.
Hey.
Are you mad at me, Daddy?
I let you down.
No, no. Not at all, sweetie. I--
I should've been more mature.
I should've handled the pressure.
Stop, stop.
We're gonna get you better, all right?
Nothing else matters.
Excuse me.
We've got you on
what we call a banana bag.
Plenty of vitamins, nutrients.
I got the cute doctor.
Are you mad at me, Daddy?
I let you down.
What's going on?
I should've been  more mature.
I should've handled the pressure.
What's wrong with her?
Anterograde amnesia,
short-term memory loss.
Evidence of a hypoxic brain injury.
Might be a result of getting cut off
from the oxygen when she flatlined.
Probably the result
of that rapid detox
you told us to push on her.
You gonna put that down?
You gonna sulk?
I'm not gonna indulge you.
Treatment of hypoxic
brain injuries consist of--
[ Exhales]
Cameron, Chase,
and the dark one.
Foreman, right?
Patient flatlined
for, like, 30 seconds.
Gotta be oxygen deprived
for longer than that
to lose brain function.
- We can't be sure
how long she was--
- Her brain's fine.
Memory loss.
You're saying that's
not a neurological symptom?
No, I'm saying
what I'm saying.
Her brain's fine.
She's faking?
She's got post traumatic
stress disorder.
We got models
fighting in Iraq now?
Show me a woman on heroin
who looks like that,
and I'll show you a woman
who's been sexually abused.
That's your proof?
That she's good-looking?
He manages her career.
Travels the world with her.
At her side 24/7.
He's either a very good dad
or a very bad dad.
House:
You saw that touckhus.
Would the fact that
she's your daughter
really stop you?
Oh.
Her brain is running
away from reality.
When the drugs
can't do it anymore,
it starts to shut down.
Your theory has the advantages of
being completely unprovable
and completely exculpating you.
When you guys are done talking,
do an MRI and an LP.
When her brain checks out
as normal, then we'll know that
Daddy really, really loves her.
Where's House?
Said he was
in too much pain to work.
Who's covering?
He called 15 minutes
after his shift started.
It's too late to find anybody.
- Exam room one.
- Ugh.
- Hi.
- Where's Dr. House?
Wish I knew. Huh.
What's the problem?
It's personal.
And it's so personal
he didn't bother writing
anything in your chart.
It's getting worse.
What is?
It's personal.
- Fine. You can wait.
- Doctor.
I tell you what.
I am gonna give you
Dr. House's personal pager number.
Why would your mind
go to abuse so fast?
'Cause I had a funny uncle.
You were abused?
What? No.
Why would your mind
go to that so fast?
I just had a funny uncle.
Great stories, always filthy.
I don't know
if it's something
with this case,
or you got something
personal going on.
The whole break-up thing.
- It's personal.
- House.
Your pain is affecting
your decision-making.
You got a problem
with a call I make,
question the call.
Don't make it personal.
Are you saying pain
can't affect your mood?
If I'm right about the pain,
you're gonna want
to rush everything.
Which is what you're doing.
Don't.
Thank you.
Are you doing your daughter?
What?
We should probably
talk privately, huh?
Come on, walk with me.
- I'm not--
- He's not.
I'm sure he's not.
She is a babe, though.
We're gonna need you
to keep still.
I am.
What do you think that means?
It's either neurological
or psychological.
The only thing we know for sure is
it's gonna screw up the MRI results,
which is gonna make
House think he's right.
This is a waste of time.
Let's just get the LP.
I should take your head off.
Your glands are fine.
See, now you're my patient.
You got doctor-patient
confidentiality. No worries.
So, what did you do to her?
- Why would you possibly think--
- Hard to imagine anyone
not wanting to nail her.
- You son of a--
- It's a compliment.
A heart-shaped ass.
Those perfect, perky
all-natural breasts.
That is my daughter
you're talking about!
No, that's your daughter
you were talking about.
"She just instinctively
knows how to walk."
"Designers just love
that heart-shaped ass,
those perfect, perky--"
I'm  her manager.
I have to promote her.
Oh, that makes sense.
So you compartmentalize.
When you're dealing
with the press,
you're her manager.
When you're helping
with homework,
you're her dad.
When you're making
sweet, sweet love,
- you're her manager.
- All right.
Do you love her?
- I have never touched her.
- Do you love her?
What are you doing?
You trying to trap me
into saying--
Do you love her enough
to admit that you slept with her?
Psychology conditions
can manifest themselves
in physical problems.
Sometimes, these can be
extreme enough to kill.
There are treatments, but
only if there's a diagnosis.
Are you gonna admit that
you slept with your daughter or
are you just gonna let her die?
One time.
PTSD.
Get her a psych referral and
pack her bags. He did her.
Don't think so.
Daddy thinks so.
Could be mistaken.
He said he was drunk.
Maybe it was
some other daughter.
Elevated proteins in her CSF.
You're wrong about PTSD,
and I was wrong about
the hypoxic brain injury.
Daddy didn't do this to her.
And neither did we.
We have to call
Child Protective Services.
Doctor-patient confidentiality--
Doesn't apply
in abuse cases.
You know that.
Cameron:
We're mandated
to report sexual abuse.
Is it okay
if I save her life first?
Or do you want to make sure
that Daddy doesn't get
visitation rights to the gravesite?
Okay, elevated proteins
in her CSF could mean
dozens of different things.
Viral encephalitis.
CNSV.
Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease?
So we're just gonna
leave a child molester
in the same room as his victim?
It's got windows.
Fine. Arrest him.
Use Cuddy's handcuffs.
If you're too distracted
to deal with this because
your leg hurts, then--
Yeah, I'm distracted!
I'm all hung up on
this 15-year-old patient
who's cataplectic,
can't remember what she had
for lunch, and is rapidly
losing control of her body.
And I want her father here
in case they got any more secrets
that I need to know about.
Now, if you're not too distracted,
go take out a piece of her brain.
Stick it under  a microscope.
Wilson!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You really think we need to
jump straight to brain biopsy?
Nope. Let's continue
playing pin the diagnosis on
the supermodel until she's dead.
Heard you killed
your supermodel.
Only for a minute.
Just for my own clarity,
how many more patients
do you have to kill
before you admit this leg thing
just might be a problem?
Three.
I need your help.
We're gonna do something
called a burr hole biopsy.
We drill a small opening
in the back of your skull.
Doctor, maybe you and I
should talk about this first.
No.
I just think Alex doesn't need
to be overwhelmed right now.
I think she should have a say
in what happens to her body.
We're gonna remove
a small piece of brain tissue.
Do--do you have to
shave my hair?
Hair grows back.
I guess I won't
remember anyways.
There's a good chance
the amnesia's only temporary.
Okay.
Find a way to
kick up the contribution.
What did House do now?
House, this is God.
Look, I'm a little
busy right now.
Not supposed to talk
during these things.
You got time Thursday?
Let me check.
Oh, I've got a plague.
How about Friday?
You'll have to
check with Cameron.
Oh, damn it.
She always wants to know
why bad things happen.
Like I'm gonna come up
with a new answer this time.
House.
Quick, God.
Smite the evil witch!
Are you sitting on evidence
that your patient was
sexually abused by her father?
God, why have you forsaken me?
Cuddy:
Don't worry. I've contacted
Child Services for you.
I left you get away
with more than anyone
in this hospital.
Shielding a child abuser
isn't covered.
Cooperate with
this investigation,
or I'll fire you.
Chase:
What do you think
House is gonna do to you?
No idea.
Well, you did the right thing.
If you hadn't gone to Cuddy,
I would've.
If this guy had known
we had to report him,
he'd never have told House the truth.
She's a child.
She needs to be protected.
She dropped out of high school
to make millions of dollars.
Why does she need more protection
than some crack whore shivering
in the clinic waiting room?
I think you're just
afraid to piss House off.
There's that too.
MRI looks exactly the same
as it did two years ago.
Nerves don't seem to be regenerating.
I figured as much.
Several different researchers
have proven psychological pain
can manifest as physical pain.
You think I have
a conversion disorder?
You want me to see a shrink?
Brilliant idea
sending Stacy away.
It's really done
wonders for you.
Listen, none of this has
anything to do with Stacy.
Right. Giant coincidence
that you've gone completely
off the rails since she left.
Inducing migraines,
worsening leg pain--
Ow!
Aw. You miss Stacy too?
Brain biopsy shows
no white matter disease.
Cameron, you gonna
go tell Cuddy?
Or has she already
got you wired for sound?
I had to do
what I thought was right.
So white is out.
That just leaves gray.
Foreman:
Neuronal ceroid lipofuscinosis.
Heller Syndrome.
Any one of
the mitochondrial
encephalopathies.
Am I in trouble?
You had to do
what you thought was right.
They call it gray area
'cause you never really
know what's there.
We can't test
for any of those things.
So I'm not in trouble?
You can torture
yourself all you want.
What if everything we're seeing
is just smoke signals?
Okay.
Who's sending them?
Tumor.
If has cancer anywhere
in her body, she could also
have paraneoplastic syndrome,
which would be causing
antibodies to attack her brain.
Antibodies are
stupid that way.
Paraneoplastic syndrome's
awfully rare in a 15-year-old.
15-year-olds who look
like that are awfully rare.
It would explain
the aggressive behavior, the cataplexy,
the memory loss, even the twitching.
It's perfect.
What if it's not?
We could waste weeks
searching for a tumor that
we don't even know is there.
Then let's make sure
it is there.
There's no test
for paraneoplastic syndrome.
Sure there is.
The squeeze the tube test.
What did the biopsy tell you?
It wasn't definitive.
But the twitching
should stop right about...
Now.
Oh, my God.
House:
Could've just
been a coincidence.
Twitching does
tend to stop and start.
Let's be sure.
IVIG vacuums her blood.
Neutralizes the stuff
that's making her twitch.
It's actually kind of cool.
Wonder if I could
make you dance.
Enough.
This is unbelievable.
You did it. You fixed her.
No. All I did was
prove that she has cancer.
I need a favor.
I'm not in a giving mood.
It'll help us both.
I need a shot
of morphine in my spine.
If your leg hurts,
take your Vicodin.
It's not enough.
Get a syringe.
Morphine is extreme,
even for you.
Yeah, read that
on the insert.
Get one of your lackeys to do it.
I don't want them knowing.
That you're on the road
to becoming a junkie?
That I'm in this much pain.
I don't want them
questioning my judgment.
I can't ask Wilson because
he figures it's all in my head.
Well, I agree with him.
I'm going home.
Well, what about this?
What are you doing?
Is this in my head?
'Cause I could swear I remember
a thigh muscle being here.
I'll get a syringe.
- It's gotta be cancer.
- It's not cancer.
You seem to be back
to your old miserable self.
So I just randomly predicted
she'd respond to IVIG?
Her twitches are gone.
Her memory's getting better.
What did you take?
If the increased pain
was psychological,
no drug's gonna help.
If you think it'll help,
the drugs will help.
- Power of the mind.
- You're right.
The more I talk to you,
the more the pain floods back.
Knew the twins were real.
Chase owes me.
- You check the pancreas?
- Oh, come on!
You're just making up
organs now, aren't you?
We checked the pancreas.
- Obviously you've taken something.
- You check the bones?
There are a lot of bones, I think.
And none of them have cancer.
Ovaries?
There's no mass.
If anything, they're undersized.
No leukemia, no Hodgkin's.
We checked everything.
Unless they've invented
a new organ, it's not cancer.
Differential diagnosis.
It's gotta be cancer.
There's gotta be
something we missed.
You gotta learn
to let go, Foreman.
Maybe the protein level
was some sort of anomaly.
It might still  just be PTSD.
Just PTSD?
Yeah, Daddy's diddling her.
Nothing to worry about.
Chase:
Okay, let me rephrase.
Maybe the protein level
was some sort of anomaly.
Oh, my God!
It might be PTSD!
If it was PTSD, the twitching
wouldn't have magically disappeared
when we started the IVIG.
Mmm, wrong.
What it wouldn't have done
was medically disappear.
Nothing to stop it from
magically disappearing.
She was watching me
stop and start the medicine.
You think she's faking?
Not consciously.
But if her subconscious is
trying to get away from it all,
cancer's gotta be a lovely vacation spot.
Tell her you've gotta
give her a fresh IV.
Don't tell her you're
starting her on saline.
We'll see if
the twitching comes back.
How long has
the social worker been in there?
Just went in.
She was in
with the dad before.
You switch the girl's IV?
About half an hour ago.
When is she gonna
start twitching?
If she's gonna start twitching,
another few minutes.
We've gotta wait
for the remaining IVIG
to clear her system.
That was quick.
What's gonna happen?
What did you think
was gonna happen?
- The father had sex--
- Do you have any
medical evidence of that?
- He admitted--
- He denies that conversation
ever took place.
- She--
- She denies it too.
I'm sure you meant well.
[Alex flipping through TV channels]
You have to tell her the truth.
Nothing happened.
You don't have to
be afraid of him.
They can protect you.
From what?
Things are fine.
You think things are fine.
They're not.
He's my dad.
He's abusing you.
He's not a bad person.
I seduced him.
You're the child.
He's the adult.
- He has the responsibility--
- I got him drunk.
I had to get him drunk.
I wanted to
have sex with him.
You're sexually
attracted to your father?
No.
But by sleeping with him,
now he lets me do whatever I want.
I also slept with my photographer,
my financial manager, and my tutor.
If I hadn't, I'd be getting Cs
and posing for newspaper ads
back in Detroit.
Hmm. Come on.
We all do it.
No, we don't.
After you father slept with you,
you were traumatized.
My dad was last.
You've never taken a run
at your boss or a professor
or somebody else you needed?
You're 15.
You're smart.
You don't have to--
I am not that smart.
I am that beautiful.
What's wrong with me?
Aw! George,
get your butt over here!
George:
Help me!
How did you get
my pager number?
Please!
Problem is
if I give you an epidural,
you won't be able
to feel when to push.
- You're not funny!
- Pretty sure I am.
You just can't appreciate it
because you're in pain.
George, if you don't
get off your ass and help me--
Oh, shut up!
Got yourself
the perfect man: a woman.
He's got more estrogen
coursing through his veins than--
Oh! Aw! Ohhhhhh!
- Who did her vaginal exam?
- I did.
Did she have hair?
What are you getting at?
Right now I'm getting at
whether or not she had hair
down there.
Uh, not much.
She manipulative
yet completely docile.
Everybody tells us
that outburst on the catwalk
was out of character.
She's never had a period.
You're thinking
this is hormonal?
I'm thinking
she's the ultimate woman.
I-I need to schedule an MRI.
The twitching stopped.
Because we changed your medicine
back to the real stuff. Stop talking.
You gave me fake medicine?
That's what I said.
In the vain hope that
you wouldn't feel
the need to also say it.
Stop talking.
Wilson already did an ultrasound.
Said her ovaries were undersized.
The ultrasound would be the way to go
if you were looking for ovarian cancer.
What are we looking for?
That.
Oh, my God.
Looks like a tumor, doesn't it?
But those are--
Yep.
We found a tumor.
She has cancer?
Technically, no.
So it's not cancer?
No, it's cancer.
But he has cancer.
On his left testicle.
I don't have testicles.
She's not a guy.
His DNA says you're wrong.
Frogs and snails
and puppy dog tails.
You've got male
pseudohermaphroditism.
See, we all start out as girls.
And then we're differentiated
based on our genes.
The ovaries develop
into testes and drop.
But in about 1 and 150,000 pregnancies
a fetus with an XY chromosome, a boy,
develops into something else.
Like you.
Your testes never descended
because you're
immune to testosterone.
You're pure estrogen.
Which is why you get
heightened female characteristics.
Clear skin. Great breasts.
The ultimate woman is a man.
Nature's cruel, huh?
This is obviously a joke.
This is--is impossible.
No, a joke would be
me calling you a homo.
See the difference?
I'll schedule him for surgery.
No. You're wrong.
I'm a girl.
Look at me!
How can you say
I'm not a girl?
See? They're all
looking at me. I'm--
I'm beautiful!
That anger,
that's just the cancer talking.
Put your clothes back on.
I'm gonna cut your balls off.
Then you'll be fine.
How's the patient?
Post-op.
I set him/her up
for a psych visit.
Calling her "him/her"
isn't really helping.
Good news is I don't think
Dad's gonna be sleeping
with him/her again.
See, now it's gross.
I need another shot.
When did the pain
start coming back?
A few hours ago.
About an hour after
you solved the case?
If I wanted to be psychoanalyzed,
I'd get Wilson to give me the shot.
Same dosage?
If you'd be comfortable,
I might be able to deal with
a few less cc's of morphine.
It wasn't morphine.
What did you give me?
- I told you I wanted--
- It was saline.
I gave you a placebo.
[Piano playing Bach's French
Suite #5 in G Major Allemande]
"Desire" by Ryan Adams
# You know me #
# You don't mind waiting #
# You just can't show me #
# But God I'm praying #
# That you'll find me #
# And that you'll see me #
# That'll you run and never tire #
# Mmm, desire #
# Desire... #
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : Vaccine
www.forom.com