Hey,guys!
Guess he got away.
Can baby shoes come out to play?
Come on.
Hands on your head,climb out.
I can't climb out if my hands are on my head.
Just keep 'em where i can see 'em,man.
Go 'head. Go 'head.Come on.
You high,popo?
Yeah,man.
Catchin' morons makes me high.
Take your shirt off by your collar and turn around.
Whoo,would you  look at that!
Dude's got a weapon.
All right,you have the right to remain...stupid!
Watch the gun.
Anything you say will be completely incomprehensible.
Seriously,man,careful!
Seriously,man?Seriously?
Your mama know what you do?!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync:YTET-Vicky8800
-=House=-
Season 2 Episode 20
Aww...that's sweet.
Your dad's proud.You made the local paper.
--From my article.
Give it a rest.
You read what he wrote in the margin?
"Our friend lazarus sleeps,but I go that i may wake him up."
He's not proud of me.He's proud of jesus.
Everything I do right is god's work.
Everything I do wrong is my own damn fault.
Cop with a sense of humor.
Differential diagnosis.
Guy's in the E.R.,Bleeding on everybody.
Drugs?
He's a cop.
Good point.How about...drugs?
Tox screen was clean.
He did,however,get hit by a bullet.
Just mentioning it.
He was shot?
No,somebody threw it at him.
I'm thinking trauma.He's got bullet fragments lodged in his brain.
According to baby shoes,the cop was laughing before he got shot.
Baby shoes?
--Guy who shot him.--Reliable witness.
His name is baby shoes.How bad can he be?
Fragments are in the wrong part of the brain to cause euphoria.
So let's expand the search.Factor in the cough and the cloudy lungs.
Why are we ignoring the elevated heart rate?--'Cause he's in shock.
What if the heart was already fast before he got shot?
You mean after the foot race?
He's giddy.Indicates a blockage of oxygen.
Carbon monoxide gas would elevate the heart rate
and cause coughing and impair neurological functions.
He got co poisoning outdoors?
Yeah.
All 'cause those bastards didn't ratify kyoto.
Or he got co poisoning indoors
and moved outdoors before he'd inhaled enough to make him drop dead.
Test his arterial blood gas.If his carboxy hemoglobin levels are higher than 15%,
stick him in a hyperbaric chamber.
You go check the cop car for gas leaks or--
if it was the cop car,his partner would be sick.
Well,maybe she is she just doesn't have as good a sense of humor.
Also check his personal cars,work,home.
I'll check the precinct.
Blood tests confirm you have low-level carbon monoxide poisoning.
We're putting you inside a high-pressure chamber to...
You don't really care,do you?
Do you live near a gas supply?
Uh,yeah,me.
After,like,a huge enchilada.
Anything toxic you have at your home?
Any paint solvents,anything unhygienic?
Uh,no.
No,I keep a pretty clean home.
If you start having trouble breathing,you can press this button,
and the chamber will decompress.
Like this?
Don't now.If you have trouble.
Ah,it's broken.
All right,well,if you have problems we'll push it for you.
Muscle contracture.
How bad does it hurt?
Not...not at all.
Looks wild,though,huh?
Your brain's not getting enough oxygen.You're losing motor function.
We should start this right away.
Should I be scared?
No,you probably have a carbon monoxide leak in your place.
We have a guy there checking things out.
Sounds okay.
How about the gas intake valve?
Looks great.
It's down in the furnace room.
Your system's fine.
If you had a carbon monoxide leak,half the force would be sick.
Then why are you here?
I was wondering if you could do me a favor.
Yeah.I've,uh...I've got a disability.
These are speeding tickets.
A lot of emergencies.
He's feeling better now,but...you never know.
I'll see what we can do.
Where's your partner sit?
Place is a cesspool,but I don't think I need to test for anything.
Nope,waste of time.
You know about the marijuana?
I've heard rumors since junior high.
The cop's acting high because he is high.
He's got--legionnaires' disease.
It's a good thing joe got shot.
The whole precinct would have got wiped out.Anarchy on the streets.
Takes 48 hours to test for legionnaire'S.
And only two seconds to recognize if the symptoms fit
while staring at the rancid,unchanged water of an ac unit.
Marijuana explains the high carboxy,the cloudy lungs,and the happiness.
Pot doesn't explain the fact that he's gotten worse since he was admitted.
Why don't we agree to disagree?
Actually,why don't we agree that you'll disagree with me
while treating him for legionnaire's?It's not as pithy,but...
I feel a lot better.The meds are working.
Heart rate's normal.Cohp levels are down.No fever.
Take some deep breaths.
You seem disappointed.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
You got a problem with cops?
Please don't talk.
In my experience,people who just don't like cops have a reason--
I need you not to talk.
No rales.
these clouded areas of the upperobes...they're the infiltrates we found yesterday.
Not there anymore?
They're clearing up.You had legionnaire'S.
Now you don'T.
So you didn't,um...you didn't find anything at my place?
Nothing...medically relevant.
So there's,uh...there's nothing I need to worry about,then?
Not this time.
Whatcha doing?
I want to make sure he sees what's involved.
What we found was fairly advanced.
These cloudy areas here,and here.
These parts of your lungs simply weren't functioning.
They're okay now,right?
Everything's okay now?
I'm fine.
You're blind.
I bumped into something.That doesn't mean I can't see.
I'm sure it's frightening,but you only think--
what's dr. Cameron wearing?
Dark blue pants,white shirt.Black shoes.
Ooh,almost.'Cept for the pants,shirt,and shoes.You're blind.
he really thinks he can see?
He can physically see.His brain just can't process it.
No chance this is a practical joke?
No way.
Anton's blindness indicates damage to both occipital lobes.
Must be from the trauma.
Bullet fragments just happen to hit the same spot in both lobes?
Stroke could cause anton's blindness and euphoria.
Office krupke is clotting in his brain.
Start heparin to thin the blood,find the clot,and yank it out.
Clot would be at the top of the bilateral vertibral arteries.
Great.Chase...stick your fingers in there,grope around till you find it.
Oh,wait...when you turn him into a vegetable,
then there's gonna be frivolous lawsuits.
You know what would be better?Contrast mri.
Do we have one of those?
You can't do an mri.If the bullet fragment's magnetic,
they'll move and rip his brain apart.
Well,let's flip a coin.
Heads,mri;tails,he dies.
The police issue kevlar vests don't have the ceramic plate insert
that would shatter a bullet,they would just catch it.
So the bullet shattered on its own.
Meaning baby shoes was using 0.38 caliber hollow points.
Which,unfortunately,are ferromagnetic.
It's just so cool that you know that.
We could do an angio to find the clotting.
Waste of time.The skull creates too much artifact.We'll never get a decent view.
Next best thing to an mri.--And a waste of time.
Angio might show--oh,god,it's a coup!
Fine!Go do your angio.
When you're do wasting your time,meet me down in the morgue.
we're going to snake a catheter in your femoral artery
and up into your brain so we can check for clots.
Keep this on throughout the procedure.
Unless the pot's already made you sterile.
I have a stressful job.You got no idea.
I grew up with cops like you.
One part bully,nine parts hypocrite.
what is wrong with you?
Just having some fun.
That man is sick and scared.
The man's a crooked cop.
Maybe you should take yourself off the case,foreman.
Don't have to like someone to be their doctor.
Hey,how you doing there,buddy?
Just sit still and we'll have you back out there scaring the crap out of people in no time.
Happy?
What did the angio tell us?
What are you looking for?
I called my mom.She didn't pick up.
What did the angio tell us?
That foreman should be off this case.
he's a neurologist.
Unless you think the patient's optic nerve is in his spleen...
he doesn't like cops.
foreman,policemen are our friends.
If you and I ever get separated shopping--
I was just busting the guy's chops.
See?--He was just busting the guy's chops.
Foreman is essential to solving this case.
Medically,what did the angio tell us?
Appears to be some clotting,possibly around the circle of willis.
Based on the progression of symptoms,the clot is growing.
We need to cut into--
saying there appears to be clotting is like saying there's a traffic jam ahead.
Is it a 10-car pileup or just a really slow bus in the center lane?
And if it is a bus,is it a thrombotic bus of an embolic bus?
Think I pushed that metaphor too far.
Angio can't tell us that kind of information.
Oh,so you're saying it's just a waste of time.
It gave us some information without killing him.
You don't know that an mri will kill him.
The bullets have a ferrous base!
Little tiny pieces trapped in his head.They're not going anywhere.
maybe it's worth attempting surgery to remove the fragments.
Surgeons say inoperable,or the patient's on blood thinners.
Other than that,perfect planning.
You got a better plan?
Much.
Bullets identical to the one that baby shoes popped joe with.
Let's see how magnetic it is.
Did anybody hear a--
I shot him.He's dead.
the bullet split into four fragments,no exit wounds.
Only used a half load of gunpowder.
We won't be exactly precise comparing the location on an x-ray to an mri.
How unprofessional was foreman?
As him yourself.He's right here.
worse than usual.Better than you.
He berated joe for being a bad cop.
Berated or humiliated?
I'm not sure.I didn't have my thesaurus with me.
One implies that he took pleasure in it.
I wanna know if it was repressed black anger or just giddiness.
You think I'm sick?
I think that an appropriate response
to watching your boss shoot a corpse is not to grin foolishly.
But the fact that I've grown bored by your insanity is proof of nothing.
Dr. Foreman,dr. Chase requests your assistance.
I can't even imagine the backwards logic you used to rationalize shooting a corpse.
Well,if I'd shot a live person,there's a lot more paperwork.
Then it won't be a problem for you to stand beside the casket at the wake
and explain why a cancer patient has a bullet hole in his head?
The man donated his body to science.
Yes,it's a tragedy. If I hadn't shot him,his body could have spent the next year
letting first-year med students use the carpool lane.
He's set.
Do not turn that on,house.
You're mad because I put a bullet in his head.
At worst,all I'm doing now is taking it out.
My bad.
They have to,uh,shut down the magnet to fix it.
Mri is gonna be out of commission for at least two weeks.
Well,it doesn't matter.
We obviously can't use it on this patient.
no...but there are other doctors in this hospital,and other patients.
That helps explain how they can afford all the fancy equipment.
I'm sure i'm pulling my weight.
Is doing nothing an option?
I'm just saying.Maybe the clot will break up on its own.
The giddiness seems to have gone away.
The blindness hasn'T.
Echo his heart.
Looking for what?The problem is obviously neurological.
The clots are in his brain.The source of the clots may not be.
Do a complete transthoratic echocardiogram.
Maybe we get lucky.Maybe the clots are coming from his heart.
heart's clean.
Where else can we look?
We could ultrasound his legs,look for a dvt.
I need you to move over.
Joe?You okay?
Tachycardia.Heart rate 150 and rising.
He's bleeding out.
House wanted to thin his blood.Sure did a good job.
Bp's crashing.He's going into shock.
Intracranial bleeding.We need to relieve the pressure.
We need a surgical team.
Foreman,get out!
boy,is he screwed!
We clot his blood,he dies.We thin it,he dies.
Am I the only one who finds this funny?
Oh,man.
i'm not sick!
Did you hear the one about the guy who bled into his brain
and had to have a hole drilled in his skull to relieve the pressure?Hilarious!
Someone laughs,they're dying?That's absurd.
But not funny.
If I'm not sick,all you're doing is locking me up with the source.
I'll get sick,prove you right.
If you're not sick,it's not contagious.You've got nothing to worry about.
If you are sick,the two of you are staying in there until we find that why.
So you might want to make friends with the pig.
Good news is I can finally get my mri.
No,you can't!
You blew up the machine!
Not the portable one,chuckles.
Chase and cameron are bringing it to scan your non-bullet-riddled head.
Wh-where are you going?
To the office.Got work to do.
Eat your meals.
Take your temperature every half hour and any meds i command you to take.
So I'm just a regular patient now?
No.
You get your own thermometer.
Check your blood.
Anyone with an elevated sed rate gets to be foreman's new roomie.
He should be a part of this.
He's a patient.
He's not irrational.--He's not objective.
He's got the most motivation to get this diagnosed.
Right,you're not even friends with him.Why would you care?
There's an area of increased t2 attenuation in the cingulate cortex.
Kind of...mushy.
Cingulate cortex controls emotions.
This mushy spot explains the euphoria.Question is,what's causing the mush?
Question you might want to ask a neurologist.
Foreman is a selfish jerk,but he's a neurologist,
and he's the only one who's been in that apartment.
This is why he shouldn't be here.
You wouldn't call him a jerk if he was here.
If you think he screwed up at that apartnt,you'd keep it to yourself.
No,I--well,we'll never know.
But as long as he's not here,he's just like any other patient.
Which means we can dumpn him all we want.
What's eating the selfish jerk's brain?
West nile or eastern equine encephalitis--test foreman's blood.
Given that he's the only one who got it,
person-to-person transmission is
less likely than some sort of deadly toxin foreman picked up at the guy's home.
Who wants to go next?
You're ready to sacrifice yourself for a guy who doesn't consider you a friend.
He's just a patient,right?It's the job.
Hey...you don't have to go anywhere.
Joe's apartment is right downstairs in the lab.
Foreman brought back samples of everything.
What was that,"who wants to go next?"
Some kind of...test?
Don't worry.You made the right call.
Foreman stumbled into whatever it is without knowing.
He's way smarter than you are.
Damn,chase!
You suck at this.
Sorry,it's this damn suit.
I can do it myself.And I'll throw that out.
What'd the mri show?
I can't be a part of the differential,and I can't even know what the differential is?
You'd tell any other patient what you found out.
Mri showed a lesion on your cingulate cortex.
What's the thinking?
Toxins are in the lead.
Viral's a distant second.
Do you think the lesion could be an abscess?
It's just a small,soft area,more mush than--
was there inflammation in the lining of the ventricles?
There was an increased signal there,yeah.
What are you thinking?
Staph infection.
Toxins lead to neurodegeneration,which causes the lesion.
Not without a fever.
The cop had a fever.
Mine could be coming.I could have got it directly from him,
or a dirty dish towel at his place.
Give us omaya reservoirs. Deliver linezolid directly into our brains.
And we're cured.
samples tested negative for toluene,arsenic,and lead.
what about the blood?
Negative for west nile and eastern equine.
We have to go back to joe's apartment--
no one goes back to that place till we know what we're looking for.
Get some of that cop tape.Stick it over the doors and the windows.
I'll take all the hazmat precautions.The chance of infection is next to nothing.
I was never that great at math.
But next to nothing is...higher than nothing,right?
It's not your fault he got sick.
It would be his fault if we did.
We should get a sample directly from joe's brain.
We can't do a biopsy.
There's too much edema from the bleeding because you gave him heparin.
Well,I don't think this is the time to be pointing fingers.
I didn't give foreman any.
You want to give foreman a brain biopsy?
Come on,really,who doesn't?
This could be a simple staph infection causing neurodegeneration.
Without a fever?Not a chance.
Joe had a fever. --He also had legionella.
The mush might be forming an abscess.
And since there was inflammation of the lining of the ventricles,it makes sense.
The staph releases toxins,causes neurodegeneration,causes a lesion.
This is a waste of time.
We should put an omaya reservoir in foreman's brain and start administering anti--
if I'm gonna be arguing with foreman,I may as well do it directly.
Kernig's sign,negative.
Brudzinski's sign,single positive.
Patient joe luria,distal and proximal arm contractures,
duration four seconds.
Staph infection most commonly presents on the skin.
Most commonly?
You wanna treat me like any other patient,do it.
But the house I know never uses phrases like "most commonly."
You're not laughing anymore.
No.
Think that's a good thing?
Sorta doubt it.
Staph would be in your heart,lungs,spleen,liver,or kidneys before it gets to your brain.
Your organs are clear.It's not staph.
The infection could be limited to a brain abscess.
Which I would have seen in your mri.
Sign this so that I can take out a piece of your brain.
Let me see the mri.
There was no abscess on the image.
Let me see it,then.
I liked you better when you were jolly.
Mri was taken over an hour ago.
That soft spot could now be an abscess.
If it was staph,you'd have a fever.Which you don't!
101.6.
What idiot gave you that?
Put the omaya reservoir in my skull and treat me for the staph.
triangle.
this one?
Uh...circle.
Next.
Foreman,why aren't you answering?Is there a problem?
Uh,s-square.
tell me your date of birth.
Is that house?--yeah. Next.
A square again.Why is he here?
Because my neurologist is having surgery.
Thought I was just another patient.
You didn't believe that crap,did you?
Date of birth.
The omaya reservoir is inserted in the parietal lobe.
My spatial recognition is the issue,not my memory.
Did you say omaya?
I could have sworn you said biopsy.
Hey,I'm just messing with your head.
Mother's maiden name,please.
Get out of my temporal lobe,house.
Hello?
Are you awake?
They told me somebody was sick like me.
I'm up.
Your voice...
aren't you my doctor?
Not anymore.
You're the guy who doesn't like cops.
Yeah.
Can you see?
You can't?
Not a thing.
You've been blind a while.
The fact that you're aware of it now...
it could be a sign of improvement.
It hurts so much.Doesn't it?
I'm okay.
It's gonna hurt.
The morphine barely takes the edge off.
I'm gonna die,aren't I?
You die,I die.It's not gonna happen.
Why not?
You're just too stubborn to die?
They took a piece of my brain.
Whatever's wrong with us...they'll find.
Do you believe in prayer?
Not really.
Neither do I.
My dad always prays.
So does mine.
Do you wanna try it?
Try prayin'?
Okay.
How is he?
Still dying.
Well,you've almost mastered another skill,though.That's good.
Foreman's biopsy results.
Non-specific signs of inflammation.
That's it?
We also swabbed for staph.Negative.He's not even a carrier.
Well,at least foreman was wrong too.
Yeah,there's that.
Can I go to joe's apartment now?
No.
Go back to the lab.
Start retesting all the samples that foreman collected.
For what?
Everything.
Bacteria,toxins,fungus.Anything that likes to feast on brain.
That's thousands of--
better hurry.
Cameron,suit up.You're gonna monitor foreman.
He's on to hand contractures.He'll be in anton's blindness soon.
Run hourly checks,because when he does go blind,he won't be able to tell us.
We'll use the data to construct a timeline so we can see how far behind joe he is.
Why are you still here?
You're being cautious.
You're being...common.
When you don't give a crap about--
how many of your guys have caught cancer from their patients?
Let me know when that happens.Then we can have this conversation.
It's just another case,huh?
Gee,I bet you can even have unprotected sex
with your cancer patients without catching a damn thing.
Boy,I wish I had your job.
Biopsy showed nothing.
How can there be nothing?You cut out a piece of my brain.
It's nothing personal.We just didn't find anything.
Can you up his morphine for god's sake?
He's already maxed out,20 milligrams per hour.
What about toxins?
Everything was negative.
There was a cupboard above the stove.Did you see it?
I didn't check all the food,but could be listeriosis.
We didn't go back.Follow right.
Who did?
House said we shouldn't go.Too dangerous.
The answer's gotta be in that apartment.Not going is too dangerous!
I'm sorry.
You're thankful.
If house would have pointed at you instead of me,you'd be the one in here.
Look straight forward,tell me when you can see--
it's your job to go back!You're a doctor!You go where the disease is!
Say when you can see the light.
I'm dying,and you're sitting here measuring how fast I go?
Tell me when you can see the light!
My vision's fine!
Your left-side periphery is reduced.
It's fine,I'll prove it.
Ow! Son of a bitch!
Now we're both exposed.
You got two choices.
You can go tell house what just happened and get your own cot board in here,
or you can go back to that apartment...
you save me,the cop,and yourself.
it's not sspe.I checked your past vaccinations against joe'S.No batch matches.
Blood show antibodies for coxsackievirus?
Guys,could you please shut him up?
He's over his limit on morphine.
Where's cameron?
She said she has some stuff to do.Said she'd be back soon.
what are you doing?
Foreman!
Stop!I can't take it!
Imagine being constantly reminded of the...pain you're about to be in.
I can't take it!Stop it! Stop it!Stop it,stop it.
Mainline morphine into his carotid could stop his heart!
So could pain-induced stress cardiomyopathy.
Either the morphine kills him or the pain does. --You're condoning this?!
I'm certainly not going in there to stop him.
That'll make you feel better.
Joe has a new symptom.Hyperalgesia.
The infection's spreading to the pain center of the brain.
Make it stop!Make it stop!
His brain's telling him that his whole body's in pain,
and because of the location,the painkillers do nothing.
Suit up.Put the guy in a coma before the pain kills him.
What if he used cedarwood to hide the pot smell?
Aureobasidium fungus could grow there.
Did you find any cedarwood anywhere?
No,but maybe--maybe what?
Maybe somebody could go back,take a second look?
And why aren't you pissed off that cameron's playing hooky
while your life hangs in the balance?
Why doesn't anyone listen to me anymore?
I decided you were wrong.
God,you're weak.
Guy steals your article...
tells you you're not his friend...
and you still want to risk your life for him.
Foreman broke my skin with a tainted needle.
Yeah.
God,you're weak.Guy tried to kill you.
First thing on my list of things to do would be to stab him back.Shoot him.
I've got a gun in my desk.
Last thing on my list would be to lie to my boss about it
and then give the bastard everything he wanted.
I'm not here for foreman.I'm here to save myself.
even with a needle stick,your chances of infection are pretty slim.
That's why you're wearing the suit.
You wanted to be here.
He just gave you the excuse.
What does that guy have to do to make you hate him?
Give me the bag.
Mildewed dish towel.--To retest for staph.
What is that,mouse droppings?
Hamster droppings.Could carry toxocara.Explain the blindness.
Now,that I recognize as oven crud.
Could be meat with trichinella.Would explain the high fever.
What's with rye bread?
Mold could be responsible for ergot poisoning,which would explain the contractures.
There are three loaves.--So?
You're going back in there.
Guy who lives on take-out pizza does not buy three loaves of rye.
That's looking too far into the future.
Unless he cares about something a lot more than his diet.
You on the roof yet?
Yeah,I'm here. I don't see any birds.
Whistle or something.
Do that come hither thing.
they came that fast because it's their behavior pattern.
Joe's been feeding them.
Now look down.You see a river of pigeon turd?
Uh...no.There's barely any.
It's not weird,it's cheap.
Joe's a guy whlooks for the easy way.
Probably been stealing cable from his neighbors.
Why not steal fertilizer from rats with wings?
You see a shovel or a dustpan?
Mmm,found a scraper.Looks used.
Sitting on a bucket.
Bucket full of pigeon crap.Perfect home for cryptococcus neoformans.
Yep.
Fungus enters the brain through the sphenoidal sinus,
where it dances its triple threat of happiness,blindness,and intractable pain.
Let's hope this experience teaches our cop a lesson.
Don't cut corners when you're growing your pot.See you back home.
I was there.
I should have found it.
Yeah,you could have saved us a lot of time.
Get me a flush of ampho b and flucytosine.
I'll start us both.
I was waiting for lab confirmation.Haven't heard from house yet.
Look at his eeg.
Theta band's been increasing steadily since--since we put him under.
Guy's unconscious,but still in pain.
Theta bands could indicate at least half a dozen different things.
One of which is pain.
The fact that he's no longer screaming makes us feel better,not necessarily him.
Chase!How's cameron?
She's not giddy.
Fever's down.White count's improving.
Has she said anything to you?
You mean like,"I completely understand why foreman did what he did,and I hold no grudge?"
What I did...did save my life.
Get in here and help!Forget the suit!
He's tachycardic!Wide-complex looks like v-tach!
It's not cryptococcus!
What?--House was wrong.The samples were negative.
So what is it?
We don't know!--Give him in the amio.
Do we have any more leads?
that was our lead!Foreman!
So the treatment isn't doing anything.
Foreman!He's in v-fib!
No good.Hit him again.
Come on,man.Come on,joe.
Hit him again!
give him an amp of epi!
Nothing!
He's has multiple-system failure.
Foreman.
Come on,joe.
foreman!Time of death.
No.
Time of death.
12:26 pm.