Deep fried shrimp, and lobster.
Never had lobster.
What, do you boil 'em or grill 'em?
Which one's better?
Ah, just get 'em both.
And I know I need a strawberry malt,
and then there's those
chocolate donuts that come in a box?
We'll do our best to accommodate.
Tomorrow you'll be moved to a holding cell.
That's where you'll get your last meal.
You also have a constitutional right to
the spiritual advisor of your choice.
Naw, I don't need none of that.
One last thing to think about:
After I read the execution warrant,
you'll be given an opportunity
to make a statement.
You might want to take some time
and think about what you want
to say as your final words.
Yo, Clarence! You hear that?
A spiritual advisor of my choice! He-he.
Don't matter, you goin' to hell anyway.
You think I'll get another stay?
You should. Supreme Court say it ain't right to kill retards.
Cut the chatter! Exercise time.
Be back in an hour. Enjoy.
Why did you hit me so many times, Clarence?
You know why!
You could have stopped.
You stabbed me in the back, man.
- I never st...
- You couldn't fight fair.
Like you did?
I had a wife and three kids.
You are a sick bastard!
Open the door! Open the door!
Hey! What'd I ever do to you, man?
2XO1- ACCEPTANCE
Original Airdate 13-SEP-2005
You can't go in there.
Who are you, and
why are you wearing a tie?
I'm Dr. Cuddy's new assistant.
Can I tell her what it's regarding?
Yes. I would like to know
why she gets a secretary and I don't.
I'm her assistant, not her secretary.
I graduated from Rutgers.
Hmm. I didn't know
they had a secretarial school.
Well, I hope you took some classes
in sexual harassment law.
Does the word "ka-ching"
mean anything to you? I'm going in now.
Dr. House, we are in the middle of a meeting.
What's with hiring a male secretary?
JDate not working out?
He is cute. Be careful.
She's not like you.
She can't just walk into a bar and
pick up her soul mate in twenty minutes.
I met Mark at a fundraiser
that happened to be held at a...
You met me at a strip club.
You were the worst
two dollars I ever spent.
We'll catch up later.
Stacy, it's House.
I know you can handle it.
Nothing to handle. It's obvious
he wants to talk to you alone.
If you have a problem working
with Stacy you should have said so.
What was I supposed to do?
Ask her to leave?
That's just rude.
Death row guy.
I want the case.
How do you even know about him?
You don't have access
to the hospital's mainframe.
No, but "partypants" does.
You stole my password?
Hardly counts as stealing;
it's a pretty obvious choice.
Well, I have already assigned
Death Row Guy to Dr. Nolo.
Nolo? Well, I don't want to say
anything bad about another doctor,
especially a useless drunk...
You are addicted to pain pills.
But I'm not useless.
Tell Nolo I'm talking over.
Dr. Nolo is a board certified cardiologist.
Oh, good. I'm sure he'll explore all the usual
options for why a guy's heart starts beating
so fast it pumps out air instead of blood.
Wait a second...
there are no usual options!
How badly do you want this?
I will give you
two more clinic hours this week.
Don't bend over for the soap.
Cameron: Just the heart, or
the patient have any other complaints?
The patient's not talking to anybody.
Where are we going?
You are going to
the clinic for two hours.
Me? Why?
Talk to Cuddy.
She's got me going to
Mercer State Prison,
Capital Sentences unit, I don't know.
Aren't there better ways
to spend our time?
Good question.
What makes a person deserving?
Is a man who cheats on his wife
more deserving than
a man who kills his wife?
Uh... yeah. Actually, he is.
What about a child molester?
Certainly not a good guy,
but he didn't kill anybody.
Maybe he can get antibiotics,
but no MRIs. What about you?
What medical care should you
be denied for being a car thief?
Tell you what: the three of you work out a list
of what medical treatments a person loses
based on the crime they committed.
I'll review it when I get back.
Your patient shanked
one inmate his first month here,
broke another one's neck,
nearly decapitated one of my guards...
Relax, I've got a great bedside manner.
Too dangerous to
house him in the infirmary.
You don't have to worry,
we've taken every precaution.
I've had my men clear from the cell
all pens, paperclips and staplers.
Any supplies that
might be used as a weapon.
Open her up!
For your visit,
we've got him cuffed and shackled.
And yet, you're staying out there.
Uhp! You're going to
have to give me that.
Wouldn't want anybody to get hurt.
- Hi. - Hi.
- I'm Dr. Cameron.
How're you feeling?
Eh. Little cough, no big deal.
Okay, then.
What're you doing here?
I just got a job at the university.
They need a health clearance.
Apparently I'm a little anemic,
so they made me get some more tests.
- Any family history of anemia?
- Not that I know of.
My mom died of cancer
when I was a kid, my dad's heart
gave out a couple of years ago.
Brothers and sisters?
I'm afraid it's a short
family history. That's it.
I had a husband once,
but... didn't stick.
My tests should be back,
probably in that file.
Probably.
Is everything okay?
Wilson:
Did you redo the x-ray?
Twice.
Well, you don't need a consult.
You know the diagnosis.
All she has is a cough.
Bluish tinge to the fingernails,
lips... he's hypoxic.
What's that mean?
He's not getting enough oxygen.
You know how people say
you can't live without love?
Well, oxygen's
even more important.
He's got fluid in his lungs,
breathing rate of 50...
he needs to be intubated
and put on a respirator.
Don't have a respirator.
Better get one in about an hour,
or you're gonna lose him.
I'll make out a requisition.
The state's already
sentenced this man to die.
I think the state was
a tad more specific about "how".
This is Dr. Gregory House.
I need an ambulance to pick-up
at Mercer State Prison.
Wasted call, my men
will stop them at the gate.
No way a Death Row inmate
leaves my prison,
least not through the front doors.
You work fast.
So do you.
- Is that a shock?
- Yeah.
It was easy.
Once I convinced the clerk
to take it to Judge Markem,
she's a sucker for
Eight Amendment arguments.
Stop, I'm getting turned on.
House!
Ruh-row!
It was just a consult?
You expect us to shut down
an entire floor for this guy?
Did you do something to your hair?
Stacy?
You said you cleared with her...
Come on. You've known me
how long and still you can't tell
when I'm joshin' ya?
Take him back to prison. Now.
No, can't. Ironically,
I'm bound by this court order
which your ace attorney got.
I have to make him all better
before shipping him back
for the state to kill him.
Is it just me,
or is that weird?
Anyway, we're walking.
Somebody left this on my chair.
It's clever. 'Cause it forces me
to either deal with the file
or never sit down again.
Cindy Kramer.
I told her you'd see her.
You shouldn't have told her that.
She's got metastatic squamous
cell lung cancer, six months, tops.
Have you even looked at the x-ray?
No, just guessing.
It's a new game.
If it's wrong,
she gets a stuffed bear.
A spot on a x-ray doesn't
necessarily mean that she's terminal.
I love children.
So filled with hope.
It could be pneumonia.
It could be sarcodosis.
Could be, if she didn't already have
swollen hilar lymph nodes
on the other lung.
Could we at least
brainstorm for other ideas?
Thank you.
I still think it could be
pneumonia and sarcodosis,
but we should
check for tuberculosis
and definitely rule out
congestive heart failure.
The five stages of dying.
Exactly. Personally, I think
it's all just new-age crap,
but from your tear-filled,
puppy-dog eyes
I think I've made my point.
Now go tell Cindy
Whatever-her-name-is that she's dying.
Tachycardia,
pulmonary edema, likely suspects?
The Death Row guy?
That's who you're working on
instead of Cindy?
God, I've got to learn
not to beat around the bush.
By dying, I mean
no matter what we do.
Very, very soon
she is going to be dead.
Is it still to subtle?
I took an oath to do no harm.
Yeah, well, it's not like
they make you sign it or anything.
We cure your patient,
he goes back to Death Row.
He goes back to
Death Row, they kill him!
He stays here and
we don't treat him, he dies,
and I still don't treat
Cindy Lou-Who.
Can we get on with this?
Yeah, I knew I could count
on your help for your homie.
Exactly, I'm black.
I sympathize for guys
who grew up in the city
kept down by the man.
Makes sense to me.
It's a bunch of crap.
You can't blame society for the fact
that you chose to become a killer.
The guy's probably a heroin addict,
which explains the tachycardia,
which caused the pulmonary edema.
How does an inmate on Death Row
get his hands on heroin?
Are you serious?
The man knows prisons.
When we've got a yachting question, we'll come to you.
Okay, drugs it is. Test his hair,
blood, and urine, the works.
Thanks for getting my back.
I thought you seminary boys
were against the death penalty.
I left the seminary.
Over their stance
on capital punishment?
I'm against
the death penalty in principle.
In practice, however,
watching a murder die causes me
a lot less grief than annoying my boss.
Guard: We gotta
check you out before you go in.
Department of Justice statistics
show that it's a racially
motivated form of punishment.
Black defendants are
ten times more likely to get
a death sentence than whites.
Doesn't mean we need to
get rid of the death penalty, do we?
It just means we need
to kill more white people.
It's okay, you're in a hospital,
we're taking care of you.
Chase:
Stay calm, you're gonna be...
push two milligrams Atvan!
Water... water.
What's the differential
for being thirsty?
He was just a little dehydrated,
and out of his mind.
We upped his saline drip,
he's fine now.
Blood and urine tests came back clean,
no sign of opiates in his system.
Don't do that.
What, you have some
House theory explaining
heroin use despite a negative test?
Nope.
Only I get to write on the board.
So it's not drugs.
What else can cause
the heart to do wind sprints?
Got the blood work back, any...
...thing out of the ordinary?
His bi-carb is low.
Yeah, but which column?
Could be the result of the tachycardia,
could be the cause?
It's the cause.
Why, because you want it to be?
Let's see how well that works
with your other patient.
We're just talking semantics here.
We should put him
on a bi-carb drip and send him back.
Right, buff his numbers.
Don't bother trying to
figure out the underlying cause.
I thought you cared about patients.
Foreman:
Our job isn't to make sure
he can bounce his grandkids on his lap,
our job is to get him healthy enough
to go back to Death Row.
Our job is to diagnose him.
What?
Mommy and Daddy are having a little fight,
it doesn't mean we stop loving you.
Now, go outside and play.
Get Daddy some smokes
and an arterial blood gas test.
Wow. That was impressive.
Okay, what number am I thinking of?
Were you trying to get me fired?
If you didn't want me working here,
why didn't you just say so?
I just don't want you
working here, in my office.
But anywhere else
in the building is fine.
- It's a big hospital.
- I'm a lawyer. You're a jerk.
There's gonna to be some overlap.
God, I hope that was a euphemism.
Cuddy just reamed me.
- I hope that one means
what I think it means.
- For trusting you!
She figured when she hired me
she'd at least have someone
you couldn't walk all over.
The number was six,
by the way.
I need to know,
can I trust you?
If I hadn't lied to you
about Cuddy's approval,
my patient would be dead.
Great.
Now I know.
Now we can work together.
I'm drawing some blood
from your femoral artery.
- From my what?
- Runs through your groin.
You think you're gonna stick me
in the jewels with that?
It's really closer to your thigh.
Technically, at this point,
it seems like your jewels are
more for display purposes, anyway.
Hold up, hold up. Give me
some pain killers, or something.
Tough guy like you don't need 'em.
Forget that, numb me up, man.
You got some gang ink?
Let me see that.
It's a Native American symbol.
It means "the force of life. "
That's what you tell
all these white dudes
so they let you play doctor?
Yep. Got 'em all fooled.
For real, how a brother like you go
from gang-banger to wearing a white coat?
How's a guy like you go
from loving a woman
to punching her skull in?
Bitch stepped out.
Argh!
Sorry about that.
Guess I didn't use enough lidocaine.
Blood gas came back with
a pH of 7.28 and decreased HCO3.
Which means two things.
Most importantly,
Cameron was wrong about the bi-carb,
and less significantly,
we have a new symptom.
Anion gap acidosis.
Who's chubby? Come on,
pretend he loves puppies.
Pretend he's a human being.
What've you got?
I think we should
reconsider drugs.
He already tested negative.
That's why I said reconsider.
Back in juvie, I cut up
oregano and sold it as pot.
Is that how you put yourself
through med school?
What if Clarence thought
he was taking heroin,
but it was something else?
What "something else" could
lead to anion gap acidosis?
Mudpiles.
Well, you don't have to ask.
Just wash your hands
before you come back.
Methanol, uremia, diabetes...
Oh, it's a mnemonic.
That makes sense, too.
Paraldehyde,
INH, lactic acid...
- Rewind.
- INH?
Yahtzee!
Drugs for tuberculosis.
Nearly a quarter of the prison
populationis infected with TB.
Clever entrepreneur like Foreman here,
chops up his meds, passes it off as heroin.
INH poisoning would
explain all the symptoms.
Who wants to head over to the prison
and find Clarence's secret stash?
- Fine, I'll do it.
- Great, Chase it is.
I assume you have
a reason beyond wanting to
make me completely miserable?
You've got a prettier mouth.
Better chance the inmates
will open up to you.
Perhaps I'll come out
looking just as monsterous?
I mean, isn't that what I deserve?
John, it wasn't your fault.
The man's in a coma.
He didn't mind.
- I asked.
- You're getting crumbs all over him.
Why do you think they put TVs
in coma patients' rooms, anyway?
Some people think
they can still hear.
So leave them a radio.
His eyes are closed;
who thinks he can see?
You know why people
are nice to other people?
Oh, I know this one. Ah...
Because people are
good, decent and caring.
Either that, or people are cowards.
If I'm mean to you,
you'll be mean to me.
Mutually assured destruction.
Exactly. You're gonna eat these chips?
You gonna get to your point?
You need people to like you.
I don't care if people like me.
Yes. But you need people to like you
because you need people.
Unless you think you can get
the next court order yourself.
If Stacy can't trust you,
you can't use her.
And that's not even dealing
with the greater agenda...
of getting her to dump her husband
and fall in love with you all over again.
I know you're friends with her, but
there is a code.
Bros before hos, man.
- Crap.
- What is it?
Death Row guy is dying.
Bradycardia. His heart rate's
dropped to 30, it's not going
to hold that much longer.
Are you just waiting to call time of death,
or are you gonna give him atropine?
Foreman:
Temporary fix?
Right. Anyway, those diabetics
are all hung up on insulin.
They're just gonna
have to take more.
Atropine's only gonna
buy you a few hours!
We don't even know
what's wrong with this guy...
Just get out of here.
This is Chase.
Did you beat any confessions
out of anybody?
I haven't spoken to any inmates.
Does anybody do their jobs anymore?
I've decided Clarence's life
isn't worth risking mine for.
I appreciate your candor.
Did you even go to the prison
or are you just out playing polo?
I'm searching both Clarence's cells.
I figure, if he's on something,
it's stashed somewhere.
Unless he finished it.
Yeah, that'd be a shame.
He could have shoved it anywhere,
there's envelopes stacked to the ceiling,
bottles of copier toner, boxes of rubber bands
Call it off.
Come on back.
What's going on?
You're dying.
That deserves a last drink.
You're okay.
Thanks. That means a lot.
All the tests have been inconclusive?
Diagnostics is more of
an art than a science.
Should I be worried right now?
I work for one of the top
diagnosticians in the country.
We're pouring all of our
energy into figuring this out.
Thought you convicts
knew how to drink.
You're at least three shots behind.
Now you're four shots behind.
You better give me
the next one or I'll kill you.
House...
I was just waiting
for test results, I was...
Little busy right now.
Getting my drink on.
Unbelievable.
Oof. That's the finest piece
I seen in ten years.
I could've hit that.
And you didn't.
Eh.
Then you're the one
that should be locked up.
Tell me something,
I've been trying to figure this out.
Why does a guy...
...who's on Death Row
suddenly try to off himself?
You know, you drank that copier fluid.
It's not as visually dramatic
as slitting your wrists
with a homemade shiv,
but it'll do the trick.
It just hit me all of a sudden.
It was like, they tell me
when to eat, when to sleep,
when to walk, when to talk, everything.
I had to take control
of something, right?
When you die,
I figured that was
as good as anything.
And that thought just came to you.
Just like that.
Man, I told you.
Twenty-three hours a...
Mmm. Well, look.
Here's the good news.
The copier fluid you drank
contains about 90% methanol,
which is very poisonous
and you took more than
enough to kill yourself.
The bad news is
the alcohol you drank
contains so much ethanol
that it's gonna bind with that
nasty formic acid raging through your body,
and you're just gonna
pee it out. Harmlessly.
Man, you are drunk.
Yes, I am. I also saved your life.
Ha! At least for now.
Morning!
Your head hurt?
No, you just have
a very grating voice.
You always were a light weight.
Why are you talking to me?
Can't it be enough that
I want to cause you pain?
The patient's okay now,
you're going to send him back?
Absolutely.
Can I trust you?
You used to.
I still think the patient's sick. I'm keeping him here.
Now, either you can do your job
and keep the hospital informed, or
you can help me make sure
the hospital is not informed
and buy me some time.
Chase:
Have you done a CT?
Yeah, I have?
Does it have contrast?
She's done everything she needs to do
except tell her patient that she's dying.
I told you, only I get to
play with markers.
Our prisoner has a new symptom.
I'm not telling Cindy that she's dying
until the diagnosis is confirmed.
I am not buying that
CLARENCE is trying to
take control of his life by suicide.
Healthy people don't kill themselves.
Healthy people don't kill other people.
Guy just filed an appeal
in a state that hasn't actually
killed anybody in about 30 years.
What if it wasn't suicide?
What if it was an escape plan?
Drink enough methanol to
get transferred to a hospital,
try to escape from here?
Excellent. Explains everything,
except the symptom that got him here.
His heart went nuts
before he got stuck in that storage cell
and chugged a toner martini.
I think there's something
going on in his head.
Check for intracranial lesions,
brain infections, autoimmune diseases...
do a CT, LP, full workup.
State's paying, so go nuts.
Where'd you get these scars?
I got shived my first month in.
After I healed up I got my ass.
You guys still think I'm sick?
Obviously.
Why you care?
Why don't you just let me die?
I'm different than you.
Right, you love me
like your own mama.
That's why the nurse says
you kicked her out
when my heart nearly stopped.
Take a deep breath.
Any family history
of mental illness?
I always heard my pa was crazy;
I never met the man with
my mom, it was the drugs.
Any siblings?
I got a brother,
pretty much raised him on my own.
Inspirational story.
- He doin' time, too?
- Hey.
He's a good kid.
Don't go judgin' what you don't know.
How's his health?
I haven't heard from him
since I went inside.
Spent 16 years with him,
changed his damn diapers.
Can you imagine your whole life
bein' about the worst thing you ever did?
You killed four people.
Somehow, making mac and cheese
just the way he want kind of
loses its significance.
Oh no. Now you've left
your entire body in my chair.
What does that mean you want?
I need a segmental
bronchoalveolar lavage.
I take it the CT
with contrast came back.
- They're not definitive.
- Biopsy would be.
Biopsy would be
invasive and unnecessary.
And definitive.
But you don't want definitive,
you want to hang on to your
delusions as long as you can.
A lavage could prove
it's not cancer.
But you need me
to approve the procedure.
Must be a bitch.
The answer is no.
Why? Because it's me?
I'm over you.
I've jumped on the bandwagon.
I hate you, okay?
Great. Let's treat her.
What is it?
You won't help Cindy but you're
obsessed with this piece of dirt!
Are you just trying to prove that
who someone is doesn't matter,
that all that matters is your stupid puzzle?
Fine. Treat them the same.
That's all I'm asking. One test.
Wow, that is remarkable.
According to those
patchouli-oli selling new-agers,
it's supposed to be
the terminal patient,
but you're going
through the five stages.
You just made a completely
seamless transition
from anger to bargaining.
Cover two more of my clinic hours,
you can have your one procedure.
No lesions, no aneurysms.
Ironically, the mind of a killer
looks completely normal.
If someone asks you
to describe me to them,
what's the first thing
you'd tell them?
Insecure.
What are you asking?
Like, if you were setting me up
on a blind date.
Would you describe me
to the girl as the black guy,
a neurologist, car thief?
This guy's really
getting to you, isn't he?
There's no sign of infection.
You're gonna have to do the biopsy.
Cuddy:
Your Death Row guy's still here!
Yeah, sorry.
Just gotta get him stabilized.
Probably keep him on fluids
for a few more hours, then off he goes.
Oh yeah? 'Cause I'm figuring
that you still think he's sick.
Figuring requires deductive reasoning.
I'm figuring that you did no figuring.
Stacy just ratted me out, right?
So much for attorney-client privledge.
I'm the client, you moron.
Stacy has a duty to this hospital.
- Right.
- I'm sending him back to prison.
Whoa, can't. Court order.
Court order says he has to
be declared healthy.
Doesn't specify what doctor needs
to make that declaration.
- What is it, Clarence?
- My gut!
Would you describe it
as a shooting pain?
A throbbing pain?
Or maybe an imaginary pain
because you don't want to
go back to prison?
Where does it hurt?
My gut, I feel like
I'm getting stabbed!
Well, he'd know.
Let me take a look.
Oh, so everybody lies
except a convicted murderer.
I don't think he's faking this stuff.
What do you think, Doctor?
I didn't have any choice.
No, you had to tell Cuddy.
She's your boss, I get it.
Hitler thought he was
doing the world a favor, too.
Yeah, pretty much
on that same level.
Gandhi didn't march the sea
because his buddies asked him too,
Pol Pot didn't wipe out the teachers
because he wanted to make friends.
You're not making
friends right now.
I trusted you.
I know.
Wilson's a fool.
I'm an idiot.
I had to do
what I thought was right.
It's the only reason
anyone does anything.
The surgery went fine.
They removed almost
a foot of necrotic bowel.
They're shackling him
and taking him to recovery.
I wonder.
I wonder why Clarence
killed that second inmate.
Fine, I'll bite.
What the hell are you talking about?
Everything we do
is dictated by motive.
Why did he kill his girlfriend?
Because he's a maniac!
Is that the reason he gave?
She was cheating on him.
Jealousy.
That gets him sent to prison,
where he kills inmate number one. Why?
Guy attacked him first.
Revenge.
Who'd he killed after that?
Prison guard.
Got a file full of abuse complaints.
Probably been kicking
Clarence's ass for months.
Clarence is just ridding
the world of bad seeds.
Call that one "retribution".
Then he kills inmate number two.
Anybody know why?
Nuh-uh. It's not in there.
All of a sudden
I got to have a reason?
It's an anomaly.
Doctors love anomalies.
Dark spot on an x-ray,
bright spot on an MRI...
Killing that second inmate
is the homicidal equivalent
of blood in the urine.
It doesn't fit.
I'm interested in
things that don't fit.
Tell me why you did it.
Your other victims
you were almost bragging about.
What was different
about this guy?
It happened
when I was in gen-pop.
I was in the library, just readin',
and I started feelin' real nervous.
This guy was staring at me,
I could feel his eyes.
Digging holes in the back of my neck,
made me feel crazy.
Sweat was pouring
down my face.
I could hear my heartbeat
racing in my ears.
I just raged out on the dude.
So what's the differential for raging out?
Excess testosterone, steroids...
Adrenaline...
Prep Clarence for surgery.
Care to share with the class.
Oh, come on.
Do I have to spell it out for you?
Pheochromocytoma.
Actually, I'm not sure how you spell it.
But you said it yourself, adrenaline.
Pheochomocytoma sits
on top of the adrenal gland,
randomly spits out oodles of the stuff.
It's perfect, it explains everything.
The tachycardia, pulmonary edema,
the vasoconstriction that cause
the necrotic bowel...
Even explains how he had
the strength to rip the rail off his bed.
But pheo's extremely rare.
I love rare. Set up an MRI.
Where's Cameron?
Like I don't know.
Dr. Cameron?
Could I borrow you for a consult?
Bittersweet thing about being
head of the oncology department,
I get CCed in all the biopsy results.
Yeah, I know.
She's terminal.
Yeah. So I take it you were
in there informing her?
Well, I... I hadn't exactly
gotten around to that, but I was just...
Doing what?
Making friends?
Cindy's divorced.
She doesn't have any kids,
no siblings, both her parents are gone...
It's not your job
to be her friend.
Do you understand?
And it's not worth it.
She feels better her few final days,
and you're not the same, maybe for years.
You don't think it's worth it.
I know it's not worth it.
My husband w...
I met him just after he was
diagnosed with terminal brain cancer.
If I hadn't married him,
he was alone.
When a good person dies,
there should be an impact on the world.
Somebody should notice.
Somebody should be upset.
Pheo what?
I don't even remember.
It's just a fancy way of saying
small, adrenaline-secreting tumor.
Yeah, that clarified it for you.
All you need to know is
if I'm right, we can fix it.
Just need to find it.
We need an MRI.
It's completely painless for most people.
But not for me?
I assume you got
those tattoos in prison.
Prison tats often contain
inks with heavy metals.
The MRI's basically a giant magnet.
It'd suck those metallic inks
right out of your skin.
Stop squirming.
Don't make us do this again.
Big baby.
Still don't see anything.
Clarence:
Turn it off!
There's Waldo.
Found it, Clarence.
Clarence:
Turn it off! Turn this damn thing off!
Keep him in there
until you guys see it too.
Son of a bitch.
Looks like they got
the pheo out successfully.
So what now?
Clarence goes back to Death Row.
Just like that?
He's cured.
That tumor caused random shots of adrenaline,
which obviously led to the rage attacks that
made him a murderer in the first place.
By God, you're right!
Let's call the surgeons,
we've got to save that tumor.
Put it on the witness stand.
We could testify
at Clarence's appeal.
You smell that?
I think that is the stink of hypocrisy.
You wouldn't even consider the notion
that Clarence's social upbringing was
responsible for what he became,
but now you're sprinting to
the witness stand to blame
everything on a little tumor.
A person's upbringing and their biology
are completely different.
Yeah. See, you only
overcame one of them.
Well, let's just give
Clarence a free pass, hmmm?
Course, you're probably going to
piss off all those other pheo sufferers
who managed to control
their rage attacks and become lawyers,
race car doctors, and even doctors.
Removing that tumor puts a stop
to those random shots adrenaline,
but doesn't absolve him.
You want him to be executed?
That's not what I'm saying.
Got an opinion?
Everyone's got an opinion.
I, uh, I think I'm gonna testify
at Clarence's appeal.
You'll do what you think is right.