This is awkward.
The cute, smiley, popular girl.
I think she murdered me.
So, you think that
if a girl likes me,
there must be something
wrong with her.
That's not what we're saying.
Dad!
She's my little...
Why are the coppers after you?
I didn't mean to hurt them.
I didn't mean to hurt anyone,
especially not you.
What are you doing?
Bruno!
You killed him!
# TCHAIKOVSKY:
Dance Of The Sugar Plum Fairy
How would you describe your ability?
I call it lacto-kinesis.
What's it like being called
the world's first superhero?
That has to be
the shittest power ever.
# The city breathing
# The people churning
# The conversating
# The price is what?
# This place is heaven
# If you see them! #
Hey, man.
I can't believe
this guy has gone public.
You better believe it.
Because he's going to
make a fortune.
Maybe we should think
about doing the same?
The early bird catches
the massive pay cheque.
Nice cock, man.
Fuck off.
I don't think going public's
a good idea.
Look, we finish our community
service in two days. Count them.
I don't know about you,
but I'm not exactly swamped
with lucrative job offers.
We need to think about
cashing in on our powers.
I mean, I'm immortal.
I shouldn't be flipping burgers,
I should be eating burgers,
massive burgers,
the size of my head.
Think about it, we could have
really cool superhero names.
Captain Invincible.
Mr Backwards.
I sound retarded.
The Invisible Cunt.
Why do I have to be
the Invisible Cunt?
Because you just are, man.
Get over it.
I mean, what's the point in
all of us having superpowers
if we can't use them
to make obscene amounts of money
and shag loads of drunk,
impressionable girls.
It's clearly what God intended for
us. I for one will not let him down.
Simon!
What?
What's going on
with you and Jessica?
After what happened with her dad,
she said she can't see me, so...
Seeing a girl
whose dad tried to kill you...
it's never going to work.
You'll meet someone else.
Trust me.
What was that?
They know what about us.
Who?
Everyone.
What are you talking about?
There are reporters and
TV cameras outside, lots of them.
Bullshit.
No way.
Are you serious?
Right. I think
I might take a little peek.
Don't open the door.
That was really
quite a lot of reporters.
How did they find out about us?
What? No, I didn't do anything.
I don't think I did.
I'm almost certain I didn't.
You!
You told them about us.
Yeah.
You sit on your arse
doing nothing for six weeks
and then you sell us out.
Looks like that, doesn't it?
Is that ironic?
Never too sure.
You're our probation worker.
You're supposed to sort us out.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Like you give a shit.
That's a good point. See you.
Where you going?
Antigua. Hm.
So, this is goodbye,
so long, and fuck off.
Wanker!
I'm actually very surprised
that it hasn't happened sooner.
We haven't really been that careful.
What are they going to do to us?
They'll treat us like freaks.
They'll lock us up
in a secret military facility
and conduct experiments on us.
Hey, no-one's experimenting on me.
I'm not a monkey.
What are we going to do?
We have to go into hiding.
We assume new identities.
We break off all connection
with our family and friends.
We wear disguises
and only go out after dark.
I'm not loving the sound of that.
Do you expect me
never to see my mum again?
Who's going to do my washing? Huh?
You have not thought this through.
There is an alternative.
Who are you?
I'm the person who can make it
so you don't need to go into hiding.
If this is handled right,
you're all making some serious money.
What are you thinking?
This isn't why we got our powers.
No. There is no why,
there's only what.
What are we going to
spend all our money on?
None of us even know
what we're doing after.
It's better than signing on.
What about the people we killed?
I guess we should ask her
about that. -Yeah.
I'm not saying we have,
but what would happen,
hypothetically speaking,
if it came to light that we may
have killed one or two people?
Probation workers and such.
No-one important.
I would say that these people
you may or may not have killed
were evil.
You were protecting society.
You're not murderers.
You're heroes.
Superheroes.
Rich, famous superheroes.
And if that doesn't work,
we vanish the bodies
and pay off the relatives.
Good answer.
Sign us up.
Good.
We're making a mistake.
We should all stick together.
Just do it with us.
This will change everything.
Call me when you change your mind.
I don't know.
Do you trust her?
They're waiting for you.
They're calling you the ASBO Five.
I haven't even got an ASBO.
No-one cares.
OK, any questions you don't want
to answer, just let me handle it.
Teeth, good.
Hair, beautiful.
Cock, in.
Flies, up.
Let's go be famous.
Hello, ladies!
Phew!
Laura, hi.
Have we heard anything from the
French about this cheese deal?
Do they know what I can do?
They know. They're calling
you Monsieur Grande Fromage.
Mr Big Cheese.
Can we do this later?
I'm really busy right now.
Have you got it?
Take her straight to the hotel
and don't let her talk to anyone.
How wonderful.
No, we're very excited.
Ah!
Jesus!
Sorry.
Why are you skulking
around in my bathroom?
My parents are freaking out
about the invisible thing.
I didn't have anywhere else to go.
Can I stay with you?
Sure, man.
Hang back a few minutes, though.
I'm just going to go
slip these girls one before
they sober up.
Sorry I'm late.
I was just enjoying the fruits of
our new-found fame and celebrity.
You know I'm not actually
talking about fruit.
Although you should see the
size of my fruit bowl... Massive!
Did you shag those skanky girls?
I most certainly did.
Loving the canapes.
I was just saying, if there's
anything you don't want to see
in the papers, tell me now
and then I can deal with it.
Everything about me has
already been in the papers.
Do any of your
ex-boyfriends have
any intimate photographs
or videos of you?
I'll delete them.
Make sure you do.
Right. Is there anything
else I need to know?
Yes?
Just before I started
my Community Service,
- there was an incident with this girl...
- What kind of incident?
Really?
I picked her up in this
dentist's waiting room.
She was having
some kind of oral surgery.
So we go out -
a few drinks, a couple of kebabs,
then it's straight back to her place
and start with the shagging.
I've built up a nice rhythm...
I'm getting really close
to blowing my load,
just hovering in the pleasure zone.
And then BAM! All hell breaks lose.
I tripled myself.
I'm not familiar with that term.
You know... Tripling.
It's when you cum, puke and shit
yourself all at the same time.
Fuck's sake!
Three bodily functions.
Doing the triple.
You're telling me that's
never happened to you?
No.
Anyway, I lied about my name,
so she probably doesn't even remember me.
I don't think she's ever forgetting you.
Anyone else?
I shagged a monkey.
Technically, it was a gorilla.
What are we doing here?
I wanted you to meet my other clients
and also some potential sponsors.
Just relax and enjoy yourself.
I should mingle.
Laura.
Down the wrong way.
Hi.
Good to see you.
Oh, you're that milk guy, innit.
It's not just milk.
It's all dairy products.
So you're here to
make the coffees then?
I'm done making other people coffee.
People make my coffee now.
So what's the point
in having your power?
Were you one of those fat kids
who had milk seeping out
of his man boobs during puberty?
No.
We had a kid like him at our school.
We used to milk him every lunchtime.
I wasn't one of those kids.
Get off me - what are you doing?
I'm milking you!
Get off!
This reminds me of school.
That was some good times.
Fuck off!
That's what the kid at my school used
to say and he had a nervous breakdown.
Nathan.
How would you feel about
blowing your brains out
live on national television
tomorrow night?
Yeah, I am definitely up for that.
Another please.
Hi.
Be nice to him, yeah?
I'm not promising anything,
but I'll definitely try.
Maybe a tuxedo - what do you think?
Why not? They're planning to
film it at the Community Centre.
Right. It's like a whole
going back to my roots kind of vibe.
Daisy! Daisy!
Excuse me.
Who's she?
That's Daisy.
More and more people with
powers are coming forward.
What can she do?
She can heal people -
any illness, any disease,
she plans to cure the world.
She's like a pretty, modern day
Mother Theresa with a superpower.
She is going to make a fortune.
Daisy! Daisy!
That's far enough...
No, no, let him through.
What's your name?
Neil.
I'm just going to
touch your legs, OK?
Steady!
I'm walking.
Thank you.
Hi, honey.
Where are you going?
There's somewhere I need to be.
I thought you liked me.
Well...
So now there are other people with
powers you're not interested in me?
There's a guy downstairs
who can rewind time.
You can do stuff with milk.
I'll show you what I can do.
What are you doing?
What is that?
That's the Greek yoghurt
you ate earlier.
It's moving up into your trachea.
You think I'm a nobody.
You're nothing.
Oh Jesus, no!
There's puss seeping out of my cock.
Ugh!
One of those three girls, or the girl
I shagged in the toilets at the club,
one of them had
poor personal hygiene.
This is a catastrophe of
tsunami-like proportions.
No girl in her right mind is
going to have sex with that.
You should ask that
Daisy girl to cure you.
Right.
She wants to cure the world,
she can start with my cock.
'We'd just found that other boy's
body stuffed in the locker and then
'Curtis grabbed my hand
and he's all like,
' "Oh, I wanna bone you,
I wanna shag you senseless." '
'This was just the beginning.
'The five young offenders
soon found that
'each of them had been
affected by the storm.
'Afraid they would be
outcast from society,
'they swore a pact of secrecy...'
Oh, for...
Hi.
Hi. Come in.
Right.
It's Nathan, right?
Right. I just wanted to swing by and
say hi, as one superhero to another.
That's really sweet of you.
So, how mad is all this?
Totally mad. And look at you,
with your wonderful, amazing power.
I saw what you did with
the guy in the wheelchair.
That's like curing two
normal people. Double points.
And so...I was wondering...
if you could maybe help me out
with a small, personal
affliction of my own.
Of course.
What is it?
Well...
I appear to have contracted
a sexually transmitted
disease of some kind.
I honestly don't know how I got it.
I'm sorry. I don't do
sexually transmitted diseases.
No?
Because of the rubbing.
Go to the doctors. They'll
give you some antibiotics.
And how long will that take to work?
Out there, there are loads of
drunken girls, staggering around,
waiting to be shagged. Do you
really want to disappoint them?
I'm sorry. I'm just not
prepared to spend my life
rubbing other people's genitalia.
C'mon. Just give it a quick rub.
It's lovely and clean.
It's pine forest fresh.
I'm not going to rub your cock.
Where's your humanity?
It's not going happen.
OK?
No. That's fair enough.
I suppose have only myself
and the dirty bitch
I had sex with to blame.
What's that?
That's my Mother Theresa, Young
Humanitarian of the Year Award.
It's for the charity
work I did in India.
Good for you,
and good for Mamma Theresa.
God rest her beautiful soul.
Myself next year myself.
Gotcha!
Urgh!
Get off!
Oh!
Fuck, what have I done?
Hey...look...just...
heal yourself! All right?
Heal yourself. That's it.
Rub it better, now, rub it better.
What did you do?
It was an accident.
She was rubbing my cock.
She started foaming at the mouth,
she tripped, and impaled herself
on her Mother Theresa, Young
Humanitarian of the Year Award.
I know it sounds unlikely...
But there it is.
The police are going to
want to interview you again,
but they seem to be satisfied
that Daisy's death was an accident.
Oh! Thank you!
I just want to say...
it's a tragedy.
And no-one is more upset
about this than me.
But what's done, is done.
I think we should all move on, huh?
Stronger, fitter, wiser.
This could only happen to you.
She was going to cure the world.
There's only so many times
I can say I'm sorry!
And if you're so cut up about it,
why don't you...
..And fix this entire situation?
You know it doesn't work like that!
- I'm getting pretty sick
of hearing that! - Prick!
You fuck up like this again,
and I will finish you.
I'll try not to.
I'll tell you something, though.
It's all cleared up.
You know... Down there.
As clean as a new pin.
If you're still in hiding, you should
probably do your invisible thing.
Oh, hey!
You're alone?
Uh-huh. So are you all right then?
I thought I'd feel
like we'd made it.
You know, all this fame stuff.
It just...
feels a bit... pointless.
Of course it's pointless.
That's why famous people pretend
to care about the Africans.
- He knew it would be like this.
- Who?
Simon.
We should've listened to him.
Do you know where he is?
No. No, I haven't seen him.
Nuts?
He said picking up litter
was the best time of his life.
I think that demonstrates
his rather low expectations.
If you see him,
tell him he was right.
Cheerio.
What's up with you?
I never said that,
about picking up litter.
When was that taken?
Where did you get that?
Someone gave it to me.
Who?
What is this place?
The guy in the mask...
He lived here.
Who is he?
It's you.
You came back, so that we could
be together in the future.
You...
And me...
We're together?
Yeah, we were,
and we will be again...
I hope we will be.
You think you're surprised?
Imagine being me!
You're still you,
but you're different.
You're more confident, and...
My power doesn't work on you.
You can touch me.
And then I die?
You saved my life.
You said
if you didn't come back and die,
you wouldn't become
the person you needed to be.
It's like in Terminator, when John
Connor sends Kyle Reece back in time
so that he can be his father.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
You protected us.
You're like a proper superhero.
When do I turn into this superhero?
So what happens now?
I have no fucking idea.
I don't understand.
Since this whole thing
with the storm went public,
I've been taking
on new clients all the time.
The truth is, I don't have time
to represent you any more.
I'm sorry.
# DELIBES: The Flower Duet
What are you doing?
That's the cheese you had earlier,
slowly clogging your arteries...
OK, stand by for rehearsals, please.
If blowing my brains out
live on national television
doesn't get the ladies juiced,
nothing will.
How do I look?
Like a prick in a suit.
That's sexual jealousy,
because of my prowess as a lover.
Is it true
you shit yourself when you die?
That only happened the once.
And I've got a bucket standing by,
just in case.
Do you want that?
Just lost my appetite...
No, I'm lactose intolerant.
Does that mean you're afraid of cows?
No. It means I don't eat
cheese or dairy products.
Oh. I never knew that about you.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
We'll talk later, yeah?
Have I got time to go to the toilet
before you shoot yourself?
A piss, yes. A shit, probably not.
I'll come with you.
Oh, gross!
What's that?
There's something dripping
from the ceiling. I dunno what...
Kelly?
Quit dicking around.
Ah! Christ!
Sorry, man!
What fucking prick did that?
This guy really is
the most unbelievable tool.
I told you.
Roll titles.
Live in 20.
Going live in five, four, three...
And now, for your viewing pleasure,
I will blow my brains out,
live on national television.
Enjoy.
Alisha?
Kelly?
What is that?
It's milk.
That milk guy?
We need to get to the hotel.
Oh, shit.
No!
And that, boys and girls, is how
you shoot yourself in the head.
I wouldn't recommend
trying it at home.
I'm not being funny, but you might
want to fuck off out of here.
I'm expecting some seriously horny,
barely legal groupies
knocking on that door any second.
They're walking into a trap.
What's that?
The milk guy.
He's got Alisha.
What? When did this happen?
He killed me, Nathan.
I'm fucking dead.
Curtis, wait!
Alisha? Nikki?
Curtis?
You nipple-sucking, breast-feeding
momma's boy! You killed her!
Does that feel strange?
You can't...kill me.
I'm...immortal...
I'm not trying to kill you.
That's the mozzarella wrapping
itself around your central cortex.
You're going to spend the rest
of your life as a vegetable.
Nathan?
Why did you do it?
Because the only time people like me
really get noticed
is when we kill
a shitload of people.
They'll talk about this for years.
They'll talk about me.
Monsieur grand fromage!
That cheese shit won't
work on me, dickhead.
I'm lactose intolerant.
Then maybe I'll just
have to stab you instead.
They're all dead.
You have to save them.
We have to go back to before we were
famous. We have to stop him. Do it!
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
What?
There's something we need to do.
That's it, then.
It's over.
No more community service.
I thought we'd be, like,
all celebrating and shit.
It doesn't really feel
like there's much to celebrate.
I just want you to know...
being here with all of you, it's
been the best time of my life.
I had a week in Spain last year.
That was way better.
What is up with all of you?
All the shit we've been through.
We're all here. We're all alive.
We made it.
Great(!) And I have no job,
no money, no girlfriend,
nowhere to live, no useful skills or
qualifications. OK, so I'm immortal.
But other than that, I've
basically got fuck all going for me.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
Or the day after that?
Huh? We have just been shat out
onto a huge pool of piss with all
the other long-term unemployable.
Does anyone fancy a drink?
Yeah, sure, man.
Y'know, apart from all the killing
and the dying and stuff,
this community service really wasn't as
bad as I thought it was going to be.
# I don't know what's happened
to the kids today
# I don't know
what's happened to the kids today
# I don't know what's happened
to the kids today
# I don't know
what's happened to the kids today
# I don't know what's happened
to the kids today. #
I can give you your life back.
There was this guy took my power.
You sold your powers?
Yeah, mate.
That's how babies get turned into dwarves.
I like dwarves. Me too.
My waters have broken!
The baby's coming!
I'm Jesus Christ,
and I have been reborn.
Where are you going?
I'm going to kill Jesus.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd