Previously on Lost:
- You killed Naomi!
- She wants her people to come here.
And trust me, when they do,
we had better be far away from here.
If you want to live,
you need to come with me.
- Who are you?
- Daniel Faraday.
I'm here to rescue you.
This is the team? These are the
wrong people for a mission like this.
None of them have field experience,
military training.
You can't drop them in unprotected.
There's only so much I can do.
Where's the chopper?
Where did it crash?
What kind of pilot do you think I am?
I put her down safe and sound.
- Get up. You're coming with us.
- We need to stay where we are
- so they can find us.
- See, there's your problem.
We don't want to be found.
You want to know why we're here?
I'll tell you why.
We're here for Benjamin Linus.
Now where is he?
Did Ben mention knowing
anyone off the island?
- You're sure of that?
- This is real simple.
Do you know where he is, or don't you?
- What do you want with him?
- I want to locate him.
The people who hired me told me
his name's Benjamin Linus.
They gave me this picture,
that's all he told me.
They said find him.
And for what they're paying me,
I don't need to know anything else.
Do you?
You want Ben? OK, he's with Locke
and your friend...
- Charlotte.
Locke's got her too.
We know where he's heading.
Locke's the guy that killed Naomi.
Give me back my gun, Shephard.
You want your gun back, I want answers.
You don't trust me, I don't trust you.
You're supposed to be dead.
Am I asking a billion questions? No.
We both have the same problem,
this Locke guy.
Even if Locke has your friend,
you can't waltz in there and grab her.
- They're armed.
- How about that? So are we.
- Why don't we move out?
- You're not going anywhere.
- Will that helicopter fly?
- It's what she does.
- Then you can take me to your ship.
- Sayid, wait a second.
We did call these people
to get us off this island, didn't we?
Well?
I burned a lot of fuel coming in.
I can't carry much weight.
- I'll take three of you.
- In case you zoned out
while tweezing your goatee, one
of these yahoos took Charlotte prisoner.
I can bring her back safely.
And if I do...
will you take me to the ship?
Absolutely.
You bring Charlotte back safe...
...and I will take you off this island.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
It's a long walk to the next hole.
Do you need a ride?
Thank you, but no.
My ball is right here.
You're the first person I've seen
out here all morning.
I believe we're paying quite a premium
for that kind of privacy.
Indeed, we are.
Is this your first time
in the Seychelles?
I'd use the five iron.
I think I'll stick with the seven.
Tell you what. 50 euros says mine
goes closer to the pin with a five.
Let's make it 100.
Amazing, huh? How we wager.
Makes just about anything more fun.
Not bad.
So, what do you do for a living,
my friend?
- I do nothing.
- Nothing?
Doesn't pay for a vacation here.
I was the recipient
of a large settlement.
- Corporate merger?
- Actually a plane crash.
Oceanic Airlines flight 815.
I'm Sayid Jarrah...
...one of the Oceanic Six.
That's...
That's amazing.
I remember reading all about it.
Take your shot, my friend.
It appears you were right
about the five iron.
Enjoy your round.
Don't worry about the wager.
- It's all in good fun.
- No, you won. Allow me to pay you.
- It's fine, thank you.
- I insist, Mr Avellino.
"Is it free?" was the full extent
of my German.
What are you looking for?
I love Europe.
Everyone speaks English.
- I'm looking for Potsdamer Platz.
- You don't need a map.
It's one block down,
right across the street.
Thank you.
I'm Elsa.
Sayid.
Could I have an espresso, please?
What sort of business
brings you to Berlin?
I'm a head-hunter.
A corporate recruiter.
- And what do you do?
- My employer is an economist.
He works in emerging markets.
Actually, I don't really understand
what he does,
which doesn't matter
since all I do is shop for him.
And if this goes off,
I'm at his side instantly.
Which is wonderful, since he's only
in Berlin once or twice a year.
Which is why you're enjoying
a luxuriously long midday coffee.
Yes.
Do I...
...know you from somewhere?
I'll tell you exactly where
you know me from...
...if you let me take you to dinner.
This is the restaurant
you're taking me tonight. 8.00.
Well, if you can find it.
- Hello?
- I made contact.
Good.
Take a look at this.
Naomi had it with her.
She was looking for Desmond.
Whatever their real agenda is
it's clear they're not sharing it.
Maybe Desmond
can shed some light on this.
How long would it take
to get to the beach and back?
Couple of hours.
You mind?
Anything I can do to help.
Sayid.
So how are we gonna do this?
You know the best candidate
for this kind of mission.
- And what kind of mission is that?
- I'll make Locke release Charlotte,
and I'm going to do it
without any bloodshed.
As opposed to the way I'd do it?
The last time you encountered him
you put a gun to his head
and pulled the trigger.
That's not good diplomacy.
Hey, Jarrah.
You think you're going
after Charlotte without me?
Of course not.
Well, good.
Is there anything else?
- Yeah. Give me my gun back.
- We leave in ten minutes.
Ready to give us a name, Gizmo?
He's not gonna tell you who
his spy is on their boat, James.
Yeah, and why not?
Because that's the only thing
keeping him alive.
Here's an idea.
Why don't we take a gun,
point it to his big toe
and send that little piggy to market?
And if he still doesn't want to tell us,
we'll move on to the roast beef.
- Why don't we do that?
- Then we have to carry him.
John, how much further is it?
- I need to feed Aaron.
- It should be here, the cabin.
Maybe we got turned around.
Could be anywhere.
No, it was here.
What's in this cabin
that's so important?
John's looking for somebody
to tell him what to do next.
I guess I was mistaken.
It doesn't...
It doesn't matter.
Plan's the same. We keep moving.
The barracks aren't far.
If her team is with Jack's group,
they know we're going to the barracks.
Yeah, and Red here was wearing a vest,
which means her posse's gonna come
expecting a gunfight.
If all they want is her,
maybe we should let her go.
I thought we were just gonna go hide.
Why do we need to take prisoners?
Because she'll be valuable.
- How is she gonna be valuable?
- He means as a hostage, love.
- This is not what I signed up for.
- What did you sign up for?
If we let her go, they'll look at it
as a sign of good faith.
They'll look at it
as an act of foolishness.
I'm trying to come up with a compromise.
We're beyond compromise.
And right now, Hugo,
I'm making the decisions.
Is that going to be a problem for you?
Kinda sucks, huh?
What's that?
Being told not to come along.
Now you know what it feels like
to be me.
Does that mean I should
wait 20 minutes and go anyway?
Touch?.
You should go with them, Kate.
- You're serious?
- Yeah.
What, don't you trust Sayid?
I don't trust Locke.
What's preventing him from doing to me
what he did to Naomi?
Sawyer won't let him.
You got room for one more?
Oh, yeah, she gets a gun.
- The gun's a last resort, Kate.
- You give Locke that same speech?
Hey! Let's move out.
This guy, Sayid, where is he from?
Iraq.
Iraq?
So he's just gonna go
and work everything out?
What was he, a diplomat?
No.
No, he was a torturer.
Naomi, were you close to her?
Nope. Met her on the boat.
You don't seem particularly affected
by her death.
Sure, I'm affected. She was hot,
and I dug her accent.
Nice.
And this woman, Charlotte.
You don't care about her, do you?
- Define "care".
- So much for camaraderie.
Who's the one going after one
of their crash buddies with guns?
Actually, I do care about Locke.
Maybe you can tell me how he managed to
split your happy little family in half.
There was a fundamental debate whether
your people came to rescue us...
...or kill us.
Which side did you land on?
I'll let you know when I decide.
You look fantastic.
This is why I wanted to take you
to the opera.
If a man can't wear his tuxedo
by the fifth date, why bother?
You know what?
I'm not bringing it.
If tonight's the night he calls,
so be it.
I'll carry it.
If he does call,
I don't want you fired over me.
You should tell your employer
there is newer technology.
Oh, I've tried.
He's very old-fashioned.
You know how bosses can be.
Do you have a boss?
Everyone has a boss, Elsa.
Come on, we don't want to be late.
Why are you still here?
I mean, when we met, you said
you would be in Berlin for one week.
The job I'm on is proving harder
to accomplish than I thought.
Oh...
...right.
I was hoping it was because of me.
Let's go.
Strauss awaits.
- What's his story?
- Daniel? Couldn't tell you.
Half the stuff he says
goes way over my head.
The other half goes way, way over.
Frank, can I?
Sorry to interrupt. May I please
use the phone just for a sec?
- For what?
- I want to call Regina on the boat.
Since we're waiting
maybe I can just try to...
- What is it, Daniel?
- I'd like to do an experiment.
- Just...
- OK.
You just keep it to that
science stuff, all right?
If Minkowski gets on there,
hang up right away.
Yeah, thank you, thank you.
- Hello?
- Regina?
Hey, hi, it's Dan. Hang on.
- Can you hear me?
- Yeah.
Yeah? OK. Hang on.
I'm... oh... Yes.
I am all set here. I have a fix.
Are you locked in?
- Getting your signal pretty clear.
- OK, great, then.
OK.
Fire the payload.
Payload away.
Don't sweat it. He does this kind
of stuff on the boat all the time.
Forty kilometres to beacon.
Thirty-five kilometres to beacon.
Thirty kilometres to beacon.
Twenty-five kilometres to beacon.
Twenty kilometres to beacon.
Fifteen kilometres to beacon.
- Ten kilometres to beacon.
- Regina?
Five kilometres to beacon.
Zero.
I don't have it.
That's weird.
That is far more than weird.
What's with the swing set?
These people had day-care?
- You think they're here yet?
- Let's find out.
It's coming from in there.
Hurley, what happened?
They left me.
Locke's gone off the reservation, man.
He took this one chick hostage.
He said Walt was the one who
told him to kill the other chick.
- Walt?
- Dude, don't ask.
I was trying to argue with him
so he would chill, but...
How about you stop babbling?
Tell us what happened to them.
Where are they?
- Who are you?
- Where the hell did they go, tubby?
Oh, awesome, the ship sent us
another Sawyer.
Hurley, where did they go?
Guess they were too busy tying me up
to tell me. I don't know.
- So they all left? All together?
- Yeah. They were freaked.
Locke said the people on the ship were
coming to rescue Charlotte and kill us.
So... are you?
Not yet.
Did they say anything that suggested
where they were going?
Locke said they were going
by Ben's house before they took off.
Why would he go there?
For all I know they could've
locked Ben in the closet too.
Where's Ben's house?
- You mind if I ask you a question?
- Shoot.
Did the Red Sox really win the Series?
Hey, don't get me started
on that, all right?
My dad's from the Bronx.
I bleed Yankee blue.
I can't believe it's been 100 days
since I've seen a game.
It's the payload.
It's finally here.
- What is that?
- It's a rocket.
Oh, no.
Thirty-one minutes.
This is not good.
Your friends are back.
Well...
...Iook at that.
Look for anything that might show
where they've gone.
I'll start in here.
Sayid!
Don't worry, Kate's fine.
Good job, Hugo.
Sorry, dude.
I'm sorry, Sayid. Nothing personal.
- Where's Locke?
- Talking to that angry Chinese guy.
I'm not going to hurt you, Hurley.
Yeah. I saw you snap that guy's neck
with that break-dancing thing
you do with your legs.
I think I'll hang back here.
Well...
...I guess they're running out
ofjail space.
- I lost a dollar, you know.
- How'd you manage that?
I bet John that you wouldn't be
stupid enough
to fall for your friend as bait.
What do you know about friendship?
I know it's no use having friends
you can't trust.
So I'm your prisoner?
If that sort of thing turns you on.
What are you doing here with Locke?
- I'm not with him.
- Yeah, you are, James.
- What are you doing with Jack?
- I went with Jack
because I believe he can
get us off this island.
Then I guess that's the difference
between us.
I ain't lookin' to leave.
Why not?
'Cause I ain't got nothing
back there for me.
And what's here that's so much better?
Why do you want to go back, Kate?
Seem to recall you being shuttled off
to jail before we landed here.
So if you think there's anything
waiting for you other than handcuffs,
then you really don't know
how the world works.
Look around us, Freckles.
We've got roofs over our heads.
- Electricity, showers, beds.
- How long, Sawyer?
How long do you think
we can play house?
Why don't we find out?
Iced tea.
- Thought you might be thirsty.
- I'm thirsty.
I'm sorry about all the theatrics,
but I didn't know
how many of you there'd be
or whether you'd be armed.
I had to cover my bases.
What have you done with Miles and Kate?
Kate's with Sawyer,
and Miles is somewhere else.
He's fine.
- All I did was ask him some questions.
- Did he answer any?
- No.
- Did you have more luck with the woman?
Not particularly.
Why don't you turn her over to me?
- Why would I?
- I agree these people are liars,
and they're certainly
not here to rescue us.
But if I return safely with Charlotte,
they'll take me to the ship.
It's our best chance of finding out
who they are and what they want.
Well, then, I can save you
a lot of trouble, Sayid,
because Ben says
he's got a spy on the boat.
Who?
It's a secret.
Forgive me, but the day I start
trusting him is the day I sold my soul.
Give me Charlotte,
allow me to do things my way,
or a war is coming which we
will both be powerless to stop.
Why would I give you Charlotte
for nothing?
I think you misunderstood me.
I never expected you
to give her to me for nothing.
- Should we get dressed?
- No.
We're gonna have to get out
of this bed at a certain point.
Why?
Well, for one thing, because I know
that eventually you're gonna have to go
to thatjob of yours, you know?
The one you never talk about.
There's nothing to talk about.
It's just a job.
I know nothing about you.
I understand you don't want
to talk about the crash,
what happened to you.
What about life now?
What about you?
It's what you do
when you're in love, right? You...
In love?
Yeah.
OK.
No more secrets.
What do you want to know?
He's here. My boss.
I... I have to go.
Now?
Where?
The Hotel Adlon.
My dress.
Elsa.
You have to leave Berlin.
What?
- You can't be here anymore.
- What do you mean?
- Why would I?
- People will be asking questions soon,
about what happened to your employer.
And you can't be around
to answer them.
My employer?
This is about my boss?
- Who are you?
- It had nothing to do with...
The caf??
You meant to meet me there?
You used me to get to my boss.
What did you say?
People will ask
what happened to him?
- It's best you don't know.
- You're gonna kill him?
You're gonna kill him?
Do you even know him?
- His name is on a list.
- A list? What list?
- You have a list.
- It's my employer's.
- Who is that?
- It doesn't matter who he is!
You kill people 'cause they're
on a list? Innocent people?
The man you're working for
is not an economist.
What do you think you're?
Hey, I'm gonna ask you one last time.
Why was Naomi
carrying this picture of me?
You gotta understand something,
she was senior management.
She stayed on her own.
Naomi told me you people
were hired by her.
So you look me right in the eye
and tell me
you've never seen or heard
of Penelope Widmore.
Fine. You don't want to tell me
the truth?
I'll find someone who will.
See, when that takes off, I'm on it.
He's back.
- Where's Kate?
- She decided to stay.
- What happened to Miles?
- I traded him.
- Traded him?
- I promised you Charlotte. Here she is.
- You cheated.
- Did I?
Yes, you did.
Lucky for you that guy's nothing
but a pain in my ass.
- Hey.
All right. That gives us room
for one more.
Charlotte?
Go back? With all the fun
I'm having here? No.
I've got work to do.
Seat's yours if you want it, Daniel.
No, thank you. I think I should
probably stay with Charlotte.
All right.
Frank.
Frank?
Just... just one thing.
Just be sure that you follow
the same exact bearing
that we came in on, OK?
No matter what.
By that I mean no matter what.
Just... stay on it.
Roger that.
Be careful.
I don't have to talk you out of coming.
As much as I like helicopter rides,
you got this one under control.
- Wish me luck.
- Good luck.
Send me a postcard.
You said we have room for one more?
Yeah. Why?
We should bring Naomi home.
Take your shirt off.
Is she dead?
Yes.
Why didn't she kill you?
She was trying to get
information from me.
What sort of information?
She wanted to know who I worked for.
She wanted to know about you.
Of course she did.
Why are you crying?
Because it hurts,
or because you were
stupid enough to care for her?
These people
don't deserve our sympathies.
Need I remind you what they did
the last time you thought
with your heart instead of your gun?
You used that to recruit me
into killing for you.
Do you want to protect
your friends or not, Sayid?
I have another name for you.
But they know I'm after them now.
Good.