What's that?
Cheat sheet Faraday drew for me.
You don't know where your boat is?
I know where it is.
Why are you flying
directly into the thunderhead?
Why don't you just sit
back and let me do my job, huh?
Is that Penelope?
She told Charlie she didn't
know about this boat, correct?
Aye.
What do you expect to
find when you get there?
Answers.
Hold on!
On your soddin' feet!
Move! Move! Move!
What are you waiting for, hume?
What's the matter, hume?
Did you not hear me?
I'm sorry, sir. I was--I
was having a dream, sir.
You were having a dream, were you?
And what were you dreaming about that
it took you so sodding
long to get to your mark?
I was in a helicopter, sir, and
there was a storm, sir.
And...
I don't remember the rest, sir.
Well, at least it was a
bloody military dream.
Right! All of ya!
In the yard! Four minutes!
And you can thank private hume
for having to do it in double-time.
Move!
- One, two, three!
- Three!
- Four!
- One, two, three!
- Five.
100 Crunches!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
One! Two! Three...
I hope your dream was worth this, mate.
Sorry, pal. It's just...
I've never had a dream that
was so vivid. It was--
it was like I was actually there.
Have you got something to say, hume?
I asked you a question!
We're almost through it.
I see daylight.
What do you think you're doing?
Desmond, are you all right?
Who are you?
How do you know my name?!
Here you go.
All right, they took off a day ago.
Why haven't we heard from 'em?
I'm gonna tell you again, as I have been
telling you all night, doctor, I don't know!
You heard the same thing as
I did when we called the boat.
What makes you think I know anything?
Because you're not worried.
Excuse me?
Your boat's 40 Miles off the coast.
It should've taken 'em, what,20
minutes to get there?
So why aren't you worried?
Well, should I wring my hands together
and whisper a prayer on their behalf?
Come on.
Maybe we should
just-- just tell 'em.
- Tell us what?
- Dan...
Let's not confuse anyone.
Well...
Daniel, maybe if you talk real
slow, we'll be able to follow.
Your perception of how long
your friends have been gone...
It's not necessarily how long
they've actually been gone.
What does that mean?
This is a mistake.
It'll be fine. It'll be fine.
As long as Frank flew on the bearings
that I gave him, if he stayed on it, it...
It'll be fine.
And what if he didn't?
Then there might be side effects.
We're at 2,000 feet. Sit down!
- What am I doing here?
- What the hell's going on?
- Something's wrong with Desmond.
- How do you know my name?!
Hold him in his seat!
- I'm trying!
- Let go of me!
Keep him away from the stick!
We'll be there in two minutes!
What are you doing back?
Who are they?
Survivors of 815.
So you brought them here.
What the hell were you thinking?
Where--where
am I?
- All right, just take it easy.
- Who are you people?
- Buddy. Okay, now, take it easy, buddy.
- Wh-what am I doing here?
- Who are you people?
- My friend is disoriented.
Look, I'm not your friend!
I don't know you! I don't know you!
When did he start doing this?
He was fine when we took off.
When we hit
some weather--
hey, Faraday told me as long
as I stayed on the vector--
What's your name, my friend?
Sayid.
Okay, Sayid.
Look, we're gonna take your
buddy down to the sick bay, okay?
I'm going with him.
Let our doctor look at him
first, then you can come down.
You got my word on that, okay?
All right.
Hey, listen to me--
th-this is a mistake, right?
- I don't know these people. I don't know these people.
- No, no, no. Oh, no, no, I understand.
No, but this is wrong!
I'm not supposed to be here.
20! 21! 22!
- "Here"?
- "Here" what?
What the hell are you
doing on your feet?
Are you finished with your
crunches because you want to run?
Right! Squad!
On your feet!
Right face!
10 Kilometers! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Get moving, or so help
me, I'll kill you myself.
What the hell's the matter with you, des?
If I told you, you'd think I was crazy.
I already know you're crazy.
This morning, when I was in
the yard doing crunches...
I left.
What do you mean, you left?
I was on a boat.
And then--then I was back
here, right--right where I started.
Des, if you're trying to
get tossed out of service--
Billy, I am telling you the truth, man.
Who else was on this... Boat?
Anyone you recognize?
Penny.
There was a photo.
- Penny was in the photo.
- What?
Oi, Des!
Where you going?
Thanks for this morning, hume.
Watch your step.
Watch it. Watch your step. Take it easy.
I'm not here. This...
This--this
isn't happening.
You are here, and this is happening.
Look, we're gonna take care of you.
W-what am I doing here?
- It's all right. You're gonna be okay.
- I'm not supposed to be here.
- Who are you people?
- Well...
My name is Keamy, and this is Omar.
I'm from Vegas, and he's from Florida.
But as for where we are, I--
we last ported in Fiji.
So at least we know we're
still in the pacific.
All right, my friend.
Now you just relax, okay?
We're gonna go get the doc, and he's gonna wanna ask
you some questions to--to help us sort all this out.
Wh-what do you mean, "sort out"?
Wait a minute. What do you mean?
I'm not supposed to be here!
Open this door! Open this door!
It's happening to you, too, isn't it?
What's happening to Desmond?
Your friends know what's wrong with him.
Well, if they do, they're
not sharing it with me.
Then perhaps you'll share how we took off
at dusk and landed in the middle of the day?
Listen, I don't know what's
happening to your buddy, all right?
But you gotta trust
me when I tell you this.
I am trying to help you.
You want to help me?
Give me your phone.
Let me call my people.
You give me that weapon, and
I'll give you this phone.
Be quick.
Don't go trying to call Baghdad.
Those phones only call each other.
Hello?
Jack? It's Sayid.
I'm on the freighter.
Are you okay? Where
the hell have you been?
Something happened during the flight, and
now Desmond's in their sick bay.
Hold on. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
All right, you're on speaker.
On the helicopter, something
happened to Desmond.
He doesn't appear to
recognize me or know where he is.
"Side effects"?
Wait, your
friend, um, Desmond--has he...
Has he recently been exposed to high
levels of radiation or electromagnetism?
Okay, look, uh, we don't know why,
but going to and coming from the
island, some people can get a little...
Confused.
So... What? This is amnesia?
No, this is not amnesia.
Can you hear me?
Are you all right? Hello?
I was just on a ferris wheel.
See, Ray?
I'm not crazy.
It's happening to him, too, Ray, and
it's gonna happen to you.
It's gonna happen to all of us.. Everyone!
Once we start heading to
that island again.
Would you please step aside?
No. No.
Ray, no.
I need you to relax for a minute.
No. No it's notgonna stop it, ray!
Nothing can stop it, ray!
Nothing can stop it!
And how are you feeling?
What the bloody hell is going on?
I understand you're disoriented.
- You're not gonna stick me with that, brother!
- I...
Don't wanna stick you with anything.
It's okay.
I just wanna check your eyes.
Why?
So I can help you.
What's your name?
Desmond.
Desmond, why don't you tell
me about the last thing you remem--
Hello?
Penny?
What do you want, Desmond?
Um, Penny, listen, I'm, uh...
I'm in trouble, and, uh... But I...
I think something's happening
to me, and...
I'm confused and... I...
I need to see you.
You broke off with me, and
then you joined the army,
and now you call with some expectation
that I still care about you?
Yeah, I'd say you are confused, Desmond.
No, no, I'm not.
It's--it's...
Look, I-I have got two days
leave starting tonight.
- Can I--can I--can I
come and see you? - No!
No, and don't bother showing up at
the flat either, 'cause I have moved.
Moved? Where?
It doesn't matter.
Look, Desmond, I'm going to go.
- Please, just don't call me again.
- No, no. No, listen.
Penny, Penny, I
ne--Penny, I need you.
Did you just...
Experience something, Desmond?
What the hell, Frank?
You're not supposed to be down
here, and definitely not with him.
Sorry, doc, but I got
Faraday calling from the island.
- He needs to talk to the scottish guy.
- No, Faraday's not talking to my patient.
- Now get out of here.
- But he's not your patient.
Give Desmond the phone.
Give him the phone now!
Hello?
Desmond? Desmond, my
name is Daniel Faraday.
We met yesterday before you took off, but I'm
guessing you don't remember that. Am I right?
Took off? What?
Desmond, we don't have long to talk, so I
need you to tell me what year you think it is.
What do you mean, what
year do I think--it's 1996.
All right, Desmond.
Desmond, look, you--you
gotta tell me.
Where are you?
I-I'm in--I'm in
some kind of sick bay.
No, no, no. Not right now, Desmond.
Wherare you supposed to
be? Where are you in 1996?
I-I'm at camp millar.
It's, uh, royal scots regiment.
It's, uh, just north of Glasgow.
- Dan, you might wanna-- -
Y-yeah, yeah. No. No, I'm thinking. I'm thinking.
Desmond, listen, when it happens
again, Desmond, I need you to get on a train.
Get on a train and go to Oxford.
Oxford university.
Queen's collegephysics
department, all right?
W-what? Why?
Because I need you to find me.
Where is it? Where is it?
What?
My journal, my journal.
I need my journal, or I won't believe him.
Why does he think he's in 1996?
I don't know. I don't know.
It's unpredictable.
It's a random effect.
Sometimes the displacement's only a
couple of hours. Sometimes it's years.
Wait, wait, this has happened before?
The phone now, please. Thank you.
- Desmond, are you still there?
- Doc?
- Hey, doc, are you okay in there?
- Talk to him.
I can't hold them for long.
Um, yes. Yes, I'm here.
Okay, Desmond, listen, when
you find me at Queen's college,
I need you to tell me to
set the device to 2.342
What?
All right, you got it? 2.342.
And it must be oscillating at 11 hertz.
You got it, Desmond?
2.342, oscillating at 11...
Just--ju remember that--2.342
at 11 hertz, all right?
And one more thing, Desmond.
If the numbers don't convince me, I need
you to tell me that you know about Eloise.
- Easy, easy.
- Get off the phone.
Tell me that you
knowabout Elo-- ...
Not a single piece of
original thinking...
The concept of "original"--
the opposite of derivative.
I am the one for you to impress, mr.
Hollister, and I'm not impressed.
So go. Go try again.
Um, sorry, are--are
you Daniel Faraday?
You are?
Uh, I'm sorry. I'm--I'm Desmond
hume, and, uh, I was told I could find you here.
And I think I have...
I've just been to the future.
- The future?
- Yes.
Uh, I-I spoke to you there.
You, uh, you told me to come
here to--to Oxford to find you.
You--you said
you'd help me.
Why didn't I just help
you there in the future?
Sorry?
Why would I put you through the
headache of time traveling?
You--you now what I mean? It just
seems a little... Unnecessary?
And don't you think my esteemed colleagues could've
come up with something just a little more believable?
What kind of a prank is that?
Time paradox--so
whole uninspired.
Set your device to, um...
2.342 and--and make
sure it oscillates at 11.
Okay, now--now
you...
You're gonna tell me who
told you those numbers.
- You did.
- No, this is...
This is ridiculous.
I know about Eloise.
What--what
is all this?
This is where I do the
things Oxford frowns upon.
All right, this...
This future version of me, uh, he--he
referenced this meeting, right?
Obviously. So--so I would
remember you coming to Oxford, right?
I would remember this, here, right now.
- Actually, um, no.
- No?
Maybe you just forgot.
Yeah, right. How would that happen?
This--this
is changing the future?
You can't change the future.
What's that for?
Radiation.
Do I get one?
You don't need one.
For prolonged exposure.
I-I do this 20 times a day.
So what do you put on your head?
Yeah.
This... This is eloise.
What does this do?
This...
If the numbers you gave me are
correct, what this will do...
is unstick Eloise in time, just like you.
- What happened?
- Wait, shh, shh.
She's not back yet.
There she is.
Okay, here goes... Everything.
Come on, ce on.
That's it.
That's it. That's it.
It worked!
Th-this is incredible.
I'm sorry. How is a rat running
through a bloody maze so incredible?
What is incredible is I just
finished the maze this morning,
and I'm not gonna teach her how
to run it until hour from now.
S-so--so you--you
sent her to the future.
No, no, no, her consciousness, her mind.
So--so how does
that help me?
You?
Help you? I don't understand.
Am I supposed to help you?
Didn't I send you back here to help me?
I don't know why you sent me here.
All I know about you is you--
you end upon some bloody island.
An island?
What island? W-why
would I go to an I--
Desmond, give me the phone.
Hey, come on! Everybody relax!
Listen, look, Daniel wanted to talk to the
guy, so we brought him the phone, that's all.
You let Faraday talk to him?
He said he could help.
Faraday can't even help himself!
- Outside now.
- The captain wants to talk to you.
And I want to talk to your captain.
I'll be sure to let him know.
In the meantime, have a seat.
I need to get back.
Back where? The island?
He said he could
help. He said --
he'd tell me what I needed to do.
- Desmond, Desmond, can you
please explain to me-- - Desmond?
You're Desmond?
Do I know you?
I'm George Minkowski.
I'm the communications officer.
Before they strapped me down here,
all the calls to and from this boat
came through me in the radio room.
And every so often, I'd get this
flashing light on my console--
an incoming call.
We were under strict
orders never to answer it.
So? What's that got to do with me?
Those calls came from your girlfriend.
Penelope Widmore.
What happened?
Oh, uh, you're back.
And...
You were out almost 75 minutes.
Out?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
You just... Whew. You went catatonic
right in the middle of a sentence.
I had to carry you to the chair.
So I take it you were-- you
were in the future again?
Aye.
- For how long?
- I don't know.
Five minutes?
Why does this keep happening?
Uh, in your case, I'm guessing
the progression is exponential.
Each time your consciousness jumps, it
gets harder and harder to jump back.
I would be careful crossing the
street if I were you.
What happened to her?
She died.
Yeah, I can see that. How?
Brain aneurysm, probably. I don't know.
I'm going to do an autopsy later.
Is that gonna happen to me?
The effects seem to vary from
case to case, but, uh...
Answer me!
If this keeps happening, am I gonna die?
I don't know.
I think...
Eloise's brainshort-circuited.
The jumps between the
present and the future--
she eventually--she
couldn't tell which was which.
She had no anchor.
Wh-what do you mean, "anchor"?
Something familiar in both times.
All this--see this?
This is all variables.
It's random. It's chaotic.
Every equation needs
stability, something known.
It's called a constant. Desmond, you
have no constant.
When you go to the
future, nothing there is familiar.
So if you want
to stop this, y--
then you need to find something there,
somethin that you
really, really care about...
That also exists back here...
In 1996.
This constant...
Can it be a person?
Yeah, maybe.
But you have to
make some kind of contact.
Didn't you say you were off on
a boat in the middle of nowhere?
Uh...
Who are you calling?
I'm calling my bloody constant.
The number you have dialed
has been disconnected.
Hey, hey.
You okay?
You look a lot older now, huh?
Welcome back, Desmond.
I need to call penny.
Calling your girlfriend is
not our priority.
Listen, brother, I don't know
you, but-- but you seem to know me,
so--so if you and me are
friends, then I need your help.
I need to call penny now.
You boys are gettin'way
ahead of yourselves.
Two days ago, someone sabotaged
all the equipment.
Lost all communication with the mainland.
I probably could've fixed it, but then...
Then I went nuts.
- Where's the radio room?
- It's one deck up.
I'll take you there.
Come on.
And how do we get out of here?
Through the door.
Looks like you guys
have a-a friend on this boat.
Hey, uh...
Your nose, brother.
It's clear.
Let's go.
"The black rock" set sail from
Portsmouth, England, March 22 1845--
on a trading mission to the kingdom of
siam when she was tragically lost at sea.
The only known artifact of this journey
is the journal of the ship's first mate,
which was discovered among the artifacts of pirates
on Sante marie, Madagascar, seven years later.
The contents of this journal have
never been made public,
nor are known to anyone outside the
family of the seller, Tovard Hanso.
We open the bidding on lot
2-3-4-2 at 150,000 pounds.
150,000, Sir.
160,000? Do I hear 160,000?
160,000, Sir.
170,000, Sir.
180,000 On the phone.
200,000 Pounds.
220,000 Pounds.
260,000 Pounds, sir.
On the phone, I have
300,000--320,000.
340,000 Pounds.
- 380,000 Pounds...
- This auction's by appointment only, sir.
Do I hear 400,000 pounds?
- Yeah, listen, pal, I just need to speak to the gentleman over there just for a moment, okay?
- I'm sorry, sir.
Sold...
For 380,000 pounds to
bidder 7-5-5. Thank you.
Just for a minute, all right?
- Look-- -
mr. Widmore.
Desmond?
Can I have a word, sir?
I'm
sorry, mr. Widmore. He--
no, no, it's fine.
Possession of Charles
Dickens when he died.
- Walk with me.
- We open the bidding on this lot...
Your word. Let's have it.
I need to get in touch with Penny.
I don't know how to reach her, and
her number has been disconnected.
There was a time when if
you'd have asked her to marry you,
I'm certain she would've said yes.
Fortunately...
Your cowardice won out instead.
I take it you've had second thoughts.
And you'd like her to
give you another chance.
Why do you hate me so much?
It's not me who hates you.
Here's her address.
I'll let her tell you herself.
Desmond.
I know.
It's getting harder.
It starts happening faster, too.
Come on. Let's move.
Hey, how did this happen to you?
We were anchored here, waiting for
our orders, bored out of our minds.
Me and Brandon--he's one of the crew
members-- we--we took out the ship's tender.
We just wanted to see the island.
But Brandon started acting
crazy, so we had to turn around.
Where is he?
In a body bag.
There.
Who did this?
You got me.
But when the captain
finds out, I feel sor--
after your call, someone has to
tell me precisely what is going on.
Can you fix it, brother?
I need a minute.
Do you have the number to make the call?
George? Wake up, brother. Wake up.
You've gotta come
back. You've gotta come back.
Desmond, do you know the number?
- No.
- Well, you'd better remember it.
It's 2004.
I didn't realize it was almost christmas.
It's been...
Desmond.
No!
I can't...
Get...
Back.
What happened to him?
The same thing that's gonna happen to me.
Desmond?
What are you doing here?
I had to--I mean, I tried to call
you, but you--you disconnected your phone.
Yeah, because I moved.
Look, I don't know if
you're getting the signals, Desmond,
but I'm trying to make a clean break
from you, so if you don't mind, I'm gonna--
wait, wait, wait, wait. Pen, please wait.
I just--I just need to get
your new phone number, okay?
Why would I give you that?
Because I-I made a huge mistake.
I-I should never have broken
up with you, and--and--and...
I know--I know that
now, and--and I'm sorry and--
- Oh, don't. Just don't--
- I understand, and--
and I-I know it's--it's
too late to change things,
but I need to tell you something, and--and
I need you to listen to me, and...
Look, I-I know it's
gonna sound ridiculous, but...
Please, Pen.
I need you to listen to me.
Just say what you
need to say and then go.
I know this doesn't make any sense,
because it doesn't make any sense
to me, but eight years from now, I...
I-I need to call you, and I can't
call you if I don't have your number.
What?
Look, penny, just--just
give me your number.
I-I know--I know
I have ruined things.
I know you think things are
over between us, but they're not.
If there's any part of you
that still believes in us, just...
Just give me your number.
And what's to say you wouldn't call
me tonight or tomorrow--
I won't call...
For eight years.
December the 24th, 2004.
Christmas eve.
I promise.
Please, Pen.
If I give you the number, will you leave?
Aye.
7946-0893.
7946-0893. 7946...
All that, and you're
not gonna write it down?
It wouldn't do any good.
You have to keep that number.
- You can't change your number for eight years.
- Get out!
Just--just remember, december
the 24th, 2004.
Look, Pen, if--if you still care
about me, you have to answer.
I'm not crazy, Penny!
You have to believe me!
You have--you
have to trust me.
I do trust you, but you still
have to remember that number.
7946-0893.
It's a London number.
Excellent timing.
The patch is done, but I don't
know how long the battery will last.
I hope she's there.
I hope so, too.
Hello?
Penny?
Desmond?
Penny. Penny, you answered.
You answered, Penny.
Des, where are you?
I'm...
I'm--I'm
on a boat.
I've-- I have been on
an island, Pen.
My god, penny, is that really you?
Yeah!
Yes, it's me!
You believed me.
You still care about me.
Des...
I've been looking for
you for the past three years.
I know about the island.
I've been research-- and then when
I spoke to your friend Charlie...
That's when I knew you were still alive.
That's when I knew I wasn't crazy.
Des, are you still there?
Yes! Yes, I'm here!
I'm still here. Can you hear me?
Yeah, yeah, that's better.
I love you, penny.
I've always loved you.
I'm so sorry.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I don't know where I am, but...
I'll find you, Des...
- I promise...
- No matter what...
- I'll come back to you.
- I won't give up.
- I promise.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
The power source went dead.
That's all we have.
Thank you, Sayid.
It was enough.
Are you all right now?
Aye.
I'm perfect.