Previously on "Lost"...
Can you hear me?
Yes! Yes, I can hear you.
Hey, are you on a boat?
- What--what boat?
- Your boat.
I'm not on a boat.
Uh, na-Naomi, the parachutist.
Who? Who's Naomi?
I've got it. I've got a signal!
It's gonna work. It's happening.
We're gonna get off of this island.
Hello? Is Desmond there?
Penny! No!
I'm telling you, making that call
is the beginning of the end.
Who is this? Who is this?
I'm one of the survivors
of oceanic flight 815.
Can you get a fix
on our location?
Sit tight.
We'll be right there.
It's almost 30 minutes now since
the start of this high-speed chase.
We still have no information
about who's driving this vehicle.
Jeff, can you tell us
where the chase started?
Ruth, we're hearing reports that the
pursuit began near the la brea area,
then traveled through a warehousing
district south of the 10 freeway.
Can you see how many
people are in the car?
It appears to be just the one--
the driver.
We're not sure if that's
the owner of the car.
What you're seeing here are pictures
of the 10 freeway south of downtown.
Is that a camaro, jeff?
Yes, it looks like a-a vintage,
early '70s model.
Damn it.
Show us your hands!
Roll down the window and
show us your hands now!
Now slowly open the door
with your left hand.
Get out of the car!
Turnround... Slow!
On the ground!
Now!
Stop! Dot you know who I am?
Stop! Wait!
don't you know who I am?
I'm one of the oceanic six!
I'one of the oceanic six!
-=www. Ydy.
com/bbs=- proudly presents
com/bbs=- sync:
Lost
Season4 Episode01
... ... Across the city,
you're minding your own business
in a convenience store,
until you see something
and freak out.
Mr. Reyes,
why'd you run like that?
Who'd you see in there?
Listen, buddy,
I know you saw somebody in that store
that made you run away
and go on a high-speed--
I wasn't running
away from anyone.
If you think I care that you're a
celebrity, you crashed your camaro in
the wrong neighborhood.
I'm not a celebrity.
Is that why you kept shouting,
"hey, I'm one of the oceanic six"?
You wanna know a
funny coincidence?
Sure.
I knew somebody your plane.
Really?
Her name was ana lucia cortez.
She was my partner before
I made detective--
dark hair... Gorgeous.
Maybe you knew her.
Maybe you met her
on the plane...
Before it took off?
Sorry. Never met her.
Why don't you watch the tape?
Maybe it'll spark something.
I'm gonna get a doughnut.
You want one?
No, thanks.
And when I come back,
you're gonna tell me who you ran from.
Help! Help!
Help!
Let me out!
What the hell is
wrong with you?
What are you doing, reyes? Huh?
You trying to get tossed
into the nuthouse?
Because if that's what you want, I can
make that happen right now, my friend.
You can?
Oh, thank you!
Thank you.
Jack? You there, dude?
Beach to Jack, come in, Jack.
Beach to Jack.
Right here, Hurley. What's up?
Hey, uh, did you guys make it
to that radio tower thingy yet?
Yeah, and I talked to
the people on the boat.
They're on their way to
pick us up right now.
Seriously? It worked?
Seriously. We're all on the way
back to the beach right now,
so you better pack
your bags, buddy.
Dude, that's great!
Any luck?
Nothing. No sign of him.
It's like he just disappeared.
Why would Locke kill her?
-He hadn't even met her-
- because he's crazy.
So what if he comes back?
If he comes back,
I'm gonna kill him.
I'm gonna get
everybod together.
The sooner we get back to the beach,
the better.
Are we really going home?
Yeah, we're really going home.
I can't believe I'm actually going
to have my baby in a hospital.
-Oh, rub it in, why don't you?
-Oh, no.
You ladies need a hand?
No, we're just wrapping
things up, thanks.
You know,
you must be very proud of bernard.
I hear he's quite the hero.
Look, everyone up here knows that
the real hero is your man, claire.
If Charlie didn't
turn off that gizmo,
we'd still be getting a busy
signal on that fancy phon
so you better make sure you treat
him real good when we get back.
Rose!
Okay, thanks. I have enough.
I need you to do me a favor.
I need you to take alex and get
as far from here as possible.
-What?
-We don't have time for this.
Everyone who stays
here is going to die.
Now get alex and
get away right now.
I don't care where you gO.
Just go.
I will not have my daughter--
she's not your daughter.
Did I ever tell you
I won the lottery?
I got, like, $150 million.
Worst thing that
ever happened to me.
Oh, yeah,
who needs $150 million, right?
Now it'll all be gone,
'cause they all think I'm dead.
When we get rescued,
and I go back...
I'm gonna be free.
I wanna do a cannonball.
I've been walking up and down this
beach every day and looking out at
this water,
and I wanna do a cannonball.
Hurley...
You wanna do a
cannonball, cannonball.
Are you all right, Desmond?
We need to get to Jack.
We can't let him get in
touch with that boat.
Easy, Scotty. Everything's cool.
Boat's on the way.
-What?
-On the way?
No. Hey, where's Charlie?
No, that woman-- Naomi--
she lied.
Look, the people on the boat
aren't who they say they are!
-What?
-Then who are they?
-Desmond, where's Charlie?
-I don't know. But we need to get
in touch with Jack now!
We can call him.
We have a walkie.
-Where is it?
-Get it.
-What do you mean the people aren't
who they say- - where's Charlie?
I'm--I'm--I'm sorry,
brother. I...
You think that's our ride?
Hello?
Hey, Jack.
This is george minkowski.
We're trying to get a lock on your
signal there, but we're getting some
rf interference.
We're gonna need to rejigger some
of the settings on your sat-phone.
Uh, sure. Okay.
Just tell me what I gotta do.
How about you put Naomi on?
Naomi went to get
some firewood.
Can you hold on for a second?
Let me see if I can...
Where is she?
I don't know.
We gotta call the doc.
Did you listen to Desmond?
- Charlie wrote on his hand-
- Look, I'm sorry he's dead,
but I don't even know what the
hell "not penny's boat" means.
Calling Jack
accomplishes nothing.
It would accomplish
warning him...
It also means warning the people on the
freighter that we're suspicious of them.
I have no doubt they're
monitoring our communications.
-If we call Jack-
-You know what? I got the walkie.
I'm making the call.
We better get goin'.
Going where?
I found blood--the
girl's trail.
Probably crawled away.
Can't be more than ten
minutes ahead of us.
We should go now and find her.
We're taking him with us.
And why would we do that?
Because I don't trust
him with anybody but me.
All right, listen up.
I need all of you to head back down to
the beach, and when these people
show up,
we wanna make sure that we're
real easy for them to find, okay?
You look worried, Jack.
The only thing I'm worried
about is missing our ride home.
I found her trail.
She's headed west
across the island.
Rousseau already found it.
We're going after
her right now.
What? Are you sure it's hers?
Unless someone
else is bleeding.
But if she didn't want us to find her,
then she could've created a dummy trail
I think we should follow both--
Kate, 6 hours from now, we'll be
sitting on that boat laughing about the
fact that there was one final
thing that we couldn't agree upon.
Naomi is hurt.
She ran into the jungle. She's not
thinking about leaving fake trails.
You're right.
I'll track her down.
Why don't you get everybody
back to the beach?
You got it.
Be careful, okay?
What the hell's gotten
into you, hugo?
They'll all be back in the morning.
If we just wait--
you don't wait with warnings.
You... warn.
Here I was thinking I was
gonna get a good night's sleep.
You almost got me that time.
How about best out of seven?
Are you ready for
your meds, hugo?
Oh, by the way,
you have a visitor.
Mr. Reyes.
Hello. My name is
matthew abbadon.
I'm an attorney for
oceanic airlines.
Can we talk for a few minutes?
Okay.
I'm here, Mr. Reyes,
because we've heard about your recent...
Episode.
Your arrest,
your incarceration here--
frankly, we feel
terrible about it.
So on behalf of oceanic, I'd like to
extend you an invitation for a
little upgrade.
What... Kind of upgrade?
To a facility where the paint
isn't peeling off the walls,
where you'd have
your own bathroom.
-You can see the ocean from-
- I don't wanna see the ocean.
No problem.
Actually, thanks.
I'M... I'm fine right here.
Are you fine, Mr. Reyes?
What do you mean?
You're in a mental institution.
Who'd you say you were again?
I'd like to see
a business card.
I must have left them at home.
Then we're done, dude.
Are they still alive?
What?
You heard me.
Nurse!
Get out of here!
You better get outta here!
Help me! He's after me.
No, no, no, no.
That guy's after me! Help me!
You all right there, hugo?
Yeah, dude, I'm fine.
You wanna talk about it?
Talk about what?
Charlie.
I mean...
You two were buddies.
I just thought...
We'll probably get to Jack
faster if we don't talk.
I'm gonna head up and tell
them to slow down a little.
I can keep up.
All right, ese.
Just... Holler if you need me.
Guys?
Guys! Guys!
The blood trail ends here.
What do you mean?
It ends.
What, are you telling me that
she stopped bleeding here?
No, I'm telling you that she
fooled us and doubled back.
Better call the boat, ll 'em she's
getting a really big bundle of firewood
where is it?
Okay, I probably should have told you
that I saw her take the phone, but you
beat me up, Jack.
I owed you one.
What are you talking about?
Kate took it when
she hugged you.
She found thright trail, too,
but you wouldn't listen to her,
so I guess she's taken
matters into her own hands.
But look on the bright sid at least
somebody around here knows what the hell
they're doing.
Hello?
Who's this?
Uh, this is Kate.
You with Jack?
No, no, he's not here.
Where's Naomi?
Uh, we're looking for her.
What do you mean,
you're looking for her?
Give me the phone.
Naomi, listen to me.
You're hurt. Let me help you.
Help me?
I just spent the last three days
trying to get you people rescued,
and you throw this
knifen my back.
- No, that was not us.
- Who?
- His name is John Locke.
- What?
He said that you weren't
who you said you were.
I swear to god we would never hurt you.
You know us.
Please, we need your help.
Please help us.
Give me the phone.
George, it's Naomi.
Naomi, where have you been?
What's going on over there?
I had an accident.
I'm hurt.
What? A-an accident?
What--what--what accident?
What happened?
Naomi!
Hello?
I hit a tree branch
when I parachuted in.
Took it through my gut.
Why did they tell me you
were getting firewood?
I guess they were afraid to tell you
what happened to me till I could talk to
you myself.
We've lost our signal,
and can't come get you.
Can you change your
tracking frequency?
Yeah.
Try it now.
Clear as a bell.
Hang on, Naomi. We'll--we'll
get you back here asap, okay?
I'm sorry, george.
Just tell my sister
that I love her.
Hello?
Help!
There's nothing here.
Hello, hugo.
You got yourself good
and lost out here, hugo.
How did you get
separated from the group?
I just...
Fell behind, I guess.
Is that why you were
shouting for help?
Well, I got scared.
What Desmond said happened down in
that station-- "not penny's boat"...
Are you sure that's what
Charlie wrote on his hand?
Jack should never have
called those people.
I couldn't agree more.
It's gonna be hard to...
Talk him into thinking they're
not coming here to rescue us.
Well, we're just gonna have
to try our best, hugo,
because if we can't
talk him out of it...
Then Charlie died for nothing.
Where the hell you been, hugo?
Sorry.
I was just, uh, I got lost.
What are you doing here?
I came here for the same reason you
did--to warn Jack about the people on
that boat.
I already gave it a shot, but I figured
I might have better luck with
some support.
You want my support?
You can tell me why you
destroyed that submarine.
Still in one piece.
Rambo.
I'll tell her.
He's dead.
Charlie'S... dead.
No.
I'd watch out if I were you.
What are you
talking about, dude?
There's a guy over there.
He's staring at you.
What guy?
That guy.
Hey, man.
Don't run.
Hurley. Just... just...
Sit down.
I wanna talk to you.
Come on.
Don't do what you did
in the store. Okay?
There's no need to...
freak out.
No need to freak out?
I'm trying to buy some
jerky and a slushee,
and suddenly you're standing
there over by the ho hos.
You're dead.
What do you expect me to do?
Can we just... sit down?
I may be in a mental hospital,
but I know you're dead,
and I'm not having an imaginary
conversation with you.
I am dead.
But I'm also here.
Okay, prove it.
Okay. Okay.
Did you know you were going to
die when you swam out there?
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you would have
tried to stop me.
And since I was gonna do it anyway, I
thought I would spare you all the drama.
And now you have
to do something.
But you're hiding from it.
That's the real reason you ran
when you saw me in the store.
- You knew I was here to tell you-
- no, I'm not listening to this.
No, 'cause you're not here.
I am here. You're being a baby.
I'm gonna close my eyes and count to
five, and when I open 'em, you'll
be gone.
- I am here.
- One...
- don't do this.
- Two...
- they need you.
- Three...
- they need you, hugo.
- Four!
- You know they need you.
- Five!
What... what happened?
I mean, how-- how did he...
He was trying to help us.
Jack
You********
*********
it's not loaded.
Let go of me!
- Do you know what he did?
- Yes, I know what he did!
All I did...
All I have ever done...
Has been in the best
interest of all of us.
Are you insane?
I know I...
I have a lot of
explaining to do.
But I never did anything
to hurt any of you.
I even risked my life to tell you that
there was a traitor in your midst.
She helped us, John.
All you ever did was blow up every
chance we had of getting off
this island.
You killed Naomi!
Well, technically,
he didn't kill her yet.
Yes, he did.
She just died.
She didn't give you up, John.
She covered for us,
and she fixed this.
They're on their way.
She didn't cover for anyone.
She wants her people
to come here.
And trust me, when they do,
we had better be far away from here.
I'm going to the barracks.
The others abandoned them.
It's the only place on the island
with any form of security right now.
It'll have to do until I
can think of something else.
Until then, if you want to live,
you need to come with me.
No one's going anywhere with you,
John, because they're not crazy.
He's not crazy.
What about Charlie?
Charlie went down to that place
so we could all be rescued.
And whatever he did down there...
it worked.
But then something
must've happened.
He must have heard
something before he...
I don't know why,
but it changed his mind.
Because the last thing he did was to
warn us at the people on that boat are
not who they said they were.
So I'm not listening to you.
I'm listening to my friend.
I'm listening to Charlie.
Anyone else?
There isn't much time.
Jack, with your permission,
I'd like to go with John.
He's all yours.
You said we'd never
leave the island.
If you, uh, you wanna go with Locke,
I'll be right behind ya.
I'm not going anywhere
with that man.
What are you doing?
Same thing I've
always done, Kate...
Survivin'.
You know where to find us
when you change your mind.
You ever miss?
Jack.
Yeah. I was, uh,
on my way back from a consult.
Thought I'd drop by
and pay you a visit.
Horse?
You're on.
So... consult, huh?
Does that mean you're back
doing surgical stuff?
Yeah.
"H. "
Reporters leaving you alone?
Yeah.
Still have to sign some autographs
when I go out for coffee, but...
Thinking about growing a beard.
You'd look weird
with a beard, dude.
That's h-O.
So...
What are you really
doing here, Jack?
I was just checking on you,
seeing if everything was okay.
You're checking to see if I went nuts,
if I was gonna tell.
Are you?
You're up.
Nah, you win. I, uh...
Gotta run.
It was gat seeing you, Hurley.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I went with Locke.
I should've stayed with you.
It's water under
the bridge, man.
I don't think we did
the right thing, Jack.
- I think it wants us to come back.
- Hurley...
- and it's gonna do everything it can-
- we're never going back.
Never say never, dude.
Are you thinking of Charlie?
Feels like a hundred years ago
that we came out here together.
How did this happen?
Thunder's getting louder.
That's not thunder. Come on.
Come on.
Are you Jack?
-=www. Ydy.
com/bbs=- proudly presents
com/bbs=- sync: