Previously on "Lost"...
- We'll get you back here asap.
- I'm sorry, George.
Just tell my sister
that I love her.
You killed Naomi!
She wants her people
to come here.
And trust me, when they do,
we had better be far away from here.
If you want to live,
you need to come with me.
No one's going anywhere
with you, John.
What are you doing?
Same thing I've always done,
Kate-- survivin'.
The thunder is getting louder.
Sorry, Ron.
Drone's got nothing but seafood
at 5,000 mers below.
You picking anything
up with yours?
Zip.
I'm trying to get her a peek over
this ridge as soon as I can.
Sonar's pinging
up something now.
Hey, you wanna switch feeds?
Roger that.
I'm headed on a bearing of about 1-3-7
from the coordinates we pulled off our
guy's map.
But don't hold your breath.
Magnetometer is picking up a hell
of a lot of anolies down here.
A chest full of doubloons?
Keep dreaming, Ron.
Let's swing around on the
next bridge and recalibrate.
Are you getting this?
What? What's up?
It's...
It's an airplane.
Oh, my god.
It's Oceanic 815.
This haunting footage comes
to us from the Christiane I,
a salvage vehicle in
the indian ocean.
For more than two months, it's been
scouring the depths of the Sunda trench
off Bali
in search of the remains
of sunken trading ships.
Late last night, the "Christiane"
deployed two remotely operated vehicles,
or R.O.V.S.
That verified what the national
transportation safety board had
long feared,
Essex, Massachusetts
that the aircraft...
- How you want your eggs, Dan?
disappeared after departing Sydney,
Australia, on september 22nd, 2004...
So what happened?
They found that missing plane?
- This confirms that flight 815...
- Dan?
- Did in fact crash at sea.
Even with this
tragic discovery...
- dan,why are you so upset?
- Victims families say that they're
left without any sense of closure.
- I don't know.
I can't find my vest!
- Check under your seat!
- I already did!
Get ready! Re, just take mine!
Everybody out! Now!
Hey, genius!
- No,no!
- Go!
Hey there.
Are you jack?
Yeah, I'm jack.
Who are you?
I'm daniel faraday.
I'm here to rescue you.
-=www. Ydy.
com/bbs=- proudly presents
com/bbs=- sync:??????
Lost
Season04 Episode02
Hey, dan the chopper--
how many of you were on it?
Uh, four, including me.
So what happened to
the rest of them?
Yeah, yeah, I,
uh, have no idea.
I don't know how many of 'em were
able to get out before it went down.
I just-- I jumped, and I lost my,
uh, what do you call it? My--my pack.
My phone was in my pack.
If I had my phone, I would just, uh...
We have a phone.
You--you have a phone.
Thank you. Thanks.
Minkowski.
He George.
It's Daniel.
- Dan?
- Yeah.
The chopper com went dead.
What the hell happened up there?
Yeah, I don't know. George, there was--
there was an electrical storm.
All the instruments, they just--
I think they went down.
But listen, I made-- I made
contact with some of the survivors,
and, uh, we were just, uh--
- Dan, am I on speaker?
Would you give me
just-- just one second?
- Don't worry.
- I don't know...
Naomi covered for us.
They don't know what
Locke did to her.
You sure about that?
Okay, okay.
So the boat hasn't heard
from anybody else yet,
but, uh, these are
G.P.S. transponders,
and my team and I are
all wearing these.
The transponrs will send the
locations back to the ship,
and then the ship will send all
the locations back into the phones.
Oh, there is my signal right there, and
hopefully, we'll get the signals from
the rest of the team soon.
Will you help me find 'em?
Absolutely.
Okay. Thank you.
Hey, where are the
rest of your people?
Most of them are
back at the beach.
Most of them?
Dude what's wrong with you?
You're gonna get
struck by lightning.
Storm's about to pass, Hugo.
It's a freakin' monsoon.
We gotta...
Let's go.
Why you going east?
I thought you said the
barracks were due south.
Because, James,
we have to make a little detour first.
Detour to what?
There's a cabin
I have to go to.
But the cabin was
back that way.
What did you say, Hugo?
I, uh, thought your were talking
about the airplane cabin.
Why are we wasting our time
going to some shack anyway?
Because we're supposed to.
Right, like you were supposed to throw
a knife into that Naomi chick's back?
You mind telling us who you're getting
your orders from, colonel Kurtz?
I got 'em from Walt.
Jack still isn't back.
Anything?
No, but it's a big island.
The freighter could be
approaching from the other side.
That's the spiriT.
Juliet, you lived
amongst the others.
Why would Ben say the people
coming here intend to do us harm?
Because he's a liar and he's trying
to scare us. That's what Ben does.
Or because the people coming
here intend to do us harm.
How many guns do you have left?
Is that from your chopper?
Yeah, yeah.
That, uh, yeah, they...
Reduced the weight load
when we started going down.
I guess that's why
they pushed me out.
What's this for?
I'm not in charge of,
uh, packing, so...
You're not, huh?
We should, uh...
- Daniel, why did you bring the gun?
- You wanna keep moving?
Yeah... as a precaution.
Precaution against what?
Uh, okay, see, um...
Rescuing you and your people...
Can't really say its
our primary objective.
Then what is?
It's Miles.
It's Miles. Come on.
What the hell do you
mean you saw Walt?
In a dream?
No dream. It was Walt.
Only... taller.
Taller?
What, like a giant?
Okay, what exactly
did walt tell you?
He said I had work to do,
that I had to stop is woman, Naomi,
from bringing the rest
of her people here.
What, you didn't ask
any follow-up questions?
Ben had shot me and
left me for dead.
Walt saved my life,
so I pretty much took him at his word.
He shot you, yet here you are, fit as
a fiddle, trompin' through the jungle.
The bullet went in one side,
came out the other.
I'd probably be dead if I
still had a kidney there.
Anything else?
It's down there.
Hey, Miles!
Miles!
Is he dead?
Back up, handsome.
Miles! Take it easy. It's okay.
They're here to help us.
It's okay, Miles.
They're just trying to help.
Back away from him!
Hands where I can see 'em!
Kate, it's all right.
It's okay.
You're Kate!
You wanna tell me
where Naomi is?
What?
Naomi-- the woman you killed!
Where is she?
Inglewood, California
For friends and families of
the passengers of Oceanic 815,
this can only be described
as the worst-case scenario.
With the plane accounted for
and a salvage mission unlikely,
authorities are confirming
all 324 passengers dead.
Ms. Gardner?
I'm Miles Straume.
We spoke on the phone earlier.
Oh, please come in.
Which room is it?
It's upstairs at
the end of the hall.
I get paid in advance.
$200, cash only.
You told me $100 on the phone.
That was before my buddy at the police
station told me your grandson
was murdered.
It's gonna be $200.
Fine.
No matter what you hear,
don't come up.
You're not doing your grandmother
any good staying here, man.
You're causing her
a lot of pain...
I wanna go downstairs
and tell her you've gone.
But the only way I'm gonna be able to
do that is if you tell me where it is.
So where is it?
You can go now.
Did it work?
Yeah.
He's at peace now.
Here.
You get a refund, half off.
Wasn't as tricky as I thought.
Thank you.
Miles. Miles!
What are you doing?
These are good people.
They why'd Naomi
use the damn code?
Yeah, you remember when she said,
"tell my sister I love her"?
Well, she doesn't
have a sister.
That's what we're supposed to say if we
get captured and have a gun to
our heads.
Like right now jack here would say,
"tell my sister I love her. "
You get it?
We didn't kill your friend.
Then take me to her body.
Miles, what about Charlotte?
What about Frank?
- Take me to Naomi!
- Naomi was killed, but not by us.
It was-- it was a man by
the name of John Locke.
He's not with us anymore.
Kate, seriously,
if I have to ask you again--
Look, even if I took
you to her body,
- you wouldn't know what happened.
- I'll know!
Now take me to her body.
Alex.
Alex, hey.
What?
Something I need to tell you.
Keep your mouth shut,
Mr. Linus.
Karl.
Now if you're gonna sleep with my
daughter, I insist you call me Ben.
Easy kid.
Guy's just trying
to get in your head.
Go take a walk or somethin'.
Mind if I ask you
a question, James?
Yeah, I do.
Why'd you leave Kate behind?
You're wasting your time, Yoda.
I know it's not pleasant,
but let's face it.
You really don't
stand a chance now.
Chance at what?
James, look at yourself.
Yes, on this island,
you're brave, daring, handsome.
You're someone.
But if you left with them...
Back in the real world,
a lowlife scam artist like you
could never compete with
a first-class surgeon.
I think Kate was really upset when
you made your choice to come with us.
Thank god she has Jack
there to comfort her--
James!
- Don't.
- Don't what?
Anyone want to tell me why
we're keeping this guy alive?
We're keeping him alive because he's
been on this island a lot longer than
any of us,
because he has information we need, and
because apart from his mouth, he's
completely harmless.
His mouth put that
hole in your gut?
Okay, James, let's execute him
right here, right now, in front of
his daughter.
It's only a matter of time
before he gets us, Johnny.
And I'll bet he's already
figured out how he's gonna do it.
So you walk him.
What is he doing?
The light...
Is strange out here,
isn't it? It's...
It's kind like it doesn't--
it doesn't scatter quite right.
Dan?
Your name's Dan, right?
Listen, dan, I know that you don't
want anybody to get hurt, right?
So why don't you
just put that away?
Because, um, Miles...
would kill me?
But we're just trying to help--
Kate, you're
wasting your breath.
Let's just let this play out
and see what happens, okay?
They didn't kill her.
It happened like
they said it did.
It's Charlotte.
She's only 3
kilometers from here.
All right, then.
Let's go get her.
I said let's gO.
You need to put the guns down.
What?
Put the guns down.
Now why would I do that?
Because our friends are out in the
jungle right now holding a gun at your
head and his head.
So I'm gonna forget about
the misunderstanding.
Just put the guns down.
Come on.
How stupid do you think I--
I don't know, Miles.
How stupid are you?
815: RETROUVE!
How many different languages do you have
to read that in before you believe
it's true?
How many different
languages are there?
Excusez-moi.
He wants to know if we're lost.
Remind him that people in our line of
work are terrible at keeping secrets.
I know about the dig.
He says the site is closed.
Then tell him to open it.
Dinosaur?
Not by a few million years.
It's an ursus maritimus.
Wait, "ursus" as in bear?
As in polar bear.
Charlotte, we're in the desert.
This is a hoax, right?
He wants to know what you're
doing with the hammer.
Excavating.
Is that a collar?
Hi yourself.
We were worried when you didn't get
back, so we went out to the cockpit and
tracked you from there.
Thanks for that,
for what it's worth.
Don't mention it.
Somebody could've told me
that the calvary were here.
I gave you that... wink.
What are your names?
Uh, I'm Daniel Faraday,
and this is Miles--
Don't tell him my last name.
I guess this is just Miles.
What do you do for
a living, Daniel?
I'm a physicist.
I mean,
I guess you could call me a physicist.
I don't really like being
pigeonholed into one--
Dan, I swear to god, you say one more
word, I'm gonna break your fingers.
And what do you do, Miles?
I collect soil samples.
Well, that's nice.
Well, maybe you can help me.
You say you're not here
on a rescue mission,
and the world at large
believes us to be dead.
But here we are, alive and well and you
don't seem surprised to see us.
Oh, my god.
You guys were on
Oceanic flight 815.
Is that better?
I can't believe you're alive.
How many of you are there?
Why do you wanna know?
Why wouldn't I want to know?
48 of us survived the crash.
That's not counting
the tail section.
- They're pretty much all dead now--
- Hugo.
So you've all been living
here this entire time?
Is that your baby?
Yeah. This is Aaron.
Did you have him
here on the island?
That's amazing.
Well, I've got about a million
more questions I want to ask you,
but they can wait until we
get you back to the freighter.
We've all got one of these transponders
so if we just sit tight,
they're gonna be
here soon, okay?
This team of yours--
how many of you are there?
Four, including me.
And what happened
to your helicopter?
I don't know.
The pilot was trying to put it down.
Where?
I don't know.
I had to jump.
It was chaos.
I'm lucky to be alive.
Get up. You're coming with us.
What? What?
We need to stay where we are
so that they can find us.
See, there's your problem.
We don't want to be found.
I wouldn't mess around
with that if I were you.
It can't hurt to try
and call someone else.
Oh, it can hurt.
What'd you do?
I didn't do anything.
Your friend-- Charlotte.
She's moving.
And she's moving fast.
She's running from something.
According to this,
she's right here.
- Charlotte?
- Charlotte!
Over there. Over there.
Vincent.
Locke's got her.
We want to caution our viewers that the
images they are about to see are graphic
in nature.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Authorities have released dramatic
footage of the sunken remains of Oceanic
flight 815.
The national transportation safety board
has set up a hotline for family members
of the Oceanic victims.
The N.T.S.B. has begun the
victim identification process.
We have confirmation that this is
the pilot-- captain Seth Norris.
In a statement, the N.T.S.B. said
that, "due to the sheer depth of the...
recovery of the bodies
would be next to impossible.
We can only hope that identification
will provide closure to the families of
the victims."
National transportation safety board,
Oceanic hotline.
Yeah, let me speak
to your supervisor.
Yes, sir.
Are you a family member
of the deceased?
No, I'm not, but I got
some information on the crash.
May I please speak
to your supervisor?
Sir, if you could
just tell me--
Look, I'm staring at the
television right now.
You're broadcasting footage of the
wreckage and saying that that's the
pilot, Seth Norris.
Yes, sir?
Well, that's not him.
Please hold.
Who am I speaking with?
Doesn't matter who I am.
You're showing footage of Seth Norris,
and that's not him.
Listen, this guy married his
high school sweetheart at 19.
He always wore
his wedding ring.
And I'm telling you,
there's no ring on that body.
Sir, it's likely the
ring fell off when--
I'm telling ya,
that is not him.
And how actly is it that you
know all about captain Norris?
Because I was supposed to be
flying Oceanic 815 on that day.
That's them.
That's somebody from my team.
What's wrong with you people?
We're here because of you.
I just almost died jumping out of a
helicopter because you called us
for help.
Maybe we should go see
who launched that flair.
Yeah, I mean,
they could be hurt, John.
She's lying.
And whatever they came for,
it isn't us.
- We keep moving forward as planned.
- Sure.
Who are we to argue
with taller ghost Walt?
You know what?
You people do
whatever you want.
I want you to come with us.
I'm not asking for permission.
And if you think you're gonna
bloody stop me from getting to my--
What did you do,
you soof a bitch?
Vest.
What?
Vest. Vest.
Is he alive?
He's got a pulse.
Frank? Frank.
Frank.
Are you okay?
What happened?
We got struck by lightning.
Frank, where's Charlotte?
She bailed out just
before we went down.
I don't know where she is.
Where's the chopper?
I saw a cow.
Lapidus, where's the chopper?
- Where did it crash?
- Crash?
The hell kind of
pilot you think I am?
I put her down safe and
sound right over there.
So this is the team?
You've familiarized yourself
with their profiles?
Unfortunately, yes.
With respect, these are the wrong
people for a mission like this.
None of them have field experience,
military training.
You can't just drop
them in unprotected.
It'll be a disaster.
They're not unprotected.
They have you.
There's only so much I can do.
Your modesty is
positively charming.
This is a high-risk covert
op in unstable territory.
It's dodgy enough without
having to babysit a head case,
ghostbuster, anthropologist
and a drunk.
To be fair,
he's also a pretty good pilot.
It's madness.
What if we find
survivors from 815?
There were no survivors.
Yes, I know.
But what if there
are survivors?
There were nosurvivors
of Oceanic 815.
Don't ask questions.
Just do what you were hired for.
Every member of this team was
selected for a specific purpose.
Everything relies on you getting them
in, getting them out and preventing
anyone from getting killed.
Think you can do that?
Sure.
Why not?
Well?
There's some minor damage,
but the mechanical systems are intact.
So it'll fly, then?
Absolutely.
Can I have the phone now?
Tell you what.
I'll give you the phone if you tell
me what you people are doing here.
I'll tell you what we're doing
here if you give me the phone.
Don'n't say anything
about your sister.
Hello?
Regina, it's Miles.
I need to talk to Minkowski.
Minkowski can't come to
the phone right now.
It's important. Go get him.
Miles, he can't come to
the phone right now.
All right,
have him call me when he can.
I gotta go.
What are you doing with her?
We're taking her with us.
What's the point?
That's-- that's not Naomi.
It's just meat.
Miles, we can't just
leave her here.
Miles is right.
We burned up most of the damn
fuel flying around in that storm.
We barely got enough to
get back to the freighter.
We're not gonna carry
any unnecessary weight.
I'll take her on the next run.
I promise, Dan.
There's a blanket over
there by my backpack.
- Would you grab it?
- Yeah.
Look as bad as it feels?
How bad does it feel?
- What's your name again?
- Juliet.
Juliet.
Juliet what?
- Juliet Burke.
- Juliet Burke...
You weren't on that plane,
were ya?
Miles!
Yeah?
This is Juliet,
and she was not on the plane.
What?
You sure?
You know how many times I
studied that damn manifest?
Believe me,
there's no "Juliet Burke" on that plane.
She's a native.
Really?
Where is he?
Back off!
Where's who?
You wanted to know why we're here?
I'll tell you why we're here.
We're here for Benjamin Linus.
Now where is he?
James, listen to me. Please--
Keep your mouth shut.
You okay?
I feel like I've got a cinder block
on my chest, but I'll survive.
I'm sorry you got shot.
I didn't intend
for that to happen.
Really?
'Cause it seemed like you were
about to shoot me yourself.
What good would
you be to me dead?
Well, I feel much
more comfortable now.
Thanks.
I guess this is the part where I'm
supposed to say, "I told ya so."
James, I stand correct.
You want me to do it?
No, it's my mess.
I'll clean it up.
No, wait!
Danielle, you should escort
Alex away from here.
- No! No!
- Alex, come on, let's go.
- Come on. Alex.
- She's right. Let's go.
Anyone who doesn't want to
see this should leave now.
John, we should
talk about this!
Claire, what if one of those
bullets had hit you or the baby?
John, listen.
I have information
that you need.
I have answers.
What is the monster?
What?
The black smoke, the monster.
What is it?
I don't know.
Good-bye, Benjamin.
Her name is Charlotte Lewis.
Charlotte Staples Lewis.
Born July 2nd, 1979,
Essex, England.
Parents-- David and Jeanette.
Eldest of three, all girls.
She was raised in Bromsgrove,
did her undergraduate studies at Kent,
took her phd in cultural
anthropology at Oxford.
She's here with two other
team members and a pilot.
Their names-- Daniel Faraday,
Miles Straume, Frank Lapidus.
Your instinct was right, John.
These people are a threat,
and if you shoot me, you'll never
know how great a threat they were,
because I know what
they're doing here.
I know what they want.
What do they want?
Me, James. They want me.
How do you know all this?
Because I have a
man on their boat.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:??????