Previously on Lost:
- Who are you?
- Daniel Faraday.
I'm here to rescue you.
I just almost died
jumping out of a helicopter
- because you called us for help.
- She's lying.
Whatever they came for, it isn't us.
Is that from your chopper?
Yeah. That...
Yeah, they reduce the weight load.
What's this for?
Rescuing you and your people...
...I can't really say
it's our primary objective.
Then what is?
Hello. I'm sorry I'm late.
- You must be Dr Burke.
- Juliet.
Juliet. I'm Harper Stanhope.
Please sit.
Today is just a meet and greet
so that we can get to know each other.
Please don't take this the wrong way,
but I really don't think I need therapy.
How about we call it "talking"
instead of therapy?
- OK.
- Good.
Let's talk.
So you've been here a week...
...and what's
your least favourite part so far?
I don't like being treated
like a celebrity.
And is that surprising?
- You're big news right now.
- Yes, I know.
I guess I don't like being
the centre of attention.
It makes me feel isolated.
Alone.
Well, maybe you feel
that all eyes are on you...
...but you're not a celebrity.
And soon enough you'll realise that
you're no different than anyone here.
- I know. I never meant that I...
- Yes?
Harper, I'm sorry for the interruption.
I know you don't like me busting in,
but Ben would like to see the doc.
She's all yours, Tom.
It was nice talking to you, Juliet.
Welcome to the island.
Harper's a real piece of work.
But if you give her a week, she'll
have you crying about your daddy.
I'm speaking
from personal experience here.
Welcome to your humble abode.
This is for me?
The whole house?
You're here to help us with some
very important research, Juliet.
We pulled out all the stops.
Two bedrooms, two baths,
washer, dryer.
Fresh linens, a well-stocked fridge.
And I know you love the opera.
We have all the classics on CD.
Ben, this is amazing.
Seriously, you shouldn't have gone
to all the trouble.
I'm only gonna be here for six months.
Right, of course, but...
...we want you to feel at home.
Need some help?
I'm fine. I just can't seem
to get it steady.
OK.
Nice. Thanks.
Why are you going to all this trouble
when we're about to leave this island?
We still need somewhere
to sleep tonight.
Juliet, have you seen
Charlotte and Faraday?
- All their stuff's gone.
- No, I haven't.
You have the sat-phone, right?
He saw them going into the jungle.
Why didn't he say anything?
You said they are friends.
Aren't they?
We got a lot of ground to cover,
so let's fan out.
If you cut their trail,
call out to me, I'll come to you.
Jack?
Hello, Juliet.
Long time, no see.
What are you doing here?
I came to deliver a message...
from Ben.
The two people you're looking for,
Faraday and Lewis,
they're headed to the Tempest.
And if they figure out
how to deploy that gas...
...then everyone on this island
is going to die.
- Why don't you stop them?
- Because Ben wants you to go.
How can Ben know where they are
when he's a prisoner?
Ben is exactly where he wants to be.
- How am I supposed to stop them?
- By pointing the gun
and pulling the trigger.
Hey!
Who are you?
I'm an old friend of Juliet's.
I just told her where the people
you're looking for are headed.
Maybe you and your gun can go too.
You OK?
I was just looking for some gauze.
I didn't know anyone was here.
How'd you manage that?
I... I work over at the power station.
I pressed up against a transformer.
Take a seat.
Let me take a look at it.
You're Burke, right?
The baby doctor.
What gave me away?
I heard we lost Henrietta this morning.
It's OK. It's not your fault.
Pregnant women
are dying on this island.
I was brought here to help fix that.
So whose fault is it?
Believe me, no one expects you
to fix it overnight.
You have anyone to talk to?
Any friends here?
- Maybe Harper.
- Harper hates me.
We only talk because we have to.
I get the feeling that she's a mean
and spiteful person.
She's my wife.
She's your wife?
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't worry about it. It's OK.
OK, you're... you're set.
Much obliged, ma'am.
Hey, I know this place can wear on you,
but if you need to talk...
...I'm around.
Good to know.
Oh, if you promise not to tell your wife
what I said about her...
...I won't tell anyone you lied
about how you hurt your arm.
I know a chemical burn when I see one.
You got a deal.
By the way...
...I'm Goodwin.
Juliet.
Faraday and Charlotte
are heading for the Tempest.
- The Tempest?
- It's safer if I don't talk about it.
No, talk about it, please.
It's an electrical station
that powers the island.
Why would they go there?
If there's something
you need to tell me...
...now's the time to do it.
What I need is for you to help me.
Will you help me?
If we move all night,
maybe we can still catch them.
Thank you.
I think it's that way.
What happens if I...
What if I can't do it?
Dan.
Look at me.
I know you can do this.
We should get going.
Yeah.
Come on.
It's OK. It's OK. It's Kate.
So they have Miles?
Yeah, but he's fine.
They're treating him fine.
I thought you two
were with Jack at the beach.
What are you guys doing out here?
Jack was trying to communicate
with Sayid and Desmond,
but the sat-phone ran out ofjuice.
It's totally dead.
There's no way we can call the boat.
So we volunteered to get spare batteries
out the packs we threw out the chopper.
So if you threw your pack
from the chopper,
what's that?
This... I just borrowed this.
Mind if I take a look?
Go ahead, Dan, show her.
Batteries, huh?
What's this?
What?
- That woman, what was her name?
- Harper.
- The two of you friends?
- Not exactly.
- She was my therapist.
- You people had therapists?
It's very stressful
being an Other, Jack.
- Seemed hostile, even for a therapist.
- There are things from your past
- you'd rather not talk about.
- Yeah. You read them all in my file.
Trust me, Jack,
you don't want to see my file.
The problem occurs somewhere
during the second trimester
when the mother's immune system
is triggered.
The white blood cell count plummets.
It's like the immune system
turns on the foetus.
- May I?
- Sure.
- Any thought yet on a cause?
- It's really too early to tell,
but only women who have conceived
on the island does it happen to which...
Hey, Juliet.
Ben, I didn't know you were here.
Ethan's out sick.
I have an extra egg salad on rye.
I was just checking if Juliet wants it.
Thanks. I already ate.
I have an appointment
with your wife in ten minutes.
Great. Tell her I said hi.
Oh, will do.
- Ben?
- No, I'm fine.
So, Juliet, what do you think of Ben?
He's great.
Very smart and intense.
Challenging.
- He's been really good to me.
- Of course he has.
You look just like her.
I'm sorry?
I see you and my husband
have become friendly.
Yeah. He's great.
He's been really helpful.
When did you start sleeping with him?
What?
Look, Juliet, I'm not an idiot,
so just tell me.
When did it start?
OK, I'm not doing this. We're done.
No, please respect me enough
to spare me the pretence
that you are actually offended.
I know. I followed you.
Watched you.
- I'm sorry.
- It doesn't matter anymore.
But what does matter
is that you listen to me
and that you believe me.
Now if you continue to have
a relationship with Goodwin...
...there will be consequences.
- I don't want him to get hurt.
- I would never hurt him.
I am not talking about you.
I am talking about Ben.
Hi, John.
Hey, Claire.
Is there something I can do for you?
I want to know
what's going on with Miles.
Right now not a whole lot.
I'm bringing him food and water
until he decides to talk.
I'd like to talk to him myself.
Why would you want to do that?
John, we have to find out
who these people are
and where they came from... and why
they're not interested in rescuing us.
- You don't think I'll get that?
- No, I...
I just think we might be
taking the wrong approach.
I mean, you killed one,
Ben shot one.
Now we're holding one prisoner.
You know, it's not hard to understand
why they might think we're hostile.
I might be just
a little less intimidating.
- It's not going to happen, Claire.
- John.
You do remember what Charlie said
about these people.
All Charlie said
was whose boat it isn't.
Don't you want to know whose boat it is?
- Rabbit today?
- We're running out of chickens.
This didn't have a number on it, did it?
What?
Eat, change. Put your laundry
and dishes by the door.
I'll be back to collect them
in 15 minutes.
So has the revolution begun yet?
What are you talking about?
Well, you're the leader now.
I know it's a tough position.
You have to deal with all those people
second-guessing decisions.
It starts out so innocently, doesn't it?
A question here, a comment there.
And then if you're not careful,
you find you have a full-blown
insurrection on your hands.
Believe me, your people
are gonna be so angry
when they realise
you still don't have a plan.
And I assume you have a plan.
I always have a plan.
Does it involve
you raising $3.2 million?
That's a lot of money.
Wait.
Maybe this will get you started.
Put your laundry and dishes
by the door.
I can help you, John.
We have shared interests.
- Or at least a common enemy.
- Our friends on the freighter.
Not them. The one they work for.
Let me out of here.
Give me some semblance of freedom.
Let me sleep in a bed,
eat with utensils,
and I give you my word
- I'll tell you everything...
- See, there's the problem.
I don't trust your word.
All right, then.
I guess I'll have to show you.
I hope this is good.
I don't know much about wine.
I swiped this off the sub.
There.
Thanks.
I wish we could do this all the time.
I hate that we have to be so... private.
What's the matter with being private?
It's ridiculous. I've been sleeping
on the couch for a year.
Why am I notjust telling her?
I don't think it's a good idea.
Why not?
Ben wouldn't like it.
That's what this is about?
You're worried about Ben?
Why, because he has a crush on you?
- You know?
- Come on, everyone knows.
He follows you around like a puppy.
And you don't think that's a problem?
A little less than a kilometre from here
he has me working with chemicals
that could kill every man, woman
and child if I flipped the wrong switch.
Trust me, Ben has enough on his plate.
The last thing he cares about
is you and me.
I just...
...get the feeling
that he would be upset.
What's Ben gonna do?
Goodwin!
- You see where the tail landed?
- Probably in the water.
You can make that shore in an hour.
Ethan, get up to that fuselage.
There may actually be survivors.
And you're one of 'em.
A passenger. You're in shock.
Come up with a story if they ask.
Stay quiet if they don't.
Listen. Learn. Don't get involved.
I want lists in three days. Go.
Something's wrong. We should've
caught up with them by now.
These people base-jumped
out of a helicopter.
Let's give them
the benefit of the doubt.
Hey. Hey.
It's OK. Hey. It's all right.
It's OK.
Hey.
It's OK. You're all right. Come on.
Take it easy.
- I'll go get her some water.
- Yeah. Thanks.
What happened?
I was going back to the beach and...
I ran into Faraday
and that woman... Charlotte.
I think she hit me.
They disappeared out of camp
last night. Trying to catch up.
Do you know where they were headed?
Some sort of... power station.
Jack.
They had gas masks.
Juliet.
Juliet!
All right, no tricks.
You're not leading me out
into the jungle so you can disappear
or shoot me in the back.
No tricks, John.
We don't even have to leave
the living room.
So let's have it.
We have a deal, right?
How do I know you won't run off and
meet your people first chance you get?
If my people still wanted me they'd
have stormed this camp long ago.
It's behind that picture.
Thirty-six, 15, 28.
"Red Sox"?
I taped over the game.
This is Charles Widmore.
This is the man whose boat
is parked offshore.
This is the man that's been trying
to find the island.
Who's the man in the blindfold?
One of my people that had
the misfortune to get caught.
- How does Widmore know of the island?
- I don't know, but he does.
What does he want?
Three months ago
in Gainesville, Florida,
the Virgin Mary seemed to appear
in a patch of mould
on the side of an old housing complex.
When word got out, over 5,000 people
came to see her face for themselves.
You've survived an airline crash
on this island.
One minute you're in a wheelchair,
the next doing jumping jacks.
If 5,000 people came out
to see a piece of mould,
how many people do you think
would come out to see you?
Charles Widmore
wants to exploit this island.
He'll do everything in his power
to possess it.
Everything I know about Charles Widmore
is contained in this file.
Some of it's vague, some of it's
guesswork, some of it's concrete,
but this is everything,
and now it's all yours.
I'm sorry I didn't tell
you all this sooner...
...but it was the only
bargaining chip I had left.
There's one more thing I need to know.
Your man on the boat,
I want you to tell me who it is.
All right.
But you might want to sit down.
She came through here.
So did they, about
half an hour ahead of her.
- What happened?
- Sorry?
At Locke's. Why did you stay?
I stayed because I had
to find something out.
Are you gonna tell me
or are we gonna keep walking through
the jungle like it doesn't matter?
I stayed to find out if the people
on the freighter know who I am.
If they knew that I'm a fugitive...
...that I'm wanted for murder.
Do they?
Yeah, they know.
We should keep moving.
God knows where Juliet is.
Hi, come on in.
Sorry, have to get this ham
out of the oven, or it'll dry out.
Please, don't mind me.
- How are you feeling, by the way?
- Never better.
Smells delicious.
Ben, I thought this was a dinner party.
Just you and me.
I guess I should've made that clearer.
No, it's fine.
I hope you like dinner rolls.
I do indeed.
I want to thank you for how wonderful
you've been with Zach and Emma.
They're really sweet kids.
Ben, they've been asking me
about their mother in Los Angeles.
- I'm not really sure what to say.
- They'll stop asking in time.
They're children.
Do they really belong here?
They're on the list, Juliet.
Who are we to question
who's on the list and who's not?
Now that we have everyone on the list
for the tail section what about Goodwin?
He's been undercover for three weeks.
He's making a case
for this woman, Ana Lucia.
He thinks she'd be
a valuable member of our society.
But between you and me,
I don't see it.
He feels very passionately about her.
Almost inappropriately so.
After losing Ethan, it's a risk.
Goodwin stays where he's at
right now, Juliet.
There's no reason for him
to hurry back, right?
But his assignment will be over soon.
I promise you.
Warning: Computer switching
to manual operation.
This attempt is unauthorised.
Warning: Manual entry.
Override denied.
Repeated attempts to access
storage tanks
will result in contamination.
Repeated attempts to access
storage tanks...
Hey!
Juliet, what are you doing here?
Final warning.
Manual override failed.
- Step away from the computer.
- I'm so sorry. I can't do that.
Manual override failed.
Counter-measures will begin.
Hey!
One minute to contamination.
Wanna release the gas?
You'll die with the rest of us.
No, no. I'm not trying to release it.
I'm trying to render it inert.
Juliet, I just want to make it safe.
Forty seconds to contamination.
Thirty seconds to contamination.
Warning: Contamination imminent.
Evacuate immediately.
Twenty seconds to contamination.
Whatever he's doing, tell him to stop.
We're trying to disable it
before he can use it against us.
Juliet...
...Iook me in the eye
and tell me you are certain
Benjamin Linus wouldn't use this gas
to kill everyone on this island!
We know he's used it before.
If you wanna stop us,
you have to shoot us both.
Ten seconds to contamination.
- Daniel!
- Yeah, I'm trying.
Come on!
... five...
... four...
... three...
... two...
That... that was a close one.
- What are you reading?
- Shephard's file.
Mikhail dropped it off.
He's a spinal surgeon, Ben.
He has extensive experience
in tumour removal.
- How about that?
- He can help you.
I thought you'd be more excited.
What's wrong?
I need you to come with me.
After our last raid on the tail-section
survivors, they ran off, left the beach.
I sent Pickett and Tom to track
their location. They came across this.
I'm sorry, Juliet.
Sorry about what?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Goodwin.
What happened?
We don't know.
There weren't any witnesses.
I can only assume they found out
he wasn't one of them.
- Guess I should've listened to you.
- Why are you showing me this?
Why did you bring me out here?
What, you mean instead of his wife?
You knew this would happen.
You sent him out here because
you knew this would happen.
You wanted this.
You wanted him to die!
Why?
You're asking me why?
After everything I did to get you here,
everything I've done to keep you here,
how can you possibly not understand...
...that you're mine?
Take as much time as you need.
Kate, it's all right.
They're on our side.
"Our side", Juliet?
She just knocked me unconscious.
Yeah. I'm very sorry about that,
but I had no choice!
Look, Daniel's inside
securing the facility.
If you come with me,
I'll be more than happy to explain
exactly how we just saved your life!
All right, let's go.
I'll take their word for it.
You OK?
He wanted me to kill them.
Ben. He told me to kill both of them.
- How can he tell you anything?
- I don't know.
But he knew how to get to me, knew where
they were going, what they were doing.
Don't you understand?
These people came here
to wage war against Ben.
And Ben's gonna win, Jack.
And when he does, you don't
want to be anywhere near me.
Why not?
Because he thinks that I'm his.
And he knows how I feel about you.
He knows where to find me.
Beat that.
Son of a bitch!
How'd you get so damn good
at horseshoes?
I don't know. Guess I'm just lucky.
What the hell are you doing out?
See you guys at dinner.