These are the last two eggs.
From my own bookshelf?
Help you pass the time.
I've already read it.
You might catch something you
missed the second time around.
Why did you move me from
the rec room down here?
I wanted you under my own roof.
Where are you keeping
your other prisoner?
Miles, is it?
Oh, you don't want to share.
Actually, I was hoping you
would share, Ben, seeing...
as you claim to have a spy on his ship.
I feel for you, John. I really do.
You keep hitting dead ends.
You couldn't find the cabin.
You can't make contact with Jacob.
You're so desperate
to figure out what...
to do next, you're even
asking me for help.
So here we are, just like old times...
except I'm locked in a different room.
And you're more lost than you ever were.
I know what you're trying to do.
It's not gonna work.
Excellent, John.
You're evolving.
Done with your breakfast?
What's that all about?
Who knows?
It's Locke.
Mornin', ladies.
Good morning.
Mornin'.
Mmm, coffee smells good.
Well...why don't I go make you a cup?
Kinda weird, ain't it?
Sittin' on porches, drinking
coffee out of mugs.
Anyway, I found some
clothes about your size.
Hung 'em in a closet.
So after I kick out Hugo...
I'm not moving in with you, James.
Well... then why did you stay?
That's none of your business.
Oh, you got a secret agenda, huh?
Well, if you're
spying for Jack--
I'm not spying for anyone.
- So why don't you tell me--
- Because I don't trust you.
This is about the pregnancy thing.
- James...
- Yeah?
Go home.
Okay, fine.
See you later, then.
Are you ready?
Is there a back entrance?
Yeah, but you're going in the front
door with your head held high, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
Let's do this.
Why'd you do it, Kate?
Coming through.
Hey, folks, we're not
making any statements...
or answering any questions right now.
Excuse us.
The people against
Katherine Anne Austen.
The honorable Arthur
Galzethron presiding.
The bailiff will read the counts.
Will the defendant please rise?
Katherine Anne Austen,
you are charged with...
fraud, arson, assault
on a federal officer,
assault with a deadly weapon, grand
larceny, grand theft auto
and murder in the first degree.
Miss Austen, how do you plead?
Not guilty.
Thus entered.
I'll now hear argument on bail.
Your honor, we are requesting
that the defendant be...
remanded into custody for
the duration of the trial.
Your honor, my client's been
free pending arraignment.
Now suddenly she's a flight risk?
She's the very definition
of a flight risk.
She has one of the most
recognizable faces in America.
Where is she going to run?
Miss Austen, based on your prior...
history, I'm inclined
to agree wh the people.
You are hereby remanded into federal
custody for the duration of your trial.
- Your honor, my-
- Bailiff, please take the defendant into custody.
Sorry.
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-...
sync: ?¬?®??????
edited by rogard
Lost Season 04 Episode04
Albuquerque?
Too hot.
New York?
Too many people.
More than Seoul?
What's wrong with Seoul?
Sun, we're going to leave
this island any moment now.
I learn English...
for you...
to live... in...America.
I want...
to raise my baby at home.
In Korea.
You mean our baby.
Hey, look! Jack!
- Jack!
- You're okay!
Hey, man.
This is, uh, Charlotte and Dan.
Their helicopter already took Sayid
and Desmond back to their freighter.
They can make arrangements to
get all of us off this island.
Where's Kate?
She stayed with Locke.
Hello, Kate.
Is that blood?
I just... killed a chicken.
What can I do for you?
I want to talk to Miles.
Where are you keeping him?
Why do you need to talk to him?
Well, that's personal.
No.
And what gives you the right
to decide whether or not...
You may think this is a
democracy, Kate, because...
of the way Jack ran things.
But this is not a democracy.
Then I guess that
makes it a dictatorship.
If I was a dictator, I would just
shoot you and go about my day.
Dinner's at 6:00 if you're hungry.
Hey, Hurley! Wait.
- You bringing that to Miles?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, Locke asked me to do it.
- Cool.
That dude creeps me out.
He's still in the rec room, right?
No, I moved him to the boathouse that...
You just totally scooby-doo'd me,
didn't you?
Sorry.
You're not gonna let him go, are ya?
No. No, I promise.
Just don't tell Locke it was me.
So the Arab traded you, too, huh?
Do you know who I am?
Excuse me?
Do you know what I did?
What did you do?
Answer the question.
Okay.
I'll tell you what you want to know, but
you gotta do something for me first.
I'm not letting you go.
I don't want to be let go.
I am exactly where I want to be.
What I want...
is one minute... of someone's time.
You bring him to me, and I will tell
you everything I know about you.
Who?
Who do you think?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Listen, the D.A. has decided
to try this case herself,
which means they're gonna
do a full court press,
and we need to start
talking about cutting a deal.
What kind of deal?
Honestly, my best guess,
I'd say she'll take...
a 15-year sentence, and you serve seven.
No way.
If you go to trial, Kate, you're
looking at 20 years on each count,
not to mention a life sentence
on the murder charge.
No.
Kate, you confessed to your mother
that you killed your father,
and now she's their star witness.
So you tell me:
What am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed to win this thing?
Put me on the stand.
And take a chance with
the D.A. crossing you? No.
The way I see it, we've
got one shot at this.
What's that?
We make it about character,
not about what you did or didn't do,
but about who you are.
What do you mean, who I am?
I want him in the courtroom.
Absolutely not.
We need him, Kate. It'll
generate tremendous sympathy.
Duncan, listen to me.
You are not bringing him in here.
All right, you wanna make this
about me, about my character? Fine.
But you are not using my son.
Maybe we should try a number
other than the boat, like...
911.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
We're just having some trouble
getting ahold of their boat.
You haven't heard from Sayid?
You said they left yesterday.
And I'm sure they're fine.
What if Locke was right?
What if these people
are here to hurt us?
Locke has no idea what he's doing.
Then why is Kate with him?
Are you sure he's got Ben in his basement?
I saw Rousseau take
him in there last night.
Does Locke ever go out?
No. He's been in there cooking all day.
He invited us all over for dinner.
Oh, can you get Aaron for me?
Just pick him up and
rock him a little bit.
Yeah, I'm just...
not very good with babies.
I wouldn't want him to get more upset.
Here, I got him.
It's okay.
Here we go, muffin. Yeah. There we go.
You're so good with him.
What?
Just the last thing I ever thought
I'd be good at is being a mum.
You know, you should try it sometime.
Hey, Aaron. Come on, sweetie.
Please rise.
Court is now in session.
Please be seated.
Don't fire me, okay?
What?
We got killed in the opening.
I had to do this.
Does the defense have a witness?
Yes, we do, your honor.
The defense calls Dr. Jack
Shepherd to the witness stand.
Your honor, I'd like to
renew my objection...
to this witness on the
basis of relevance.
And I'm going to renew my
overruling of your objection.
You are to be aware that this
witness did not meet the defendant
until after the alleged crimes
she is being charged with.
He's to be viewed as a
character witness only.
Proceed.
Please raise your right hand.
Do you swear to tell the
truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the
truth, so help you god?
Yes.
Dr. Shephard...
could you please tell the ladies
and gentlemen of the jury
if there are any of
you who don't read...
newspapers or the internet
or watch television...
How you met the defendant?
On september 22, 2004, Kate...
Miss Austen and I were both
passengers on Oceanic flight 815,
which crash-landed on an
island in the south pacific.
Were you aware that miss Austen
was a fugitive being transported
by a United States marshal on that
flight to Los Angeles for trial?
I did learn that eventually, yes.
From the U.S. marshal?
No, the marshal died in the crash.
I never spoke to him.
Miss Austen told me.
Did you ever ask her if she was guilty?
No. Never.
Well, it seems like a
reasonable question. Why not?
I just assumed that there'd
been some kind of mistake.
And why would you think that?
Only eight of us survived the crash.
We landed in the water.
I was hurt pretty badly.
In fact, if it weren't for her,
I would have never made it to the shore.
She took care of me.
She took care of
all of us. She--
She gave us first
aid, water, found food, made shelter.
- She tried to save the other two, but they didn't--
- Stop.
Miss Austen, please sit down.
This has nothing to do
with... with anything.
This is my trial, and I don't
want him to say anything else.
It's fine. I have no
more questions, your honor.
Miss Dunbrook, your witness.
That was very moving, Dr. Shephard.
I only have one question for you:
Do you love the defendant?
Objection.
You opened this door, Mr.
Forrester. I'm going to allow it.
Dr. Shephard?
Do you love Miss Austen?
No.
Not anymore.
So... what do you want to watch--
'Xanadu' or 'Satan's Doom'?
I'm reading.
- Turn that thing down, damn it.
- Sorry.
Hey.
Can I come in?
Sure. I believe you know my roommate.
- Hi, Hurley.
- Hey, Kate.
Got somethin' in your eye, Hugo?
Why don't we talk in the kitchen?
I know it's in a box, but, uh...
it's pretty damn good wine.
I tested it.
So how's the life at Casa di Claire?
Baby Aaron keeping you up all night?
No. No, he's a good sleeper.
Good for you.
You are terrible at this, freckles.
Terrible at what?
You already said you
didn't stay behind for me.
So at least be woman enough to tell
me you wanna use me for somethin'.
I wanna use you for somethin'.
See? Wasn't that hard.
For what?
For Ben.
I want you to help me bust him out.
You wanna play backgammon?
You're on.
Do you think I know what I'm doing?
Do you...
regret following me out here, or are you
worried about what we should do next?
All I know is I'd be a lot more
worried if I was sitting on that beach.
And the rest of the group,
what are they saying?
I think they're saying, 'baa.'
That's the nice thing about sheep.
They're predictable.
But I ain't so sure about Kate.
What do you mean?
I need your word you ain't
gonna do nothin' to her.
- Why would I do anything to her?
- Just give me your word, John.
You know what? Forget it.
No, no. No. All right.
You have my word.
She came to me about an hour ago,
said she wanted my help busting
Ben out of your basement.
Why?
She talked to that guy...
Bruce Lee from the freighter--
the guy you got locked up.
He told her to bring Ben
down to him for a chat.
No, that's impossible.
She doesn't even know where Miles is.
What? The boathouse down by the dock?
If Hugo knows, everybody knows.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Where are you going with that?
Whatever Miles has to say
to Ben, he can say to me.
Son of a bitch.
Come on.
You got one minute. Go.
How about some privacy?
55 seconds.
You know who I am?
Yes.
You know who I work for?
Then you know he's put a lot of
time and energy into finding you.
So now I found you, and I can
tell him exactly where you are.
Or I can lie and tell
him you were already dead.
And I'd be willing to
do that for $3.2 million.
You've arranged this meeting
so you could blackmail me?
It's extortion, if you
wanna get technical.
3.2? Well, why not 3.3 or 3.4?
What makes you think I have
access to that kind of money?
Do not treat me like I'm one of them,
like I don't know who you
are and what you can do.
Your friend Charlotte has
seen me. She knows I'm alive.
I'll take care of Charlotte.
You just worry about
getting me the money.
You have two days.
My present situation is
a little bit restricted.
Can that be amended?
Okay.
- One week, in cash.
- Time's up.
- Don't even think about--
- I said time's up!
Ooh, this is hot.
You got your meeting.
Now I want my answer.
We got your name when
you called the freighter.
Of course, we know about you and
everybody else on the 815 manifest.
Then prove it.
Your name is Katherine Anne Austen.
You're wanted for murder,
fraud, arson, a...
whole bunch of other
stuff I can't remember.
You're a fugitive, got caught in...
Australia, and the feds
are bringing you back.
So, yeah, we know.
If I were you, I'd stay
right here on the island.
Who knows? Maybe you
didn't survive the crash.
Come on.
Go back to your house, Kate.
John, this has nothing
to do with you--
Go back to your house, Kate!
You okay?
I couldn't sleep.
Yeah. The beds take a
little getting used to.
I didn't wake Aaron, did I?
No, Aaron was born on this island.
He can sleep through anything.
John?
What are you doing?
I'd like a... a moment alone with Kate.
Would you excuse us, please, Claire?
It's okay.
Kate, I just need to know
what they said to each other.
Miles told Ben that he would lie to
the people he works for on the boat,
tell them that Ben was
dead, for $3.2 million.
Listen, John, I'm sorry.
I asked you where he was--
You're not welcome here anymore.
I want you gone by morning.
I worked it out so you two can
have a few minutes of privacy.
I don't need any privacy.
You need to talk to her, Kate.
I'll be outside.
Hello, Katherine.
Was it true, what he said?
Dr. Shephard-- that you're a hero.
Why won't you talk to me?
Because, mom, the last time
I tried to talk to you,
when you got sick, when I
risked my life to see you,
you screamed for help
and called the police.
Please.
I don't want to fight
with you, Katherine.
Why are you here?
Because...
I...
It all changed when I
thought you were dead.
My doctors have given me six months
to live for the last four years.
I don't know how long I'm going to last.
I came here to tell you that I...
I don't want to testify against you.
Then don't.
I want to see my grandson.
You came here to make a deal?
I just wanna meet him.
I don't want you anywhere near him.
We're finished.
We're finished!
Oh, hey, freckles.
Are you okay?
Look, I'm sorry I couldn't do nothin'.
I wanted him to think
that you fooled me, too.
No sense in him not trusting both of us.
He wants me gone by tomorrow.
What, he... banished you?
Well, I un-banish you.
You can stay right...here.
This is my house.
Okay, me and Montezuma's house.
You're gonna be all right.
I'll keep you safe.
Time.
Okay, tell me.
What do you remember?
Okay, uh, queen of diamonds.
Then we... six... of... clubs.
Sorry.
And we have the red 10
of...hearts, maybe?
It's two out of three.
It's not bad.
It's progress.
Three cards, Charlotte.
Is that progress?
Hey.
Been calling your boat all day.
Why isn't anyone answering?
We're here. How should we know?
If they're not answering,
then they're probably--
Now are you telling me there
is only one line on that boat?
There is another number that we're
only supposed to use in emergencies.
It's an emergency.
Put it on speaker.
Yeah?
Regina, it's Charlotte.
Why are you calling me on this number?
Minkowski wasn't answering.
The people on the island
want to talk to...
their friends, make
sure they're all right.
What... friends?
They left last night.
Frank took 'em up in the helicopter.
What do you mean, they took off?
I thought the helicopter was with you.
Morning.
Listen, I don't know what
you think you're doing,
- but you're wasting your time.
- Open your mouth.
Open your mouth.
Wide.
Don't talk. Bite down. Bite down.
I realize that when I tied
you up in here the other day,
I made the mistake of
failing to introduce myself.
My name is John Locke,
and I'm responsible...
for the well-being of this island.
Eventually, Miles, you're
gonna tell me who you are
and you're gonna tell me
about the people on the boat
and you're gonna tell me why
you're so interested in Ben.
In the meantime, however, you're
gonna keep your mouth shut.
I learned something yesterday.
No use having rules if there's no
punishment for breaking them.
You'll be fine if you
bite down on the trigger.
Enjoy your breakfast.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Just--slow down. Slow.
Oh, Come on.
It's not like we ain't
never done it before.
Yeah, I'm cool we didn't
go all the way last night.
I get it.
You were sad.
But, I mean, how can you resist after
that whole,'I'll keep you safe' thing?
No. Sawyer... just...
What?
What? What'd I say?
Just... forget it.
Oh, right.
You still think you might be pregnant.
I'm not worried.
And I'm not pregnant.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I mean...whoo!
Would it have been the
worst thing in the world?
Yes! Yes, it would've been
the worst thing in the world.
What would we have done with a baby?
I'm going back to the beach.
Beach?
What, you're leavin' because of this?
That's that?
You crawl up in my bed one
second, the next, you're just--
Good-bye, James.
Don't make this about me, Kate.
You didn't want a baby
any more than I did.
You're just lookin' for some excuse
to split, and now you got one.
Well, that's all right, freckles.
I ain't gonna hold it against you.
I'm just gonna sit right
here in my comfy bed,
because in about a week,
you'll find some reason to get pissed
at Jack and bounce right back to me.
Miss Dunbrook.
Are the people ready to proceed?
May we approach the bench, your honor?
Please.
Unfortunately, your honor, our
chief witness, Diane Jansen,
the mother of the defendant, is unable
to testify because of medical reasons.
How long will you need?
I can't say right now.
What I'll do is grant
a recess for lunch,
but be prepared to proceed with
your case after we return.
This court is now in recess.
All rise.
We have to talk.
My key witness spoke to her daughter
yesterday, and now she's got cold feet.
Quit posturing, and let's get to it.
What are you offering?
Four years in.
No jail time.
Kate Austen is a worldwide
hero who saved...
five other peoples'
lives after a plane crash
and nearly starved to
death on a deserted island,
and after all that, you
put this woman on trial...
for rescuing her mother
from an abusive husband.
If you think that jury is gonna
give her actual time, then...
you must have a hell
of a closing, Melissa.
All right.
Time served, plus 10
years' probation and...
agreement that she does
not leave the state.
What does that matter?
- She can go anyw--
- I'll take it.
No. Wait, Kate--
Give me something to
sign, and I'll sign it,
and then I walk out the back door.
I just...
I just want this to be over.
I can do that.
10 years' probation, and you stay put.
I have a child.
I'm not going anywhere.
Hey.
How did you know I'd be here?
Uh, your...your lawyer
gave me the heads-up.
He owed me one.
Thank you... for saying what you did.
You're welcome.
You know, Jack, I've heard you
say that story so many times,
I'm starting to think you believe it.
I just-- I just wanted to tell
you that what I said in there...
I didn't mean it.
You wanna follow me?
Come by for a visit?
I... I actually have to
get over to the hospital,
but, um, maybe you and I could grab
some coffee together or something?
I know why you don't
wanna see the baby, Jack.
But until you do, until you want to...
there's no...you and me going for coffee.
But, um...
if at any time you change
your mind, come and see us.
Yeah. Okay.
Bye.
Hello?
Kate!
I'm so glad you're back.
He missed you so much.
Did you keep him away from the tv?
Absolutely.
I just put him down for a nap.
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Hi, mommy.
Hi, Aaron.