Previously on Lost:
- We're gonna have to take the boy.
- Dad!
Walt!
No!
I'm going after my son.
I'm going after my son,
And nobody is gonna stop me.
We need him!
One of our people was captured by yours.
- So go get'em back.
- We can't do that, but you can.
And if you do, we'll let
you and Walt go free.
I'll do it. Give me the gun.
I'll kill him.
Michael?
You lived up to your word.
We live up to our word, too.
You're gonna take this boat
and follow a compass bearing of 3-2-5,
and if you do that exactly,
you and your son will find rescue.
Who are you people?
We're the good guys, Michael.
- Walt!
- Dad!
Come here! Come here!
Thank you all for your patience.
I know it's taken me a few days to...
figure out our next move,
but I don't want to do anything
until I knew more about our situation.
You deserve to know everything that I do,
so... no more secrets.
As you all know,
Miles here and three of his people
came to the island about a week ago.
So I brought him up from the boathouse
to share with us
exactly why they're here.
We're here for him.
Um, we kind of, like,
knew that forever ago.
Well, all right then.
Problem solved.
How soon do we turn him over?
We can't turn him over.
And why the hell not?
Because once they have me,
their orders are to kill
everyone else on the island.
Wait. so...what, he's one of us now?
You're--you're gonna protect him?
He tried to kill you, John.
Yeah. He won't even tell us who
his spy on the boat is.
It's Michael.
What?
My spy on the freighter is Michael.
I'm sorry.
You mean the same guy that killed
two women in cold blood
to set this little bastard free?
And then sold all of us out
so he could get off the island,
that Michael?
Yes, James.
That Michael.
The rules of desertion...
still apply to everyone.
Nobody leaves this ship
without my say-so!
I'm not beating these men to scare you.
I beat them to save your lives!
Do you remember what happened
to the last two men
who took off in this boat?
Remember what happened to Minkowski?
As soon as we get the engines fixed,
we're back in the hunt.
In the meantime,
everybody just hold on.
Johnson!
Yes, sir.
Clean this mess up.
Sir.
Hello, Michael.
- Not now, man.
- Yes, right now.
Why are you on this boat?
I'm here to die.
Hey!
That was a nice meetin', John,
but I thought there wouldn't gonna
be any more secrets.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the 3 million bucks
your buddy here asked for.
Yeah.
Miles offered his loyalty
in exchange for the money.
But as I haven't seen
a bank on the island,
I didn't think it worth mentioning.
Somethin' funny?
Linus will find a way to get it.
And how will he do that?
He wants to survive.
And considering a week ago
you had a gun to his head,
and tonight he's eating pound cake...
I'd say he's a guy who gets what he wants.
It's fine. Okay, thanks.
Bye, guys.
Alex?
May I have a word with you?
I think we've heard enough
from you for one night.
I'm sorry. You're just gonna have
to listen to a little more.
It's okay.
What do you want?
This is a map to the temple.
It's a sanctuary.
It may be the last safe
place on this island.
How come we don't know about this?
Well, it wouldn't be a sanctuary
if I told everyone, would it?
The rest of our people are already there.
If you leave now, you can
get there in a day and a half.
If it's safe, why don't we all go--
Hurley, Claire, the baby?
Because the temple's
not for them, Karl.
It's only for us.
These people that are coming--
they know who I am, Alex.
They're here to capture me.
They'll kill anybody
that gets in their way.
If they knew who you were,
that you were my daughter,
they would use you to get to me.
We don't have much time.
Maybe he's right.
I agree.
We should go.
These people-- you said they're dangerous.
More dangerous than you?
Yes.
But your mother will protect you.
Okay, now go.
Where is he?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
He's in the engine room.
I don'understand it.
It should be working.
Gaskets are all corroded.
Can I help you?
The captain sent us down
to help with the repairs.
Oh, thanks. We're okay.
Hey, Jeff, man, you know what?
We need a pressure valve.
You mind grabbing one
from the, uh, supply room?
Not at all.
You shouldn't be here.
Hey, Sayid, what are you doing?
- Why are you here?
- Listen...
If they see me talking to you--
Then talk quickly.
- You won't understand it!
- I'll understand perfectly, Michael.
You just start from the beginning
and explain how you came
to be on this boat.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to wake you, Mr. Dawson.
It's...
What happened to me?
You were in a car accident.
It's a miracle you're alive.
How badly am I hurt?
Shh. You just need to rest now.
It's a cold night.
I brought you some extra blankets.
Ugh. Let's get some light in here.
Now I thought I heard someone shout,
and something tells me it wasn't him.
You okay?
You're lucky to be alive.
EMTs say they found you in a wrecked car.
There's a note pinned to your chest.
You didn't have any I.D. on you.
You want to tell me your name?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
You want me to call Walt?
What?
The note pinned to your chest.
It was written to 'Walt.'
You want me to call him?
No.
Okay, then.
Hey, Ma.
Can I... come in?
No. You know the answer to that.
- I wanna see him.
- No.
Just let me talk--
I don't know what you said to that boy,
but whatever it was,
he doesn't want to see you.
Please, Ma. He's my son.
I have a right.
I thought you were dead.
They said your plane crashed
in the middle of the ocean,
but you show up here fine and dandy,
only I can't tell anybody but you or Walt,
I can't call you by your real names.
He barely talks to me,
but he does wake up screamin'
in the middle of the night,
and I'm the one that's got to tell him
it's gonna be okay.
So until you can explain to me
where you were for over two months
and what happened...
you gave up your rights.
Will you, uh...
Will you tell him I love him?
Yeah.
What can I do for ya?
How much can you give me for that?
Why is there Chinese writing all over it?
It's Korean. And-- the
guy who gave it to me.
You don't look like you speak Korean.
I'll give you $300 for it.
I'm not looking for money.
What are you looking for?
I want a gun. I want a gun with bullets.
Come on. Let's just get this done.
Help me just get this done.
Excuse me, sir. You got the time?
No, man. No.
Come on, Michael.
How about for an old friend?
Manhattan, huh?
We let you leave one island,
you just go to another one.
Will you just relax?
I just came here to--
Now are you ready to talk like adults?
Yeah.
Enough!
Do it. Go ahead, do it!
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
How do you find me?
We are the ones who
sent you home, Michael.
Did you honestly think we
weren't gonna keep tabs?
What do you want?
Your help.
Why would I help the son of a bitch
who kidnapped my son?
We gave him back to
you in one piece, Mike.
You're the one who lost him.
You told him, didn't you?
You couldn't carry the guilt
of what you did to those
two women all by yourself,
so you shared it with a 10-year-old kid.
Is that why you wanna
kill yourself, Michael?
Because that's the way
he looks at you now?
Because he knows you're a murderer?
Go away!
I got some bad news for you, amigo.
You can't kill yourself.
The island won't let you!
What'd you say?
No matter how bad you want to,
no matter how many different ways you try,
It won't happen.
Give it a shot if you don't believe me.
You got more work to do, Mike.
When you figure that out,
I'm in the penthouse at the Hotel Earle.
The wreckage of Oceanic flight 815
has been found.
This footage confirms
the airplane did, in fact, crash at sea.
At these tremendous depths,
there is little hope of
recovering any remains.
Investigators are equally skeptical
about the chances of retrieving
Oceanic 815's black box.
The real story behind
what happened to this fateful airliner
may have been lost along with
the 324 passengers onboard.
But even with this tragic discovery,
the victims' families were hoping today...
I didn't expect you that fast.
Is this the guy who hit you
with the champagne bottle?
Yeah, but I had it coming.
Arturo, Michael and I have
some business we have to attend to.
- Will you get some air?
- Of course.
Ciao.
Help yourself to the chow.
I don't make it to the
mainland too often...
So when I do, I like to indulge myself.
So you people can just... come and go?
Some of us. You want a drink?
What I want is for you to tell me
what my plane is doing at
the bottom of the ocean.
That's not your plane. It's a phony.
A man named Widmore put it down there,
and he staged the whole wreck.
Staged? Why would he stage a--
Because he doesn't want
anyone else finding
where the real plane ended
up... except for him.
I'm supposed to believe this?
Did the bullet bounce off your skull,
or did the gun just jam on you?
Prove it.
Sorry?
Prove that this guy, Widmore,
did what you say he did.
Prove it.
That's the cemetery in Thailand
where Widmore dug up the
300-odd corpses he needed.
And the purchase order for the old 777
bought through a shell company,
and the shipping logs
for the freighter he used
to drop the whole mess
down a trench deep enough
to guarantee that no remains
are ever gonna be identified.
Do you have any idea what it would cost
to bring those bodies up?
What you want from me, man?
In a few days,
a freighter is porting in Fiji.
It's Widmore's boat.
We have reason to believe
he's finally found
the coordinates of the island,
and he's heading right for it.
So congratulations, Michael.
Your shore leave is over.
You just got a job on that boat.
Meet Kevin Johnson.
You're joining the crew
in Fiji as a deckhand.
You want me to go undercover?
Why the hell would I go back
to work for you people?
Because if Widmore finds the island,
it's good night for everybody on it.
He'll kill them all
without thinking twice.
You wanna redeem yourself
for what you did?
This is your only chance.
You can save all their lives.
No. I can't. I can't go
back to that island.
I didn't say you were
going back to the island.
You're going on that boat so
you can swab decks, Michael.
You're going so you can
kill everyone onboard.
Hey.
You are engineer?
Nah.
Just a deckhand.
Well, we're all equals on this boat...
as long as you play decent hold'em.
I'm George... Minkowsky.
Kevin Johnson.
Ah, nice to meet you, Kevin.
All right, well, why don't you go check in
with Naomi over there, and, uh,
I'll be seeing you? Welcome.
I'm reporting for duty. Kevin Johnson.
Naomi Dorrit. Pleasure.
So you're from the States, yeah?
New York.
Yeah, I could tell from the accent.
Manchester?
How'd you guess? You can head onboard.
Oh, uh, one of these crates
was delivered for you.
I'll have it divered to your berth?
Yeah. Thanks.
Welcome aboard, Kevin.
Your name isn't Kevin.
Don't worry.
80% of the people on this boat
are lying about something.
Orange?
No, thanks.
Yeah?
How was your trip?
I figure flying can't be
too much fun for you.
What do you want?
You get your care package?
Yeah.
Wait a day or two until
you're out in the open sea,
then you're good to go.
You can stow your gear
downstairs, all right?
Welcome aboard, Keamy.
Oh, you met some of 'em now.
Got some names and faces,
and you're gettin' cold feet, huh?
Yeah, actually, I am.
Well, here are a few more names for ya:
Sun, Sawyer, Jack.
Sun, Sawyer, Jack,
Claire, her baby.
And the only way you're
gonna save their lives
is if you man up and get on that boat.
Or maybe you wanna come back
and explain to your kid
how you let all of them die, too.
It's game time. Are you in or out?
I'm in.
Good. Then ditch your phone
and go do your job.
I am going first,
and that's all there is to it.
No offense but I was flying these things
when you were still in grade chool.
If anybody's gotta go
first, it should be me.
Yeah, I need you here
to transport the science team, Frank.
What the hell are you gonna be doing?
That's need-to-know. You don't.
So much for the fairer sex, huh?
Frank Lapidus, chopper pilot.
Kevin Johnson.
Deckhand.
So what's your story, Kevin?
Sorry?
How'd you end up on this tub?
Looking for a little adventure.
Ah, adventure.
Yeah.
Well, how do you like this for adventure?
You ever hear about Oceanic 815?
Yeah.
What would you say if I told you
the plane they found in that trench
wasn't Oceanic 815?
Then what is it?
You know those nuts that think
the moon landing was faked?
Well, this is like that...
Only real.
That's why I signed up for this trip,
because the owner of
this boat believes me.
- Charles Widmore.
He believes that 815 is
still out there somewhere.
I mean, can you imagine
what would happen...
if we found some of those people alive?
Pull!
Another clip.
Good job.
Pull!
Kill shot! Yeah!
What are you guys doing?
What's it look like we're doing?
We're shooting things.
Pull!
I, uh...
thought we were going
on a rescue mission.
Don't you have something to mop up?
Come on. Let's go.
Pull!
You can do this, man. you can do this.
7... 1...
7-7-6
7-7-6.
Okay.
Don't do it, Michael.
I love you, Walt.
(Not yet)
What, are you going Nicholson on us?
What?
You know, Jack Nicholson in 'The Shining,'
when he's bouncing that
ball against the wall?
Next thing you know,
you're gonna go after
your wife with an ax.
I'm not married, man.
Well, I'm sorry to interrupt,
but you got a call.
A call?
Yeah. from the mainland.
They patched it through to the radio room.
It's gotta be a mistake, man.
Nobody even knows I'm here.
Well, you're the only
Kevin Johnson onboard,
so somebody knows you're here.
Said he really needs to talk to you.
His name's Walt.
Yeah, here you go.
Hey, uh...
It's kind of personal.
Mind if I take this alone?
Take your time, Kev.
You just push this yellow button
- and, uh, turn this knob on the console.
- Got it.
Okay.
Walt?
I'm so sorry, Michael,
but he's still in New York.
So I'm afraid you're stuck with me.
Michael?
Are you still there?
You put me on this boat,
talked me into blowing it up,
and when I push the damn button,
a flag pops up.
You actually activated the bomb?
It's not a bomb! It's a...
It's a joke.
There are people on your boat
who are innocent.
They have no idea
that the man they work for is a monster,
a killer without conscience
or a greater purpose.
I had to show you the
difference between him and me.
When I'm at war, I'll do
what I need to do to win,
but I will not kill innocent people.
Ana Lucia and Libby...
They were innocent.
You killed them, Michael.
No one asked you to.
I don't blame you, Michael.
We did you have your boy.
****
And what wouldn't a man do for his son?
What do you want... from me?
I want you to compile a list of names...
Every person on your boat.
When I call again, you'll
give me that list.
Then you will disable
the radio room you're sitting in.
When the crew is disoriented
by their lack of communication,
you'll take out the engines, too.
That way, the boat can
never get to this island,
and your friends will be safe.
Will you do that for me, Michael?
Yeah.
Then consider yourself
one of the good guys.
So you're telling me...
that you're working for Benjamin Linus?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I'm telling you.
Hey, Sayid.
Guys!
Hold it! Uhh!
Let me go! What are you doing?!
Shut your mouth.
What the hell is this?
This man is not who you think he is.
He was a passenger on
Oceanic flight 815.
I spent two months with him on the island
before he betrayed us.
This is the man who
sabotaged your radio room.
He destroyed the ship's engine,
and his name isn't Kevin Johnson.
It's Michael Dawson,
and he's a traitor.
Let's stop here and drink.
Two minutes, then we keep moving.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Karl.
I don't know.
I just have a bad feeling about this.
What if your dad is... playing us?
Look, I don't like taking
orders from my dad
any more than you do.
But I know he doesn't want me to get hurt.
Well, at least we've
got something in common.
I promise not to tell if you won't.
Alex!
Karl...
Karl, Karl! No!
Come on. Come on.
He's gone.
Duck!
No, no, we have to get Karl.
- He is gone. He's gone!
- No...
He's gone! Listen to me.
I need you to take my hand.
On the count of three, we're going to run.
Can you do that with me?
I love you.
I love you very much, Alexandra.
Are you ready?
One...
Two...
Three!
Wait! Wait! Don't! I'm Ben's daughter!
I'm his daughter!
edited and synced by rogard