Jack?
Jack!
Jack, I need you to wake up.
Can you hear me?
You okay?
Come on! come on! I just wanna know why.
What happened?
He knows somethin'!
I want the truth! I don't know. that's the truth.
I'm telling you, I don't know why, but there's no signal now. signal?
What, there was a signal when you called them last night. that's right.
So--so--so what? now they're just ignoring us?
How are we supposed to know why they're not answering?
Oh, who's talking to you? and in case you haven't noticed,
We're not on the bloody boat, are we? just watch your tone, red.
I just wanna know why. hey!
Everybody just needs to calm down, okay? jack,
These people are lying to us.
I know they're lying. I know it.
Sooner or later, their people are gonna come back for them,
And when they do, we'll be waiting for them.
Unless they run off again. listen to me.
Jack, are you all right? no, I'm fine.
We just have to be patient, okay?
I've gotten us this far.
I said I was gonna get us off the island--all of us.
I promised that I would.
Jack?  Jack?  Jack?
Jack? jack? jack?
Jack
Jack.
Is he all right?
Jack?
Jack
Jack.
Hello?
Dr. shephard?
Just confirming your 11:00 consult with ms. berenberg.
It was moved up yesterday,
And I know how you are with your calendar.
Yeah. yeah, I remember, jane. I'll, um... I'll be in there.
Thank you, doctor. all right. bye.
Ow. son of a bitch.
A-rod.
Morning.
Morning yourself.
I bought you a razor.
What, you don't like the scruff?
Razor's by the sink, jack.
Morning.
"alice took up the fan, and as the hall was very hot,
"she kept fanning herself
"all the time she went on talking,
"'dear, dear. how queer everything is today.
"'and yesterday, things went on just as usual.
"'i wonder if I've been changed in the night.
Let me think. was I the same when I got up this morning?'"
"'but if I'm not the same, the next question is,
"who in the world am i?'
Aha, that's the great puzzle."
You're a natural.
Yeah?
Yeah.
My old man used to read me that story.
Really?
What?
It's just...
It's just sweet hearing you say nice things about your dad.
I don't say nice things about my dad?
Well, he was a good storyteller. I'll give him that.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just, i... I love seeing you with him.
I'm so glad you changed your mind.
I'm so glad that you're here.
Me, too.
Keep him in the shade. I'll get him some water.
Give--give him some air, guys.
You okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine. I'm good. I'm good.
Hey, what happened? he passed out.
You fainted?
I'm fine. I'm just, uh... just a little dehydrated.
No, jack. you're not okay. you're burning up.
I'm fine. I'm fine. I just...
Just need to get a little rest. jack--
I'm fine.
You okay? yeah, just a bit woozy.
How's your head?
It's better. bit of a headache,
But at least I'm not seeing things anymore.
Yeah? what'd you see?
Back off, donger.
I'm just making conversation. let's make some time.
I wanna cover more ground before we gotta camp tonight.
If we hoof it, we can make it to the beach by noon tomorrow.
No!
What?
Who's danielle and karl?
Y-you mean rousseau? the french woman?
Oh, my god.
Is this your french woman?
Karl
Karl.
How'd you know they were down there?
Your buddies do this?
They're not my buddies, man.
I didn't sign up for this.
Can we just--can we just get out of here, please? can we just go?
Yeah, yeah, of course. but don't worry.
Once we get back to the beach, everything's gonna be fine.
All right?
Come on.
Let's go.
I hate being sick.
What do you think it is?
It's food poisoning.
What makes you think that?
I've got some cramping, dehydrated, nausea.
I respectfully disagree.
Do you?
You want to lift your shirt up?
If it's food poisoning, you got nothing to worry about.
It's your appendix, jack.
When did the pain start?
Yesterday.
Has it ruptured?
Not yet.
Well...
I guess we're just gonna have to take it out.
Do you remember where the medical station is?
-Or don't you? -Yes, I remember.
These are the instruments that I need you to bring back.
-You'll find them in the drawers in the exam room. -"clamps"? sutures"?
Juliet, I don't know what these look like.
I can help you. I'm familiar with surgical instruments.
I thought you were a physicist. Yeah, well,
I've done some animal autopsies, too, so if--if-- no.
We can't trust them. -See, Dan? I told you.
They're convinced we're trying to kill 'em.
-Might as well keep playing the part. -Damn it, charlotte.
That right there, that right there.
Your--your attitude-- your very bad attitude--
It's exactly why they don't trust us.
Come on.
Juliet, please.
Don't blame us for--for this, for whatever is happening.
We're scientists. We don't want anyone to get hurt.
We just wanna help. Please let us help.
Either of them tries to run? Shoot 'em in the leg.
Get back here as fast as you can. Okay.
Thank you.
We need to create a sterile environment.
Find a hard surface, wash it down,
Gather as many tarps as you can.
Hey, juliet.
If everything that we need is at the medical station,
-Then why don't we just bring jack there? -Because if we move him,
There's a good chance that his appendix will rupture.
And if that happens, he's gonna die.
Don't even think about it.
What?
Don't look at her. Don't talk to her.
Don't mess with her.
You got a restraining order. 20 feet.
What are you, her big brother?
No. I'm the guy who's gonna put a boot in your face
Unless you say, "yeah. I getcha."
Yeah. I getcha.
Honey, I am sure Jack is gonna be okay.
An appendectomy
Is just about the most common kind of surgery there is.
That's not what I was thinking about.
I was thinking, "why did he get sick?"
Why? It's just-- it's just bad luck.
The day before we're all supposed to be rescued,
The person that we count on the most
Suddenly comes down with a life-threatening condition,
-And you're chalking it up to bad luck? -Well, what are you saying,
That--that Jack did something to offend the gods?
People get sick, Rose. -Not here.
Here, they get better.
When was the last time you did this?
An appendectomy or shaving a man's stomach?
In my residency.
I did a lot of 'em back then.
Then you know the incision needs to be
2 inches lower than where you're shaving.
I'm just cleaning the area.
Thank you.
I wanna talk you through it.
What?
I don't want to be unconscious.
We can use the lidocaine
To numb the area.
And then I can watch the procedure,
Help you out.
And, uh, how are you gonna watch
Flat on your back with my hand in your abdominal cavity?
We can use a mirror. kate can hold it.
If someone's going to be in there,
Shouldn't it be someone with medical experience?
-Bernard's a dentist-- -No, I want it to be kate.
Okay.
Don't worry, Ms. berenberg. You're in good hands.
Thank you.
-I'll see you tomorrow at 5:00 a.m.? -Mm-hmm.
And remember, no solid food. okay?
-Thank you, doctor. -Have a good evening.
Jack?
Will you take a look at this x-ray?
-Uh, it's in the L4. I wanna know what you think. -The L4. yeah. yeah.
Oh, Dr. Shephard, there's a call for you.
It's a dr. stillman from Santa rosa hospital,
Says it's about a friend of yours.
He's refusing to take his meds,
And he's stopped sleeping.
What about his therapy sessions?
Therapy's... been rendered useless.
And why is that?
Because he doesn't think I exist.
Hey, hurley.
Hey, jack.
Why aren't you taking your meds?
Cause we're dead...
All of us.
All the oceanic six-- we're all dead.
We never got off that island.
Hurley
Hurley...
That is not true.
What'd you do today?
What did I do today?
I, uh...
I woke up, took a shower.
Uh, kate and I fed the baby.
I thought you didn't want anything to do with aaron.
I changed my mind after the trial.
Living with kate...
Taking care of aaron...
It all seems so perfect...
Just like heaven.
Just because I'm happy
Doesn't mean that this isn't real, hurley.
I was happy, too, jack...
For a while, anyway.
Then I saw charlie.
He likes to sit with me on the bench
Out on the front lawn.
It's pretty cool, actually.
Okay.  so what do the two of you talk about?
Well, yesterday, he told me you were gonna be coming by.
He wanted me to give you a message.
A message?
He made me write it down so I wouldn't mess it up.
"you're not supposed to raise him, jack."
Does that make any sense?
No, that... doesn't make any sense.
Do you think he means aaron?
Take your meds, hurley.
Just take 'em.
Hey, jack?
Charlie said someone's gonna be visiting you, too.
Soon.
We're here.
Why don't you let me go first?
Um, you know, make sure everything's safe.
Okay.
Be careful, dan.
Absolutely.
Do you think she knows he likes her?
She's a woman. She knows.
Jin. Come on.
Where do you suppose all this power's coming from?
Add that one to the list, dan.
Let's just grab the equipment and go, shall we?
Are you all right?
This is where Juliet brought me.
This is where I saw our baby.
They're not going to help us, Jin.
Don't worry about them.
I promise you Sun.
I will get you and our baby off this island.
Whoa! hey, you want a hand with the baby?
Oh, no, thanks. I'm fine.
You sure? I'm good with kids. what part of "restraining order"
Don't you understand?
Get behind me, claire.
Who the hell are you?
-Lapidus?  -Miles?
Lapidus? miles?
You two know each other?
You gotta hide, man, right now. what?
Keamy's coming back,
And if he sees you, he'll kill all of ya.
And he's close, man. you gotta hide now!
Go! hide! come on.
Just hide!
Come on. come on. let's go!
Where's the chopper? it's about a click back that way.
Did you bring the kit? yeah, it's right here.
Jeez, man, he looks bad. what the hell happened?
You do your job. I'll do mine.
Okay.
It's gettin' dark, man.
We gotta leave now.
Mr. keamy, we gotta get back to the chopper.
Keamy, we gotta get back, cause I'll tell ya right now,
I am not flying faraday's bearings at night.
I'm not gonna do it.
So if you wanna get back, we gotta leave right now, sir.
Fine. you lead the way.
Come on.
Okay. come on.
Watch it now.
The tent's all set. everything's ready.
Good. thanks.
Listen, I could use an extra pair of hands in there.
You wanna help me out? um, I don't... I don't think that's a good idea.
It's just holding a mirror.
Jack wants to watch the surgery, "talk me through it."
What?
I'm just surprised
He's not taking it out of himself by now.
Jack
Jack.
What are you doin'?
I don't need a stretcher. I can walk 50 feet. I'll help you.
They're gonna be back with the instruments soon.
We need to be ready to go as soon as they get back.
See you in there.
So it looks like I'm gonna be your nurse.
Wouldn't be the first time.
Listen, um...
If something happens to me-- shut up, Jack.
Fair enough.
Kate?
Wake up, Kate.
What time is it?
It's late. I just got home.
Were you working?
No. i...
I just... had to stop and get something.
It just took a while.
What's going on? what's wrong?
The other night, when I was reading to aaron,
You said...
That I was a natural.
Do you really...
Do you really think that I'm good at this?
Yeah.
You're good at this.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Of course I will. yes.
Look, they're back.
Did you find everything?
Yes, ma'am. entire list.
Is he okay?
For now. sun, we need to sterilize these.
There's a pot of water boiling over here.
Charlotte
Charlotte.
Yeah?
I konw you understand me.
Pardon?
I know you speak Korean.
You smiled when Sun and I talked about you
And you were listening to us at the station
I'm sorry.
Perhaps I can get your wife to translate--
If you continue to lie...
I'm going to hurt your friend Daniel.
I'm going to break his fingers one at a time.
Do you understand that?
What do you want?
When the helicopter comes for you...
You're going to take my wife off this island.
What about you and the rest of your friends?
Just get her on the helicopter.
You know, Jack,
They found some chloroform at the medical station.
I could knock you out.
Wouldn't you rather be dreaming about something nice back home?
No, I'll manage with the lidocaine.
Kate
Kate.
Just hold it right there.
Okay, now this is gonna numb the area of the first incision.
After that, I would like to be able to tell you
You're not gonna feel a thing, but... you will.
You ready?
Okay. here we go.
Okay, Jack. one more.
Oh! okay, try not to move.
Just stay still.
Spreader. Kate, i-i can't see it.
Sorry. don't worry about the mirror. just stay still. spreader.
That's good. that's good. yeah.
This is it.
That's good.
Knock him out, bernard. no! no. hey.
Not wanna be unconscious.
You don't want to be out of control. Kate.
Kate, you need to leave. bernard! no. Kate.
Kate, you need to go. bernard! please. no!
Kate, get out of here! bernard. Kate...
-Jack -Kate
Jack. Kate.
Kate, get outta here! damn it, bernard! knock him out!
I'm sorry, Jack, but I agree.
Ryan Laker
Laker, ryan.
Patient is male, 36.
Osteoblastoma is present
In the posterior area of the lumbar.
I am recommending biopsy for...
Jack?
You okay?
Uh, yeah. I'm--i'm... I'm okay.
I, uh...
I just, uh...
The, um, the smoke detector was...
Was beeping, and I just...
Okay. thank you for keeping us safe.
Erika, um...
Do you mind doing me a favor?
Yeah, sure.
Can you write a script for...
Clonazepam?
For you?
Yeah, um... I just got a lot going on right now,
And I'm just a little snowed under
With all my caseload, and Kate and I got engaged.
Just... not sleepin' very well at night, you know? just...
Thank you.
You know, getting engaged
Is supposed to help reduce stress, not create it.
Yeah. you're right.
Maybe you should talk to someone.
I'll do that.
Good night.
Yeah, I'll just have the nanny stay
For an extra couple hours.
Jack's never home before 8:00 anyway.
I could stay for at least an hour.
I-i gotta go. Jack's home. Yeah, okay.
I'll call you later. Bye.
Hey.
Hey.You scared me.
Sorry. I thought you'd be in bed.
Who was that?
That was Noreen.
Noreen?
Yeah. She's one of the moms from the park.
What?
Nothing. I just...
Never heard you mention her before.
Well, now you have.
I'll see you upstairs.
Dad?
Hey.
Don't worry.
It went well.
She did good.
She said you could go back inside if you want to.
Thank you.
Okay.
He didn't lose that much blood.
I got the appendix out
And put everything back where it belongs, I think.
So he's gonna be okay?
He should be fine.
We just have to talk him into resting.
Good luck with that.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
Don't worry about it.
You had enough going on.
You know, he kissed me.
What?
The other day, when you came back
From the other side of the island, Jack kissed me.
Oh.
It was nice.
But it wasn't for me. it was for him.
I'm pretty sure he was trying to prove something.
Prove what?
That he doesn't love someone else.
Thank you, Juliet.
Thank you for saving his life.
I know you're awake.
Hey.
You're home early.
Where's Veronica?
I sent her home.
The baby's asleep.
Good.
Why was she here?
Sorry?
The nanny.
She only works till 4:00.
I came home at 6:00.
I had to run some errands, so...
I asked her to stay a couple extra hours.
What's going on, Jack?
Why are you home so early?
I went to see Hurley.
Today?
Last friday.
Why didn't you tell me? I would've gone with you.
Because he's crazy, Kate,
And I didn't wanna upset you.
Where were you today?
I'm gonna ask you...
To trust me.
Trust me. Just leave it be.
Where were you?
Jack, don't.
No, I heard you on the phone last night.
Who were you talking to?
Just let it go.
-No, no, I wanna know. -No, jack.
I wanna know where you were. I wanna know who you were with.
It doesn't matter, Jack. please.
No, tell me. Tell me!
I was doing something for him.
For who?
For Sawyer.
I made him a promise.
It...
What?
It doesn't matter. It has nothing to do with us.
Then why won't you tell me?
Because--because he wouldn't want me to.
But he's not here, is he? no.
No, he made his choice.
He chose to stay.
I'm the one who came back.
I'm the one who's here.
I'm the one who saved you.
Jack
Jack.
You can't-- you can't do this.
If you have problems, you need to figure them out.
All right? 'cause I can't have you like this around my son.
Your son?
You're not even related to him!
Hey, sweet pea.
Hey.
Morning.
It's way too early for chinese.
Where's Claire?
Ladies' room?
Nope.
She just walked off into the jungle.
What?
When?
In the middle of the night. Just got up and left.
-You let her go alone? -She wasn't alone.
Well, who was she with?
She called him "dad." I'd have followed them,
But I have a restraining order.
Claire!
It's okay. It's okay.
I've got you.
Claire!