-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
Lost
Season 4 Episode 11
Where do you think you're going?
Out.
With who?
Him?
Yes, and you can't stop me.
I'm in love.
He's twice your age, Emily.
So what, mom?
Are you jealous?
Emily, wait a minute.
Emily, listen to me!
Emily!
Get back here, young lady,
right now!
You can't stop me!
I love him!
Emily!
Honey, can you hear me?
That's good.
Try and stay awake now.
Keep it steady.
Out of the way.
She's bleeding.
Her heartbeat's dropping fast.
I'm pregnant.
What?
What did you say?
I'm pregnant.
I'm five-- I'm almost six months.
She-she's pregnant.
Get the clamps ready.
That's it, Emily.
Good girl.
- Baby's crowning.
- She's crowning.
Dilated and ready to go.
That's it.
Okay, sweetheart.
All right, there you go.
Wrap you up nice and warm.
We'll just take you over here now.
Margaret, would you put
him in for me, please?
My baby.
It's a boy, honey.
He's okay for now.
He's just real early.
Can I hold him?
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
He's just too little.
We have to take him away now.
But...
Name--name him John.
Please!
His name is John!
Who builds a cabin in the
middle of the jungle anyway?
That's a good question.
So? How about answering it?
I don't know.
And why are we even going there?
Because hopefully,
the man who lives in the cabin
can tell us what to do about the
people who are trying to kill us.
We've been walking all day.
Are we gonna get there soon?
How long?
I don't know.
I've been following him.
What?
What do you mean,
you've been following him?
I'm not even in front.
I have no idea where the cabin is.
Hugo's the last one that saw it.
Oh, this is just awesome.
What do you think we should do, John?
We're making camp.
What?
Here in the dark with the monster and...
him?
The rest will do us good.
Dude, what's gonna happen when
those freighter guys come back?
I don't know...
yet.
Desmond.
The helicopter's here.
All right, get him on the litter.
Careful with him!
Get him down over there.
Be careful.
Okay, guys, unload it.
Come on. Pick it up.
Pick it up. Let's go.
What did this to him?
A black pillar of smoke threw
him 50 feet in the air,
ripped his guts out.
What?
I need you to tell me exactly how
many people are on that island
and where every single one of them is.
And why would I do that?
Keamy!
What the hell do you
think you're doing, mate?
You gave me up.
What?
Linus knew who I was.
He knew my name.
He knew everything about me.
No, I'm not the one who gave you up.
Then who did?
Do you know who I am?
What?
My name.
Do you know my name?
Keamy.
Martin Keamy.
Did you give it to him?
Who?
Benjamin Linus--
did you give him my name?
Yeah.
Wait. Wait!
Martin, no!
Martin, we need him.
He's the only one who
can fix the engines.
And what makes you so sure about that?
Because he's the one who broke them.
Hello there.
Who are you?
I'm Horace.
And what are you doing out here?
Oh, building a place-- a little
getaway for me and the missus.
No, I mean, sometimes you need
a break from the D.I., you know?
The Dharma Initiative?
I'm not making any sense, am I?
No.
That's probably because I've
been dead for 12 years.
Hello there.
You gotta find me, John.
You gotta find me.
And when you do, you'll find him.
Who?
Jacob.
He's been waiting for you
a real long time, man.
I'm Horace.
Godspeed, John.
Hugo.
Mallomars.
Wake up, Hugo.
What?
Time to get up.
We're gonna get going.
I thought we didn't know
where we're going, dude.
We do now.
I used to have dreams.
Dr. Miller, Dr. Miller,
please call the switchboard.
Hi, Emily.
Mrs. Locke, it's good to see you.
How is he?
He's amazing.
He's the youngest preemie to
ever survive in this hospital.
He's had infections,
pneumonia, you name it.
And every time, he knocked them out.
He is a fighter, your little John.
That's wonderful.
The other girls say
he's a miracle baby.
And today, we're gonna take
him out of the incubator
so you can hold him for
the very first time.
I...
I can't do this.
I'm sorry. I can't!
So who do I talk to about adoption?
You can't smoke in here, Mrs. Locke.
Of course.
I'm sorry.
Is that the father?
I, uh...
I don't know who that is.
Can I ask you somethin'?
Sure.
Why am I here, man?
You're here because you can see the
cabin, and that makes you special.
Well, I have a theory as to why
we're the only ones who can see it.
I'd love to hear it.
I think we can see it
'cause we're the craziest.
So how'd you figure
out where it was, dude?
I didn't.
We're not going to the cabin.
We're gonna make a pit stop first.
Pit stop?
Where?
You ever wonder what happened
to the Dharma Initiative, Hugo?
There must have been at least a
hundred of 'em living on this island,
manning the stations,
building those homes,
making all that ranch
dressing that you like.
And then one day, they're all gone.
They just disappeared.
You want to know where we're going?
We're going to see them.
Wow.
What happened to 'em?
He did.
That game's stupid.
He's right in here.
Come on in.
Melissa, stop that!
Co on now. Take your
brother in the kitchen.
There's someone here
who wants to see John.
It is coming down like
cats and dogs out there.
This nice gentleman wants
to talk to you, John.
So I want you on your best behavior.
Understand?
He's all yours.
You like Backgammon?
Yeah?
You seem to have a pretty
good sense of the game.
I'm Richard, John.
I run a school for kids who are...
extremely special,
and I have reason to believe
that you might be one of them.
Mind if I show you a couple
of really neat things?
Did you draw that, John?
I want you to look at these things...
and think about 'em.
Okay, now tell me, John,
which of these things belong to you?
T-to keep?
No, no, John.
Which of these things
belong to you already?
Are you sure the knife
belongs to you, John?
You sure about that?
Well, it doesn't.
How did he do?
I'm afraid John isn't
quite ready for our school.
I'm sorry I've wasted your time.
What did you do?
What's he doing down there?
So...
this is where you shot Locke
and left him for dead, huh?
Yes, Hugo, I was standing right where
you are now when I pulled the trigger.
Should have realized at the time
that it was pointless, but...
I really wasn't thinking clearly.
Is that why you killed
all these people, too?
I didn't kill them.
Well, if the others didn't wipe
out the Dharma Initiative--
They did wipe them out, Hugo,
but it wasn't my decision.
Then whose was it?
Their leader's.
But I thought you were their leader.
Not always.
The cabin?
He was building it.
Did you find what you were looking for?
Yes, Hugo. I believe I did.
I need your key.
What?
Captain.
Mayhews just died.
Doc couldn't do anything for him.
The crew's asking a lot
of questions about...
what happened to you guys over there.
You tell the crew that
I'm dealing with it.
Then you can go gas up
the chopper, Frank.
We're going back.
Going back?
- What the hell for?
- Gas up the chopper, Frank.
Okay.
Listen, Martin.
While you were gone, there
was some sort of a sickness.
The crew...they've been exhibiting
some very strange behavior.
Regina threw herself
overboard, for God's sake.
Now I would be derelict in my
duty if I didn't point out
that this might be exactly
what's happening to you.
I appreciate your concern.
Give me your key.
That's not the protocol--
Thank you.
The reason there are two keys is we're
only supposed to open the safe together.
You're here, aren't you?
What is that?
It's the secondary protocol.
What does it say?
It says where Linus is going.
How would Mr. Widmore know that?
'Cause he's a very smart man,
and if Linus knows that
we're gonna torch the island,
there's only one place that he can go.
What do you mean,"torch the island"?
That was not the agreement.
I agreed to ferry you here
for an extraction mission.
Fix my gun.
That injured man...
that was no gunshot.
What do you think happened to him?
I don't know.
But when they go back, they'll
be certain it doesn't happen again.
Omar!
Keamy wants you in the armory.
He said I wasn't supposed to
let those two out of my sight.
I'll watch them. Go.
There's a pantry below our galley
with enough room for two men.
I've left you a supply
of food and water.
You need to go there.
Michael--is he dead?
No, but not for lack of bloody trying,
which is precisely why
you two need to be...
hiding before Keamy
comes back on this deck.
Hiding is pointless.
Give us your zodiac raft so we can start...
ferrying people back
here from the beach.
The only way to save our lives is
to get our people off that island.
Meet me behind the
container in ten minutes.
The boat will be in the water.
The cabin's here.
I came from over there.
Up the coast.
Here you go.
Drink up, dude.
Digging through dead bodies
takes it out of you.
It's gonna be dark soon, Hugo.
If you head that way,
you'll hit the coast,
and all you have to do is take it
north until you reach our beach.
Uh, what?
I forced you to come with us
at gun point, and I'm sorry,
Hugo, but I was led to believe that
we needed you to find this place.
Oh, I get it.
Now you got your magic map,
you don't--
you don't need me anymore.
I'm offering you a chance to leave.
I don't want to put you in
harm's way against your will.
And you think walking through the jungle...
at night by myself is
gonna be any safer?
I'm not sure it is.
I think I'll stick with you guys.
This way?
What?
He actually thinks staying was his idea.
Not bad, John. Not bad at all.
I'm not you.
You're certainly not.
Somebody, let me out!
Please let me out.
- Please, somebody, let me--
- John, you okay?
I'm fine.
Get to class, ladies.
Tardy bell just rang.
John, you're bleeding.
Come on.
Let's go to the nurse's office.
- You wanna talk about it?
- No.
I know you're probably upset right now,
but I do have some
exciting news for you.
I got a call from Portland recently.
There's a company up there
doing some very exciting things
in chemistry and new technologies.
They're called Mittelos Laboratories.
I spoke with a Dr. Alpert.
He's very interested in
finding young, bright minds
to enter in these new fields of science.
They want you to go to
their camp this summer.
Science camp?
Yes.
Don't you understand that things
like science camp are the reason
why I get stuffed into lockers?
- John, this is a great opportunity.
- How do they even know about me?
Well, they must have sent
a rep to the science fair,
your display at Costa Mesa.
I'm not a scientist!
I like boxing and fishing and cars.
I like sports!
I'm gonna tell you something,
something I wish someone
had told me at your age.
You might not want to be
that guy in the labs,
surrounded by test
tubes and beakers,
but that's who you are, John.
You can't be the prom king.
You can't be the quarterback.
You can't be a superhero.
Don't tell me what I can't do.
Why didn't you tell me?
Tell you what?
That you're a survivor of 815.
'Cause you wouldn't have believed me.
You didn't think I'd believe you?
I tell you that I'm one of
the only people in the world
that think that that plane on the
bottom of the ocean is a hoax,
and you didn't think I'd believe you?
I didn't know if I could trust you.
Your boss put that plane there.
Man, I thought I was Mr. Conspiracy,
but you got me beat there.
Listen to me.
You can't fly that guy back. Keamy.
You let me worry about Keamy, all right?
You can't fly him back!
He is gonna kill
everyone on that island.
Everyone.
And you don't want that
on your conscience, man.
Trust me.
Hey, boss.
Just getting him down
to the engine room.
Stay on a heading of exactly 3-0-5.
Faraday says that's the only
safe way to and from the boat.
What will you tell Keamy if he
notices the zodiac is missing?
I'll tell him you stole it.
Now go.
Desmond.
I can't go with you.
Why not?
I've been on that
island for three years.
I'm never setting foot on it again.
Not when Penny's coming for me.
I'll be back with the first
group as soon as I can.
Stay on that bearing, yeah?
I will.
You need to go.
Now.
It should be about 200 yards this way.
You sure it's gonna be there, John?
I'm sorry?
The cabin. What if it's moved again?
It hasn't moved because I was told
that this is where it would be.
I was told a lot of things, too.
That I was chosen, that I was special.
I end up with a tumor on my spine and
my daughter's blood all over my hands.
I'm sorry those things
happened to you, Ben.
Those things had to happen to me.
That was my destiny.
But you'll understand soon enough
that there are consequences
to being chosen,
because, destiny, John,
is a fickle bitch.
Guys?
Cabin.
Okay, okay, okay.
Good job, man.
Good job, John.
Okay, we'll try it some more tomorrow.
He's all yours.
Come on up.
It's all right. Come on.
Don't give up, Mr. Locke.
Excuse me?
I'm just saying, don't give up.
Anything's possible.
You should read my file.
My spine was crushed.
There's a 98% chance I'll never
get any feeling back in my legs.
So I don't know
why I'm even trying to--
As a matter of fact,
I did read your file.
You survived falling eight
stories out of a building.
That's a miracle, Mr. Locke.
Let me ask you something.
Do you believe in miracles?
No.
I don't believe in miracles.
You should.
I had one happen to me.
Hey, look. I just want
to go back to my room.
You know what you need, Mr. Locke?
You need to go on a walkabout.
Wha-what's a walkabout?
It's a journey of self-discovery.
You go out into the
Australian outback
with nothing more than
a knife and your wits.
I can't "walkabout" anything.
In case you haven't?noticed,
I'm a cripple.
Is that what you are, Mr. Locke?
I went on my walkabout convinced I was
one thing, but I came back another.
I found out what I was made of,
who I was.
And here you are, an orderly.
Oh, I'm a lot more than
just an orderly, John.
When you're ready, Mr. Locke,
you'll listen to what I'm saying.
And then, when you and me
run into each other again...
you'll owe me one.
Hey, Doc.
Wanna hear something weird?
Yeah, sure.
You know that morse code message
that I got from the beach?
It said that the doctor washed up
on the shore with his throat slit.
But I'm the doctor.
Crazy, right?
Everything here?
Yes, sir.
Good. Get it packed up.
What are you gonna do with all that?
Fire her up, Frank.
Mr. Keamy, I was hired
to fly scientists.
Get your ass in the cockpit
and fire up the chopper, Frank.
I'm not taking you.
I'll kill you, Frank.
Yeah, well, you do that, you'll
never get back to the island
'cause I'm the only pilot you got.
Sorry, Doc.
Does that change anything, Frank?
Huh?
Another 30 seconds goes by
and someone else's turn--
I fixed your gun.
Now stand down, Martin,
or I will fire.
I don't think you want
to do that, Captain.
What's that on his arm?
Hey!
What'll it be, Frank?
We're flying.
Come on. Let's go, boys.
Come on!
Bring the rest of the weapons on board.
Let's go
Let's go!
- Everything's down in here.
- Let's move out.
Thanks, Captain.
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Let's go!
Hey! What did I say to you?
You told me not to leave my tent.
I was hungry.
Jack, you have to rest.
You can't run around.
I know that it is hard
for you to ask for help
but if you tear your stitches--
Right.
Okay.
I got it.
Doctors make the worst patients.
Jack!
I think they want us to follow 'em.
All right.
Let's do this.
I'm not going in there with you.
What?
The island wanted me to get sick,
and it wanted you to get well.
My time is over, John.
It's yours now.
Yeah, I'm cool with you
going in alone, too.
Good luck, John.
Are you Jacob?
No.
But I can speak on his behalf.
Well, who are you?
I'm Christian.
You know why I'm here?
Yeah, sure.
Do you?
I'm here...
because I was chosen to be.
That's absolutely right.
Claire?
Hi, John.
What are you doing here?
Don't worry. I'm fine.
I'm with him.
Wh-- where's the baby?
The baby's where he's supposed
to be, and that's not here.
It's probably best that you don't
tell anyone that you saw her.
Why?
- Why is she--
- We don't have time for this.
The people from the boat are
already on their way back,
and once they get here, all of these
questions won't matter one bit.
So why don't you ask the one
question that does matter?
How do I save the island?
Did he tell you what
we're supposed to do?
He did.
Well?
He wants us to move the island.
Lost
Season 4 Episode 11