We got a little chop ahead.
Put that away.
You're freaking me out.
We need this thing.
With the cargo we got
back there? Bad mojo.
- Ms Decker?
- Yes.
- Wanna let 'em know we're landing?
- Sure. Of course.
We're coming in for a landing.
It's a military facility
just west of Honolulu.
It's completely private.
Your families are already here.
Now, there's a lot of press
that want to speak to you.
But as far as Oceanic is concerned, you
don't have to speak to any reporters.
We'll talk to them.
Is that all right with all of you?
It's fine. We all agreed.
We just want to get it over with.
OK. They're referring to you
as the "Oceanic Six."
Not the best branding as far
as we're concerned, but it is catchy.
We'll see you on the ground.
We all know the story.
If we get any questions that we don't
want to answer, or that we can't answer,
let's just keep our mouths shut.
It's OK. They'll think
that we're in shock.
We are in shock, Jack.
Well, then this should be easy.
It was Sayid and Desmond
in the helicopter, right?
I mean, it had to be.
Why else would they have dropped
that thingamabob right over us?
- Then why wouldn't they just land?
- I don't know,
but this is tracking the chopper. They
want us to know where they're going.
It's a phone, right?
Can't we just call?
Well?
Don't try anything stupid.
Understood.
- Put her down over there.
- Is that them?
You sure?
We're still five klicks from the site.
I said put her down, Frank!
Gear up. We hit the ground,
we deploy to the Orchid.
Heads down. Let's do this.
- You know what the Orchid is?
- No.
I didn't hear Desmond or Sayid either.
Kate.
- You wanna take a walk?
- Absolutely.
- I'll get the guns. You get some water.
- OK.
You can't possibly be serious.
- You just had surgery.
- I'll be fine.
- If your sutures rip, you won't be.
- I can't sit around
- Recovery is not sitting around!
- I have to.
- Why?
- Because I promised those people
that I would get them off this island.
Don't bleed to death, Jack.
I'll see you in a couple hours.
Daniel?
- What's wrong?
- Did you hear what he said?
They're going to the Orchid.
Using the secondary protocol.
What are you talking about?
We have to get off this island...
...right now.
We're catching up.
The chopper must have landed.
Why don't you take a break?
You're bleeding.
No, I'm not bleeding.
I'm... I'm suppurating.
It's discharge. My body is just fighting
an infection around the stitches.
You know when most people are lying
and they can't look you in the eye?
You do the exact opposite.
Hey, long time no see.
Who are you talkin' to
up there, Genghis?
Where's Claire?
We lost her.
You what?
She walked off
in the middle of the night.
We looked for her for a day,
but she was just gone.
I was hoping maybe she
went back to the beach.
She didn't.
What are you all doing out here?
What is that phone for?
Chopper flew over the beach.
Someone tossed this out.
I think it must have been Sayid.
Well, you better hope it ain't Sayid.
If he's with those animals
who blew up half of New Otherton,
you do not wanna tussle with 'em.
They tried to kill you?
Just like Locke said they would.
So, what, we're supposed
to just turn around and hide?
'Cause it seems like
that didn't work so well for you.
Didn't you just do the "run through
the jungle with a walkie" plan?
That helicopter
is our only way off this island.
What's with you
and gettin' off the island?
Stop it! You two
fighting each other now?
Look, I put Sayid and Desmond
on that chopper.
It was my call. It's my responsibility.
I'm going after it,
whether they're on it or not.
- You can all head back to the beach.
- Jack.
No, no, no. You can't go by yourself.
Just take care of the baby, OK?
That son of a bitch is stubborn.
Hold up! You don't get to die alone.
Based on the location of the wreckage,
our best estimate
of the crash site is here.
From there, the survivors
were carried
by the ocean's current to here.
An uninhabited island in
the Lesser Sunda Islands called Membata.
As you all read in your briefing books,
on day 103, a typhoon
washed up the remnants
of an Indonesian fishing boat,
including basic supplies
and a survival raft.
On day 108, the remaining six survivors,
including Ms Austen's baby, which she
gave birth to on the island of Membata,
used this raft to journey here,
an island called Sumba.
They then came ashore near
a village called Manukangga.
This photo was taken
by the local fishermen who found them.
Once it was discovered who they were,
they were then transported
to Honolulu by the U.S. Coast Guard.
As you can imagine, this has been
an extraordinarily trying experience.
They have, however,
agreed to answer a few questions,
so, ladies and gentlemen,
the survivors of Oceanic 815.
Dr Shephard! Dr Shephard!
Can you tell us what it was like
when the plane hit the ocean,
how you survived?
It... it all happened really fast.
I remember the impact.
I remember the plane
filling up with water.
A group of us got to the emergency door
and got out before it went down.
And those of you who survived
you swam to the island?
No. We had cushions,
we had some life jackets.
We were in the water for over a day
before the current took us in.
By then, there were
only eight of us left.
What happened to the other three?
One of them, his name is Boone Carlyle,
suffered tremendous internal injuries
and died a few days after the crash.
A woman, Libby,
she didn't make it through
the first week.
Charlie Pace,
he drowned a few weeks
before we were able to leave.
Mr Reyes, you were worth
more than $150 million
at the time of your..."death".
How does it feel to know
you'll get that money back?
I don't want it back. Any of it.
That money was bad luck.
Can somebody translate that?
She asked me if my husband was one
of the people who died on the island.
The answer is no.
He never made it off the plane.
Are you aware of the situation
in Iraq, Mr Jarrah?
Do you have any plans to return?
There is nothing for me in Iraq.
And Mr Shephard, now that
you are home, what are your plans.
I haven't really thought
too much about it.
My father died in Sydney.
I was bringing him home for the funeral
when the plane crashed.
Even though the body is...
I'd like to put him to rest.
Ms Austen?
What was it like
giving birth on the island?
Scary.
Your son, Aaron? How old is he?
Just a little over five weeks.
So that would've made you
six months pregnant
when the U.S. Marshal Service
apprehended you in Australia
for an outstanding murder warrant?
I'm afraid Ms Austen's legal issue
is off the table. Next question.
Mr Jarrah, given
the amazing circumstances
surrounding the survival of you six,
is it possible
there are any other survivors
from the crash yet to be discovered?
No. Absolutely not.
You did good.
Mr Jarrah?
There's a woman outside.
Says she knows you but wasn't
on our list of family members.
Her name is Noor Abed Jaseem.
Nadia?
Nadia.
Over here.
Sayid!
Where's Desmond?
He's fine, on the freighter. I'm going
to take people back, six at a time.
We have to go right now, before
the helicopter gets back to the boat.
Why do we have to go to the boat
before the chopper gets back?
Because the men on that helicopter
have every intention of killing us all.
What?
Jack and Kate
just went running after it.
So when is someone
gonna tell me where we're going?
We're going to a place
called the Orchid, Hugo.
What's that?
It's a greenhouse.
And why are we going
to a greenhouse, exactly?
You heard John.
We're going to move the island.
Right. And how are we gonna do that?
Very carefully.
If you could move the island
whenever you wanted,
why didn't you just do it before
the psychos with the guns got here?
Because doing it is
both dangerous and unpredictable.
It's a measure of last resort.
Awesome.
Allow me.
May I have that mirror, please?
You know those are 15 years old.
- What are you doing, dude?
- Communicating.
Communicating with who?
Who do you think?
All right. Now we can go.
Wait, what was that?
What did you tell them?
None of your business, John.
If you wanna run off in the jungle
after that chopper, you should do that.
In the meantime we need
to get them off this island.
If I can catch up to Jack and Kate...
I can start ferrying people now,
get them there safely.
By time you get back, I can have
most of these people on our boat.
I trust you know the bearing.
You'd better get going.
Thank you.
All right, first group in the raft.
We can fit six!
OK, OK, hold on.
Sun is pregnant. She should go first.
Sayid? What are you doing here?
Jack thought...
That's why I'm going after him.
How far ahead is he?
I don't know. He's with Sawyer.
I left them about an hour ago.
Jack's got a sat-phone,
headed for the helicopter.
I can track them.
Look, you are not gonna catch up
to them unless I go with you.
Then let's go.
- Sun?
- Where's Claire?
- Get Aaron to the boat.
- What?
I'm sorry. Just... I'll see you there.
Just keep him safe!
All right, this is just
the first trip. Here we go.
Mom?
Dad?
Mr Tron? Lady Tron?
Hello?
Why am I doing this?
Surprise!
Happy birthday!
Hugo, what are you doing with that?
I don't know, I thought
there was a prowler or something.
Jesus Christ is not a weapon.
OK. Enjoy your party.
Happy birthday, Hurley.
- Hey, Kate.
- Hey.
- Hey, little buddy!
- Say hi.
Jack's running late.
Happy Birthday, Hugo!
Wow, you guys are here!
Interesting choice of theme.
Yeah, mom really doesn't get it, dude.
Hey, how's everybody doing?
What're you talking about?
Building a fire or hunting boars?
Guess not.
Listen, do you mind excusing us
for a little while?
I wanna show you your birthday present.
Bye-bye now.
- I don't want anything.
- Hugo, it's your birthday.
- Gotta get somethin'.
- Not with the money.
- I don't want anything from the money.
- Relax.
I got you this before
you gave us the money.
Check it out.
You fixed it.
Yeah. After the crash,
I worked on it as a memorial to you.
When I was fixing it up,
it was almost like I was with you.
But now you're back. And it's all yours.
Wanna take her for a little spin?
Something wrong, son?
Is this some kind of joke?
- What're you talking about?
- Four, eight, 15, 16, 23, 42.
Did you do this?
Do what?
Those are the numbers! There!
The numbers I won the lottery with!
Wow, what a coincidence.
No! No, not a coincidence. I don't
want this! I don't want any of it!
Hugo, wait a minute. Hugo. Son!
Hugo. Hugo, come on,
where are you going? Hugo!
OK. So let's say this greenhouse place
does what you say.
And I get it,
it's really dangerous and unpredictable.
But suppose somehow it works,
and we move the island.
Doesn't that mean the dudes
with guns move too?
Yes, I suppose they would.
Isn't that, you know, a problem?
I'm working on it.
Well, what about me?
I still wanna get off it!
I'm afraid it's a little late
for that, Hugo.
May I have the binoculars, please?
You might want to get
down lower to the ground.
And why might we want to do that?
Because we're at the Orchid.
What are we waiting for?
We're waiting
because Charles Widmore,
the man trying to capture me
and kill the rest of you,
knows about this place
and knows what we need is inside.
I thought you said you had no idea
why he was trying to find the island.
- I wasn't being entirely truthful.
- Yeah.
When are you ever entirely truthful?
You need to see this.
What am I looking for?
Look over there, on the left side.
Watch the plants at the back.
I don't see any...
They're already here.
Hey, we're back!
Where's Sayid?
He had to go after Jack.
They're headed for the chopper.
- You OK?
- Yes, I'm fine. Thank you.
I'm going back for the next group.
Engine's fixed.
Tell Hendricks to try it.
OK. Engines should be working.
Indeed they are.
All right, well, take us to the island.
But make sure you stay
on a bearing of 305.
It gotta be exactly 305.
We've got some kind of RF interference
with the Fathometer.
I can't see the reef, mate.
RF interference? How is that possible?
The radio room's down.
I don't know, but something
on this boat is broadcasting.
If we don't turn it off,
I'm not going any closer
than five miles off the coast.
Then I'll find it.
Cut yourself shavin'?
Juliet took out my appendix
a couple days ago.
- You kidding me?
- Nope.
Well, what else did I miss?
We're here.
Lapidus!
You know this yahoo?
- Yeah.
- Yahoo?
This yahoo dropped that phone
on you guys so you could find me,
and I could fly you outta here.
So why don't you do me a favour
and get in that back compartment.
There's a toolbox, see if you can find
something to get me outta these.
You heard the man.
Can I get you boys a nice cold glass
of lemonade while I'm back there?
Where are Desmond and Sayid?
They were smart enough
to stay on the boat.
Right now that's the safest place to be.
When the boys I brought over here
come stompin' out of this jungle,
- you're gonna want to be long gone.
- Where'd they go?
Up by some greenhouse. Perched
up there waiting to snatch Linus.
We cut you free,
you'll fly us out of here?
- Hell, yeah.
- Hang on, Shaggy.
The hit squad's grabbing Ben Linus?
I don't see what's gonna stop 'em.
And what are they gonna do
to the people with him?
Nothing good.
Hugo's with Ben.
Son of a bitch.
About ten months ago,
I wrote what I wanted to say
at my father's funeral
on the back of a cocktail napkin
at the Sydney airport.
I don't remember what I wrote,
but whatever it was,
he would've hated it.
My father couldn't stand eulogies.
"The only good thing about a wake
is the free booze", he'd say.
Not much of a wake because
I won't even be able to bury him.
So, what I want to say
is not for my father.
It's for me.
Goodbye, Dad.
I loved you.
I miss you.
Thanks very much for coming.
Thank you for coming. Thanks.
- I'll see you back at the house?
- Yeah.
- I love you, sweetheart.
- I love you, Mom.
I'm so glad you're home.
- See you soon.
- OK.
You did that well.
I had a lot of practise.
Excuse me. May I have a word with you?
Mr Shephard...
...I'm very sorry for you loss.
Thank you.
How did you know my father?
I believe I'm the reason
he was in Australia when he died.
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
- Why would he have come to see you?
- Oh, he...
He didn't come to see me.
I was still in the hospital.
I never saw him.
He came to see his daughter.
My daughter, Mr Shephard.
- My father didn't have a daughter.
- Yes. He did.
If you don't believe me,
check his phone records.
Would you like to know the strangest
thing about all this, Mr Shephard?
My daughter was on your plane too.
She was on flight 815.
You were in the air for six hours.
Probably just a few rows from her.
And you never even knew
she was your sister.
She was one of the ones who died
when your plane hit the water.
Her name was... Claire.
I didn't mean to burden you
with this, but...
...you needed to know.
I'm... sorry for your loss.
Your son is beautiful.
Thank you.
I don't understand.
How did you get back to New York?
Walt and I... we took Ben's boat
and followed his bearing.
A couple of days we came to a island,
you know, with people. I sold the boat,
and we hopped a cargo ferry
back to the States.
We didn't tell anybody who we were.
And now you're working for Ben?
I do not work for Ben.
I'm trying to make up for what I did.
I'm trying to help you out here.
- Translate what I said.
- I understand.
Hey, Michael! I need you! Now!
Oh, my God.
Now!
What's the matter?
These aren't Jack or Sawyer.
They're different tracks, fresh.
And they're doubling back behind us.
Whoever you are, come out now!
All right. All right, let's just relax.
- All right, let's relax.
- Stop!
- Put the guns down.
- I said stop!
- Please, just drop your guns.
Take one more step...
I said drop your guns.
I see two of them,
but not the one who killed Alex.
He's there.
Hold onto that for me, will you?
What?
Listen to me very carefully, John.
I'm not gonna have time to repeat this.
You're gonna go into that greenhouse
through that hole there.
Once inside you're gonna turn left,
go about 20 paces until you see
a patch of anthuriums on your left.
They're in an alcove against
the north wall. Face that wall,
reach down with your left hand, find
a switch that activates the elevator.
The elevator takes
you down to the actual Orchid Station.
- Whoa, wait, what?
- OK.
Maybe I missed
the part where you explained
what I'm supposed to do
about the armed men inside.
I'll take care of them.
And how the hell are you gonna do that?
How many times
do I have to tell you, John?
I always have a plan.
Ben.
Ben!
My name is Benjamin Linus.
I believe you're looking for me.