Previously on Lost...
You better trust me when I tell you this...
I am trying to help you.
- Do I know you?
- I'm George Minkowsky.
I'm the communications officer.
Wher's the radio room?
I'll take you there.
And how do we get out of here?
Through the door...?
Looks like you guys have a friend on this boat.
You're pregnant.
Juliet, she was their fertility doctor,
studying pregnant women.
There is a reason The Others wanted her baby.
It was for research.
What happens to pregnant women
on this island?
They die.
You want me to help you and your baby?
I have answers to your questions,
but you have to come with me,
right now.
The baby isn't Jin's.
I want to look at your baby and
determine the date of conception.
If you got pregnant here...
We'll cross that bridge
when we come to it.
The baby was conceived about 8 weeks ago...
You got pregnant on the island.
So how long do I have?
Most of the women made it to the
middle of their second trimester.
Nobody made it to their third.
Lapidus!
You ready?
I'll be up.
Don't be late, Frank.
Regina.
Frank.
I didn't hear you.
Sorry, I didn't mean to spook you.
The captain wanted me to bring
these guys some food? ? ?
Okay.
You know, your book is upside down.
Just trying to help.
Thought I'd check in on you guys and
bring you some food.
How are you feeling, by the way?
Much better, thanks.
Why are we being held captive?
We had nothing to do
with Minkowsky's death.
this has nothing to do
with Minkowsky.
The captain wasn't very happy that you two
decided to bust out of sick bay
and into our radio room.
We didn't bust out.
The door was left open.
We assumed that was you.
Why the hell would I do that?
Did you have any contact
with our people on the beach?
No luck.
Something must have happened to the phone.
Lima bits?
Sorry, we had a little problem in the kitchen.
Just stay put, all right?
I still want to talk to the captain.
No, you don't.
Regina.
What's wrong?
Sayid and Desmond left three days ago.
Why haven't they come back?
Perhaps they are returning with the ship.
Now come on...
we have more important things to talk about.
Like what?
Let's talk about baby names.
Good. You're getting better.
But no, Jin.
It's bad luck to talk about baby names now.
Superstitious?
I don't want to jinx him.
You mean her.
Oh, it's going to be a girl, is it?
Ji Yeon.
I want to name her Ji Yeon.
I don't want to talk about names.
You don't like Ji Yeon?
No, it's beautiful.
I'll tell you what.
Let's get off the island first.
Then we can pick a name.
Deal.
Emergency services.
I need an ambulance...
What seems to be the problem?
I'm pregnant...
and I think something's wrong.
LOST
4x07 Ji Yeon
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: YTET - ?????? ????????
completed and edited by rogard
Can I help you?
Is there something you're looking for?
Yes...a panda.
This way, please.
Good.
Give me that one.
Would you like it gift wrapped?
No, I have to get to the hospital.
How much is it?
Fifty thousand won.
Maternity ward?
Yes.
Why didn't you say so?
You must be very happy...
Boy or a girl?
I...I don't know yet.
Don't worry.
Everyone loves a panda.
Yes, yes. I'm on my way...
I'm on my way.
I understand.
Good luck!
Jin!
Kate and Jack are back.
What happened?
You mean, before or after
the redhead knocked me out?
She hit you?
When I ran into them on my
way back from Locke's camp.
Why would she do that?
I guess she didn't wanna have to explain
why she was on her way to a poison gas factory.
Juliet told Jack that it was a power station.
Why would Juliet lie about that?
Force of habit?
Why were they going there?
To turn it off, to deactivate the gas.
I guess they wanted to
earn some brownie points.
Do you think they're really going to rescue us?
In all the time they've been here,
they've talked about a lot of things,
and none involved rescuing us.
Good morning.
I hope they resolve their kitchen issues.
Sayid.
What's that?
It's a note.
Three days ago, when I was in Locke's camp,
Ben claimed he had a spy on this boat.
Don't trust Captain.
Hello.
My name is Sun.
Hi, Sun.
I'm Daniel.
Something I can help you with?
I'm two months pregnant.
Oh, you're...
Wow, that's...
Congratulations.
So are you here to rescue us?
It's a simple question.
Are you or are you not going to rescue us?
The thing is, um...
it's not really my call, Sun.
Then whose call is it?
Thank you.
Uh, can you pass, uh, the cereal?
Pretty good English, Jin.
Thank you.
I... understand better than I, uh, speak.
Has Sun been teaching you,
or are you just picking it up?
Uh, Sun teach me.
Uh, Sawyer, too.
Sun is... better.
I bet.
Hey, Sun. How you feeling?
I'm good. Thank you.
The morning sickness has
stopped, which has been nice.
That's good. Well...
if you need anything,
just let me know, okay?
Would you like some breakfast?
Jin...
You need to do as I say
and not ask questions.
What's the matter?
You need to find food for two days.
Meet me at the tent in twenty minutes.
Why?
What's happened?
We're going to Locke's camp.
What are you doing?
I needed another bottle of those
vitamins you gave me, the--the prenatals.
You could've just asked.
You're right. I should have.
What happened to the
last ones I gave you?
Sorry?
The last bottle I gave you.
There should be 20 left.
Are you planning a trip?
Please, just give me the vitamins.
Where are you going, Sun?
- We're going to Locke's camp.
- What?
Why?
Because I don't trust these people.
Whether you trust them
or not, you can't go there.
Locke doesn't want to leave the island,
and I've told you, Sun, pregnant women...
they don't survive here.
Yes, you did tell me that.
You don't believe me.
Look, I know that I have been less than
truthful about certain things since coming here,
but I promise you, Sun, I promise you...
I'm not lying about this.
After everything you've confided in me,
I should at least have your trust.
Claire's baby is fine.
I feel fine.
All I have are your stories that
I'm going to get sick.
I'm going to do what's best for
me and for my baby, because, no...
I don't trust you.
It's okay. It's going to be okay.
Is that--?
Yes. Oceanic Six.
Stop! What are you doing?
We remove all jewelry.
It's for the swelling.
No! Not my ring!
Nothing will happen to it.
It's okay.
Mrs. Kwon. I'm Dr. Bae.
I'm on duty for Dr. Park.
Where is he? What's happening?
He's away at a conference...
Get her something for the pain.
Now let me take a look...
Is something wrong with my baby?
It is in distress.
What's wrong?
I don't know yet.
That's what I'm going to find out.
Is there anyone we should contact?
Your husband? Your parents?
Just get Jin...my husband...
Jin...
Just get Jin...
I'll try to reach him.
Get my...husband...
I'm sure he'll be here soon.
Jin...
Taxi!
Yes, I'm on my way...Hello?
Hello...
Hey! What is this?
Stop!
You bastard!
I will kill you!
If I find you!
I will hunt you down
and rip your head off!
I need another panda!
I'm sorry, that was the last one.
What about that one?
It's right behind you!
That one is on hold.
They're quite popular.
How much do you want?
It's already paid for.
What about this...
In the year of the dragon
it brings good luck.
I need the panda.
Don't lose this one.
Once you hit the stream,
you wanna head northwest,
pretty much in a straight line
for about a day and a half.
Thank you.
I'm gonna have to tell Jack.
But I'll give you guys a nice, long head start.
I'd tell him myself, but he wouldn't understand.
No, he wouldn't
You better get going.
Be safe, okay?
Thank you.
She's not going anywhere.
Sun, this is a bad idea.
What concern is it of yours?
Do you understand your wife's
medical condition right now?
Translate for me.
No.
Your wife is very sick.
If she doesn't get off this island
in three weeks, she will die.
If you let her go, your wife is in danger. Jin...
Danger.
Wherever Sun go... I go.
Sun. Please.
Jin.
Your wife had an affair.
What?
Sun was with another man.
She thought the baby was his.
Jin...
Talk to me. Let me explain.
It was a long time ago.
Look at me.
Just look at me.
I understand you're angry.
And I have no excuse.
Please let me explain.
Let me explain!
Jin...
You going fishing?
Uh, you mind if I... tag along?
Oh, I am sorry. I-I didn't mean to interrupt.
No. Come.
You sure?
Yes. Come.
You realize we're the only
two married guys on the island?
Married.
Yeah, well, no, not to each other. No.
You got it.
It's not easy, is it?
Oh, I mean, it's--it's wonderful, but...
let's face it. Every decision
that you make takes twice as long
'cause you always gotta talk them into it.
Rose...
has cancer.
She's sick.
Dying.
Well, at least, she was dying.
She says she's better now.
She says it's this place...
the island.
But when the camp split up,
I was sure that she'd want to go with Locke.
Why would she want to leave the
island and risk getting sick again?
Uh, then why do you stay with Jack?
Because it was the right thing to do.
Locke?
He's a murderer.
See, it's all about karma, Jin.
Do you know karma?
You make bad choices,
bad things happen to you.
But you make good choices,
and then good-- hey!
Hey, hey, hey! You got one.
Yeah. Here, pull it in.
Wow, look at that!
Yeah, you see?
Now that's karma.
We must be the good guys, huh?
How long's that gonna go on for, eh?
Can't they just fix whatever the
bloody hell's causing that?
That sound is not mechanical.
What, you think somebody's doing that?
Somebody's just banging
those pipes again and again?
That's exactly what I think.
Gentlemen...
thanks for your patience.
The captain would like to see you now.
Where's the helicopter?
Lapidus is running an errand.
What kind of errand?
I'm a doctor. I don't know where he's going.
Did he go to the island?
You know anywhere else he could land?
What's he going to do?
I said I'm just a doctor.
What did Lapidus say?
He didn't say anything.
What is he doing?
That woman just jumped
over the side of the ship!
Don't just stand there!
What's the matter with you people?
What's wrong with you? Get a rope!
Why aren't you doing anything?
Bring a rope!
Get a rope!
- Get a rope!
- Stop!
She just jumped!
It's over.
She's gone.
Everybodyget back to your posts.
That was an order.
I'm captain Gault.
I suppose you two have a few questions.
So what can I do for you?
What?
You boys said you wanted to speak with me.
Let's just start with why
a woman jumped over the...
side of your ship,
and you did nothing to stop it.
I didn't jump in or order my crew to jump in
because I didn't want to lose any more people.
What exactly is going on here?
Some of my crew has been dealing with...
what might best be described as
a heightened case of cabin fever.
I think it's got something to do with
the close proximity of the island.
Why don't you turn around, then?
I've tried, but we have a saboteur on board,
and he's done one hell of a job on my engines.
I've got my crew working
around the clock to repair them.
And then you'll take our people home?
Then we move to safer waters.
Those are my orders.
And I don't suppose you'll tell us
who gave you those orders?
Sure, I will.
Charles Widmore.
This is Charles Widmore's boat?
That's right. You know him.
Do either of you know what this is?
It's a flight data recorder,
otherwise known as a black box.
That's exactly what it is.
Now here's the funny thing.
This black box comes from
oceanic flight 8-1-5.
A salvage vessel recovered
it from the bottom of the ocean.
It took a considerable amount of
Mr. Widmore's resources to procure it.
It was found with the wreckage of the plane,
along with all 324 dead passengers.
That's not the complete story,
as you are well aware, Mr. Jarrah,
given the fact that you're
standing here, breathing.
The wreckage was obviously staged.
Now can you imagine what kind of resources and...
manpower go into pulling off
a feat of that magnitude?
Faking the recovery of a plane crash?
Putting 324 families through a
grieving process based on a lie?
But what's even more disturbing--
where exactly does one come
across 324 dead bodies?
And that, Mr. Jarrah, Mr. Hume, is just one
of the many reasons we want Benjamin Linus.
I'm sorry.
I had to stop you any way I could.
It wasn't your place to stop us.
I know you don't trust me, but you
need to get off this island. We all do.
You want to leave?
More than anything.
I don't know if that boat out there is
the answer or not, but it's something.
I need to go home.
So do you.
Sun...
In about three weeks, you'll be in
an almost constant state of nausea.
A week after that, you will experience
shortness of breath that won't go away.
A week after that, you will lose
consciousness and slip into a coma.
And then, Sun, you will die.
And when your heart stops beating...
so will the baby's.
And that, Sun, is why it is my business,
because you are my patient.
If you go...
you will die...
and your baby will never be born.
I have to perform a c-section.
No.
You don't understand...
the medication makes a
natural birth difficult.
No, no! Not until Jin...
We've got to get to surgery.
Where is my husband?
He's no here yet.
We cannot wait.
Jin.
Dr. Bae.
The baby is crowning.
Ok, Sun. You need to push now.
That's it... Push! Push!
You can do it.
That's it. Push.
You did it.
Congratulations.
You have a baby daughter.
So what'd you think of the captain?
He was surprisingly forthcoming.
Yeah, he tells it like it is.
Just don't piss him off.
You know what I mean?
I think you'll like your room.
It's on a quiet part of the ship.
This ship isn't moving.
Well, if you say so.
That shouldn't still be there. Damn it.
Hey, Johnson. Is that you?
- Johnson?
- Yeah.
Mop this up.
Sorry.
I gotta go up on deck.
No, you're gonna mop this up!
Kevin, this is, uh...
Sayid.
Desmond.
Kevin Johnson.
Nice to meet you, Kevin.
I made...
dinner.
I thought you had left me.
Will you let me try to explain?
It won't matter.
Just listen, maybe...
I know why you did it.
I know the man...
I used to be.
Before this island
I withheld my affections...
and I know...
that whatever you did...
you did to that man.
His actions caused this.
So I forgive you.
So I will go to Locke's camp with you.
I don't want to go there anymore.
Why?
Juliet was very convincing.
We have to get off this island.
These people have a helicopter.
We have to try.
I'll do all it takes to protect
you and the baby.
I promise.
Thank you.
There's just one thing.
And please, the truth....
Anything.
Is...
the baby...
mine?
Yes, Jin.
I swear the baby is yours.
It's yours.
I love you so much.
I thought I had lost you.
I love you, too.
And you will never lose me.
I am Jin-soo kwon.
I represent Paik Automotive.
Yes.
I heard the Ambassador
is now a grandfather.
I came to present a gift.
Wait here.
Excuse me.
Is it a boy or a girl?
A boy.
Yes?
Mr. Ambassador,
this panda is a symbol
of Mr. Paik's eagerness....
to do business in the
great country of China.
Please accept his congratulations.
Thank Mr. Paik for me.
Tell him I'll call.
Leaving so soon?
It wasn't my baby.
Well, maybe someday...
Don't rush me.
I've only been married two months.
I can't believe you came all this way.
Are you kidding?
Is anyone else coming?
No.
Good.
So...
Where is she?
Come here.
She's awesome.
Thank you.
Would you like to hold her?
I don't know.
I...
I kind of have two left hands.
I trust you.
Wow.
She looks just like Jin.
Yes...
She does.
So...
I guess we should, like, go see him.
Of course.
Jin....
you were right.
It's a girl.
The delivery was hard on me...
The doctor said I was
calling out for you...
I wish you could've been there.
Jin....
She's beautiful.
Ji Yeon.
I named her just like you wanted.
I miss you so much.
Lost
Season 4 Episode 7
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: YTET - ?????? ????????
Proudly Presents