you know,I've been thinking
about time travel again.
Why,did you hit a
roadblock with invisibility?
Put it on the back burner.
Anyway,it occurs to me if I
ever did perfect a time machine,
I would just go into the
past and give it to myself,
thus eliminating the need for me
to invent it in the first place.
Interesting.
Yeah,it really takes the pressure off.
Sounds like a breakthrough.
Should I call science magazine
and tell them to hold the cover?
It's time travel,leonard,I
will have already done that.
Then I guess
congratulations are in order.
No,congratulations
will have been in order.
You know,I am not going
to enjoy this party.
I know,I'm familiar with you.
The last department party,professor finkleday
cornered me and talked about spelunking for 45 minutes.
Yes,I was there.
You know what's interesting
about caves,leonard?
- What?
- Nothing.
Well,then we'll avoid finkleday,we'll
meet the new department head,
congratulate him,shake his hand and go.
How's this?
"Pleased to meet you,dr.Gablehauser.
"How fortunate for you that the
university's "chosen to hire you,
despite the fact "that you've done
no original research in 25 years,
"and instead have written
a series of popular books "
that reduce the great concepts of
science "to a series of anecdotes,
"each one dumbed down to accommodate the
duration "of an average bowel movement.
Mahalo.
" "Mahalo's" a nice touch.
You know there only eight
consonants in the hawaiian language?
Interesting. You should lead with that.
Oh,god,look at this buffet.
I love america.
You don't have buffets in india?
Of course,but it's all indian food.
You can't find a bagel in
mumbai to save your life.
Shmear me.
Well,here's an
interesting turn of events.
What?
Howard brought a date?
A more plausible explanation is that his work
in robotics has made an amazing leap forward.
Hey,what up,science bitches?
May I introduce my
special lady friend summer?
Howard,I told you touching's extra.
Right. Sorry.
Here comes our new boss. Be polite.
Hi,fellas.
- Eric gablehauser.
- Howard wolowitz.
Howard,nice to meet you. And you are?
An actual real scientist.
How was that?
I can't believe he fired me.
Well,you did call him a glorified
high school science teacher
whose last successful experiment
was lighting his own farts.
In my defense,I prefaced that
by saying,"with all due respect."
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:??????
The Big Bang
Theory Season01 Episode04
Morning.
You're making eggs for breakfast?
This isn't breakfast,it's an experiment.
'Cause it looks a lot like breakfast.
I finally have time to test my hypothesis
about the separation of the water molecules
from the egg proteins and
its impact vis-a-vis taste.
Sounds yummy.
I look forward to your work with bacon.
As do I.
You know,I'm sure if you just apologize to
gablehauser,he would give you your job back.
I don't want my job back.
I've spent the past three and a half years
staring at grease boards full of equations.
Before that,I spent four
years working on my thesis.
Before that,I was in college,and
before that,I was in the fifth grade.
This is my first d oayff in
decades and I'm going to savor it.
Okay.
I'll let you get back
to fixing your eggs.
Not just fixing my eggs,I'm
fixing everyone's eggs.
And we all thank you.
use new eggs.
hi. Hey,I'm running out to the market.
Do you guys need anything?
Oh,well,this would be one
of those circumstances that
people unfamiliar with the law of
large numbers would call a coincidence.
I'm sorry?
I need eggs.
Four dozen should suffice.
Four dozen?
Yes,and evenly distributed
amongst brown,white,
free-range,large,extra large and jumbo.
Okay,one more time.
Never mind. You won't get it right.
I'd better come with you.
Oh,yay.
How come you didn't go into work today?
I'm taking a sabbatical because
I won't kowtow to mediocre minds.
So you got canned,huh?
Theoretical physicists
do not get canned...
but yeah.
Well,maybe it's all for the best.
You know,I always say when one
door closes,another one opens.
No,it doesn'T.
Not unless the two doors are connected by
relays or there are motion sensors involved.
No,no,I meant...
or if the first door closing creates a change
of air pressure that acts upon the second door.
Never mind.
Slow down.
Slow down. Please,slow down!
We're fine!
You're not leaving yourself
enough space between cars.
Oh,sure,I am.
No,no,let me do the math for you.
This car weighs,let's say 4,000 pounds.
Now add 140 for me,120 for you...
- 120?
- Oh,I'm sorry.
Did I insult you?
Is your body mass somehow
tied into your self-worth?
Well,yeah.
Interesting.
Anyway,that gives us a total
weight of,let's say 4,400 pounds.
Let's say 4,390.
Fine.
We're traveling forward at--
good lord-- 51 miles an hour.
Now let's assume that your brakes
are new and the calipers are aligned.
Still,by the time we come to a stop,
we'll be occupying the same space
as that buick in front of us,
an impossibility that nature will
quickly resolve into death,mutilation...
oh,look,they built a
new putt-putt course.
This is great.
Look at me.
I'm in the real world of ordinary people just
living their ordinary,colorless workaday lives.
Thank you.
No,thank you.
And thank you,ordinary person.
Hey,you want to hear an
interesting thing about tomatoes?
Uh,no,no,not really.
Listen,didn't you say
you needed some eggs?
Yes,but anyone who knows anything
about the dynamics of bacterial growth
knows to pick up their refrigerated
foods on the way out of the supermarket.
Oh,okay,well,then maybe you
should start heading on out then.
No,this is fun.
Oh,the thing about tomatoes-- and
I think you'll really enjoy this--
is they're shelved with the
vegetables,but they're technically a fruit.
- Oh,interesting.
- Isn't it?
No,I mean what you find enjoyable.
Oh,boy.
What now?
Well,there's some value to taking a multivitamin,but
the human body can only absorb so much.
What you're buying here are the
ingredients for very expensive urine.
Well,maybe that's what I was going for.
Well,then you'll want some manganese.
Well,that was fun.
Maybe tomorrow we can go to one
of those big warehouse stores.
Oh,I don't know,sheldon.
It's going to take me a while to
recover from all the fun I had today.
Are you sure?
There are a lot of
advantages to buying in bulk.
For example,I noticed that you purchase
your tampons one-month supply at a time.
What?
Think about it.
It's a product that doesn't spoil and you're going
to be needing them for at least the next 30 years.
You want me to buy 30
years worth of tampons?
Well,30,35.
- When did your mother go into menopause?
- Okay.
I'm not talking about this with you.
Oh,penny,this is a natural human process,and we're
talking about statistically significant savings.
Now,if you assume 15 tampons
per cycle and a 28-day cycle...
are you fairly regular?
Okay,no warehouse store,but we're
still on for putt-putt golf,right?
Hey,I just ran into penny.
She seemed upset about something.
I think it's her time of the month.
I marked the calendar
for future reference.
What's with the fish?
It's an experiment.
What happened to your
scrambled egg research?
Oh,that was a dead end.
Scrambled eggs are as good
as they're ever going to be.
So... fish?
I read an article about japanese scientists who
inserted dna from luminous jellyfish into other animals,
and I thought,"hey,fish nightlights.
" Fish nightlights?
It's a billion-dollar idea.
Mum's the word.
Sheldon,are you sure you don't want to just
apologize to gablehauser and get your job back?
Oh,no,no,no,I have too much to do.
Like luminous fish.
I'm sorry. I didn'T...
that's just the beginning.
I also have an idea for a bulk
mail-order feminine hygiene company.
Oh,glow-in-the-dark
tampons!
Leonard,we're gonna be rich.
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
Well,you did the right thing calling.
I didn't know what else to do.
He's lost all focus.
Every day he's got a new obsession.
This is a particularly disturbing one.
Mommy?
Hi,baby!
Oh,you got yourself a loom? How nice!
Thank you.
Honey,why'd you get a loom?
I was working with luminous
fish,and I thought,hey...
"loom."
Mom,what are you doing here?
Leonard called me.
I know,but why?
Because one of the great minds of the 21st
century is raising glow-in-the-dark fish
and weaving serapes.
This is not a serape,this is a poncho.
A serape is open at the
sides; a poncho is closed.
This is a poncho.
And neither is a reason
to call someone's mother.
Really? When was the last
time you left the house?
I went to the market with penny.
Yeah,that was three weeks ago.
Well,then buckle up-- in the next four to
eight days she's going to get very crabby.
Sweetheart,your little
friend is concerned about you.
Yes,well,I'm not a child-- I'm a grown
man,capable of living my life as I see fit.
And I certainly don't need
someone telling on me to my mother!
Wait,where are you going?
To my room-- and
no one's allowed in!
oh,he gets his temper from his daddy.
- He's got my eyes.
- I see.
All that science
stuff,that comes from jesus.
Sheldon,your mom made dinner.
I'm not hungry!
Oh,leonard,don't trouble
yourself. He's stubborn.
He may stay in there till the rapture.
We so sure that's a bad thing?
I tell you,I love the boy to
death,but he has been difficult
since he fell out of me at the k-mart.
Excuse me for being so bold,but I now see
where sheldon gets his smoldering good looks.
Honey,that ain't gonna
work,but you keep tryin'.
I made chicken.
I hope that isn't one of the animals
that you people think is magic.
You know,we have an indian
gentleman at our church,
a dr.Patel-- it's
a beautiful story.
The lord spoke to him and moved him
to give us all 20% off on lasik--
you know,those that needed it.
Leonard: That is a lovely story.
Um,are we gonna do
anything about sheldon?
Oh,we will.
You have to take your time with sheldon.
His father,god rest his
soul,used to always say to me,
"mary,you have to take
your time with sheldon."
Sounds like a wise man.
Oh,not so wise.
He once tried to fight a
bobcat for some licorice.
So,everybody grab a plate and a
pretty place mat that shelly wove.
Has shelly ever freaked
out like this before?
Oh,all the time.
I remember one summer when he was 13,
he built a small nuclear
reactor in the shed
and told everybody he was gonna provide
free electricity for the whole town.
Well,the only problem was,he had no
what you call "fissionable" materials.
Anyway,when he went on
the internets to get some,
a man from the government came
by and sat him down real gentle,
and told him it's against the law to
have yellow-cake uranium in a shed.
Well,what happened?
Well,poor boy had a fit.
Locked himself in his room
and built a sonic death ray.
A death ray?
Well,that's what he called it.
Didn't even slow down the neighbor kids.
It pissed our dog off to no end.
You know,you two make a cute couple.
uh,no. We're not...
we're not-not a couple. We're singles.
- Two singles.
- Yeah.
Like those... individually
wrapped slices of cheese that...
we're friends.
Did I pluck a nerve there?
- Oh,yeah.
- Okay.
All right,everybody,it's time to eat.
Oh,lord,we thank you for this
meal and all of your bounty.
And we pray that you help
sheldon get back on his rocker.
Now,after a moment of silent meditation,I'm
gonna end with "in jesus' name,"
but you two don't feel
any obligation to join in.
Unless,of course,the
holy spirit moves you.
Oh,my god,this is the
best cobbler I've ever had.
It was always sheldon's favorite.
You know w thathe secret ingredient is?
- Love?
- Lard.
Hey,look who's come...
You'll spook him.
He's like a baby deer-- you
got to let him come to you.
This is ridiculous.
Damn it,sheldon,snap out of it!
You're a physicist-- you belong at the
university doing research,not hiding in your room!
you don't hunt,do you?
good morning,snickerdoodle.
Morning.
Oh,well,that looks awful
fancy. What is that?
It's my idea of what dna would look
like in a silicon-based life-form.
But intelligently designed
by a creator,right?
What do you want,mom?
You know how your daddy used to say that
you can only fish for so long before you got
to throw a stick of dynamite in the water?
Yeah.
Well,I'm done fishing.
You put those on.
What for?
Because you're gonna
go down to your office,
you're gonna apologize to your
boss and get your job back.
No.
I'm sorry,did I start that sentence with
the words,"if it please your highness"?
I'm not going to apologize-- I
didn't say anything that wasn't true.
Now,you listen here.
I have been telling you
since you were four years old,
it's okay to be smarter than everybody,but
you can't go around pointing it out.
Why not?
Because people don't like it!
Remember all the ass-kickings
you got from the neighbor kids?
now,let's get crackin'.
Shower,shirt,shoes,and let's shove off.
There wouldn't have been any ass-kickings
if that stupid death ray had worked.
Problem solved.
Really?
That's impressive.
Leonard,the lord never gives
us more than we can handle.
Thankfully,he blessed me with two
other children who are dumb as soup.
Excuse me,dr.Gablehauser,are you busy?
Well,actually...
sheldon,he's just doodlin'.
Get in here.
Dr.Gablehauser.
Dr.Cooper.
Let's go,baby--
we're losing daylight.
as you know,several weeks
ago in our first encounter,
we may have gotten off on the wrong
foot when I called you an idiot.
And I just wanted to
say that I was wrong...
to point it out.
I'm sorry,we haven't been introduced.
Dr.Eric gablehauser.
Mary cooper,sheldon's mom.
Now,that's
impossible--
you must have had him
when you were a teenager.
Oh,aren't you sweet.
His father's dead.
- Recently?
- Long enough.
Please.
sheldon,shouldn't you be working?
Okay.
Hey,how did it go?
I got my job back.
Really? What happened?
I'm not quite sure.
It involves a part of the human
experience that has always eluded me.
Well,that narrows it down.
I'm very proud of you,honey.
You showed a lot of courage today.
Thanks,mom.
Mom?
Is dr.Gablehauser going
to be my new daddy?
We'll see.
Sleep tight.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:??????