all right,just a few more feet. And...
here we are,gentlemen,the
gates of elzebob.
Good lord.
Don't panic. This is what the
last 97 hours have been about.
Stay frosty. There's a
horde of armed goblins
on the other side of that gate
guarding the sword of asaroth.
Warriors,unsheathe your weapons.
Magic wielders,raise your wands.
Lock and load.
Raj,blow the gates.
Blowing the gates.
Control,shift...
b!
oh,my god,so many goblins!
Don't just stand there,slash
and move,slash and move!
Stay in formation!
Leonard,you got one on your tail.
That's all right,my tail's
prehensile- - I'll swat him off.
I got him,leonard.
Tonight I spice my
mead with goblin blood.
Raj,no,it's a trap! They're flanking us!
He's got me!
Sheldon,he's got raj.
Use your sleep spell!
Sheldon... sheldon?
I've got the sword of asaroth!
Forget the sword,sheldon,help raj!
There is no more sheldon.
I am the sword master!
Leonard,look out!
Damn it,man,we're dying here!
Good
- bye,peasants!
the bastard teleported!
He's selling the sword
of asaroth on ebay.
You betrayed us for money? Who are you?
I'm a rogue night elf. Don't you
people read character descriptions?
Wait,wait,wait! Somebody
just clicked "buy it now.
" I am the sword master!
Our whole universe was
in a hot,dense state
then nearly 14 billion years
go expansion started... wait!
The earth began to cool the
autotrophs began to drool,
neanderthals developed tools
we built the wall
we built the pyramids
math, science,history,
unraveling the mystery
that all started with a big bang bang!
THE  BIG BANG THEORY
Season 01 Episode 03
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Ooh,I'm all sweaty. Anybody want to
log on to second life and go swimming?
I just built a virtual pool.
No. I can't look at you
or your avatar right now.
sounds like your neighbor's home.
Excuse me.
Don't forget the mail you
took accidentally on purpose
so you'd have an excuse to talk to her.
Oh,right,right,right,right.
Stealing
snail mail- -
Penny,the mailman,did it
again... he... oh,sorry.
Um,oh,hi,leonard. This is doug.
Doug,this is my neighbor leonard.
What's up,bro?
Not much...
bro.
Is everything okay?
Yeah,no,I just... I got
your mail again. Here.
Thank you. I've got to
talk to that mailman.
Oh,no,that's probably
not such a good idea.
You know,civil servants have a documented
propensity to,you know,snap,so...
okay. Well,thank you again.
No problem. Bye.
Oh,and bye... bro.
Penny for your thoughts.
What's the matter?
I'm fine. Penny's fine.
The guy she's kissing is really fine.
Kissing,what kind of kissing? Cheeks?
What is wrong with you?
I'm a romantic.
Please don't tell me that your hopeless
infatuation is devolving into pointless jealousy.
I'm not jealous. I'm just
a little concerned for her.
I didn't like the look of
the guy that she was with.
Because he looks better than you?
Yeah.
He was kind of dreamy.
Well,at least now you can retrieve
the black box from the twisted,
olsmdering wreckage that was
once your fantasy of dating her
and analyze the data so that you
don't crash into geek mountain.
I di. Greesa love is not
a sprint,it's a marathon- -
a relentless pursuit that only ends
when she falls into your arms...
or hits you with the pepper spray.
No,I'm done with penny.
I'm going to be more realistic
and go after someone my own speed.
Like who?
I don't know... olivia geiger.
The dietician at the cafeteria
with the limp and the lazy eye?
Yeah.
Oh,I don't think you have a shot there.
I have noticed that leslie winkle
recently started shaving her legs.
Now given that winter is coming,
one can only assume she's
signaling sexual availability.
I don't know. You guys
work in the same lab.
So?
There are pitfalls. Trust me,I know.
When it comes to sexual harassment
law,I'm a bit of a self taught expert.
Look,howard,if I were to ask leslie
winkle out,it would just be for dinner.
I'm not going to walk into the lab,ask
her to strip naked and dance for me.
Oh,then you're probably okay.
Hello,leslie.
Hi,leonard.
Leslie,I would like to
propose an experiment...
- goggles,leonard.
- Right.
Leslie,I would like p
toropose an experiment.
Hang on.
I'm trying to see how long it takes a 500
- kilowatt oxygen iodine laser
to heat up my cup a' noodles.
I've done it. About two
seconds. 2. 6 for minestrone.
anyway,I was thinking more of a bio- social
exploration with a neuro- chemical overlay.
Wait,are you asking me out?
I was going to characterize it as the modification
of our colleague- slash- friendship paradigm
with the addition of a date
like component,
but we don't need to
quibble over terminology.
What sort of experiment
would you propose?
There's a generally accepted
pattern in this area.
I would pick you up,take
you to a restaurant.
Then we would see a movie,
probably a romantic comedy featuring the
talents of hugh grant or sandra bullock.
Interesting.
And would you agree that the
primary way we would evaluate
either the success or failure
of the date would be based
on the biochemical reaction
during the good night kiss?
Heart rate,pheromones,etc. Yes.
Why don't we just stipulate that the date
goes well and move to the key variable?
You mean kiss you now?
Yes.
Can you define the
parameters of the kiss?
Close
- mouthed but romantic. Mint?
Thank you.
shall I count down from three?
No,I think it needs to be spontaneous.
What do you think?
You proposed the experiment. I think
you should present your findings first.
Fair enough.
On the plus side,it was a good kiss.
Reasonable technique,no
extraneous spittle.
On the other hand,no arousal.
- None?
- None.
Well,thank you for your time.
Thanyok U.
None at all?
Sheldon,if you were a robot,and
I knew and you didn'T... ...
would you want me to tell you?
That depends.
When I learn that I'm a robot...
will I be able to handle it?
Maybe- - although the history of
science fiction is not on your side.
Okay,uh,let me
ask you this- -
when I learn that I'm a robot,
would I be bound by asimov's
three laws of robotics?
You might be bound by them right now.
That's true.
Have you ever harmed a human being
or through inaction allowed
a human being to come to harm?
Of course not.
Have you ever harmed yourself or allowed
yourself to be harmed except in cases
where a human being would
have been endangered?
Well,no.
I smell robot.
Hey,what's going on?
Internet's been down for half an hour.
Also,sheldon may be a robot.
So how'd it go with leslie?
Oh,we tried kissing,but
the earth didn't move.
I mean,any more than the 383 miles
that it was going to move anyway.
Oh,I've seen that look before.
This is just going to
be two weeks of moping
and tedious emo songs
and calling me to come down
to pet stores to look at cats.
I don't know if I can take it.
You could power down.
Well,as usual,wolowitz has the solution.
I happen to know a place where
there are plenty of eligible women
and leonard could have his pick.
remember the latin hips.
Shoulders stay still,and... we sway.
One,two,three... ...
five,six,seven.
I think mrs. Tishman's
got her eye on you.
I've been there. You're in for a treat.
She said,"you don't know me"
doyou "n't even care"
oh,yeah...
oh,good lord.
She said,"you don't know me"
"you don't wear my chains"
oh,yeah. God,that's a good song.
If you're compiling a mix
cd for a double suicide.
Oh,I hope that scratching
post is for you.
I know what you're thinking. I've
taken your asthma into account.
There's a feline geneticist in san diego
who's developed the cutest
little hypoallergenic calicos.
Leonard,listen to me...
I've been thinking about names.
I'm kind of torn between
einstein,newton and sergeant fuzzy boots.
Leonard,do you really think
you can satisfy your need
for a relationshh witip
a genetically altered cat?
Maybe.
If it's a cute,little,cuddly cat.
Oh,come on. Leonard...
this is obviously about penny.
It doesn't matter.
The woman's not interested
in me. The woman rejected me.
Okay,look,I think that you have as much of a
chance of having a sexual relationship with penny
as the hubble telescope does of discovering at
the center of every black hole is a little man
with a flashlight searching
for a circuit breaker.
Nevertheless,
I do feel obligated to point out
to you that she did not reject you.
You did not ask her out.
You're right.
I didn't ask her out.
I should ask her out.
No,no,now that was not my point.
My point was don't buy a cat.
No,but you're right.
I should march over
there and ask her out.
Oh,goody,we're getting a cat.
Uh... no.
Oh,hey,leonard.
Good afternoon,penny. So,hi... hey.
Uh...
I was wondering if you
had plans for dinner.
Uh,you mean dinner tonight?
There is an inherent
ambiguity in the word "dinner.
" Technically it refers to the largest
meal of the day whenever it's consumed.
So to clarify here,by
dinner I mean supper.
- Supper?
- Or dinner.
I was thinking 6:30 if you
can go. Or a different time.
Uh,6:30's great.
Really?
Great.
Yeah,I like hanging out with you guys.
Us guys?
Yeah,you know,sheldon,howard,raj.
Who all's coming?
They... might all be there.
Or a subset of them might be there.
Algebraically speaking,there
are too many unknowns.
For example,sheldon
had quiznos for lunch.
Sometimes he finds that
filling,other times he doesn'T.
It's no fault of quiznos-
- they have a varied menu.
Okay,whatever. It sounds like fun.
Great. Did we say a time?
6:30.
- And that's still good for you?
- It's fine.
- 'Cause it's not carved in stone.
- No,6:30's great.
I'll get my chisel.
Why?
To... carve the... I'll see you at 6:30.
How do I look?
Could you be more specific?
Can you tell I'm perspiring a little?
No.
The dark crescent shaped patterns
under your arms conceal it nicely.
What time is your date?
6:30.
Perfect. That gives you
two hours and 15 minutes for
that dense molecular cloud
of aramis to dissipate.
Is it too much?
Not if you're a rugby team.
By the way,if it should ever
come up,you didn't join us
because you stuffed yourself with
a chicken carbonara sub at quiznos.
Why would I join you?
No reason.
Oh,you know what,maybe
this isn't such a good idea.
Oh,no,well,now there's always the
possibility that alcohol and poor judgment
on her part might lead to
a nice romantic evening.
You're right. Alcohol,poor
judgment- - it could go well.
Of course there is
the other possibility,
that this date kicks off a
rather unpleasant six months
of the two of you passing
awkwardly in the hall,
until one of you breaks down
and moves to another zip code.
You could've stopped
at "it could go well.
" If I could've,I would've.
I mean,I'm a perfectly nice guy.
There's no reason we couldn't go to
the restaurant,and have a lovely dinner,
maybe take a walk afterwards,talk
about things we have in common.
You love pottery? I love pottery!
There's a pause,we both
know what's happening.
I lean in,we kiss.
It's a little tentative at first,but
then I realize she's kissing me back.
She's biting my lower lip! She wants me!
This thing is going the
distance! We're going to have sex!
Oh,god,oh,my god!
Is the sex starting now?
I'm having a panic attack.
Oh,okay. Uh,well then... calm down.
If I could calm down,I wobe having a panic
att... that's why they call it a panic attack.
All right,all right.
Uh,s- s- sit down.
Yeah,sit down. Now close your eyes.
- Why?
- Just do it.
Okay.
Now try to increase
your alpha wave activity.
What? !
It's a biofeedback technique.
It's relaxation through
brain wave manipulation.
I read a paper about it in
journal of american neuroscience.
It was a little sparsely sourced,but
I think the basic science is valid.
I probably have it here somewher E.
Who am I kidding? I can't
go through with this.
You need to call her and cancel.
- Me?
- Yes.
- What should I tell her?
- I don't know.
- Tell her I'm sick.
- Okay.
Not the kind of illness that will make
her want to come over and take care of me,
but nothing so critical that she'll feel
uncomfortable going out with me in the future
if I want to try this again.
Got it.
So I'm assuming nothing venereal?
I'll just tell her that you had a routine
conoloscopy and haven't quite bounced back.
Give me the phone.
I thought you wanted to cancel.
I can't,because if I don't show
up she'll still be expecting you.
Why would she be expecting me?
Stop asking me all these questions.
I need to take another shower.
So are the rest of the
guys meeting us here?
Oh,yeah... no.
It turns out that raj and
howard had to work,and sheldon...
had a colonoscopy and he
hasn't quite bounced back yet.
Oh,my uncle just had a colonoscopy.
You're kidding. Then that's
something we have in common.
How?
We both have people in our lives who...
want to nip intestinal
polyps in the bud.
so what's new in the world of physics?
Nothing.
Really? Nothing?
Well,with the exception of string theory,
not much has happened since the 1930s.
And you can't prove string theory.
At best you can say,"hey,look,
my idea has an internal
logical consistency.
" Ah.
Well,I'm sure things will pick up.
What's new at the cheesecake factory?
Oh,uh,not much.
We do have a chocolate key
lime that's moving pretty well.
Good. Good.
What about your,uh...
hallway friend?
Doug? Oh,yeah,I don't know.
I mean,you know,he's
nice and funny,but...
can I get you started with some drinks?
No!
- You were saying? But...
- I'd like a drink.
Just say the "but" thing about
doug and then I'll get her back.
Okay,well,I don't know,it's just me.
I'm still getting over
this breakup with kurt
and this thing with doug
would stju be rebound sex.
Oh,don't get me started on rebound sex.
It's just... it's my pattern.
I break up,then I find some cute guy,
and then it's just 36
meaningless hours of...
you know.
I'm not sure that I do.
is that one 36-hour experience,
or is that 36 hours
spread out over,say...
one glorious summer?
No,it's usually over a weekend,
and trust me,you do
not feel good after it.
Well,chafing,right?
Emotionally.
Of course,yeah,emotional chafing.
Hey,do you want to see something cool?
I can make this olive go into
this glass without touching it.
- How?
- Physics.
Wow,centrifugal force.
Actually,it's centripetal force,
which is an inward force generated
by the glass acting on the olive...
Excuse me.
If you were riding on the olive,
you'd be in a non
- inertial reference frame and would...
are you okay?
Yeah,I'm okay.
Did you spill ketchup?
- No.
- I'm not okay.
Are you sure you don't want
to go to the emergency room?
No,no,I'm okay. It stopped bleeding.
I know,but you did throw up.
Isn't that a sign of a concussion?
Yes. But I get car sick,too,so...
okay.
Sorry about your car,by the way.
Oh,no,it's fine. You got
most of it out the window.
The poor guy on the bike.
Well,I had a nice time.
Yeah,me,too.
Well,um,good night.
Good night.
- Leonard?
- Ahye?
Was this supposed to be a date?
This?
No.
No,of course not.
This was just you and me
hanging out with a bunch of guys
who didn't show up 'cause
of work and a colonoscopy.
Okay,I was just checking.
When I take a girl on
a date- - and I do- -
she knows she's been dated.
Capital D.
boldface. Undeinrled.
Da... ted.
I think I might have a little
concussion. I'm gonna go lie down.
Good night.
So,how was your date?
Awesome!
Score one for liquor and poor judgment.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents sync:YTET-cflily