so ***** with two slits in it
and either slit is observed,
it will not go through both slits.
If it's unobserved, it will.
However,if it's observed after it's left
the plane but before it hits its target,
it will not have gone though both slits.
Agreed. What's your point?
There's no point. I just think
it's a good idea for a t-shirt.
Excuse me.
Hang on.
Uh,one across is "aegean. "
Eight down is "nabokov. "
26 across is "mcm. "
14 down is... move your finger...
"phylum" which makes 14
across "port-au-prince"
see,"papa doc's capitol
idea," that's "port-au-prince. "
Haiti.
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
Um... is this the high-iq sperm bank?
If you have to ask, maybe
you shouldn't be here.
I think this is the place.
- Fill these out.
- Thank you.
We'll be right back.
Oh,take your time. I'll just
finish my crossword puzzle.
Oh,wait.
Leonard,I don't think I can do this.
What,are you kidding?
You're a semi-pro.
No. We are committing genetic fraud.
There's no guarantee that our sperm is going
to generate high-iq offspring. Think about that.
I have a sister with the same basic
dna mix who hostesses at fuddruckers.
Sheldon,this was your idea.
A little extra money to get fractional
t-1 bandwith in the apartment.
I know, and I do yearn
for faster downloads.
But there's some poor woman who's
gonna pin her hopes on my sperm.
What if she winds up with a toddler who doesn't
know if he should use an integral or a differential
to solve the area under a curve?
I'm sure she'll still love him.
I wouldn'T.
Well,what do you want to do?
- I want to leave.
- Okay.
What's the protocol for leaving?
I don't know- I've never reneged
on a proffer of sperm before.
Let's try just walking out.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Bye. Nice meeting you.
Are you still made about the sperm bank?
No.
You want to hear an
interesting thing about stairs?
Not really.
If the height of a single step
I don't care.
Two milli... that doesn't seem right.
No,it's true. I did a series
of experiments when I was 12.
My father broke his clavicle.
Is that why they sent
you to boarding school?
No. That was a result of my
work with lasers.
- new neighbor?
- Evidently.
Significant improvement
over the old neighbor.
200-pound transvestite with
a skin condition? Yes,she is.
- Oh,hi.
- Hi.
- Hi?
We don't mean to interrupt.
We live across the hall.
Oh,that's nice.
Oh,no,uh,we don't live together.
I mean,we live together,
but in separate,
heterosexual bedrooms.
Oh. Okay,well,guess I'm
your new neighbor. Penny.
Oh. Leonard. Sheldon.
- Hi.
Hi. Hi. Hi.
Well,uh... oh,uh,welcome
to the building.
Oh,thank you. Maybe we
can have coffee sometime.
- Oh,great.
- Great.
- Well,uh,bye.
- Bye.
Should we have invited her for lunch?
No. We're gonna start season
two of battlestar galactica.
We already watched the season two dvds.
Not with commentary.
I think we should be good neighbors and
invite her over, make her feel welcome.
We never invited
louie-slash-louise over.
Well... and that was wrong of us.
We need to widen our circle.
I have a very wide circle.
I have 212 friends on myspace.
Yes,and you've never met one of them.
That's the beauty of it.
I'm gonna invite her over.
We'll have a nice meal and... chat.
Chat? We don't chat.
At least not offline.
Well,it's not difficult. You
just listen to what she says
and then you say something
appropriate in response.
To what end?
Hi. Again.
- Hi.
Anyway,um... we brought
home indian food.
And,um...
I know that moving can be stressful,
and,and,I find that when
I'm undergoing stress,
that good food and company
can have a comforting effect.
Also, curry is a natural laxative,
and I don't have to tell you,
that,you know,a clean colon is
just one less thing to worry about.
Leonard,I'm no expert here, but I believe
in the context of a luncheon invitation,
you might want to skip the
reference to bowel movements.
Oh,you're inviting me over to eat?
Uh... yes.
Oh,that's so nice. I'd love to.
Great.
So,what do you guys
do for fun around here?
Well,today we tried
masturbating for money.
Our whole universe was
in a hot,dense state
then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... wait!
The earth began to cool the
autotrophs began to drool,
neanderthals developed
tools we built the wall
we built the pyramids
math,science,history,
unraveling the mystery that all started
with a big bang bang!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents...
Sync: cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
THE BIG BANG THEOTY
Season 01 Episode 01
yourself at home.
Okay. Thank you.
You're very welcome.
This looks like some serious
stuff. Leonard,did you do this?
Actually,that's my work.
Wow.
Yeah. Well,it's just some quantum mechanics with
a little string theory doodling around the edges.
That part there, that's just a joke.
It's a spoof of the
born-oppenheimer approximation.
So you're like one of those
beautiful mind genius guys.
Yeah.
This is really impressive.
I have a board. If you like
boards, this is my board.
Holy smokes.
If by "holy smokes" you mean a derivative
restatement of the kind of stuff
you can find scribbled on the
wall of any men's room at mit,sure.
- What?
- Come on.
Who hasn't seen this differential
below "here I sit, broken-hearted"?
At least I didn't have to invent 26
dimensions just to make the mathouome ct.
I didn't invent them. They're there.
In what universe?
In all of them-
that is the point.
Uh... do you guys mind if I start?
Um... penny...
that's where i sit.
So,sit next to me.
No... I sit there.
- What's the difference?
Here we go.
In the winter,that seat is close
enough to the radiator to remain warm,
and yet not so close as to
cause perspiration in the summer,
it's directly in the path of a cross-breeze
created by opening windows there and there
it faces the television at an
angle that is neither direct,
thus discouraging conversation,
nor so far wide as to
create a parallax distortion.
I could go on,but I
think I've made my point.
Do you want me to move?
- Well...
- just sit somewhere else.
Fine.
Sheldon,sit!
Ah.
Well,this is nice.
We don't have a lot of company over.
That's not true- koothrappali and
wolowitz come over all the time.
Yes,I know,but...
tuesday night we played klingon
boggle till 1:00 in the morning.
Yeah,I remember.
I resent you saying
we don't have company.
- I'm sorry.
- That has negative social implications.
I said I'm sorry!
So... klingon boggle?
Yeah. It's like regular
boggle,but... in klingon.
That's probably enough about
us. So,tell us about you.
Um... me? Okay.
I'm a sagittarius, which probably tells
you way more than you need to know.
Yes. It tells us that you participate
in the mass cultural delusion
that the sun's apparent position relative to arbitrarily
defined constellations at the time of your birth
somehow affects your personality.
Participate in the what?
I think what sheldon's trying to say is that
sagittarius wouldn't have been our first guess.
Oh,yeah. A lot of people
think I'm a water sign. Penny:
Okay,let's see, what else.
Oh,I'm a vegetarian. Except for fish.
And the occasional steak. I love steak!
Well,that's interesting.
Leonard can't process corn.
Well,uh,do you have some sort of a job?
Oh,yeah. I'm a waitress
at the cheesecake factory.
Oh... I love cheesecake.
You're lactose-intolerant.
I don't eat it- I just
think it's a good idea.
Oh. Anyways,I'm also
writing a screenplay.
It's about this sensitive girl who
comes to L.A. From lincoln,nebraska,
to be an actress and winds up a
waitress at the cheesecake factory.
So,it's based on your life.
No,I'm from omaha.
Well,if that was movie,
I would go see it.
I know,right?
Okay,let's see,what else... um...
guess that's about it.
That's the story of penny.
Well,it sounds wonderful.
It was.
Until I fell in love with
a jerk!
What's happening?
God,you know, four
years I lived with him.
Four years- that's like
as long as high school.
It took you four years to
get through high school?
It just... I can't
believe I trusted him.
Should I say something? I feel
like I should say something.
You? No,you'll only make it worse.
You want to know the most pathetic part?
Even though I hate his lying,
cheating guts...
I still love him.
Is that crazy?
Yes.
No,it's not crazy.
It's uh... uh... it's a paradox.
Paradoxes are part of nature.
Think about light. If you look
at huygens, light is a wave,
as confirmed by the double
- slit experiments,
but then along comes albert einstein and
discovers that light behaves like particles,too.
Well,I didn't make it worse.
I'm so sorry. I'm such a mess.
On top of everything else, I'm all gross from
moving and my stupid shower doesn't even work.
Our shower works.
Really? Would it be
totally weird if I used it?
Yes.
- No.
- No?
It's right down the hall.
Thanks. You guys are
really sweet.
well,this is an interesting development.
How so?
It has been some time since we've had a
woman take her clothes off in our apartment.
That's not true. Remember at thanksgiving my
grandmother with alzheimer's had that episode?
Point taken. It has been some time since
we've had a woman take her clothes off,
after which we didn't
want to rip our eyes out.
The worst part was watching
her carve that turkey.
So what exactly are you
trying to accomplish here?
Excuse me?
That woman in there is not
going to have sex with you.
Well,I'm not trying
to have sex with her.
Oh,good. Then you won't be disappointed.
What makes you think she
wouldn't have sex with me?
I'm a male and she's a female.
Yes,but not of the same species.
I'm not going to engage
in hypotheticals here.
I'm just trying to be a good neighbor.
Oh,of course.
That's not to say that if a carnal relationship
were to develop that I wouldn't participate.
However briefly.
Do you think this possibility
will be helped or hindered
when she discovers your luke
skywalker no-more-tears shampoo?
It's darth vader shampoo.
luke skywalker's the conditioner.
Wait till you see this.
It's fantastic, unbelievable.
See what?
It's a stephen hawking
lecture from mit in 1974.
This isn't a good time.
It's before he became a
creepy computer voice. Leonard:
That's great. You guys have to go.
Why?
It's just not a good time.
Leonard has a lady over.
Yeah,right- your
grandmother back in town?
No. And she's not a lady.
She's just a new neighbor.
Hang on,there really is a lady here?
Uh-huh.
And you want us out because
you're anticipating coitus?
I'm not anticipating coitus.
So she's available for coitus?
Can we please just stop saying "coitus"?
Technically,that would
be "coitus interruptus. "
Hey,is there a trick to getting
it to switch from tub to shower...?
Oh,hi. Sorry. Hello.
Enchant? mademoiselle.
Howard wolowitz caltech
department of applied physics.
You may be familiar
with some of my work.
It's currently orbiting jupiter's largest moon
taking high-resolution digital photographs.
Penny. I work at the cheesecake factory.
Come on,I'll show you
the trick with the shower.
Bonne douche.
I'M... I'm sorry?
It's french for "good shower. "
It's a sentiment I can
express in six languages.
Save it for your blog,howard.
??????????
all right, there it goes.
It sticks. I'm sorry.
Okay,thanks.
Reyou' welcome. Oh,you're just
going to step right... okay,I'll...
- hey,leonard...
- the hair products are sheldon'S.
Okay.
Um,can I ask you a favor?
A favor?
Sure,you can ask me a favor.
I would do you a favor for you.
It's okay if you say no.
Oh,I'll probably say yes.
It's just not the kind of thing
you ask a guy you just met.
Wow.
I really think we should examine
the chain of causality here.
Must we?
Event a- a beautiful woman
stands naked in our shower.
Event b- we drive halfway across
town to retrieve a television set
from the aforementioned
woman's ex-boyfriend.
Query- on what plane of existence is there
even a semi-rational link between these events?
She asked me to do her a favor,sheldon.
Ah,yes. Well,that may be the
proximal cause of our journey,
but we both know it only exists in
contradistinction to the higher level distal cause.
Which is?
You think with your penis.
That's a biological impossibility.
And you didn't have to come.
Oh,right,yes,I could have stayed behind and watch
wolowitz try to hit on penny in russian, arabic and farsi.
Why can't she get her own tv?
Come on,you know how
it is with breakups.
No,I don'T... and neither do you.
I broke up with joyce kim.
You did not break up with joyce
kim. She defected to north korea.
To mend her broken heart.
This situation is much less complicated.
There's some kind of dispute between penny and
her ex-boyfriend as to who gets custody of the tv.
She just wanted to avoid
having a scene with him.
So we get to have a scene with him?
No,sheldon,there's not
going to be a scene.
There's two of us and one of him.
Leonard,the two of us
can't even carry a tv.
So,you guys work with leonard
and sheldon at the university?
Um,I'm sorry. Do you speak english?
Oh,he speaks english.
Hecaust jn't speak to women.
Really? Why?
He's kind of a nerd.
Juice box?
I'll do the talking. Man:
Yeah?
Uh,hi,I'm leonard, this is sheldon.
- Hello.
- Let'S...
uh,we're here to pick up penny's tv.
Get lost.
Okay,thanks for you time.
We're not going to
give up just like that.
Leonard,the tv's in the building.
We have been denied access to
the building- ergo,we are done.
Excuse me.
If I were to give up on the first little hitch I
never would have been able to identify the fingerprints
of string theory in the
aftermath of the big bang.
My apologies. What's your plan?
It's just a privilege to
watch your mind at work.
Come on,we have a combined iq of 360.
We should be able
what do you think their combined iq is?
Just grab the door!
This is it.
I'll do the talking.
Good thinking. I'll just be the muscle.
Yeah?
I'm leonard, this is sheldon.
From the intercom.
How the hell did you
get in the building?
Uh... we're scientists.
Tell him about our iq.
- Leonard...
- what?
My mom bought me those pants.
I'm sorry.
You're going to have to call her.
Sheldon,I am so sorry I
dragged you through this.
It's okay. It wasn't my first
pantsing and it won't be my last.
And you were right about my motives.
I was hoping to establish a relationship
with penny that might have someday led to sex.
Well,you got me out of my pants.
Anyway,I've learned my lesson.
She's out of my league,
I'm done with her.
Got my work,one day I'll win the
nobel prize and then I'll die alone.
Don't think like that.
You're not going to die alone.
Thank you,sheldon. You're a good friend.
And you're certainly not
going to win a nobel prize.
This is one of my favorite
places to kick back after a quest.
They have a great house ale.
Wow,a cool tiger.
Yeah,I've had him since level ten.
His name is buttons.
Anyway,if you had your own game character
we could hang out, maybe go on a quest.
Sounds interesting.
So you'll think about it?
Oh,I don't think I'll be able
to stop thinking about it.
Smooth.
We're home.
Oh,my god,what happened?
Well,your ex-boyfriend sends his regards and
I think the rest is fairly self-explanatory.
I'm so sorry.
I really thought if you guys went
instead of me he wouldn't be such an ass.
No,it was a valid hypothesis.
That was a valid...?
What is happening to you?
Really... thank you so
much for going and trying.
You're so terrific.
Really.
Why don't you get some clothes on, I'll
get my purse, and dinner is on me,okay?
- Really? Great.
- Thank you.
You're not done with her,are you?
Are babies will be smart and beautiful.
Not to mention imaginary.
- *with you,penny?
- Sure.
We can't have thai food-
we had indian for lunch.
So?
They're both curry-based cuisines.
It would be gastronomically redundant.
I can see we're going to have to
spell out everything for this girl.
Any ideas,raj?
Uh,turn left on lake street
and head up to colorado.
I know a wonderful little
sushi bar that has karaoke.
That sounds like fun.
Baby,baby,don't get hooked on me
oh,baby,baby,don't get hooked on me...
I don't know what your odds
are in the world as a whole,
but as far as the
population of this car goes,
you're a veritable mack daddy.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- proudly presents...
THE BIG BANG THEOTY
Season 01 Episode 01
YTET-cflily
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-