Let's stay focused, Johnny.
What are you looking at?
Who is she?
That's Miss Cindy,
Zeke's new aide.
What happened
to his old aide?
She got married.
So, first,
you want to rub the
glue on the paper
in any shapes
you like.
Why do people get married?
Because they love each other.
Why aren't you married?
I haven't found
the person I love yet,
because I spend
all of my time loving you.
Does that mean
we can get married?
Well, love comes in many types,
and there's lots of it
to go around.
Oh, my snow is ruined.
It's not ruined.
Oh, it's pretty.
See, look, I like the green.
Who ever heard of green snow?
It's magical.
Come here.
We'll get you cleaned up, okay?
It's okay.
Ooh, are you okay?
Oh.
Hey, hey, hey.
You gonna pay for that?
Nice of you to offer.
Now I can actually get
some cream cheese.
29-year-old teacher--
she works
with special needs children.
She--
- Love what you're wearing.
Brings out the blue
of the case file,
which means it's not
from the E.R.
So why are you here?
Because Dr. Cuddy is not here.
She's decided to spend
some more time
at home with the baby
for a while.
I'm taking over some of her
day-to-day responsibilities,
like babysitting you.
Interesting.
You have your whole life
ahead of you.
So why would Cuddy want you
to die so young?
She figured I'd spent
three years working for you.
I was inoculated.
Good.
Fun.
You get to exercise
your newfound power.
I squirm under your thumb,
resent the student
becoming the teacher,
and then push comes to shove,
and we all get to realize
what our real roles should be.
Then you put out.
That's why I took the job.
29-year-old Special Ed. teacher
coughs up blood
all over Corky.
No dyspnea,
no weight loss.
Why are you smirking?
Never thought
I'd see the day
you were taking orders
from Cameron.
Cameron's in charge?
- When did that happen?
You're gonna destroy her,
aren't you?
I am going to do my job.
If that involves
leaving her a rotting pulp...
Cameron's gonna mark
her territory.
She'll probably overcompensate
and destroy you.
Bleeding ulcer.
Scope of the stomach
and lungs were clean,
yet she continues
to spit up blood
from both
her stomach and lungs.
That means it's probably
something wrong
with the blood itself--
Leukemia,
Von Willebrand's.
Thoracic tumor
is a better fit.
Erodes into her airway
and esophagus--
Oh, will you two
stop it already?
Stop what?
- Disagreeing.
Okay, which one of us
shouldn't have an opinion?
It's not an opinion.
It's a smoke screen.
Toss out a lame idea,
instead of agreeing
with Foreman's better idea
because you're worried
that'll confirm
that he's boldly gone
where no man
has gone before.
You slept
with Foreman?
Sorry.
You were busy.
Drop it, House.
We're seeing each other,
end of discussion.
Anything else
isn't relevant.
It's extremely relevant.
Apparently,
it colors everything.
Now I have no idea
if you have differing opinions
because you have
differing opinions
or because
you're just trying to prove
that you can think
for yourselves.
How about you just judge
our ideas on their own merit?
Oh, you don't want me
to do that.
Go run
a bleeding-time test,
confirm our patient's blood
is screwy.
Then you can come back
and pretend to disagree
about why.
Time Zero.
I'm impressed.
You didn't even flinch.
I just went to my happy place.
We cannot let House
anywhere near this woman.
Where is your happy place?
My class,
with them.
Passed the first mark.
It's a great thing you do.
Not really.
Most kids,
typical children--
you hand them a pair
of scissors, and they cut.
Well, Tony--
he's got C.P.,
and when I gave him
the scissors,
we went
on a journey together,
learning to get his fingers
in those holes,
to hold the scissors apart,
to hold the paper.
I mean, when
he finally learned to cut,
we both just wept with joy.
If you ever meet our boss,
just yes or no answers, okay?
It's not slowing up.
No sign of clotting.
So there is something wrong
with my blood?
Don't worry,
we'll run some lab tests
to find out which clotting
factor is off and then--
I'm not worried.
Must be one hell of a happy place.
She's beautiful.
I know. I'm lucky.
Absolutely.
What's she like?
She's eight weeks old.
Are you asking me about her
politics or her sense of humor?
My cousin had a kid.
They acted
like they knew the thing
from the time
it was two minutes old.
I just--
I just thought--
She cries, she eats,
and she poops.
What's wrong?
I don't feel anything.
You're tired.
I'm not sleep deprived.
She sleeps fine.
I'm obviously not hormonal.
I know I'm supposed to feel amazement.
I'm supposed to love her.
I just...
I don't feel
anything at all.
Sorry.
Maybe I am just tired.
Um...
Thank you for stopping by.
I'm okay.
Lisa...
If you're...
I am feeding her,
I'm changing her,
and I'm burping her.
I'm doing everything
I'm supposed to do.
She will be okay.
Please go back to work.
OOD,
but the clotting proteins
aren't the problem.
It's her platelets, looked like
they had bite marks in them.
So now you're agreeing?
Either you folded
because I gave you crap,
or you broke up, or--
We disagree,
you blame our relationship.
We agree, you blame
our relationship.
Don't you see a problem there?
- Yes.
Don't you?
Could be lymphoma.
Not with normal LDH.
I.T.P. fits.
We should start her
on methotrexate.
Absolutely,
and total body irradiation.
Because she failed
a bleeding-time test?
TBI will promote cancers,
kill her digestive tract.
Don't forget--stop her
from bleeding into her brain.
It's premature, reckless,
and potentially lethal.
True.
Must be somebody's job
to stop me from being reckless
and irresponsible.
Nobody can stop me
from being premature.
Got a patient with I.T.P.
Need to hit her with radiation.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Methotrexate.
- Good point.
On the other hand,
if she bleeds in her brain,
she's gonna need
a Special Ed. class of her own.
Fine.
Really?
Yeah, if you think
it's right, do it.
Hmm.
Some people thought
you were gonna be brutal,
marking your territory.
Who?
- Nobody.
Just because I call him nobody
doesn't make me a racist.
I'm not gonna play games.
If you come to me
with a request
and it makes medical sense,
I'll say yes.
I need oral sex.
I'm pretty sure
biological imperative
qualifies as medical sense.
Can I return my phone call now?
I don't really see
how that's gonna be possible.
Patient won't respond
to methotrexate.
Bleeding time hasn't improved.
You have a medical dilemma for me.
I have one for you.
I need a reason to not do
total body irradiation.
Other than that Cameron
said you can't.
She said I can.
Then why don't we just do it?
Because it's premature, reckless,
and potentially lethal.
Then why don't we
just don't do it?
Because that would let
Cameron in on the fact
that I never intended to do it.
This is gonna be convoluted,
isn't it?
I figured I'd ask
for something really crazy,
so she'd shoot me down
and get the whole
"I can control House" thing
out of her perky little system.
So the next time
I went back
And asked for something
marginally crazy,
it would seem marginally
reasonable, and she'd say yes.
So, yeah, slightly convoluted.
You're screwed.
Unless we irradiate her...
without the radiation.
We book the nuclear lab.
We fill out the paperwork.
We bring the patient down there.
We do everything
but flip the switch.
Go. Do.
Don't flip.
And is there anything
we should be doing, you know,
to actually help the patient?
Trust me.
In the long term,
this'll help all our patients.
In the short term,
double the dose of methotrexate
and add prednisone.
Cameron's got the keys
to the castle.
This trial I'm running--the drug
really seems to be working.
She's kind of liking the power.
I think I'm kind of liking her
liking it.
I'm not sure what I'm gonna do
about Thirteen.
She's sort of dressing
like Cuddy.
She's on the placebo.
You can't possibly know that.
Accidents happen.
I found out.
You cannot tell her.
You'd be compromising the trial.
She knows she had a 50/50 chance
of not being on the drug.
If you feel like you're lying
to her, too bad.
I don't want to tell her.
I want to put her
on the real drug.
And you want me to tell you
that that's okay?
Her trial results
are already compromised,
just from the fact that I know.
As long as she's wasting
her time,
Why not give her something
that might actually help her?
Valid point,
except for the fact
That it's a load of crap.
Don't be an idiot.
So how long
until we start the procedure?
We already started.
Told you you wouldn't feel a thing.
You should lie back.
Just stay real still.
I'm afraid there
is someone sitting next to you.
oh, for--
God, God, God!
I have to pee.
Can we, like, call a
timeout for a minute,
let me go to the bathroom?
Yeah, sure.
We'll just start up again
when you're done.
Thanks.
Sorry. I-I didn't realize
I had to go.
No problem.
Sarah?
No pulse.
Get the paddles.
Clear!
Got a pulse.
It's not I.T.P.
No structural defects
in her heart.
What about a calcified valve
or a patent foramen ovale?
Transthoracic echo and
bubble studies show nothing.
Her heart's clean.
The patient said she had to go pee.
Maybe when she got up,
she started to urinate.
Increased the vagal tone,
caused arrhythmia,
and stopped her heart.
Who has to go pee in the middle
of a nuclear procedure?
It wasn't really
a nuclear procedure.
She didn't know that.
People don't die from peeing.
Heavy metal, toxin.
Drugs or alcohol.
Or her own body is making a toxin.
Cold agglutinins--
abnormal protein gets activated
by cold temperatures.
Like the classroom
with the broken heater
and the cold metal table
in the procedure room.
Oh, for God's sake, get a room.
Immerse her in an ice bath.
The cold will activate
her cold agglutinins.
Causing her heart to race.
Confirming our diagnosis.
And giving her another heart attack.
Lucky for me,
there's a flaxen-haired maiden
who loves to say yes.
How in the world could you
approve total body irradiation
for a patient
with possible I.T.P.?
It was the right call.
There is no medical
justification for that kind of--
Not medically, no.
Absolutely
no medical rationalization.
I had to say yes
because House wanted me to say no.
You think he was bluffing.
I'm the new kid.
He had to test me.
Don't get cute.
Don't engage him.
Do not play his games,
because you will lose.
You hired me to do this job.
Let me do it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Looks like you guys
are in the middle
of a conversation.
I can wait till Cuddy leaves.
You are gonna leave soon,
aren't you?
I mean, the nurses have got
your baby out there.
Not that they're gonna kidnap it
or anything,
but I figured that the new
mother brings the baby to work
because she wants to listen
to all the cooing.
If you're gonna wait,
you can wait outside.
Unless the new mother
brings the baby to work
because she wants
to dump the baby,
because she hates the baby
and thinks she made
a big mistake.
Can't trust that Wilson guy
with anything.
Lisa, are you--
- It's not a big deal.
I was having a bad day.
Is Wilson gonna be in trouble?
For betraying my trust
in a vulnerable time?
No.
Why would that bother me?
He was worried, made a bad choice.
It's not a big deal.
I know it seems like crap.
You probably feel like crap,
but it's not.
Legally,
you haven't adopted her yet.
There's no obligations,
no strings.
it can be undone tomorrow.
Emotionally,
you'll feel guilty
for a while,
but the kid--
she won't even know you existed.
You saying I should give her back?
Much better than having a mother
who doesn't give a crap.
Thanks.
I'm just gonna go drop it off
at the pound.
What did you want?
We got a green light.
Go draw the patient's blood.
Why?
To see if it clumps in the cold.
She's making you confirm
your theory before you treat?
She approved the bath.
Just thought we ought to do
a test to confirm.
That's more
of a yellow light, isn't it?
So she let's you nuke
the patient, no problem,
but makes you jump through hoops
to give her a bath?
Why would she do that?
I think she was playing you.
Go draw the blood.
Didn't realize the nurses
allowed any visitors in here.
They don't.
We'll just do these problems,
And then you
have to go, okay?
Okay.
I need to draw some blood.
I had a crush on my teacher
in fourth grade...
and fifth.
It's more that
Johnny was a nonverbal autistic.
Then for Sarah,
he talks,
makes eye contact.
He's like a regular kid.
Since she got sick,
he started going
back away from us.
I had to bring him in
for a visit.
I'll tell you what--
I'll close the blinds so
the nurses don't ask questions.
You can stay as long as you want.
We should have the results
in about an hour.
I'll be here.
Good job.
One minute at 39 degrees.
Oh, damn, sorry.
You all right?
Don't be paranoid.
I feel great.
Didn't expect the meds
to work this quickly.
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
You might not even be
on the real drug.
Several patients
have shown improvement.
I know my test results
have been better.
I know I have more energy.
You ever hear the term
placebo effect?
I guess I do have a few reasons
to feel good,
but...
Let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
You're good,
but not "curing Huntington's" good.
Good.
It's clumped.
House was right.
Ice bath's on.
Got a sec?
Don't be an idiot.
I know it's hard,
But you need to stay in there
for three minutes.
It's okay.
You come to procedures now?
Only the ones that might involve
stopping the patient's heart.
Cameron tell you to be here?
Shut up.
Tell me about Jonathan.
How'd you get him
to come out of hiding?
He was extremely
sensitive to touch,
yet he had a-a tactile
fascination with newspaper.
I mean, he wouldn't read it.
He would just--
just touch it,
crinkle it.
I thought maybe that was a way in,
Papier mache and...
Ohh.
And it was.
He let me into his world.
Please tell her that talking
will ruin the test.
All the kids--
I-I try
to become a part of them,
and then have them
become a part of me.
How much longer
till the heart attack?
I wanted to be a doctor from
the time I was eight years old.
Never wanted to be
a pediatrician, though.
Now they're both talking.
Well, I wanted to be
a sociologist.
I was supposed to observe
a class.
I was sent to room 2--
214,
but I went to room 241 instead.
It was a Special Ed. class,
and I just...
Oh.
I just felt at home.
Time.
Heart rate's normal.
You can get out now.
It's not cold agglutinins.
I'm not surprised.
She obviously has brain damage.
Seriously.
She screwed up a room number
six years ago,
and you decide
she has brain damage?
Transposed digits--
classic marker
for number confusion.
Means she has a lesion in her
left parahippocampal region.
This morning.
Must be contagious.
She also forgot to pee
before your fake test.
So she has a small bladder.
Shows an inability
to predict the future.
Also located in the left hemisphere
of the brain,
Close to the parahippocampal region.
Means the damage is ongoing.
Two subtle clues six years apart--
that's hardly compelling evidence.
I'm compelled.
- That's not what this is.
Every time a decent person
comes in, you set out to prove
that they have brain damage.
I never said her deranged
personality was a symptom.
You don't need to.
I've been here five years.
I can hear your thoughts
from my apartment.
Can you hear me now?
Move on to another organ.
I did.
The screwed up numbers
and forgetting to pee
points to her
being a human being.
The platelet dysfunction
and cardiac arrest
points to a pancreatic tumor.
Or multiple sclerosis.
The brain is like the internet--
Packets of information
constantly flowing
from one area to another.
Plaques in her brain
are like a bad server,
slow down the flow.
If it's in the parahippocampus,
it'll spread to the brain stem,
which means it'll be the lungs next.
Brain biopsy
will show you the plaques.
Or we could not cut
into her brain.
It's just her pancreas.
We should do an ERCP.
Well, we could settle this
with rock, paper, scissors,
but...
unfortunately, there are people
who adjudicate these disputes.
A pancreatic tumor
is much more likely to kill her.
Not this week, not next week,
not next month.
The number confusion was six years ago.
You don't think we have time for an ERCP?
- The heart attack was six hours ago.
Now, maybe it's planning to go
into hiding for a couple years,
or maybe it's gonna hit her lungs.
Stop!
We have to assume it's the brain.
I'll go fire up the biopsy drill.
No, we had to assume it's the brain
until we prove otherwise.
Do an MRI, T-2 images.
You want me to do another test?
You should be able to see
the M.S. plaques.
If they exist,
you can do your biopsy.
No.
You want to say yes.
You know you should say yes,
but you also think that this job
is about standing up to me.
So you're not gonna say yes.
You're not gonna say no.
You're just gonna waste time.
And the patient's brain,
or pancreas,
or whatever is wrong with her
is not gonna wait
for you to impress your boss.
So pick one--
either him or me.
Do the MRI.
You're still here?
The whole point of giving Cameron the job
was so that you could--
- I don't want to go home.
House told me
I should give her back.
Instead of being offended,
I've been wondering if he's right.
He's not.
He never is,
not when it's
anything personal, or human,
or...
- No, he's always cold.
He's always an ass,
but he's very rarely just wrong.
I've read
every bonding
and attachment book there is.
I feel like I'm in prison at home.
I feel like I'm free here.
Parents make sacrifices.
I don't know if I want to.
I'm not proud of this.
I feel terrible.
I feel like a failure.
But she deserves to be loved.
I-I...
I don't know what to say.
No plaques on the
left hemisphere.
Or the right.
Even magnified images of her
hippocampal region, nothing.
This is surprising.
So can we cancel the biopsy?
Go ahead with the ERCP.
I need to talk to you about Remy.
Who?
Thirteen.
What did you call her?
She's on placebo.
And you want to change that.
I'm the last person you'd ever
come to for ethical advice,
literally,
which means you've already asked
every other person,
and no one's given you
the answer you want.
Or I respect your opinion,
and I want to hear
what comes to your mind.
Has she invited
any of her lesbian friends
into bed with you?
I was mistaken.
Drug gonna cure her?
It looks promising, reducing symptoms.
No cure then.
So the pros are:
You might delay the onset of symptoms,
Give her an extra year,
maybe three.
She's still dead before you're 45.
The question is, are those few years
worth risking the rest
of your life in medicine?
No.
There, that wasn't so hard, was it?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Unless you love her.
If you love her,
you do stupid things.
Common bile duct
is clear.
No filling defects in the biliary tree.
Oh, God.
- What?
It's her lungs.
House was right.
O-2 SAT's down to 89.
Increase to 100% O-2.
Better get out.
Do we have to tell him?
The surgeons were able to
drain the pleural effusions.
The patient's breathing on her own,
But she's still pretty weak.
Lung failure proves
that one of us was right.
Who said brain?
Yes, you predicted
that her lungs would fail,
but the MRI was negative for M.S.
I was right about the where,
but not the what.
A picornavirus could cause
localized demyelination
that the MRI wouldn't pick up.
If we run a nerve-conduction study
on the surface of her brain,
we'll see the dead spots.
Are you talking
about cutting into her skull?
Actually, I'm talking
about cutting off her skull,
exposing her brain.
A pancreatic tumor could still fit.
It explains the heart,
the blood, and her lungs.
ERCP was negative.
And she agrees with me
because she agrees with me,
right, sweetie?
All we need is a more sensitive test.
Endoscopic ultrasound.
Just accept that
you've been proven wrong.
You were also proven wrong.
Why don't I get a second test?
Because if I'm right
about the brain,
then we don't have time
to indulge your wrongness.
Let me know
when Cameron says yes
to cutting off our patient's skull.
I'll be doing the endoscopic ultrasound.
Good news.
I don't need your approval
for some crazy, unproven treatment.
I just need to do a test.
You want to remove
your patient's skull.
Remind me to revoke
Kutner's telephone privileges.
I didn't realize
that was an A.M.A.-approved
treatment for M.S.
Not searching for M.S.,
but what set it off--
Equine encephalitis.
Turned a cool breeze of M.S.
into a CAT-5 storm.
I didn't realize
your patient was a horse.
There's been human cases.
Not when it's 30 degrees outside.
Transmission is by mosquito.
So she got bitten six months ago,
or it's some other infection.
Whatever it is,
it's running rampant
in the left side of her brain.
When I get in there,
I'll get you the specifics.
You're asking me to let you cut
off the top of someone's head.
I need more than,
"I'll know it when I see it."
So you want proof before you let
me go looking for the proof?
This is the test.
You have to give me something.
Cuddy's gonna love you.
The patient, on the other hand,
is gonna hate you until the day
she dies next week.
Actually, this idiot
will probably forgive you.
It looks like something
you could hang something off.
You gonna help or what?
I want kids.
Um...
I think these kids
are already spoken for.
Not now.
But since we're dating,
I just thought you should know.
But I thought,
because of your illness--
So did I.
Even when I didn't know
if I had it or not,
I just assumed
I couldn't take the chance,
but now...
Even though I know I have it,
it feels like...
an option.
You really don't have
to keep buying me things.
Just open it.
This is nice.
The picture is actually your gift.
That's your baby.
I took her picture
to one of those places
that does
that age-enhancement thing.
And according to the kid
who works there,
this is a pretty good approximation
of what your daughter will look
like 18 years from now.
That's, uh, sort of cool.
Right now she's just
this weird little creature
that sleeps, and poops, and cries.
But that...
is who she's gonna be.
You will be teaching her
how to ride a bike,
giving her advice
about friends and school
and having her heart broken.
She'll ignore most of it,
but some of it'll stick.
You're gonna be there for her
through all of that.
You just have to get
through this part.
That's all.
It's very sweet.
I'll pay you back for the photo.
Don't worry about it.
It's just the picture
that came with the frame.
You can chuck it.
Kid with a raging viral syndrome
And three dead mosquitoes.
I'm off to storm the bastille.
These aren't mosquitoes.
Fruit flies--
close enough.
Acute viral nasopharyngitis?
One of her students
has the common cold?
Team's not what it used to be.
On the other hand,
Kutner ran his endoscopic ultrasound.
Didn't find peep.
So disproving it's her pancreas
proves it's her brain?
Yes.
You used to do this job,
remember?
That's what used to pass
for evidence.
Now I do this job.
You brought me three dead bugs
and a runny nose.
I can't find you the proof you want
Because it's trapped inside her head.
And the only way I can get at it
Is to cut it open
and rip it out,
Which is apparently the one test
you won't let me run.
So either I do this,
or I do nothing.
What do you want me to do?
Say yes just because you're House?
I'd certainly like that, yeah.
Yes.
Cameron actually said yes?
Nope, I'm just obsessive
about clean cuticles.
Sawing off the top of her skull
and placing electrodes
on her brain is insane.
Right, we should be retesting
her pancreas
for the umpteenth time.
You're skipping steps
because it's Cameron.
You haven't figured her out yet,
And you want to see how far you can push.
- I'm skipping steps
because our patient is skipping
steps on the way to being dead.
If you've got
a better idea...
We should remove
her spleen.
Splenic lymphoma
explains the damaged platelets,
the heart, the lungs.
If this doesn't work,
the spleen's all yours.
Unless I kill her, of course.
Not only will this allow us
to clock your brain's
processing speed,
You'll also get free cable
for the first three months.
What's this?
A blue car.
Is that part of the test?
Nope, my lease is up next month.
You like?
I'm gonna ask you a series
of questions
designed to stimulate
left-brain function--
logic, reasoning,
problem-solving.
Or as my mentor, Old Ben,
liked to call it,
"the dark side."
If we find slow areas,
we know we found damage.
We treat.
You go home.
Ready?
I'd nod yes,
but I can't move my head.
This pen is red.
Its ink is red.
Is all ink red?
No.
Nerve conduction's
12.8 meters per second--
right within range.
Cameron's letting him cut
into our patient's skull
based on nothing but dead bugs
and someone else's runny nose.
There are two pints in a quart,
four quarts in a gallon.
How many pints
in five gallons?
House, step away
from the patient.
Who's that?
Okay, all right.
That's my old boss.
And by "old,"
I don't mean "former."
Insulting me
is not gonna make me go away.
You're not here.
Obviously I'm not trying
to make you go away.
Hint--
the answer is a number.
Um, 40?
12.4 meters per second--
conduction is still normal.
Dr. Cameron, you're actually
assisting him with this?
Yes, because I'm actually
familiar with this case.
Well, I'm familiar enough to know
that cutting into this woman's
brain is not necessary.
Is she serious?
Well, she's certainly not funny.
Put the phone down.
Pick up the baby.
Make us all happy.
Okay, settle down, baby.
It's okay.
We'll be done in a minute.
House,
I can call security.
I can--
- BP's dropping.
Get it back up.
I got a whole stack
of these.
Give her ten CCs dopamine.
Already am, thanks.
Your baby needs you
a lot more than we do.
You aren't hungry,
and you aren't wet.
I don't know what it is.
Oh, that is so annoying.
Can you make it stop?
The baby's crying is annoying you?
What's her nerve conduction?
14.3--
it's actually speeding up.
But her BP's 80 over palp.
We're gonna have to stop.
Ugh.
That doesn't make any sense.
The fact that you're wrong
doesn't make any sense,
or the fact that I believed
that you were right?
BP's still dropping.
She's gonna stroke.
I'm giving her ten more CCs,
And I'm putting an end to this.
Okay, Rachel, quiet down!
I need you to be quiet!
Please, turn that phone off!
Why does the baby annoy you,
but no one else does?
I mean, you're right
about her, but--
I don't know what you want!
I will give you anything
that you want!
I don't know what it is!
Tell me!
Please, just help me!
Please!
Really?
That worked?
She's stable.
We're finished here.
Close her up.
How long until we can perform
the splenectomy?
Can't dose her with anesthesia
till the last batch completely clears.
How come the baby annoyed her?
We should get her in there
as soon as we can.
Two hours at least.
Her blood pressure's
in the tank.
I hope she lasts two hours.
What was different?
Our patient
loves all things annoying.
She'd love this conversation.
She's an earth mother,
takes in the freaks and rejects
of humanity
And tells them they're a-okay.
So what was different?
Her head was open,
you were asking her questions,
A baby was crying.
She had low blood pressure.
According to the laws of physics,
low blood pressure
causes light-headedness,
chest pain,
but not annoyance.
Move your feet.
You decided to keep her.
Thank you for telling me.
You can go now.
Mmm.
I talked to her.
We connected.
You talked at her.
You had a chemical reaction.
You trying to annoy me?
I'm trying to explain you.
I know it doesn't make
any sense,
but it was real.
It was there.
You want to hold her?
Come up here.
Come say hi.
You think we'll bond?
Is that cute?
A little.
If I threw up on you,
you'd be pissed.
Your puke isn't as cute.
That's 'cause of your hips.
If she would've just gestated
a little longer,
her stomach sphincter
would be fully mature.
But, no,
we have to walk upright,
which means that baby's head
is too big for mommy's hips.
And by the way, your hips may be
an evolutionary improvement.
So we've evolved
to find baby puke cute,
'cause otherwise
we'd kill them all
before they became functional.
Bonding's over.
I got to go see another baby.
So I can just live spleen-free?
Plenty of people live
perfectly normal lives without--
Spleen's fine.
It's not her brain.
Of course it's her brain.
You looked at her brain.
You took off her skull.
You found nothing.
Didn't look in the right part.
Didn't look in the heart part.
In the womb,
Blood has to bypass the lungs,
Since they don't work yet.
When we're born,
we take our first big breath,
lungs expand, and the ductus closes.
Yours didn't.
She has a patent ductus arteriosis.
When you get stressed,
your blood pressure goes up
and forces open the ductus.
Blood takes a little detour,
makes it leak from your nose,
your stomach, your lungs,
and, more significantly,
keeps it flowing
to the right side of your brain
and away from your left.
Which means that when you get
stressed, you get unstressed.
That's why you're so good
with those annoying kids.
And why, when your
blood pressure dropped,
you were able to identify Cuddy
as an annoying human being.
Good news is,
we can fix the heart.
Bad news for the annoying kids.
She's incredible.
Thank you.
Great work today.
I should've trusted your instincts.
I will in the future.
I quit.
I think I just apologized.
If you want,
I can get down on my knees.
It's not because of you.
I approved an insane procedure
with no proof, no evidence, no--
You made the right call.
The problem
was a brain problem.
Without the procedure,
House never notices
the increased left-brain function.
She'd be dead if you hadn't said yes.
- I know.
But...
I'll always say yes to House.
I studied under him.
He's in my head.
And if you gave anyone else this
job, they would always say no,
because--
well, because they should.
House is insane.
Which leaves me.
I'm sorry.
# how can it be #
Hey, buddy!
# we are losing ourselves? #
Oh!
It's okay, buddy.
Come here.
Oh, I missed you so much.
I missed you.
# underneath my own hell
when the daylight comes down #
# oh, we are dying away #
# all I can say #
# when the band begins to play #
# there's no angel #
# on my side #
# and I will need you #
# #
# can you hear #
# them calling me? #
# #
# and the rusted dawn #
# of a thousand years #
# goes by #
# aah #
# all I can say
when the band begins to play #
# there's no angel on my side #
Subtitles by LeapinLar