WOW.
YEAH.
COME BACK TO BED.
GIMME A MINUTE.
YOU GET 20 SECONDS.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU-
FEMALE, LATE 20S,
TONIC CLONIC SEIZURE.
DURATION OF THE SEIZURE?
A LITTLE OVER THREE MINUTES.
DOES YOUR FRIEND HAVE
A HISTORY OF EPILEPSY?
SHE NEVER SAID.
MY NAME IS DR. CAMERON.
YOU'RE IN A HOSPITAL.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE CARE OF YOU.
- WHAT'S HER NAME?
- I DON'T KNOW.
??????????????????
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
HOUSE 505
-=??????=-
??: ??:
???:?????s
HOUSE.
EH.
I HAVE A CASE I THINK
YOU MIGHT BE INTERESTED IN.
NOT NOW.
A 26-YEAR-OLD WOMAN
HAD A TONIC CLONIC SEIZURE.
WHAT ABOUT ME SPEEDING AWAY
SAYS TO YOU "LET'S CHAT"?
HISTORY OF FATIGUE,
AND TWO YEARS AGO
SHE HAD A RETINAL
VEIN OCCLUSION.
SHE'S DIABETIC.
NO, SHE'S NOT.
AND SHE HAS NO HISTORY
OF HYPERTENSION.
IT CAN WAIT.
I KNEW I SHOULD'VE SET UP
A VIDEO CAMERA.
STAY THERE.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
I PLAYED A PRACTICAL JOKE
ON MY BEST FRIEND,
AND HE'S BADLY INJURED.
I WISH I HAD LEARNED
THIS VALUABLE LESSON EARLIER.
I WAS WAITING BY MY WINDOW
FOR AN HOUR.
WHY ARE YOU LATE?
I HAD A BREAKFAST MEETING
AT MICKEY'S DINER
WITH THE MERCY PEOPLE
TO TELL THEM...
I'M COMING BACK
TO WORK HERE.
SORRY IF IT INTERFERED
WITH YOUR PLAN
TO MAIM ME.
DONUT'S A NICE TOUCH.
IT'S JUST A WAY OF SAYING
"WELCOME BACK."
THE SEIZURE COULD BE
THE RESULT OF DEHYDRATION
OR SOMETHING NEUROLOGICAL.
OR THE ECSTASY YOU FOUND
IN HER SYSTEM.
ACCORDING TO DR. HADLEY,
THE PATIENT TOOK THE DRUGS
ABOUT FIVE HOURS
BEFORE THE SEIZURE, SO.
WHAT DOES THIRTEEN KNOW
ABOUT IT?
UH, APPARENTLY SHE WAS
WITH THE PATIENT LAST NIGHT.
AT 3:00 A.M.?
OH, YEAH.
PENTHOUSE FORUM MEETS
MEDICAL MYSTERY.
MAYBE THERE IS A GOD.
EMPTY TRANSIENT SEX?
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU
TO SPIRAL OUT OF CONTROL
EVER SINCE YOU GOT
YOUR HUNTINGTON'S DIAGNOSIS,
BUT THIS IS MORE
THAN I DARED HOPE FOR.
PATIENT'S SEIZURE RESULTED
FROM DEHYDRATION,
WHICH RESULTED FROM A COCKTAIL
OF ALCOHOL AND ECSTASY.
MYSTERY SOLVED.
WAIT.
WERE YOU DOING DRUGS?
NOT DIAGNOSTICALLY RELEVANT.
DEPENDS WHAT
WE'RE TRYING TO DIAGNOSE.
IT'S HOW STEEP OF A SPIRAL
YOU'RE ON.
OUR PATIENT HEMORRHAGED
INTO HER EYE TWO YEARS AGO.
ALSO NOT DIAGNOSTICALLY
RELEVANT.
RETINAL VEIN OCCLUSION
WAS FIXED.
HER DOCTOR SAID IT WAS
A VENOUS ANOMALY.
IS HE IN THIS ROOM?
BECAUSE IF HE'S NOT,
I DON'T CARE WHAT HE THINKS.
UNLESS HE'S A SHE
AND SHE WAS
THERE LAST NIGHT TOO,
IN WHICH CASE
I CARE VERY DEEPLY.
WHAT IF THE EYE PROBLEM
WASN'T WITH HER VEIN,
BUT WITH HER BLOOD?
WOULD EXPLAIN WHY SHE SEIZED,
WHY SHE'S ALWAYS TIRED.
SHE PARTIES TILL 3:00 A.M.
THAT'S WHY SHE'S ALWAYS TIRED.
YET YOU SEEM FINE.
SHE'S VISITED FOUR OTHER DOCTORS
IN THE PAST YEAR.
NONE OF THEM FOUND ANYTHING.
SHE'S A HYPOCHONDRIAC
WHO DRANK TOO MUCH.
BLOOD CLOTS COULD EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING.
MAKES SENSE.
BONE MARROW'S IN OVERDRIVE.
TOO MANY PLATELETS.
SORRY.
THIRTEEN,
GO STICK A NEEDLE
IN YOUR GIRLFRIEND'S PELVIS.
AND NO, THAT ONE WASN'T
A METAPHOR.
SUCK OUT SOME MARROW.
THAT ONE WAS.
I LIKE TO WATCH.
I CAN HANDLE THIS ALONE.
YOU'VE ALREADY HANDLED IT.
THAT'S WHY YOU NEED
A CHAPERONE.
OF COURSE,
I'M A VERY PERMISSIVE,
UNDERSTANDING CHAPERONE.
SO FEEL FREE TO IGNORE ME.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE
IN THE MOOD TO START KISSING,
OR GROPING,
OR SHOWERING.
YOU'LL HAVE TO EXCUSE
DR. HOUSE.
HE MISTAKES IMMATURITY
FOR EDGINESS.
YOU'RE DR. HOUSE?
I ASSUME MY NAME CAME UP
LAST NIGHT
IN THE FORM OF A MOAN.
YOU HAD SEX, THEN A SEIZURE.
COULD BE A PARTICULAR
POSITION OR ACTIVITY
THAT SET IT OFF.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A VALID
MEDICAL THEORY, DOESN'T IT?
I'M REALLY SORRY.
JUST IGNORE HIM.
WHATEVER YOU THINK WE DID,
WE-WE DID.
AND THEN SOME.
LIGHTS ON OR OFF?
DO YOU HAVE A MEDICAL
RATIONALIZATION FOR THAT ONE?
LIGHT SENSITIVITY.
ON.
HUH.
FIGURED SHE HAD MORE SHAME
THAN THAT.
DID SHE TALK DIRTY,
OR DID YOU RELY
ON VAGUE HAND SIGNALS?
SHE'S, UH, PRETTY DIRECT
ABOUT WHAT SHE WANTS.
I'M LEARNING SO MUCH.
OKAY, SCORE THE SCORE.
SCALE OF ONE TO TEN.
DON'T ANSWER.
SEVEN.
FINALLY GOT ONE RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO INVESTIGATE HIM
BECAUSE HE ATE A DONUT?
HE CLAIMED HE HAD
A MORNING MEETING
AT MICKEY'S DINER.
WILSON LOVES MICKEY'S DINER.
HE HAS THE FRENCH TOAST TOWER
WHENEVER HE SETS FOOT
IN THE DOOR.
THERE'S NO WAY HE WOULD'VE COME
TO WORK
WANTING MORE CARBS.
HE LIED TO ME.
I NEED TO KNOW WHY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL FIND OUT?
I'M WORRIED
THAT HE MIGHT BE A SPY.
HE'S BEEN GONE FOUR MONTHS.
??? the friendsHIP
HAS CHANGED.
I'M JUST NOT SURE
IF HE'S WORKING
FOR HIROHITO
OR THE NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS.
YOU PLAYED A PRACTICAL JOKE
ON HIM.
HE DIDN'T LAUGH.
I NEED SOMETHING
TO LORD OVER HIM, A LIE-
HE DIDN'T TRY TO RETALIATE.
HE MORALIZED.
HE ALWAYS MORALIZED.
HE ALWAYS MORALIZED
AND GOT EVEN.
HE HASN'T FIRED BACK.
THINGS ALWAYS CHANGE.
AND THAT SUCKS.
YEAH.
FIND OUT WHERE HE WAS.
SHOULD'VE KNOWN
IT WASN'T A COINCIDENCE.
FOUND YOUR LETTERS.
YOU RECOGNIZED HOUSE'S NAME.
AND YOU'RE THE FIRST PATIENT
I'VE SEEN
WHO ACTUALLY ENJOYED
BEING ACCOSTED BY HIM.
I WOULD'VE TOLD YOU, BUT-
WHAT EXACTLY WOULD YOU
HAVE TOLD ME?
THAT YOU SLEPT WITH ME
TO GET TO HOUSE?
THAT YOU'VE BEEN TRYING
TO GET HIM
TO TAKE YOUR CASE
FOR OVER A YEAR?
I'M SICK.
NO ONE EVEN WROTE BACK.
YOU USED ME.
- you use me.
- MY MOTIVES WERE CLEAR.
YOU MIGHT'VE FIGURED OUT
MY MOTIVES FASTER
IF YOU BOTHERED TO ASK MY NAME.
I FOLLOWED YOU TO THAT BAR
BECAUSE I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU.
SEE IF YOU'D HELP ME GET
TO HOUSE.
I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU TO BE
SO AGGRESSIVE.
WAS THAT SEIZURE EVEN REAL?
WHY WOULD I FAKE A SYMPTOM?
IT WOULD JUST MAKE IT HARDER
FOR HOUSE TO DIAGNOSE ME.
THERE'S NOTHING TO DIAGNOSE.
YOUR BIOPSY RESULTS
ARE NEGATIVE.
THEN IT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
GET DRESSED.
I'M DISCHARGING YOU.
HOUSE ADMITTED ME.
HE OBVIOUSLY THINKS-
HOUSE IS USING YOU
AS AN EXCUSE
TO STICK HIS NOSE
IN MY PERSONAL LIFE.
I'M TIRED ALL THE TIME.
SOME NIGHTS I FALL ASLEEP
AT 10:00
AND WAKE UP AT NOON,
STILL TIRED.
EVERY DOCTOR I SEE
TELLS ME
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG.
AND THAT PROVES WHAT,
EXACTLY?
THAT THEY'RE WRONG,
OR THAT YOU'RE WRONG?
OH, COME ON.
YOU EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE-
SIT BACK.
DEEP BREATHS.
TRY AND RELAX.
GET THE PADDLES.
SHE'S GONNA CRASH.
DAMN.
WE HAD TO USE PADDLES
TO STABILIZE
THE PATIENT'S HEART.
EYE ISSUE, BRAIN ISSUE,
NOW A HEART ISSUE.
SOUNDS LIKE A REAL CASE
TO ME.
yeah, I GET IT.
I WAS WRONG.
CAN WE MOVE ON?
YOU'RE JUST UPSET
BECAUSE THE WHOLE TIME
SHE WAS WITH YOU,
SHE WAS THINKING
OF MY HUGE, THROBBING...
DIAGNOSTIC SKILLS.
DRUGS WOULD EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
THIS MORNING,
YOU REJECTED DRUGS.
THAT'S WHEN I THOUGHT
THAT THIRTEEN WAS RIGHT
AND WAS JUST
JERKING HER AROUND.
CARDIAC ARREST MEANS
SHE COULD BE
A SERIOUS USER.
GREAT.
WHAT?
THAT MEANS THAT SOMETHING
SHE DID AT MY PLACE
SET THIS OFF.
EITHER SHE BROUGHT DRUGS IN,
OR SHE GRABBED SOMETHING
FROM MY MEDICINE CABINET.
AND THAT MEANS MY PLACE
NEEDS TO BE SEARCHED.
NOW, I'D BE HAPPY
TO DO THAT MYSELF,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY THAT WOULD BE
FAR LESS TITILLATING
FOR HOUSE,
SO HE'S ABOUT TO COME UP
WITH SOME CONVOLUTED
MEDICAL REASON
WHY I HAVE TO STAY HERE
WHILE HE GOES THROUGH MY STUFF.
PATIENT'S DAD
HAD BYPASS SURGERY.
MEANS SHE'S A CANDIDATE
FOR ATHEROSCLEROSIS.
SHE NEEDS AN ULTRASOUND.
THAT WAS MUCH LESS CONVOLUTED
THAN WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
I'M NOT GIVING YOU MY KEYS.
IF YOU WANT TO DO THIS,
I'M GOING.
WHO COULD PICK A LOCK?
I'LL GO.
MAKE SURE HE DOESN'T STEAL
ANY UNDERWEAR.
YOU'RE A DISGRACE
TO YOUR STEREOTYPE.
MOVE OVER.
THINK YOU CAN PICK A LOCK
FASTER THAN ME?
NO NEED TO PICK.
NICE.
STEAL FROM YOUR EMPLOYEES.
NEVER.
I HAD MY DICK MAKE KEYS
WHEN I HIRED HIM
TO DICK UP THE TEAM.
ALWAYS IMAGINED SHE'D HAVE
A SEX SWING
IN THE LIVING ROOM.
GIVE ME MY KEY.
DON'T HAVE YOUR KEY.
YOU EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE
THAT YOU HIRED LUCAS
TO INVESTIGATE EVERYONE
EXCEPT FOR ME?
WASTE OF MONEY.
I ALREADY KNOW EVERYTHING
ABOUT YOU.
THIRTEEN HAD HER PURSE.
THAT'S GOTTA BE THE PATIENT'S.
CHECK IT FOR DRUGS.
I CALL SHOTGUN
ON THE BEDROOM.
YOU KNOW THAT I STOLE A CAR
WHEN I WAS A TEENAGER.
YOU KNOW THAT MY MOM
HAS ALZHEIMER'S.
YOU KNOW NOTHING ELSE.
WANT ME TO HAVE YOU
INVESTIGATED?
WHEN DID YOU GET SO NEEDY?
NOT NEEDY.
JUST DON'T BUY IT.
YOU ALWAYS WANT
MORE INFORMATION ABOUT PEOPLE.
LOOK WHERE WE ARE.
PURSE IS CLEAN.
LAST NIGHT WASN'T
THE FIRST TIME
THAT THIRTEEN BROUGHT HOME
SOME STRANGE.
IF YOU FOUND HER DIARY-
NO TOYS.
YOU SLEEP WITH THE SAME PERSON
OVER AND OVER,
THAT'S WHEN YOU NEED
ACCESSORIES.
FIRST TIME IS PLENTY EXCITING
ON ITS OWN.
UNLESS...
YOU THINK AN ASTHMA INHALER
COULD BE USED
AS A SEX TOY?
THERE ARE WAYS OF GETTING
TO KNOW PEOPLE
WITHOUT COMMITTING FELONIES.
PEOPLE INTEREST ME.
CONVERSATIONS DON'T.
BECAUSE CONVERSATIONS
GO BOTH WAYS.
- LIKE THIRTEEN.
BROWN RECLUSE.
FOUND IT AT YOUR APARTMENT.
THEIR VENOM CAN CAUSE
SEIZURES AND HEART PROBLEMS.
UNLESS THE ULTRASOUND
SHOWED ANYTHING-
NO.
WHAT ROOM DID YOU FIND IT IN?
BATHROOM.
NICE BIDET, BY THE WAY.
VERY REFRESHING.
I DON'T HAVE A BIDET.
OH.
SPIDER'S NOT THE ONLY
INTERESTING THING I FOUND.
YEAH, MY INHALER IS FASCINATING.
IT'S GOT ITS OWN EXTENSIVE
ONLINE FOLLOWING.
YOU HAVE ASTHMA?
WHEN I WAS A KID.
IT STARTED ACTING UP AGAIN
WHEN I MOVED INTO MY NEW PLACE.
YOU MOVED?
- WHO CARES?
- HE DOESN'T.
HE'S JUST SURPRISED
HE DIDN'T KNOW.
YOU WITHHOLD THINGS
OTHER PEOPLE
WOULD NEVER BOTHER TO.
THE MOVE,
A LITTLE WHEEZE,
WHATEVER YOU THOUGHT
WAS IN MY POCKET
INSTEAD OF YOUR INHALER.
MAYBE I SHOULD MAKE
A RETURN TRIP TO YOUR PLACE.
SPIDER BITE DOESN'T EXPLAIN
ANYTHING
UNLESS THE PATIENT
WAS ACTUALLY BITTEN BY A SPIDER.
I'LL DO THE EXAM.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
THAT WOULD BE INAPPROPRIATE.
IT'D BE BETTER IF A WOMAN
GROPES HER.
THERE'S NO SEXUAL TENSION
THAT WAY.
I NEED YOU TO STAND UP
AND TAKE OFF YOUR GOWN.
I THINK I WOULD'VE FELT
A SPIDER BITING ME.
NOT NECESSARILY.
YOU REALLY NEED THOSE
AFTER EVERYTHING
WE DID THE OTHER NIGHT?
THE OTHER NIGHT
I WASN'T YOUR DOCTOR.
HOW LONG ARE YOU
GONNA STAY MAD AT ME?
HOW LONG ARE YOU GOING
TO BE HERE?
OH.
OKAY, THEN.
LOOK...
I REALLY HAD NO INTENTION
OF EVER SEEING YOU AGAIN.
SO...
HAVING ME END UP HERE
IS A LITTLE LESS
THAN IDEAL.
I GET IT.
BUT... WE JUST MET.
HOW'D YOU KNOW YOU DIDN'T WANT
TO SEE ME AGAIN?
IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL.
I'M JUST REALLY NOT THAT INTO
REPEAT PERFORMANCES.
I FIGURED I WASN'T
THE FIRST GIRL YOU CRUISED.
WHY IS THAT?
YOU'RE AWFULLY GOOD AT IT.
YOU'D THINK WITH ALL THAT
EXPERIENCE
THAT I'D BE BETTER
THAN A SEVEN.
WE JUST MET.
WE WERE BOTH DRUNK.
NOT LIKE
THERE WASN'T POTENTIAL.
LITTLE MORE PRACTICE
FOR THE BOTH OF US,
I'D SAY WE'RE LOOKING
AT A NINE.
EASY.
BUT THAT WOULD REQUIRE
A REPEAT PERFORMANCE.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO MOVE
YOUR HAND.
I DIDN'T.
MY HAND'S ON YOUR HIP.
YOU DON'T FEEL THAT?
NO.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS IT'S NOT
A SPIDER BITE.
BLOOD TEST CONFIRMS
LOW POTASSIUM LEVELS.
EXPLAINS THE NUMBNESS
IN HER HIP.
IT'S NOT GOOD,
BUT I THINK WE'VE GOT TIME
FOR AT LEAST ONE
OR TWO COMMENTS
ABOUT MY PERSONAL LIFE.
WHICH YOU JUST WASTED
WITH THAT COMMENT
ABOUT MY COMMENTS.
LOW POTASSIUM MEANS
HER HEART PROBLEM
WAS A SYMPTOM
OF A KIDNEY PROBLEM.
WHAT CAUSED THE KIDNEY PROBLEM?
COULD BE I.G.A. NEPHROPATHY.
NOT WITHOUT BLOOD
IN THE URINE.
P.S.A.G.N.?
NOT WITH NORMAL BLOOD PRESSURE.
RENAL TUBULAR ACIDOSIS.
HER KIDNEY'S DON'T FILTER ACID
OUT OF THE BLOOD.
EXCESS ACID
DRIVES DOWN POTASSIUM,
CAUSES KIDNEY CALCIFICATIONS.
IF IT'S RTA,
ALL SHE NEEDS IS SODIUM
BICARBONATE FOR THE ACID
AND SURGERY TO REMOVE
THE CALCIFICATIONS.
CT HER KIDNEYS.
IF YOU FIND CALCIFICATIONS,
WE HAVE OUR DIAGNOSIS.
WHAT'S HE DOING NOW?
HE'S PLAYING
THAT CARJACKING VIDEO GAME.
HE'D GET A LOT FARTHER
IF HE DIDN'T STOP
AT ALL THE RED LIGHTS.
MAYBE HE WAS DOING SOMETHING
HE THINKS I'LL MOCK HIM FOR.
LIKE...
JUST ABOUT ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T THINK IT'S THAT.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S JUST ABOUT ANYTHING?
YOU DON'T THINK
IT'S ABOUT ANYTHING TRIVIAL.
IF YOU WEREN'T WORRIED,
YOU WOULDN'T BE SITTING
IN MY CAR.
MAYBE HE'S SEEING A SHRINK.
THAT DOES NOT LOOK
LIKE A PIZZA DELIVERY.
DOESN'T MATTER IF IT ISN'T.
WILSON DOESN'T BUY HIS PIZZA.
THERE'S EIGHT UNITS
IN THIS BUILDING.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A PERVERT
LIKE ME
LIVING IN
AT LEAST ONE OF THEM.
YES, BECAUSE YOU REPRESENT
ONE OUT OF EVERY EIGHT PEOPLE
LIVING IN THIS COUNTRY.
APPARENTLY HE HAS DEVELOPED
A TASTE FOR PIZZA.
AH, THINGS CHANGE.
CT SHOWS ONE MORE CALCIFICATION
NEAR THE SUPERIOR PYRAMID
ON THE LEFT KIDNEY.
SEE IT.
THAT, UM, THING
YOU WERE HOPING
HOUSE DIDN'T FIND
AT YOUR PLACE.
I, UH, I FOUND IT.
HE DID THE CAG TEST
TWO WEEKS AGO.
A NUMBER THIS HIGH
MEANS YOU HAVE LESS TIME
THAN YOU THOUGHT.
IT'S UNDERSTANDABLE
YOU'D BE UPSET.
DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO SELF-DESTRUCT.
IT'S NOT NOBLE FOR YOU
TO PROTECT ME FROM HOUSE
IF YOU'RE JUST GONNA JUDGE-
THERE ARE THINGS
YOU SHOULD BE DOING.
WORKING OUT, IMPROVING BALANCE
AND COORDINATION.
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE A BLAST.
I'M HAVING FUN.
CRAMMING AS MUCH LIFE
INTO MY LIFE AS I CAN.
YOU'RE DOING DRUGS.
STAYING UP ALL NIGHT,
HAVING SEX WITH STRANGERS.
IT SOUNDS FUN TO ME.
GOOD NIGHT.
CLOSE THE INCISIONS.
SHE WON'T EVEN HAVE
A SCAR.
HER O2 STATS ARE DROPPING.
DID YOU NICK SOMETHING?
PROCEDURE WAS CLEAN.
BP'S STRONG.
WELL, SHE'S NOT BREATHING.
WE NEED TO INTUBATE.
THE BREATHING PROBLEM STARTED
AFTER WE FIXED
HER KIDNEY PROBLEM.
MEANS THE RTA
ISN'T THE UNDERLYING CAUSE.
WHERE'S THIRTEEN?
TRAFFIC'S BAD.
SHE'S PROBABLY JUST-
NOT HERE.
IT'S NOT HER LUNGS.
NO MASSES, NO INFILTRATES.
LUNGS ARE WORKING,
BUT SHE STILL CAN'T BREATHE.
DISTRIBUTION PLANT
CAN'T DISTRIBUTE
IF IT'S NOT GETTING
DELIVERIES.
IF HER LUNGS ARE FINE,
MAYBE THE PROBLEM'S
IN THE SUPPLY LINE.
AIRWAY COLLAPSE.
THAT COULD SIGNAL AUTOIMMUNE
OR SOME KIND OF DYSTROPHY
AS THE UNDERLYING CAUSE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT
IF HER AIRWAY FAILED.
MAKE IT HAPPEN AGAIN.
STICK THIRTEEN'S
CARPET CLEANER ON A TREADMILL.
METHACHOLINE CHALLENGE.
AND SOMEONE FIND THE CARPET.
EXAM GOING ON.
15 MINUTES.
GOOD MORNING,
DR. HADLEY.
JUST SPOKE TO MY BROTHER.
AND BY BROTHER,
YOU MEAN?
I MEAN MY PARENTS'
OTHER SON.
WOW.
SAME DAD.
GOT A CALL LAST WEEK
FROM YOUR P.I.
YOU LIED.
YOU DID HAVE ME INVESTIGATED.
YOU'VE BEEN TAUNTING THE TEAM
WITH WHAT YOU'VE LEARNED,
BUT YOU NEVER CAME AFTER ME.
MEANS YOU COULDN'T FIND
ANYTHING.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
STUPID, SPONTANEOUS,
OR EVEN VAGUELY INTERESTING
SINCE YOU WERE 17.
AND THAT'S JUST SAD.
I FOUND HER IN THE CLINIC
GIVING HERSELF IV FLUIDS.
AT LEAST YOU COULD'VE
LET HER FINISH.
SHE LOOKS TERRIBLE.
SHE HAS A FRESH NIGHTCLUB STAMP
ON HER WRIST.
SHE'S IN NO CONDITION
TO PRACTICE.
UNLESS THIS IS A PRELUDE
TO AN ACTUAL SPANKING,
THERE'S NO REASON
FOR ME TO BE-
I WANT HER TO TAKE
A DRUG TEST.
YOU CAN'T MAKE ME DO THAT.
BUT I CAN SUSPEND YOU
UNTIL YOU DO.
BECAUSE SHE WENT TO A NIGHTCLUB
IN HER FREE TIME?
OR BECAUSE SHE HAD SEX
PATIENT WAS UNDERGOING
ROUTINE SURGERY
FOR RTA.
DIDN'T NEED THIRTEEN HERE
FOR THAT.
AND I DON'T NEED YOU
MAKING MY EMPLOYEES
PUNCH A CLOCK
OR PEE IN A CUP.
LET'S GO.
COME ON.
THANK YOU.
BY THE WAY,
THE SURGERY WAS NOT ROUTINE.
PATIENT STOPPED BREATHING
AND YOU MISSED
A DIFFERENTIAL.
YOU'RE FIRED.
WHAT?
YOU JUST DEFENDED ME.
NO, I JUST PREVENTED YOU
FROM GETTING A DRUG TEST.
PROBABLY SAVED YOUR CAREER.
I'M ALREADY TAKING
RESPONSIBILITY
FOR ONE DOCTOR
WITH A DRUG HABIT.
I DON'T HAVE A DRUG HABIT.
THE SLUTTY PARTY GIRL
IS FUN
TILL SHE PUKES
ON YOUR SHOES.
THEN SHE'S JUST A PAIN
IN THE ASS.
I HAVEN'T SAT ON THIS COUCH
FOR FOUR MONTHS.
IT REMEMBERS MY CHEEKS.
I MISS THIS.
ME TOO.
ME TRYING TO WORK.
YOU INTERRUPTING.
OH, COME ON.
YOUR PATIENTS COULD WAIT
FIVE MINUTES.
GET ME CAUGHT UP.
COME ON,
WHAT DID YOU DO?
TRAVEL?
DID YOU GET A NEW HOBBY?
DID YOU MEET SOMEONE?
ACTUALLY, YES.
I SORT OF STARTED DATING
SOMEONE.
GREAT.
WHAT DOES SHE DO?
IS SHE... AN ACTRESS?
NO.
WHY WOULD YOU THINK THAT?
I JUST FIGURED YOU'D
WANT SOMETHING
A LITTLE MORE...
EXCITING.
SHE'S NOT...
YOU'RE GONNA FIND OUT ANYWAY
BECAUSE YOU'RE GONNA MEET HER.
SHE'S... A PROSTITUTE.
USED TO BE.
SHE MADE SOME MISTAKES.
SINGLE MOM,
HAD SOME DRUG ISSUES.
BUT...
SHE'S SO SMART.
SHE WANTS TO GO TO LAW SCHOOL.
AND... I TOLD HER
I'D HELP HER
WITH TUITION.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU KNOWN HER?
OH, I KNEW YOU'D BE LIKE THIS.
I ASKED A QUESTION.
HOUSE...
YOU ARE A DRUG ADDICT.
YOU GO TO PROSTITUTES.
YOU CAN'T BE JUDGMENTAL.
AND YET.
PLEASE, DON'T DO THIS TO ME.
I WAS HURTING,
AND I WANTED TO FEEL GOOD.
I DIDN'T EXPECT IT
TO GO THIS WAY.
I...
AMBER...
SAID THAT SHE WANTED ME
TO MOVE ON.
THAT SHE WANTED ME TO...
BE HAPPY.
AND...
DEBBIE MAKES ME HAPPY.
IF YOU'RE HAPPY, I'M...
I HEARD.
YEAH.
I'M LOOKING
FOR MY TICKET BACK.
SORRY IF I UPSET YOU.
I DIDN'T WANT TO INVADE
YOUR PRIVACY.
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
CAN YOU GET ME CAUGHT UP?
THINK YOU'RE GONNA FIND
SOMETHING WE DIDN'T?
IT'S GOOD FOR THE PATIENT.
GOOD FOR ME.
FILMS ARE CLEAN.
WE RULED OUT HYPERTENSION.
GUYS HAVE HER ON A TREADMILL
RUNNING
A METHACHOLINE CHALLENGE.
AND I STILL THINK YOU'VE BEEN
ACTING LIKE AN IDIOT.
I KNOW.
DID YOU TALK
ABOUT WHETHER THIS LUNG FIELD
LOOKS A LITTLE DARK?
IT'S PROBABLY JUST
OVER-EXPOSED.
OR HER DIAPHRAGM'S
A LITTLE FLAT.
COULD BE A SIGN
OF HYPERINFLATION.
SUGGESTS A PULMONARY
OBSTRUCTION.
LUNG CYSTS.
THEY WOULDN'T SHOW UP
ON AN X-RAY.
TREADMILL TEST
ISN'T GONNA CLOSE HER AIRWAY.
IT'LL MAKE HER LUNGS
EXPLODE.
HER THROAT'S FINE.
WE MADE HER AIRWAY COLLAPSE,
BUT IT'S NOT COLLAPSED.
YOU RUPTURED A CYST!
HER LUNG COLLAPSED.
BREATH SOUNDS ON BOTH SIDES.
MOVE.
TRACHEA'S DEVIATING
TO THE LEFT.
NICE.
CHEST CT CONFIRMED
MULTIPLE LUNG CYSTS,
ONE OF WHICH BURST
DURING THE TREADMILL TEST.
LUCKILY, THIRTEEN FIGURED OUT
THE PROBLEM AND WAS THERE
TO RE-INFLATE HER LUNG.
LUNG CYSTS PLUS
ALL HER OTHER SYMPTOMS
COULD BE AMYLOIDOSIS,
WHICH WE CAN MANAGE.
OR PULMONARY FIBROSIS WHICH-
THANK YOU.
MY EMPLOYEES CAN TAKE
CARE OF IT FROM HERE.
WE NEED TO BIOPSY THE CYSTS.
YOU FIRED ME
BECAUSE I SCREWED UP.
I JUST PROVED I CAN PULL
MY WEIGHT.
ALL YOU PROVED IS YOU KNOW
HOW TO MAKE AN ENTRANCE.
HOUSE, SHE DESERVES
ANOTHER SHOT.
SHE FOUND THE CYSTS,
SAVED THE PATIENT.
WHO WOULDN'T HAVE NEEDED
SAVING
IF THIRTEEN HAD SHOWN UP
AT THE DIFFERENTIAL
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
GIVE HER
HER JOB BACK, HOUSE.
OR WHAT?
YOU'RE GONNA QUIT?
GO DO THE BIOPSY.
I'M SORRY.
HOW MUCH CLEARER
DO I NEED TO MAKE THIS?
WHAT DOES THAT EVEN MEAN,
"DATING A HOOKER"?
HE'S AN IDIOT
WITH A MESSIAH COMPLEX.
SAVIOR TO ALL WHO NEED SAVING.
THAT'S WHY HIS FIRST WIFE
HAD A WOODEN LEG.
SECOND WIFE WAS CANADIAN.
HE'S THE ONE WHO NEEDS
TO BE SAVED.
FROM YOU OR THE HO?
THE HO'S JUST USING HIM
FOR HIS MONEY.
WAIT.
BAD EXAMPLE.
NORMALLY IN THESE SITUATIONS,
I'D FOLLOW THE GIRL,
FIND OUT SOMETHING EMBARRASSING
ABOUT HER TO SHOW HIM.
BUT SINCE THAT'S
OUR STARTING POSITION...
PROCEED DIRECTLY
TO THE LEG-BREAKING.
I'M NOT BREAKING HER LEGS.
SHE PROBABLY HAS A PIMP.
OR, AT LEAST,
AN OLDER BROTHER.
OR A YOUNGER BROTHER.
OR OVERPROTECTIVE SISTER.
FIND HER, FIND HER FAMILY,
FIND CLIENT NUMBER NINE.
JUST GET ME SOMETHING
I CAN USE
TO FORCE HER TO BACK OFF.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOUR MEETING, MANNIX.
HERE'S THE RESULT
FROM THE LUNG BIOPSY.
WHY NOT MEN?
YOU'RE BISEXUAL.
IF YOU WERE JUST BEING
SELF-DESTRUCTIVE,
YOU'D BE HAVING RANDOM SEX
WITH MEN.
BETTER CHANCE
OF GETTING ASSAULTED,
CATCHING A DISEASE.
IF THIS WERE
JUST ABOUT GETTING LAID,
IT'D BE A LOT EASIER
TO PICK UP MEN.
OR UGLY GIRLS.
THIS WOMAN'S HOT.
WHICH MEANS YOU LIKE
THE CHALLENGE,
THE CONQUEST.
IT'S THE CONTROL
THAT GETS YOU OFF.
AND CONTROLLING WOMEN
IS AS CLOSE AS YOU CAN GET
TO CONTROLLING
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO YOU.
HERE I THOUGHT I WAS JUST
INTO BOOBS.
INSTEAD OF GETTING SWEATY
WITH A STRANGER,
WHY DON'T YOU TRY TAKING IT
TO THE NEXT LEVEL?
PLAY GOD.
TELL A GIRL THAT SHE'S GOT
TEN YEARS TO LIVE.
SHE HAS LAM.
OKAY.
THIS IS NOT A TEST.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING YOUR JOB BACK
IF YOU CAN-
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO GET THIS NEWS,
AND NO ONE
SHOULD HAVE TO GET IT FROM YOU.
HEY.
THE BIOPSY OF YOUR LUNG CYST
SHOWED SMOOTH MUSCLE CELLS.
THAT'S INDICATIVE
OF A DISEASE CALLED LAM.
WHAT DO YOU DO FOR THAT?
SURGERY TO REMOVE
THE CYSTS.
BUT...
THEY'LL COME BACK.
LITTLE BY LITTLE,
THE CYSTS REPLACE
HEALTHY LUNG TISSUE
UNTIL YOUR LUNGS STOP WORKING.
I'M GONNA DIE.
YES.
I'M SO SORRY.
THEY REMOVED ALL THE CYSTS
THEY COULD.
THAT SHOULD HELP YOU
BREATHE BETTER.
HOW LONG UNTIL THE CYSTS
COME BACK?
WE DON'T KNOW EXACTLY.
I'M SORRY.
STOP SAYING YOU'RE SORRY.
I KNOW YOU'RE SCARED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I FEEL.
YOU'RE GONNA BE NUMB
FOR A FEW MORE DAYS.
THEN YOU'LL GO HOME
AND CRY FOR A FEW WEEKS.
AND THEN YOU GET ANGRY.
START TELLING YOURSELF
NOTHING MATTERS ANYMORE.
YOU START DOING
STUPID THINGS.
MAYBE YOU GO OUT TO BARS
AND PICK UP A BUNCH
OF WOMEN.
YOU'RE...
HOW LONG DO YOU HAVE?
MAYBE A LITTLE MORE
THAN YOU.
MAYBE A LITTLE LESS.
I'LL RACE YOU.
I WAS THINKING
MAYBE I'D COME BACK LATER.
SOUNDS GOOD.
OH, GOD.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ALL HER BLOOD COUNTS ARE DOWN.
IT'S A NEW SYMPTOM.
APLASTIC ANEMIA.
DOES THE WORD "FIRED"
HAVE SOME WHOLE
OTHER DEFINITION
THAT I'M NOT AWARE OF?
I DON'T WORK FOR YOU.
FINE.
DON'T PAY ME.
JUST LET ME FINISH OUT
THIS CASE.
SO YOU LIKE HER
NOW THAT SHE'S DYING.
WHAT HAPPENS
IF SHE STOPS DYING?
THERE'S NO DANGER
OF THAT RIGHT NOW.
IF WE DON'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER,
SHE'S GOT DAYS,
NOT YEARS.
APLASTIC ANEMIA TAKES LAM
OFF THE TABLE.
UNFORTUNATELY, NONE OF OUR
OTHER CHOICES ARE ANY BETTER.
PNH WITH SOME SORT
OF RESPIRATORY INFECTION.
BEST CASE GIVES HER 12 YEARS.
OR FAST-MOVING LANGERHANS.
A FEW MONTHS.
OR MASTOCYTOSIS,
WHICH CAN CAUSE SYSTEMIC SHOCK
AND KILL HER IN DAYS.
GO.
TEST FOR EVERYTHING.
NOT YOU.
YOU'RE JUST A VISITOR.
HOW'S YOUR PATIENT?
SHE DOESN'T HAVE LANGERHANS.
THAT'S GOOD.
ACTUALLY, A CANCER DIAGNOSIS
WOULD BE GOOD NEWS
RIGHT NOW.
DO YOU THINK...
I'M BORING?
YES.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT
JUST TO SCREW WITH ME.
YEAH.
WHY WOULD YOU EXPECT
ANYTHING ELSE?
I EXPECT HOUSE TO PULL
MY STRINGS.
I EXPECT CAMERON
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
I EXPECT THE NEW TEAM
TO KISS MY ASS.
AND I EXPECT YOU TO BE HONEST,
'CAUSE YOU DON'T GIVE
A CRAP.
YES, YOU'RE BORING.
THAT SPEECH WAS BORING.
THANKS SO MUCH.
YOU DON'T LET OTHER PEOPLE'S
PROBLEMS AFFECT YOU.
YOU DON'T LET YOUR OWN
AND IT'S THE SCREW-UPS
THAT MAKE US INTERESTING.
YOU'RE NEVER OUT OF CONTROL.
WHICH IS GOOD, AND...
BORING.
NEVER LOSING CONTROL
ALSO MEANS
YOU'RE NEVER PUTTING YOURSELF
OUT THERE.
NEVER PUSHING YOUR LIMITS.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
YOU DO HAVE A TATTOO, SO...
MAYBE I'M WRONG.
* HALLELUJAH STOP AND STARE *
* WHEN WILL JESUS FIND US HERE *
* COULD WE *
* SURVIVE *
* HOW CAN YOU PRETEND TO KNOW *
* WHO YOU ARE *
* OR WHERE YOU WILL GO *
* WHEN YOU *
* JUST GET BY *
* AND DREAM *
* DREAMING ALL THE TIME *
* AWAY *
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
* AND DREAM *
* DREAMING ALL YOUR TIME *
* AWAY
SHE NEEDS
A BONE MARROW TRANSPLANT.
TEST RESULTS ARE BACK?
WHAT'S SHE POSITIVE FOR?
NOTHING.
BUT WE'VE GOT A DONOR MATCH.
JUMPING TO A TRANSPLANT
WHEN WE DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE-
I KNOW SHE HAS
A BLOOD DISORDER.
COULD BE PNH.
SHE NEEDS
A BONE MARROW TRANSPLANT.
OR LEUKEMIA.
SHE NEEDS
A BONE MARROW TRANSPLANT.
OR THALASSEMIA.
- SHE NEEDS A BONE MARROW-
- YEAH, I GET IT.
BUT SHE'LL NEVER SURVIVE
TOTAL BODY IRRADIATION.
SO WE DON'T RADIATE HER.
HER MARROW'S NEARLY WIPED OUT
ALREADY.
COUNTS ALMOST ZERO.
"ALMOST" BEING THE KEY WORD.
THE NEW MARROW WOULD ATTACK
THE OLD MARROW.
SHE'LL DIE
FROM GRAFT-VERSUS-HOST.
YOU GOT A BETTER IDEA?
SHE TRUSTS YOU.
GO GET HER CONSENT.
SOMETIMES I FIND OUT THINGS
YOU'D RATHER NOT KNOW.
THIS WAS IN HIS TRASH.
HE'S USING.
YOU'RE BACK.
GENIUS.
DAMN.
I KNEW THE FAKE WORKS
WAS TOO MUCH.
WELL, YOU HAD NO CHOICE.
WHERE WERE YOU GONNA GO
AFTER FAKE HOOKER GIRLFRIEND?
HOW DID YOU KNOW
HE WAS OUTSIDE?
CANE PRINTS.
I'M ACTUALLY
KIND OF INSULTED.
NO WAY I'M A DRUG ADDICT,
BUT YOU COMPLETELY BUY
THAT I FELL IN LOVE
WITH A PROSTITUTE?
YOU PLAYED TO YOUR STRENGTHS.
BY WHICH I MEAN YOU PLAYED
TO YOUR WEAKNESSES.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU INVOKED YOUR DEAD
GIRLFRIEND'S NAME TO SELL ME.
YOU'RE MY HERO.
BEST $30 I EVER SPENT.
IT'S 30?
DID YOU KEEP HER NUMBER?
UNFORTUNATELY, I KILLED HER
AND BURIED HER IN THE BASEMENT.
SHAME.
HUNGRY?
YEAH.
SO, SERIOUSLY.
WHERE WERE YOU
THE OTHER MORNING?
UGH, DON'T MAKE ME
DO THIS AGAIN.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOU.
THEN TELL ME.
WE'RE GOING BOWLING ON MONDAY.
I'M COMING OVER
TO PLAY POKER THIS WEEKEND.
NOTHING'S CHANGED.
YOU HAVE TO TRUST THAT.
OKAY.
YOU'RE GONNA KEEP FOLLOWING ME,
AREN'T YOU?
IT'S WHAT WE DO.
BE OUTSIDE MY APARTMENT
AT 8:00 TONIGHT.
SHE SAID YES
TO THE TRANSPLANT.
GOOD.
YOU'RE IN A DOWNWARD SPIRAL
OF DESTRUCTION.
I CAN STOP.
YOU'RE GONNA KEEP SPIRALING.
KEEP SCREWING AROUND.
KEEP SLASHING AWAY
AT EVERY PERSON
WHO TRIES TO HELP UNTIL NO ONE
TRIES TO HELP ANYMORE.
TILL YOU HIT BOTTOM.
TILL YOU'RE DEAD.
UNTIL THEN...
I CAN USE YOU.
YOU'RE HIRING ME BACK?
YOU DID GOOD WORK.
I DID GOOD WORK YESTERDAY,
AND I WAS STILL FIRED.
WHAT CHANGED?
YOU WANTED ME TO SPEND TIME
WITH HER.
SEE IF I COULD STILL MAKE
A CONNECTION.
YOU CONNECTED WITH A DIAGNOSIS,
NOT WITH HER.
YOU'RE TRYING TO SAVE ME,
TRYING TO CONTROL ME.
YOU'RE DOING EXACTLY
- WHAT YOU THINK-
- CRACKS.
YOU'RE LIPS ARE CRACKED.
YOU BEEN USING
YOUR INHALER LATELY?
ALLERGIES.
DON'T DEFLECT.
YOU ALWAYS DEFLECT.
DID SHE CRY?
WHEN YOU TOLD HER
THAT SHE WAS GONNA DIE,
DID SHE CRY?
SHE... GOT UPSET. SHE-
WERE THERE TEARS?
NO.
CHOPPING AN ONION
RELEASES A MIST
OF SYN-PROPANETHIAL-S-OXIDE,
A CHEMICAL IRRITANT
WHICH CAUSES PEOPLE
TO HAVE A VERY PREDICTABLE
REACTION.
SHE HAS NO TEARS.
IT WAS EITHER THIS
OR PUT ON BRIAN'S SONG.
I DIDN'T HAVE TIME
TO STOP BY WILSON'S.
SHE HAS SJOGREN'S.
IT ATTACKS THE GLANDS
THAT PRODUCE TEARS
AND SALIVA.
ALSO, BY THE WAY,
CAUSES LUNG CYSTS AND RTA.
IT DOESN'T CAUSE BLEEDING.
IT'S LIKE YOU AND MEN.
JUST 'CAUSE YOU USUALLY DON'T,
DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN'T.
AND IT DOESN'T CAUSE
CRACKED LIPS
IN OTHER PEOPLE.
LACK OF SPIT MAKES HER MOUTH
A BREEDING GROUND
FOR A FUNGUS LIKE CANDIDA.
YOUR ASTHMA INHALER
DID THE SAME FOR YOU.
WIPED OUT YOUR MOUTH'S
IMMUNE SYSTEM.
SO SHE'S GOT WHAT I'VE GOT.
JUST THE OPPORTUNISTIC
INFECTION,
NOT THE UNDERLYING CONDITION.
ANOTHER LIFE SAVED
BY GIRL-ON-GIRL ACTION.
I'M GONNA BE OKAY?
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
METHYLPREDNISOLONE
TO GET THE SJOGREN'S
UNDER CONTROL.
AND SOME ARTIFICIAL TEARS
TO MAXIMIZE THE VISUAL IMPACT
OF THIS MOMENT.
SPENCER'S GONNA BE FINE.
AND I HEAR YOU GOT
YOUR JOB BACK.
I'M GONNA KEEP STANDING HERE
UNTIL YOU SAY SOMETHING.
I FEEL ALONE.
AND SHE HASN'T GONE ANYWHERE.
SHE GETS TO LIVE.
I'M GONNA GO HOME.
I'M TIRED.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH, MY GOD!
YOU GUYS SHOP HERE TOO?
BEST NIPPLES IN PRINCETON.
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
BECAUSE HE ATE THE DONUT.
I'M SO SORRY.
HE MUST'VE FOLLOWED ME.
I'M SURE.
WELL, YOU'RE CLEARLY
NOT PREGNANT,
SO EITHER YOU'RE BUYING THIS
AS A GIFT,
OR THIS IS SOME KIND OF WEIRD
"IF YOU BUILD IT,
THEY WILL COME" MOMENT.
I'M ADOPTING A BABY.
SHE ASKED ME TO BE
A CHARACTER REFERENCE.
THAT'S WHERE I WAS
THE OTHER MORNING.
I'M SORRY.
I COULDN'T BETRAY
HER CONFIDENCE.
I DIDN'T WANT ANYONE ELSE
TO KNOW
IN CASE I DIDN'T GET
APPROVED.
TODAY, I DID.
* IT'S A DARK ROAD *
* AND A DARK WAY THAT LEADS *
* TO MY HOUSE *
* AND THE WORD SAYS *
* YOU'RE NEVER GONNA FIND ME
THERE *
* OH NO *
ARE YOU GONNA CONGRATULATE ME?
IF YOU'RE HAPPY, I'M...
* IT DIDN'T GET THERE *
* BY ITSELF *
* THERE'S A FEELING,
BUT YOU'RE NOT FEELING IT *
* AT ALL *
* THERE'S A MEANING *
* BUT YOU'RE NOT LISTENING
ANYMORE...
??????
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
????