Am I gonna have
to give a speech?
You're the publisher.
Can't you do it?
- I can warm them up.
But you are
gonna have
to get over this fear
of public speaking
before the book tour.
Everybody.
Can I have your attention?
Thank you.
Tim has a few words
to say.
There you go, Tim.
They're warmed up.
Well, what do you say
at a time like this?
Seriously,
what do you say?
You could thank people
for coming.
Thank you, Nick.
Actually,
I'm always thanking Nick,
A man not only famous
for his ruthless editor's pen,
but his patient hand-holding
of crazy authors.
You'd think that
after three novels,
I'd start to develop
a little confidence, but...
for a book like this, we are
happy to supply the confidence.
Best-seller.
Well,
that's not gonna happen.
What?
Come on.
Short stories don't make money.
Short stories weren't making
money back in 1908.
You'd have
to be mathematically illiterate
to think they'd do as well
as a novel.
Okay, Nick, let's step away
from the champagne
before somebody gets hurt.
You slaved over this book
right next to me.
Why would Northrop even publish?
Have you failed to notice
you're our star author?
Obviously, Elaine wouldn't want
to offend you.
Uh, Honey.
I-I'm sorry.
I don't--I don't know
why I said that.
He's joking.
Nick knows as well
as anyone
what you have done
is art.
So is folding paper
into animal shapes,
but you don't expect
to make a living off it.
What the hell is wrong
with you?
You really think someone
who goes
through ten assistants a year
and doesn't return
her own children's phone calls
would give a damn
about the state
of the American short story?
Please, be quiet.
I think
something's wrong.
That title was a mistake too.
People are gonna compare you
to Salinger,
and, boy, are you gonna come up
short on that one.
Honey!
Call 911.
Help! We need help!
Cameron brought this up
from the E.R.
Doesn't look
like a friendship bracelet.
The most famous case study
in medical history.
You're telling me
this patient got
a railroad spike drilled
through his frontal lobe?
No. No trauma, but he does
have frontal lobe disinhibition.
Just like Gage.
Gage was a different person
after the spike.
Argumentative.
Impulsive.
Whereas our guy became
a different person
after chardonnay.
He was sober
when they brought him in.
There's also the nosebleed,
the collapse.
MRI show anything?
Nothing.
- Good.
What fun would that be?
So the tumor's not
in the cool neighborhood.
It's cool neighborhood
adjacent.
A well-placed tumor
in the nasal cavity
eroding into the brain
could do the damage.
Go stick a scope
up Phineas's nose.
See what you find.
Daddy, I'm always gonna win
if you keep telling me
what your cards are.
Well, then suppose
I tell you...
while I tickle you.
Mr. Greenwald, I'm Dr. Taub.
Is is Dr. Kutner.
We're here for another test.
Sorry about that.
You don't look sorry.
Um, no offense.
Although you do look
kind of cheerful.
It's a little creepy.
Should I want a doctor who's
excited about how sick I am?
I'm not--
We're going to put this
up your nose,
scan for any problems.
I can assure you that we are
completely unexcited about that.
Excuse me, sweetie.
She has an auditory
processing disability.
Marika-beleeka, you have
to get off the bed.
This might be
slightly uncomfortable.
Honey, do you mind
if I step out?
I have to make sure
the final arrangements
are in place
for the breast cancer walk.
Yeah, you do that.
I'll pretend to be macho
while a guy stuffs
three feet of plastic
up my nose.
It's too bad
it's not your nose.
Lots more room to maneuver.
I guess the walk
can wait ten minutes.
Or in a sensible world,
even longer.
Just how does tying up traffic
for six hours
stop breast cancer?
You know how it works.
People donate--
Why not spend six hours
building houses
for Habitat for Humanity?
Or is it wrong to help
two groups of people at once?
I bet there are those who have
breast cancer and no home.
It's my job, Nick.
You walked yourself last year.
- To be supportive.
And because I knew you wouldn't
have sex with me if I didn't.
I'm gonna make my call.
Make this go away.
God, that honker really is huge,
isn't it?
Wednesday night.
Low-Down-Blue-Meanie
versus the Incinerator.
I can't.
Let me rephrase.
Low-Down-Blue-Meanie--
I understand
monster truck code.
Do you understand "can't"?
not when it follows
"Low-Down-Blue-Meanie."
Is the world coming to an end
Tuesday night?
Otherwise, Wednesday--
All right,
it's not "can't."
It's "don't want to."
The fact is I just don like
monster trucks.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
You've always liked
monster trucks.
No, you've always
liked them.
I've tolerated them.
Seriously, I can only watch
so many hyped-up dune buggies
crush so many motor homes
without feeling the urge
to go see La Boheme.
And I hate opera too.
What are you hiding?
I'm not hiding it.
I'm saying it loud and proud.
Death to monster trucks.
No nasal cancer.
And no marriage either
if our patient keeps saying
everything that comes
into his head without regard
for the consequences.
You always led me to believe
you were one of a kind.
Luckily, jerkiness is
a temporary condition
for this guy.
No, it's not.
We may be able to fix
his impulse to say
his thoughts out loud,
but he always gonna be
the guy who thinks them.
But he's also gonna be
the guy who doesn't say them.
If he spent his whole life
constructing
this nice guy persona,
isn't that as much who
he really is as anything else?
You would argue that.
You're all persona.
I agree with Wilson.
This guy's a Harry Potter.
The sorting hat was going
to put Harry in Slytherin
based on his nature.
He refused,
so he ended up in Gryffindor.
Through choice.
There's damage
somewhere in his brain.
Find it.
Are you sure
you understand?
No, I'm lying.
Except I can't.
You ask me questions.
While I talk,
you look
at my brain activity to see
where it's screwed up.
Then you're gonna cut the
screwed up part out to test it.
It's depressing,
but it's not rocket science.
I think he understands.
I don't mean
to be abrasive.
Especially since you're such
a pleasure to image naked.
I'm, sorry.
- It's okay.
Thank you
for understanding.
I'd do you, though.
Really, my apologies.
This stuff just comes out.
It's okay.
- House paged.
Whoa, I would do her
in a minute
with fudge
and a cherry on top.
Would someone please explain
to this woman?
There's only so many apologies--
He has frontal lobe
disinhibition.
I've already embarrassed
myself with one doctor,
whom I am at this moment
imagining with you
in a king-sized bed
with a mirror on the ceiling.
But if I couldn't have
both of you together,
you definitely would be
my first choice.
Where's House?
It's like trying not
to think of an elephant.
Not that you're an elephant.
Your breasts, in fact,
are all Homo Sapiens--
House isn't here.
Oh, he wouldn't have paged me
if he couldn't
watch and enjoy the--
Your tush is like the pistons
in a Ferrari.
You're welcome.
That was for my benefit
You're 40 years old...
- 38.
The administrator
of a hospital...
Dean of Medicine.
People don't get personal
with you.
Except for me,
and you dismiss me as a jerk
who's jerking you around.
But that guy can only tell
the truth.
And he prefers your body to that
of a smokin' young hottie.
So that was your way
of saying I look good today.
You didn't get
the slightest kick out of that?
Don't be ridiculous,
House.
I hope you know
your pistons are second to none.
I'm okay.
I'm not jealous
of Cuddy's pistons.
Starting baseline activation.
You sure?
You looked upset.
What he was saying
was obnoxious.
You've never been called
attractive?
He didn't call me attractive.
He cast me
in his mental porno.
That's what attractive means.
It means "I'm attracted
to you, sexually."
Attracted can also mean "I'm
attracted to the whole package.
To who you are."
Slight elevation
at transaxial 60.
It could.
It never does.
It's what women choose to hear,
not what men say.
Actually,
it's exactly what men say
IF they have any brains.
All right, we have enough
for a baseline.
What can we ask him
that's indiscreet,
but that he won't hate us
for knowing?
Nick, do you vote
the same way as your wife?
God, no.
Good. He's spiking at 30.
She believes I voted
for Hillary Clinton
in the primary and Obama
in the general.
You're thinking I'm secretly
a Republican, right?
Wrong.
I secretly don't vote.
Ever.
Wait, you're 46,
and you've never voted?
Your voice is
no longer attractive to me
with that note
of disapproval.
Although I'm sure
that will pass.
Look at that.
There's a spot in the Cingulate
Gyrus that's not lighting up.
One vote makes a difference?
Not mathematically true.
Okay, Nick.
We've got what we need.
We can't biopsy that.
It's too close to the brainstem.
Could be neurosarcoidosis.
At least it's treatable.
So we give him steroids,
and if we're right,
we should start seeing
his symptoms improve
within half a day.
What are you looking at?
I find your strong attachment
to a working democracy
to be extremely sexy.
Ooh, you smooth talker.
Do you think
my nose is too big?
Relax, he also implied my
bedside manner was a little off.
You don't agree with that,
right?
No.
No one's ever mentioned
your nose before?
You're a plastic surgeon.
They tell me
it suits my face.
It does.
- Maybe.
Maybe that's just
the social contract.
I tell you
you're a people person.
How can you know the truth?
You could ask
for the truth.
What do you think
of my nose?
Please tell me the truth.
- It's fine. It's a nose.
Just proving a point.
Anyone sitting here?
Just my persona.
You know, it's amazing the
way people cling onto insults.
Or what they think
are insults.
So that wasn't an insult?
I'm not suggesting
that, like our patient,
beneath a candy shell
of compulsive nicene.
I'm not always nice.
I'm not nice to you.
Because you know
nice bores me.
Hence, still nice.
No, I'm suggesting
that you have no core.
You're what whoever you're with
needs you to be.
Okay, I guess
that could be insulting.
The interesting question
is why.
Why do you think
the world will end
in chaos and destruction
if you're not there to save it?
Because when my parents
put me in the rocket
and sent me here, they said,
"James, you will grow
to manhood
under yellow sun--"
And why'd you lie
about monster trucks?
I didn't.
I checked
your appointment book.
You got tomorrow night
marked off,
but you didn't put down
what you were doing.
So you thought
someone might look at the book--
I'm playing racquetball
tomorrow night with Taub.
Why would you hide that?
Because the world revolves
around you.
I devote time
to anyone else,
you'd end up stalking me
and harassing them.
You say that
as though it wouldn't be fun.
And maybe I didn't want
to rub your nose
in the fact that we'd be doing
something you can no longer do.
Because I'm nice.
I thought you said the
steroids were gonna help him.
What--is it his heart?
EKG says heart's fine.
It's gotta be the kidneys.
I need to get him
on dialysis.
Oh.
He's on dialysis,
and he's stable.
We know
it's not systemic sclerosis.
Hey, Cyrano de Berkowitz.
Let it go.
Chronic lymphocytic
leukemia could explain
brain and kidney problems.
The CBC showed
normal white blood cells.
So how long have you been
playing racquetball with Wilson?
Four, five times.
Could be diabetes.
Or a congenital
metabolic disorder.
Congenital disorders
generally don't wait
till you're 46 to manifest.
So he's a late bloomer.
His daughter has
a neurological condition.
First of all,
Wilson played tennis
on his college team,
and you are a Jew.
You're not athletic.
Run to the end of the hall
and back. I'll time you.
Sandy Koufax is Jewish.
Greatest left-handed pitcher
of all time.
Sandy Koufax is all you Jews
go on about.
Sandy Koufax and the holocaust.
Gets old.
There are dozens
of congenital conditions
that fit our parameters.
We can't spend time
gene testing
for all of 'em, especially
when we're only guessing
it's congenital.
Is a z-shot
offensive or defensive?
It's both.
You suspected
that was a trick question.
But I could have said
neither.
Diabetes makes more sense.
We can narrow
the testing down
to 40 likely candidates.
Test for peripheral
nerve damage.
He's got brain damage.
He's likely to have
peripheral nerve damage
no matter what the cause.
Yes, that's why we should not
test him for it.
Test the daughter.
Kutner runs the nerve test.
Taub, you might be right
about the diabetes.
Take supper away
from our patient
and run
a glucose tolerance test.
Oh, and the nurses have been
working so hard.
You can do the blood draws
yourself.
They have to be done
every couple hours.
You're punishing me
because you're jealous.
That would be petty.
I'm punishing you
because now you've joined my
best friend in lying to me.
Let me know when you're ready
to confess everything.
These can become either hot
or cold.
As soon as it starts
to feel uncomfortable,
I want you to tell me.
But you don't think
there's something wrong
with me.
No, baby, they're testing you
to help Daddy.
Yes, what you're doing
is very important.
It's like the better you do,
the better we know your dad is.
I'll start with heat.
I know it's not his fault.
I know what he says
is involuntary,
but it doesn't help.
Inside,
he's still the same man.
That's the problem.
Apparently he's been thinking
this stuff all along.
Whoever that "same man" is,
it's not the person
I thought I was married to.
You okay?
She should be feeling
something by now.
What does that mean?
Is she sick too?
Marika!
Honey!
You're burned.
Why didn't you tell me
it started to hurt?
I wanted to help Daddy.
You said the better I do,
the better Daddy has to be.
Sorry.
I'm starving.
Only way we can do
the test.
Good thing it's you
and not Dr. Hadley.
Could you keep her
away from me?
I have a rich imaginative life.
I'd rather not share it.
We all have thoughts.
We all have sexual thoughts.
We have ignoble thoughts.
I just don't want those
to be who I am to people,
especially not to my wife.
I understand.
I don't think it would be fair
to define me
by my passing thoughts.
My real choices
are my actions.
And I've never done anything
to hurt her.
I've never cheated.
You're kidding me.
You've cheated?
What? No.
Why would you say that?
Because you look guilty
as hell.
Are you serious?
Of course you're serious.
Yes, everyone knows.
God, they must think
you're a creep.
They might not know.
They might be idiots.
I just say these things.
Why'd you page me here?
I need you to update me
on the patient's condition.
Seems to be dead.
Why'd you page me here?
I need you to update me
on the patient's condition
while hitting this
against the wall.
This is the only place
we can do both.
I finished
the last blood draw.
I expect the people
who work for me
to rise
to a challenge.
Unless they don't expect
to work for me.
Last blood draw
was at 6:00 A.M.
Sugar levels never rose
above 120 all night.
So the glucose was normal.
Means you were wrong
about diabetes.
I still think
it's the endocrine system.
Maybe I just got
the wrong gland.
So you're going for thyroid
instead of pancreas?
Makes sense.
Ow.
Fine.
I'm not playing racquetball
with Wilson.
I was never playing racquetball
I have never played racquetball
with Wilson.
I thought it would be helpful
if a department head owed me
a favor.
But it's not worth this.
Not bad.
You put on a good show.
You studied up.
Wilson actually booked
a court.
If you were really
a racquetball player,
you'd know that you were holding
a squash racket.
Tell Kutner to do
a thyroid re-uptake scan,
Then go grab a nap
in one of the on-call rooms.
We're taking you to do
a thyroid re-uptake scan.
We think your--
- I'm not going anywhere
until you explain
why my daughter has
a bandage on her hand.
You just said you wanted
to run some test.
I'd known it would involve pain,
I'd have said, "hell, no."
It's a mild burn.
Since Marika has a neurological
disability like you,
we needed to make sure--
- She has no disability.
Nick, you know
about her problem
with auditory processing.
"Auditory processing"?
That's code for
"I can't stand thinking
my daughter's not perfect."
The therapist said
Marika's test scores--
were indeterminate.
She doesn't have a disability.
She daydreams.
She gets
below-average marks in school
because she's below average.
Nick!
- Do you have any idea
what the word average means?
Somebody has
to be under it.
Nick, shut up.
Oh, Honey...
I'm not saying
you're stupid.
Your mother's not the sharpest
crayon in the box,
and she does great.
See, this is why I told
your mother to keep you at home.
Didn't want you here.
Marika!
Marika, wait!
Get her...
You're burning up.
And your lungs are full
of fluid. We need to get it out.
I need 200 milligrams
of furosemide
and two milligrams of morphine,
stat.
His temperature is 103.
Infection.
The steroids must have forced
it into the open.
What kind of infection?
- It could be anything.
Staph Aureus,
tuberculosis, strongyloides...
go back to Phineas,
get a history.
We've got a history. He
hasn't been out of the country.
Get a detailed history.
No one at home is sick.
No one at work is sick.
There's no sign
of ticks or mosquitoes.
Get a more detailed history.
Ask him again.
And again
until he remembers something.
Not you.
Kutner can do it.
You're gonna be busy
with something else.
I'm here to invite you
to lunch.
Uh, why?
I've been made.
House sent me back to you
as a double agent.
Anything wrong?
Eyes are a little red.
There's a shocker.
I haven't had
a good night's sleep
since this thing started.
You should get some rest
yourself.
That's a good idea.
This is going to take
some time.
It'll be pretty exhaustive.
Are you afraid of what
you might say while I'm here?
Yes.
Are you telling me
there's something worse
than what I've already heard?
No, I-I don't know
what I'm gonna say.
I don't know
how I'm gonna hurt you next.
I think we should be
around each other
as little as possible
right now.
This is pathetic.
I know.
Tell Marika I love her very much.
She understands that.
I don't think he does.
You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
Yeah.
Guy leads a boring life.
They stay home a lot.
No travel,
no exotic pets,
no nearby standing water.
Can we get to that part?
His wife rescues dogs.
Among others, a big Rottweiler
who's taken over the house.
Our patient hates it.
Was the wife there
to hear is?
No.
- Too bad. Keep going.
The dog marks his territory
all over the living room.
I asked what the odds were
that he would have put down
food or drink
where the dog could reach.
He said he put a glass
of juice on the floor
while he was fixing
the television.
The dog was fixing
the television?
Yes.
- The patient's eyes red?
Yeah.
I'm thinking Weil's.
Bacterial.
He lucked out.
Start him on doxycycline.
If he improves,
we'll know we were right.
I told Wilson you sent me
to get information.
And now you're telling me.
What does that make you,
a quadruple agent?
He let me print out
his e-mails.
Wow. Excellent.
Information he wants us
to have.
Did he let you print out
his deleted e-mails?
No.
- Then go back there--
As long
as I was sitting there,
I thought I'd print 'em
anyway.
Top one's the one
you're looking for.
Writing to confirm Wednesday
at 7:00 P.M."
It's outgoing
to jgonzalez@nymcy.net.
There's a Joan Gonzalez
in oncology.
It's a consult.
Secret consult,
7:00 P.M.?
Oh, Joan is perky.
You're wrong. There was
a patient file attached.
Where?
It was password-protected.
No.
Wilson doesn't password-protect
his patient files.
I'm the only one he'd expect
ever to look there,
and he knows there's only one
patient I'd want to check on.
You think Wilson's sick?
If Wilson had cancer,
there'd be no reason
for him to drive three hours
to Manhattan.
He could pull strings here
and get the best treatment.
Six articles by Gonzalez.
"Managing suicidal thoughts
in oncology patients,"
"Suicidal ideation
in children with leukemia."
I don't want to ask this,
but have you ever had reason
to think he might
be depressed?
No.
Get out of here.
Your fever's down
and your lungs are clearing.
How long before
this brain thing goes away?
The infection's gone,
but the damage
the infection did...
you'll have to live with.
You're telling me
you can't fix this?
There's gotta be a way.
We'd need to remove
the damaged area
in our Cingulate Gyrus,
but it's too close to the
brainstem to risk surgery.
You can't risk it.
But I could shop around,
and maybe some better doctors
at a better hospital--
The brain stem controls
the body's involuntary systems.
The slightest mistake
could kill you.
Even if you survive,
you may never be able
to breathe on your own again.
You may never--
- I get it.
I know this seems like a lot
to deal with right now.
But people have adapted
to living
with all kinds
of neurological deficits.
Hey, at least we can promise
you it won't get any worse.
Get the hell
out of my room.
Your assistant said that
you were out of the hospital,
taking a walk.
Is there an emergency?
I don't know.
Is there?
You never take a walk
unless you've got something
you need to think about.
Maybe you just don't have
a good statistical sampling
of my walks.
The other thing you do
when you need to think
apparently, this is something
you can only discuss
with Gonzalez
at New York Mercy.
Taub. Another graduate of the
House school of being a dick.
Private Dick.
Look, I'd love to stay
for the full inquisition,
but I need
some hot coffee.
Of course you need
hot coffee.
It's 45 degrees outside,
and you left your coat upstairs.
Why?
You're going to tell me
why I forgot my coat?
Once you get outside, the
cold would have reminded you.
You could have come back,
but you didn't.
You chose to be uncomfortable.
Why would someone choose that?
Because they hate themselves?
Has it ever occurred to you
that when don't share
something, it might not
be meant as a challenge?
It might just mean
that I'd like there to be
one molecule of my life
that goes unexamined
by Gregory House.
Nick Greenwald.
I hear you're the guy
in charge.
I'm the patient
with the disinhibition.
If you're here to say thanks,
you're welcome. Now go away.
Oh, I'm not thankful.
I'm pissed.
Oh, all the more reason
to go away.
They're talking
about sending me home.
To what?
A life where I'll continually
drive away
anyone who might
for a second care about me?
Those are the breaks.
You could operate.
You could die.
So I'm either better
or dead?
I'm okay with that.
I-I've always been
kind of a...
an impatient guy.
But I've worked hard
to keep my mouth shut.
I've made my wife happy.
I've made my little girl happy.
I want that back.
Otherwise, it's no life.
I want you to remove a
small problem.
I'm not a neurosurgeon.
But your boss is.
You could assist.
I'm sure you'd like
to add to your resume.
It's too near the brain stem.
Nobody's gonna touch it.
- Your boss would.
He's an egomaniac.
I know 'cause I keep seeing him
at the club.
He just needs
a little push.
I'm sure by now you've kissed
his ass sufficiently.
Would you like me
to phrase it
as "you're politically gifted"?
I can do that.
You want me to help you?
Tell me why.
- Why what?
Why you care.
The puzzle's solved.
The guy's alive.
And the odds of coming
out of this surgery
with that same status
aren't that great.
my patient has
a quality of life issue.
He says awful things.
Hardly a medical condition.
When he leaves here, he's...
he's gonna alienate
the people he works with.
And if he ever finds
a friend
who's willing to put up
with his crap,
he'll be lucky.
Until he drives
them away too.
I'll see what I can do.
You've apparently got
this whole coat thing backwards.
I may have overreacted.
You definitely overreacted.
I knew you'd meet me
halfway.
It made me think.
You only snap on one subject:
Losing people.
So I went back
to the intel.
It's true there's only one
doctor named Gonzalez
At New York Mercy,
But there's a Javier Gonzalez
Who's a nurse
in the psych ward.
And who could you lose
who'd end up there?
Maybe the reason
I don't always open up to you
is because it's redundant.
Daniel Wilson.
Once you got a name,
it's amazing how much stuff
you can learn on the phone.
I mean, if you're a doctor
and you lie freely.
They found your brother sleeping
in the lobby
of an office building
in Manhattan.
Got aggressive
when they asked him to leave,
and the cops took him
to the Mercy psych ward.
There have been new
anti-psychotics developed
since he ran away.
He's been on them
for a couple of days.
And by tonight,
he should be in shape
to talk to me.
But you're not sure
if he wants to.
I'll be in New York
in a few hours.
I guess I'll find out.
Why wouldn't you
tell me this?
House, you and I...
we don't have
the normal social contract.
I don't expect you
to tell me the lies--
I am fully capable
of lying to you.
I've lied plenty of times.
I mean, collaborative lies.
Giving someone a hand
who maybe needs
to deceive themselves
just a little.
For two days I've been thinking
about how Danny's gonna react
when he sees me.
If I said that to anybody else,
they'd say, "don't worry.
it'll all be all right."
You wouldn't.
Because it might all go
horribly wrong.
Yeah.
Yeah, it might.
In which case,
you might want some company.
Your heart's beating.
First hurdle past.
Now we need know
if you can breathe for yourself.
Oh, thank God.
Now, do you know
who you are?
Nick Greenwald.
Former S.O.B.
Thank you.
Now I can go back
to my beautiful life
with my beautiful wife.
Maybe she'll stop whining
and cut me some slack
now that I've risked
my life.
Doesn't make sense.
We removed the problem.
We removed the damage.
Maybe we were wrong
about the problem.
I need to believe
we can get through this.
Temperature's 94.5.
Do you really think
I'm stupid?
Honey, you're not stupid.
You' just--
Please don't do this.
It could be the effect
of the surgery.
Do you at least respect me,
Nick
What do you think
of what I do for a living?
I think people who publicize
important things
are people who can't do
important things themselves.
Honey, stop.
Don't.
Do you regret marrying me?
- 94.2.
Sometimes.
Everybody wonders--
Get me a heating blanket.
Do you even love me?
- Yes.
Audrey, wait.
Let me--
V-tach. Get me the paddles.
Clear.
Echo says his heart
is structurally fine.
But his temperature
is still dropping.
He's headed for hypothermia.
I can't reach House.
It just goes to voicemail.
It means we were wrong
about infection.
His temperature's just going
up and down
because something's playing
with his thermostat.
Which means
the brain damage is spreading.
What causes brain damage
and nose bleed
and involves the lungs,
heart and kidneys?
Cancer?
We could text him.
- It's not cancer.
Normal PSA, normal blood smear,
colonoscopy normal.
Do a full body scan.
House hates full body scans.
House isn't here.
- House is right.
Everybody's got three or four
meaningless anomalies
that'll come up on a scan.
Chasing each one
will take time we don't have.
Feel free to send him
an IM.
You told me
you saw your brother once.
after he disappeared.
13 years ago.
I used to go to Princeton
whenever I could.
I must have hit
every homeless shelter in town.
And then one day,
I'm just sitting at this deli,
having a sandwich,
I look out the window,
and there he is.
He was gone
by the time I got outside.
That's why you were so eager
when I told you
there was a job at Princeton.
I thought
it was just my charm.
That's the team.
Shouldn't you answer?
They already texted me to so
they're doing something stupid.
There's a small abdominal
aneurysm.
Irrelevant.
What else you got?
Cyst in the pleura
around the lungs.
Also irrelevant.
Couldn't cause
any of the symptoms.
There's a density
in the liver.
Could be vascular malformation.
If he's got multiple AVMs,
screwed-up blood flow
would explain everything.
We can only spot them
with angiography.
We'll have to do targeted scans
with contrast
and then embolize
each one.
Can we do that
before he freezes?
We'll find out.
The spell-correct
on Kutner's phone
has got a hair trigger.
Either that, or the patient has
a cyclone in the floral
of his lungs.
You took a walk
in 45-degree weather,
and you left your coat behind.
Go ahead.
I think you were punishing
yourself.
I think you wanted to feel
what it would be like
be homeless
a New Jersey winter.
That tells me guilt.
That tells me
something happened.
The schizophrenia started
when he was a teenager.
When he was in college.
He was on meds,
but he'd still think
a professor was out
to get him because he got a B,
or he'd fight with his roommates
because he never showered.
Where were you?
Med school.
He called me every day.
Talked for hours.
I didn't have hours.
Interesting.
Later for that.
Go on.
I was tired
of being the guy
that everybody counted on,
so one night, Danny called--
one night, Danny called,
crying, upset about something.
I had to study
for an exam.
So I-I hung up...
took my things.
I went to the library
so I wouldn't have
to hear the phone ring.
I wonder
how that turned out.
My mother called
me the next day.
Danny had run away
and left his meds behind.
Which I knew meant
that he would never be able
to choose to come back,
because he'd be so detached
from reality.
So you made your one effort
to live a normal, selfish life,
and the universe immediately
smacked you down.
And because we're wired
to find meaning
in semi-random events,
you decided never to be
that careless again.
You don't think
that's a little facile?
Actually, I don't.
I think you did it consciously.
You developed
your people-pleasing talents
the way an Olympic athlete
develops his muscles.
Talk about an overreaction
to a single event.
It was a pretty big event.
Hanging up the phone?
That's what you're blaming
all this on.
That's the behavior
you've been trying to correct.
As though nothing else went
wrong in your brother' life.
Of course,
he overreacted too, but...
his glucose was normal.
We're not talking about
my brother anymore, are we?
It's House.
ADMs don't explain his glucose.
Since this is significant
moment in my life and all...
yeah.
I think I'll just go in then.
Explain that.
- Right.
You'd given him steroids.
His glucose should have been
elevated.
That wannabe cyst you found
in the whole body scan,
without the glucose,
it's an irrelevant cyst.
He has Doege-Potter syndrome.
His fibroma is secreting
human growth hormone,
which acts like insulin,
lowering his glucose.
It doesn't explain the organ
failure or the brain damage.
This whole thing
is an overreaction.
That one small fibroma.
It's benign, but his body's
acting like it's an invader.
His antibodies went to war
against it
and got carried away,
attack his other systems.
Take out the fibroma,
he'll be a happy hypocrite
again in no time.
Maybe I should call a cab.
Your wife's
probably just late.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about...
you know...
the things I said.
I have a conspicuous nose.
It suits your face.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Traffic.
I have some good news.
I was gonna tell you,
and then you got sick.
It didn't seem
like the best time.
I've been offered
a better position.
I'd be coordinating
cancer awareness walks
in three cities.
That's great.
Congratulations.
I know you've worked hard
for this.
Thank you.
# faith pours
from your walls #
Is Marika okay?
I'm sure she's moved on.
# you're not near #
Kids are so resilient.
# remembering when I saw
your face #
# shining my way #
# pure timing #
You okay?
I'll be seeing Danny again
next week.
I'd like you to meet him.
Sure.
He sounds interesting.
Go on.
I thought seeing him again
would change everything.
It would be wonderful
or terrible.
Instead...
we're just strangers.
It's kind of anticlimactic.
Which is better
than terrible.
Go on.
Does it bother you
that we have no social contract?
My whole life
is one big compromise.
I tiptoe around everyone
like they're made of china.
I spend all my time analyzing:
What will the effect be
if I say this?
Then there's you.
You're a reality junkie.
If I offered you
a comforting lie,
you'd smack me over the head
with it.
Let's not change that.
Okay.
No, see, this--
if you were implementing
the social contract,
you'd say that,
but only because...
it makes me feel better...
It is kind of fun
watching you torture yourself.
Do you think things
will work out with my brother?
No.
But when it does go wrong,
it won't be your fault.
Thanks, House.
You do
actually like monster trucks.
Absolutely.
Subtitles by LeapinLar