The trick to onions--
cut them in half lengthwise,
but leave the roots on.
Then make your
vertical slices.
Need a dozen.
Think you can handle this?
A dozen is 12, right?
Next, we add mustard greens--
spicy, and they pack a nice punch.
Plus, they're really good for you.
Improve mental function,
protect against
rheumatoid arthritis.
Even inhibit certain types
of cancer.
Are you going to chop
those onions
or give them a Thai massage?
Well, I guess a happy ending
is out of the question.
I don't recall adding
making snide remarks
to your list of duties.
Just taking initiative.
Secret ingredient:
Porcini mushrooms.
You want to reconstitute them
in a bowl of water.
You also want to hire
an assistant
who can stay focused
for longer than 30 seconds.
Why don't I hear you chopping?
Just give me a second.
You're kidding me, right?
So sorry.
- Are you okay? You want to sit down?
My lips are blue.
Cyanosis.
Pain in my back and chest.
Spontaneous pneumothorax.
What are you talking about?
- I'm a doctor.
You are?
- And I need a doctor.
You drool.
Shut up.
I know gas is expensive,
but I could've given you a ride.
Elevator's broken.
It was fine when I came up
from admitting.
Dana Miller, the cancer researcher.
Spontaneous pneumothorax.
- Awfully thin file.
She just got admitted.
Lots of things can cause
pneumothorax.
Why don't we let
eight or ten other doctors
rule out the boring stuff?
We wanna take this case.
She's maybe five or ten years away
from curing retinoblastoma.
Which would make this case
attractive to anyone
who has some vested interest
in people curing the incurable.
She hasn't suffered
from COPD.
She doesn't smoke.
She hasn't been scuba diving.
O2 Sats are low even after
chest tube insertion.
Pneumothorax could be secondary
to a bunch of things.
Cystic fibrosis,
lung cancer.
Or, to be slightly
more optimistic,
late-onset asthma triggered
by an unknown allergen.
We have a case?
- Did you just get to work?
Am I in trouble?
Did you take the elevators up?
- Yes.
So, steroids for asthma?
Yeah.
Do a CT looking for
hyperinflation to confirm.
I thought my hospital was high-tech.
I'd have to wait all day for a CT.
Dr. House gets a few perks.
He has his own scanner?
No, just very loose interpretations
of hospital procedure.
I appreciate the extra effort,
but--
Our gift to society.
we want to get you back to work
as soon as possible.
Well, I'm not working.
At least not as a doctor.
I quit.
I left eight months ago.
You mean, like, a sabbatical?
I had a uterine myoma.
Benign.
But it ruptured and
I needed emergency surgery.
I was lying there
on the table thinking,
"I can't die now.
I haven't been happy yet."
Couldn't you just buy
an overpriced German sports car,
or have an affair?
My sports car is doing
what I want when I want.
Right now I'm learning
how to run a kitchen
from one of the best chefs
in New York.
You're washing pots
and smashing garlic?
Smashing garlic makes me happy.
Before that it was
eight years studying,
12 years in that lab.
It was always
what I was supposed to do,
and never what I wanted to do.
Come here.
Look at this.
Adorable.
Elevators keep crashing.
Is mercury in retrograde
or what?
Elevators can be capricious.
Sometimes it just seems like
they're out to get you.
She keeps playing
with the blanket.
Why would she do that?
Why do you think
the elevators
would be out to get me?
I don't know.
Maybe they wanted to take time off
to spend with
their little dumbwaiter.
But they the had to leave it
at home with an elevator sitter
because you drove
the replacement elevator
to quitting
because you're incapable
of listening to anybody but me.
That's just a theory.
You're wrong.
I don't even listen to you.
Either do your job or go home.
Leave me out of it.
I am gonna do my job.
It doesn't mean
I have to do it happily.
Doesn't mean I have to do it
without resentment.
And it definitely doesn't mean
I have to do it
without seeking vengeance
on the person making me be here.
Congratulations.
You've officially dragged me
down to your level.
Okay.
Hey, Blue.
It's not asthma.
Lung volume is normal.
She did have a uterine myoma
removed eight months ago.
Central line IV could have
made a hole near the lung
at slowly expanded.
No pleural thickening.
I can't believe she quit.
People have the right
to be happy.
I saw a four-year-old
with retinoblastoma
on my oncology rotation.
The cancer had eaten through
her eye and into her brain.
Horrible diseases exist.
It doesn't mean people
should give up
recreational anything.
Why not?
Big picture--
I don't care
if Jonas Salk's life
is a miserable shell.
I just want him to cure polio.
You can't live your life
"big picture."
You've gotta look out
for yourself
and the people you care about.
Well, then, why are you a doctor?
Why aren't you sitting
by a pool in Fiji
knocking back Mai Tais?
People act in their own
self-interests.
You're all here because
you're happy to be here.
Or at least because
it's your best option.
I'm here because
I want to help people.
No, you're here because
it makes you feel good
to help people.
Taub and Foreman
are here because
they've got no other
viable choices.
And Thirteen is desperate
to make her life matter
before it's over.
So...you're happy to be here?
Does it show?
Are those...
increased interstitial markings?
Could be pulmonary fibrosis.
Do a biopsy.
Foreman.
"You've got to look out
for the people you care about."
That wouldn't have anything
to do with you
screwing over your clinical trial
by slipping Thirteen
the real drug, would it?
You said that would be stupid.
Does she know?
Because Jonas Salk would not approve.
There's nothing to know.
Got it?
Good?
- Yep.
You okay?
Just a headache.
I took some ibuprofen, but--
Where's the pain:
Front or back?
Front.
Why are there never any
interesting pictures
on these cards?
They should make a dirty version.
A sharp pain,
or more of a throbbing--
Relax, it's not a side effect.
People get headaches.
True, but I can get you an MRI.
If I'm on the drug, it's been weeks.
It's not like something's going
to suddenly crop up now.
Okay.
First card.
Train, duck...
You can't remember?
Piano.
We need a biopsy to confirm--
You need an open-lung biopsy
to confirm pulmonary fibrosis.
That's invasive surgery.
I'd be out of commission
for weeks.
No offense,
but you're not working.
What does it matter if
you spend a little time in bed?
Not working doesn't mean
I don't have places to go.
I've got my book group,
piano lessons, cooking classes.
They make me happy.
A warm apple fritter makes me happy.
It doesn't fulfill me as a person.
And working here does?
If it didn't, I'd have found a way
to go back to tucking tummies.
Well, good for you.
If your job fulfills you and
makes you happy, that's rare.
I didn't say I was happy.
I loved being a plastic surgeon.
The money, the lifestyle.
And in a lot of ways this job stinks.
Not making five bucks,
I'm always annoyed...but--
You can look yourself
in the mirror and think,
"I did something
worthwhile today."
Exactly.
Well, that's important.
And I do miss that.
But it just wasn't enough
anymore.
That doesn't feel right.
Sit up.
Ow! Oh, that's weird.
What is it? Ascites?
Ow!
Your belly's full of blood.
First her lung deflates,
like me after a cold shower.
Now her liver starts to bleed,
like me after--
You okay?
Great.
Just practicing
my clown college audition.
Someone set a trip wire.
We were with the patient
the whole time.
We were in the GRC.
Lung, liver, go.
Shouldn't you be obsessing
over who did this to you?
Nope--anybody bother
MRIing our patient's liver
for tumors?
Uh, no tumors, no cysts,
no clear etiology.
If you're not obsessing,
you must have already
figured it out.
Yes.
So I'm obsessing about why
you're not obsessing
about why our patient's liver
suddenly sprang a leak.
There's a tiny spot on the caudate lobe.
Could be a granuloma.
Erodes into the hepatic artery,
causes the bleed.
What caused the granuloma?
Blastomycosis.
Could have been asymptomatic
for months.
It hits her lungs,
we give her steroids.
It blossoms and attacks her liver.
Get a piece of her lung,
stick it under a black light.
If it glows, sick children
who need her souffles
can breathe easier.
Foreman.
Again?
You have a problem.
I told you, I didn't--
Then you really have a problem.
They way she turned her head
to look at the MRI...
I think she's losing
her peripheral vision.
Because she turned her head?
I'm happy for you.
A love so deep you're ready
to chuck your medical license
to give her powerful, unproven drugs
with dangerous side effects.
I don't want to make
any assumptions
about your feelings for me,
but I do have a birthday
coming up.
I hear Cuddy's seal training
finally came in handy.
Should I be investing
in a flak jacket?
You're safe.
No carpet bombing?
No burning of Dresden
to teach her a lesson?
Well, since you're incapable
of taking the high road,
I assume there's
some deeper,
more long-term strategy
in effect.
Cuddy's not playing games.
She's not looking for leverage.
She wants pure,
unadulterated vengeance.
And your counter-move is
to let her have it?
The only time to strike back
is when I want something.
All I want now is
to get things back to normal.
Which I can't get by escalating.
The only way to win this war
is to lose it.
Let her punch herself out.
Yeah, that makes sense too.
"Too"?
I was thinking you actually feel guilty
About taking her away from her baby.
But your explanation's good too.
It's completely inconsistent
with your character, but...
Thank you, rationalization man.
You have saved the village.
You wanna eat?
You forgot your file.
Dana Miller?
The cancer researcher?
Not anymore.
Dr. Miller, I doubt
if you'll remember me--
James Wilson, right?
Chicago.
The adenocarcinoma conference.
Impressive.
You want some cortisone for that itch?
Liver failure.
Itching is one of
the lovely side effects.
Why did you quit?
The worst thing is
is now every time I get sick,
I have to listen
to a dozen people judge me.
Do you want me
to congratulate you?
I've got four kids
in PED-ONC right now
who are gonna die.
Three of them within a year,
the other in a few days,
probably.
Breakthroughs will happen.
With or without me,
someone will find the answer.
Maybe.
I--I...
I'm in the trenches.
I'm--I'm doing triage
as best I can.
You had the chance
to end the war.
How is someone like me
supposed to keep fighting
when someone like you just...
walked away?
When I left my job,
a lot of people were furious
with me.
It was easier to be angry than
to admit they weren't happy.
that they were stuck in a rut
somewhere in their lives,
unable to move forward.
What's your rut?
Okay, you're freaking me out.
Do you think
we should have kids?
We've had this conversation.
- Ten years ago.
Things change.
On our third date I told you
that I didn't want to have kids,
and you said that
you were okay with that.
I said it because
I wanted to sleep with you.
And then I fell in love with you.
And I realized that I really
could be okay with it.
It wasn't like I had this
burning desire to have children.
God, have you been
resenting me all this time?
Is that why--
- No.
Of course not.
I'm just...revisiting.
This isn't a whim for me.
It's not a decision
that I made lightly.
Don't you ever wonder
what it would be like?
All the time.
Just not enough to make me
want to do it.
I like our life.
Are you okay?
Could you turn the TV
back on?
Look straight ahead.
Why didn't we
do this test this morning?
You see that?
No.
- Damn.
I'm losing my peripheral vision?
I am on the drug.
Does this mean
you have to tell them
and take me off it?
No, and yes.
As far as they're concerned,
you're on the placebo.
I found out last week.
The trial was getting
positive results...
so I switched you.
So my headaches...
I'll stop taking the drug,
and everything should be fine.
Specimen's negative for blastomycosis.
That's it?
I'll go give House the test results.
You can tell the patient.
Hey.
We've been dating for two weeks.
You just broke trial protocol
and risked your entire career
to give me a drug we're
not even sure will help me.
I don't think I'm ready for that.
Dr. Miller?
Mm...
- I'm sorry.
The test was negative.
So I'm gonna take you off--
what happened to your head?
I don't know. I was sleeping.
It's so itchy.
You were scratching it
in your sleep.
You scratched
right through your skull.
This is brain matter.
Need some help in here!
I did a free flap closure
to avoid any scarring.
Scarring.
She was lucky--the scratching
didn't cause any brain damage.
But the first thing she said
when we woke her up was
it still itches.
Itch receptors are only
in the top two layers of skin.
Which means she's not actually itchy,
she just thinks she is.
So the problem's in her brain?
Thank God we have you here
to interpret that for us.
Sorry, I have a headache.
Could be psychogenic.
She made big, sudden change
in her life.
Could be the result
of a mental imbalance.
She wants to do
what she wants to do.
What's crazy about that?
Why do you have to quit
to do it?
If I want to do something,
I do it.
If you can figure out a balance,
there's no burnout.
Thanks for the lesson, deep.
The itching started yesterday,
not eight months ago.
Meningitis, encephalitis...
Those are diffuse processes.
This is localized.
Could be plaques.
MS would explain,
possibly the lungs.
So would a brain tumor.
Well, how 'bout we stop guessing
and MRI her head instead?
You want to talk about
your headaches?
Not particularly.
You went off the drug,
but the headaches are worse.
You need an MRI.
The patient needs an MRI.
If she had gangrene,
would you be amputating my leg?
Those pills have codeine in them?
You're taking twice the indicated amount.
I've only been off the drug
for 24 hours,
So I think
the bigger issue here
is that I've been off you
for 24 hours.
You have worsening headaches,
loss of peripheral vision,
and a long history of pretending
bad things aren't happening.
You really think this is just
about my hurt feelings?
I don't remember demoting you.
I brought you something.
The latest issue
of Parent Magazine.
Really interesting column.
Apparently, working moms
are actually more engaged
and attentive than stay-at-home moms.
Something about personal fulfillment.
That's just a rationalization
by working moms to justify
not being with their kids.
Which is fine,
if that's what they want.
It's not what I want.
And this is Nurses Quarterly.
The point is--
- You're only here to get back at me
by dumping dirty mop water
on my carpet.
Just get it over with
so I can get back to work.
I'm sorry.
I figured...
I don't know, one of us needed
to go out on a limb.
I thought I could help you.
It's hard to have a conversation
when I'm trying not to move.
Oh, God.
Patient's MRI was negative.
No tumors, no lesions.
Where's your cane?
Where are your coworkers?
I paged them.
It could still be psychogenic.
Technically, it can't still be that,
because it never could be that.
Unless she was having
a dream about fleas--
Oh, hey!
Funny you should drop by.
We were just talking
about this patient of ours.
Tell him the part
about where two of her doctors
don't show up--
Where are you going?
Polyneuropathy.
If it's not in the brain,
it's in the nerves.
It explains the itching,
the lungs, the liver.
Shock the affected area,
reboot the nerve--
She'll be fine.
Foreman.
How bad is she?
She's got a tumor
in her optic chiasm.
You don't need your coat
to treat a tumor.
I'm going to the drug company.
To tell them that you
compromised their trial,
your ethics,
and the patient's health?
That's a great idea.
They have records
on hundreds of patients.
I can ask them for access,
find out if other patients
developed tumors
and how they were treated.
This drug inhibits cell death.
I think I could take a wild guess
at how I treat that.
Stop taking it?
Yeah.
She tried that yesterday.
Oh, my God, it's been a whole day,
And her brain tumor hasn't melted away?
If you get on that elevator,
and it's only
'cause you're worried
about getting to sleep tonight--
I want to be able
to tell her
this happened to other people,
and they're fine now.
So tell her.
I'm not gonna lie to her.
A little late for that.
You need to wait.
Because if this thing
doesn't go away,
she's gonna need you
to still have a medical license.
So I spoke with House.
He thinks we should just--
My leg is bleeding.
What happened?
I was going for the phone,
and I fell over the table.
I can't see.
What do you mean?
I can't see anything.
You gonna tip housekeeping?
Get it from Cuddy.
Don't tell me--
She burned your apartment
to the ground.
The warmth would have been nice.
No heat, no power.
Apparently Mrs. House
called the utilities
and told them we were moving.
You have 17 messages.
And your non-involvement strategy
doesn't seem to be working.
Hang up, he's here.
We've been paging you all night.
By all means, let's discuss
the failed attempts to contact me,
not the reason behind them.
Patient started experiencing
spinal shocks
before the machine was turned on.
Lhermitte's sign.
Shocks without shock,
An itch that won't stop.
She needs Dr. Seuss.
Lhermitte's sign could mean
behcet's, B-12 deficiency.
No sores, no anemia.
Where's Foreman?
- No idea.
Could be another
demyelinating disease.
Why are you asking
about Foreman and not Thirteen?
Because both questions are bound
to have the same answer.
Ebony and Ivory
are joined near the hip.
Forget the brain.
Look lower.
The spinal tumor wouldn't
explain the liver or the lungs.
But an aggressive
spinal hemangioma could.
Go find it.
You didn't answer the door.
Probably because I didn't
want to talk to anyone.
You can leave your stolen key
on your way out.
I was looking for Foreman.
I figured...
You can't see.
Where is he?
On his way to the drug company.
Tell him to come back.
I'll dial.
If they can help.
You think that drug company
has a magic tumor wand
that no one else knows about?
You need radiation,
not ritual sacrifice.
He asked for my advice
before he switched you
off the placebo.
I told him to do it if he loved you.
He only thinks he loves me.
It's the same thing.
Yes, he's an idiot.
You didn't ask him
to do anything.
You're pissed off that he did.
So let him torch his career
to pay for his sins.
Unless you actually
feel something for the idiot.
In which case, you might
want to tell him to turn around.
You're hurting him.
Good, after all the stunts
he's pulled on me.
You're physically hurting him.
That's the point.
What's the point?
What do you think
you're going to accomplish?
House shouldn't be allowed
to make people miserable
without paying for it.
You're not miserable!
- You're telling me how I feel?
You're here
because you like this.
You like working with him.
Wow, if only I'd known
I was having fun,
I wouldn't have canceled
the bouncy house.
Fire him, and go be home
with your new baby.
I like what he does
for this hospital.
What he does is who he is.
And the same goes for you.
Slow down.
Unless you want to radiate
her heart instead of her brain.
Of course, then your problems
would actually all go away.
Thanks.
I'm not beating myself up
enough already over this.
Entering the left common carotid.
You broke the rules.
Girlfriend went blind.
You gotta be ready
for losing
To be one
of the possibilities.
You're at the carotid bifurcation.
I knew that
giving her the drug
would be bad for me
if I got caught.
I never thought
it would be bad for her.
Nobody else was having
adverse reactions.
You did it because you love her.
Ironically, you never
took her into consideration.
Can't wait to see what you
get her for your anniversary.
Catheter's adjacent
to the optic chiasm.
We're in position.
Nukey, nukey.
What's going on
with everyone today?
It involves House,
Foreman, and Thirteen,
which means it's either
dumb, dangerous, or tragic,
or a combination.
I'm embracing my ignorance.
House was right about
the hemangioma.
Looks fixable.
What's that?
Hemangiomas travel solo.
This thing
has brought a friend.
Masses in her lungs and spine.
One in her pericardium.
They're everywhere.
Classic mesothelioma.
It metastasized outward
to the spine and muscles.
Ah, the irony of it.
Maybe she wouldn't be sick at all
if some other lazy cancer researcher
hadn't gone home early.
Where are Foreman and Thirteen?
Shouldn't you be saying,
"those weren't there when
we scanned her two days ago"?
Mesothelioma
shouldn't grow this fast.
Good rephrasing.
Have Wilson do a biopsy
to confirm.
No.
Something weird is going on.
It involves our colleagues--
we should know.
You want us to treat
the patient,
tell us what's going on.
Actually, all he needs us to do
is tell Wilson to do something.
So...
You always blab
to watch people react.
So not blabbing means
you don't want us to react,
which can't be good.
Is Thirteen's headache
not just a headache?
If I check with admitting,
am I gonna find her name?
A little pinch.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I...unloaded on you.
And...
- You're not sorry.
You feel bad because
mesothelioma means I'm dying.
You're a good person.
I appreciate the sentiment.
I'm not apologizing
because you're dying.
I'm apologizing
because you were right.
I am stuck.
My girlfriend died.
She was the only person I've
loved for a long time, and...
I'm still living in her apartment.
I'm surrounded by her things.
I have left it all
exactly where it was.
I don't know how to get unstuck.
The only wrong thing is...
to do nothing.
Yeah.
All right.
That's not supposed to happen.
Have you thought about
going to the drug company,
see if they can help?
I thought about it.
We need to give it more time.
It's been half a day.
This thing keeps growing,
there's other stuff in your brain
you might need later on.
If I were any other patient,
you'd both be in the lounge,
eating donuts.
You're not any other patient.
Right.
Any other patient,
you don't feel guilty.
But you don't get
to torch your career
to pay for your sins.
House told her to say that,
didn't he?
Does that make it any less true?
You think he's right?
Who cares?
You're a hypocrite.
You don't ask her
if she wants to be on the drug,
but when there's a chance
you could help her get better,
suddenly you're letting her
call the shots?
That's not being noble.
That's saving your own ass.
I'd feel worse
if he destroyed his career.
Mesothelioma doesn't bleed.
So what causes masses
that do bleed?
Avm's secondary
to schistosomiasis.
She'd be crawling with worms.
We'd have noticed it.
Gorham's disease and Kasabach-Merritt
can both cause super-aggressive
vascular tumors.
So what causes that?
Cardiac tamponade.
She's bleeding
into her pericardium,
Smothering her heart.
Syringe.
B.P.'s going back up.
It's working.
No, it's not--
look.
We're transfusing platelets, FFP,
everything to try
to keep her stable.
But we can barely
keep up with the blood loss.
At this rate, she could be dead
by the end of the day.
We need to resect
the vascular tumors,
stop the bleeding.
Too late--no surgeon's
gonna touch her now.
Should we give up?
Just let her bleed out?
Don't be silly.
You know what that would do
to our malpractice insurance rates?
We go on the offensive.
Cut off the invading army's
supply line.
You're talking about embolization?
Cut off the arteries
that feed blood to the tumors,
they wither and die.
Start with the ones in her lungs.
If they get any bigger,
she's gonna have
a hard time breathing.
So she'll have a hard time
telling us she's dead.
You can't kill the tumors
without also killing healthy tissue.
If we wipe out 3/4 of her lungs...
Let's hope that running marathons
wasn't on her happy list.
I found this.
Ahem.
In the, uh, coat closet.
Where I hid it.
Thought I'd never see you again.
Little, little Greg.
Yeah, you heard me right!
Well, you are who you are.
It's annoying, but...
it's not your fault.
It isn't about you.
I...
I'm sorry.
Because you were
doing this job perfectly
until the baby came along.
What?
I'm apologizing.
Can't you just accept my--
I accept.
We gonna have to do
this dance again in 28 days?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Yesterday, you hate me.
Today, you're practically
weeping on my shoulder.
I can only assume
that what I'm hearing
is your Aunt Flow telling me...
When I was being a jerk,
you suddenly act human.
But when I act human,
you turn back into a jerk.
Guess our cycles
aren't matched up yet.
This is your way
of saying you accept
my apology, isn't it?
Nope, this is my way of saying
You were doing a crappy job before;
You will a slightly
crappier job now.
Everything keeps going.
Nature of life.
Nature of parenthood.
Or this whole thing
is just an act.
And you've gone back to the part
you think you need to play.
You should go talk to Wilson.
Rationalization man
needs a faithful sidekick.
Now, rational man
needs to go save a life.
House.
If you're looking
for returnable bottles,
Kutner's already cleaned it out.
Damn!
Oh, well.
That means the only thing
I'm gonna get out of this...
is a diagnosis.
So the nurses gave her pads
instead of tampons.
Is that diagnostically relevant?
Fact that the nurses had
to give her anything is.
Means she's bleeding
from her uterus.
Women do that.
It's perfectly natural.
Not scary at all.
She menstruating
and she's bleeding everywhere.
There's about a 3 or 4 in 28 chance
it's a coincidence.
Which leaves a much bigger chance
that the diagnosis
is ectopic endometriosis.
She had a myoma
eight months ago.
Surgeons cut through
her uterine wall.
Every cut of the scalpel could
have sent endometrial cells
spilling out into her bloodstream.
Some of them took up
residence in her lungs,
some in her liver,
some in her spine.
And like all horny little cells,
they went forth and multiplied
till they reached a critical mass.
In the days leading up
to her next period,
when her uterus
is supposed to swell,
Everything swelled.
And when her uterus
was supposed to bleed,
everything bled.
Yes, ladies, I am blaming her period.
Granted, it's the worst period ever.
Although, frankly,
not by all that much.
Cut out the masses,
she'll be fine.
Can't do surgery
until her cycle's over
and she stops bleeding.
Well, let's hope
she can hold out till then.
In the meantime, get her
a pint of cookie dough ice cream
and a DVD of Beaches.
I'm sorry.
Foreman?
I can see you.
How you feeling?
Relative to the last
few days, awesome.
You almost died.
For the second time
in eight months.
I know.
How do you feel about
your life choices this time?
I didn't lie there
thinking "what if?"
I always worry,
on my deathbed I'll think,
"I didn't do anything
really important."
You're gonna spend
one day of your life
on your death bed.
The other 25,000
are the ones we should be
worrying about.
Go to bed happy tonight.
Dr. Schmidt.
It's Eric Foreman.
Um...actually, the trial
isn't going too well.
You told them, didn't you?
Well, you really had no choice...
On account of being an idiot.
They gonna pull the drug?
I broke protocol.
Her results are no longer
admissible to the trial.
They don't have to do anything.
Anyone else gets a tumor,
they'll put a warning on the label.
Gonna keep your license?
They'll come after me
if I attempt to participate
in any more trials.
That's very decent of them.
Well, good for me.
I'll see you tomorrow.
And the next day.
That wasn't your locker,
was it?
It's a lock-ER room.
How else are they gonna learn?
Do you think you can't
be happy without a kid?
I don't know.
# some kind of magic #
I know I can't be happy
without you.
# happens late at night #
# when the moon smiles down at me #
# and bathes me in its light #
# I fell asleep beneath you #
# in the tall blades of grass #
# when I woke the world was new #
You snore.
Shut up.
# it's a brand new day #
# the sun is shining #
# for the first time
in such a long, long time #
# I know #
# I'll be okay # #
Subtitles by LeapinLar