- 145 pounds!
Johnson!
Miller!
- Aaaah!
- Aaaaah!
- House.
House.
I know you're not asleep.
- That insight
would be a lot more impressive
if you weren't just a product
of my exhausted brain.
- Aren't you curious
about why I'm here?
- curious why
no french maid's outfit.
No spanky pants.
- I'm a hallucination...
not a fantasy.
- It's insomnia.
Four nights without REM sleep
can cause--
- That might explain
why you're hallucinating.
Doesn't explain
why you're hallucinating
Wilson's dead girlfriend.
- Probably just my secret
and very unconscious desire
to get Wilson into my bedroom.
- Or maybe your guilt
of Kutner's suicide
reminds you how guilty
you felt about me.
- Who cares why you're here?
A decent night's sleep,
you won't be.
- Guess I'll be around
a few more hours.
- Need some coffee?
- Addictive substances
are no substitute
for nature's healing balm.
Let's make this fast.
I need to sleep.
- Deaf 14-year-old started
hearing imaginary explosions.
- Exploding head syndrome.
Cool.
Well, obviously his brain
knows how to hear.
- Patient went deaf
at age four.
Complication of meningitis.
- So why no cochlear implant?
- Usual suspects are insomnia,
which he doesn't have,
migraines, which he doesn't get,
and head trauma
which didn't show up on the CT.
- Damn imaginary pen.
- Mom's signature's
on everything.
Did the dad die?
- No, I doubt it.
He was a sperm donor.
Medical records
couldn't be cleaner.
- So we're left with
temporal lobe seizure.
- Wrong.
- Someone
at the wrestling meet
would have noticed
a seizure.
- Could have just looked like
a bad shot to the leg.
Put him in the seizure lab.
See if his head blows up
all over again.
- You're gonna ignore
your own subconscious?
Gonna be the limp
leading the blind.
I need a 'scrip,
for sleeping pills.
My neighbor's dog's
been keeping me awake,
and seems strangely
invulnerable to poison.
Why is the soon-to-be-
second-prettiest Dr. Chase here?
- I'll take that
as a congratulations.
- We're discussing a case.
- Why did he
close that file?
- Wedding in two weeks?
I'd say you were pregnant,
but I don't think Chase's body
is mature enough
to produce sperm.
- It's a small ceremony.
Why wait?
- Nighty night.
- Drugs with no lecture?
He wants you out.
- Interesting case?
- Possible prostate cancer
came into the E.R.
- Pencil cup.
- Oh!
No wonder
his prostate's enlarged.
It's full of pool cues
and cigars.
- Chase's best man
doesn't get here
till the day of the wedding,
so I asked Wilson to throw
his bachelor party.
- No retired ministers
available to plan it?
- Chase doesn't want some big,
raucous party.
- So she says.
- Luckily,
there are people in this world
ready to stand up
for what's right.
- No, no, no, I don't want--
I don't want you to--
- Listen, two things
I do well.
Bachelor parties rank
towards the top.
- I get to help, right?
- Starting five hertz.
House made it through
that entire differential
without mocking our patient
for not having
a cochlear implant.
- The patient
doesn't want an implant
because he's comfortable
with who he is.
It's admirable.
- He's deaf.
It's not an identity,
it's a disability.
- It's also a culture.
The deaf have their own schools,
their own language.
Still no spiking.
- Going to 20.
Anything I can simulate
with a $3.00 pair of ear plugs
is not a culture.
No sign of seizure.
Temporal lobe activity
is still clean.
- Doctors...doctors,
he can't see.
One of his eyes.
- The limp leading the blind.
- Is that supposed
to mean something?
- I didn't think so.
- So exploding head syndrome,
plus vision loss.
- Subclavian steal syndrome.
Vascular defect coupled
with constant arm movement
could siphon blood flow
from the brain.
- We should do an angio,
check his--
- Knock yourselves out.
- How did I know
he was gonna go blind?
Don't get cute, gazoo.
You're in my mind.
You're obviously there.
- C-reactive protein.
I noticed in his file
it was slightly elevated.
I figured the stress
of the seizure lab
would drive
inflammation even higher,
lead to optic neuritis.
- That's a lot clearer than
"the limp leading the blind."
- It was just a glimmer.
I couldn't put it into words.
- It was a long shot.
I don't even remember
the C-reactive protein level.
- Obviously you do.
You just don't know it.
- How high is K2?
- I don't know.
- Me neither.
But I read a book about it
years ago.
Fierce, sexy sherpa
on the cover, bending over--
- 28,251 feet.
- Cool.
An all-access pass
to my own brain.
- Go play the kid
some music.
- Why?
- Another long shot.
- We're using iodine dye
to track blood flow
in your neck and arm.
# fight the power #
# we've got to
fight the powers that be... #
House, what are you doing?
- What does it
look like I'm doing?
Fighting the power.
Feel that?
How cool is that?
Apparently your mom doesn't
care what you're missing.
- You're an ass.
- He says he feels
the vibrations in his abdomen,
but not his hands.
What does that mean?
- It's a new symptom.
Neuropathy.
- Thought you were gonna
get some sleep.
- Case got interesting.
- Like the zoo.
Except you can bang on the glass
as much as you want.
- How did you know
about the neuropathy?
- Good question.
- Enough with the riddles.
- Tell me about it.
- Think "wrestling record."
- Juggling.
No, pins.
Three pins.
Patient was pinned
in his last three matches.
Leading up to that,
he was 15 and 0.
I figured his balance was off
from diminished sensation.
- Could be increased ICP
from a brain tumor.
- That we missed
on the head CT?
- Cutting weight
for wrestling
could have led
to rhabdomyolysis.
- He just went up
a weight class three months ago.
- Foreman's right.
- Actually, increased ICP
could make sense.
- You just said--
- I was processing.
- It also puts a new symptom
on the table.
- His deafness.
What if it was caused
by NF2 cancer
instead of his
childhood meningitis?
- So meningitis
was a coincidence?
- Or a byproduct of the cancer
suppressing his immune system.
MRI his head.
- If you're right about NF2,
his deafness may be reversible.
I'll set it up
and talk to the patient.
- You two...doing anything?
- You know what
a broken cowboy is?
It was on House's
list of requirements.
- I have three theories.
- Why is House so into
this bachelor party thing?
- He needs to have a reason
to be into a bachelor party?
- He needs a reason
to be into anything.
- Give me your wallet.
- House could be trying
to tempt Chase into cheating.
Break them up.
- You think House
is into Cameron?
- I think House is into Cameron
being into him.
Marrying Chase
would shatter that fantasy.
- If Chase cheats,
then they shouldn't be getting
married in the first place.
- So you're okay with House
getting Chase smashed enough
to make a stupid mistake?
- Being drunk doesn't
change who you are.
It just reveals it.
- You think she can do
the broken cowboy?
- God, I hope so.
- NF2 is an extremely
slow-growing cancer,
which makes it very treatable.
If we're right,
taking out the tumor
means there's a chance
you'll regain your hearing.
- No.
He said you have to.
- What's wrong?
- He wants you to treat
the cancer, but leave him deaf.
- Uh, sorry.
Doesn't work like that.
- Imaging shows
slightly elevated ICP,
but no masses
on or around the nerves.
It's not cancer.
- Slight bowing in the wall
of the fourth ventricle.
Could still indicate a tumor.
- We brought pictures.
- The fact that you sent me
on a scouting mission--
- No skirts.
- You're not on the guest list.
Bachelor parties are an ancient
and sacred male rite of passage.
- The ventricle bowing
is most likely
a pre-existing
anatomical anomaly,
not the indication of a tumor.
- No way to know for sure
without a brain biopsy.
If I get drunk enough,
there's a chance
I might make out
with one of the strippers.
Or become one.
Sold.
- We can't just drill
into our patient's brain
on a hunch.
Oh, God, not her.
She's the one that got me
hooked in with Madoff.
- Taub's right.
It's not cancer.
- Yeah, by all means,
abandon a great
diagnostic theory
because it's difficult
to prove.
Do a biopsy.
We need to take a better look
at his fourth ventricle.
- Or an older look.
- The mom's never
gonna let us touch his brain
without some evidence.
- Patient broke his nose
years ago.
Hospital could have
done an MRI.
Okay.
- The main reason
my third wife and I eloped
was to avoid
House's bachelor party.
Have you seen Caligula?
- My patient's brain now...
versus three years ago.
See any difference?
Is he telling you
to avoid the party?
- I took an oath
to do no harm.
- Sure, don't come.
If you want your wedding vows
to be meaningless.
- This should be interesting.
- You are going to commit
to that one special woman
forever,
which is beautiful.
But if your commitment
the day after the wedding
is the same as your commitment
the day before,
then the wedding
meant nothing.
So, and I see
no logical way around this,
if you want
your marriage to matter,
you have to be a wanton,
trolling,
muck-covered pig
the day before.
- You're evil.
See ya.
- The wall of the fourth
ventricle changed.
It isn't bowed
in the older scan.
- Evidence of NF2, right?
- You'd need to do
a brain biopsy to confirm.
Uh, I'm not going
to the bachelor party.
Every time I go
to one of your parties,
I end up embarrassing myself
in some new and unexpected way.
- That whole thing with
the duck was hardly unexpected.
- I'm not going.
- Okay.
- It's not okay.
Do you know who we need?
That stripper you got
for Wilson's bachelor party.
You could do body shots
right off her.
- Why go back to that well?
In the nine years
since Wilson's party,
a whole new generation
of hot girls
have been abused
by their stepfathers.
- She loved cats.
- What made you remember
the stripper loved cats?
- Chase has a cat.
They'll bond.
Ahem, House?
You, uh, entertaining yourself
up there?
- Just rehearsing
for the revival of Evita.
What'd you find?
- The biopsy shows
nerve inflammation
consistent with increased
intracranial pressure.
Something's wrong,
but it's not cancer.
- He's gonna
go through life deaf.
- He's okay with that.
- He has no idea
what he's missing.
His mom's a moron.
He's gonna
pay for her stupidity
for the rest of his life?
Are we okay with that?
- Why are you closing?
Let's put in
a cochlear implant.
- That wasn't in the paperwork.
- Really? Well, someone
must have screwed up.
I'll go track it down.
- I'll wait.
- That's a great idea.
Let the kid spend more time
under anesthesia
with his skull cracked open.
- I'll wait.
- I have been known to lie
to serve my own agenda.
An implant does absolutely
nothing to help me diagnose him.
- Let's get an implant tray
in here.
- Just--
just try to relax.
- Just during
the recovery phase...
- Her son didn't want
the implant.
- If he still doesn't want it
after having time to adjust,
I'll take it out.
I'll blind him too,
if he wants to experience
that culture.
Remove it now.
- Kid's just had brain surgery.
He's not stable.
- Ms. Miller,
I'm not trying to minimize
Dr. House's wrongdoing.
But the best thing...
- Why is she sitting?
She's not yelling,
not threatening, not pacing.
Just sitting.
- Understand, Dr. House?
House!
Focus.
I need you to say
you accept the arrangement.
- No problem.
You're not mad.
- I'm mad.
- Not mad enough.
You wanted your son to hear.
You just didn't have the guts
to make him get the implant.
- Once my son is stable,
I want that thing
out of his head.
- Why did you do this?
- Because he is ignorant,
and he's being raised
by an idiot.
- Not good enough.
You always have--
- My patient is opting
into a handicap!
It's an insult to all the other
gimps out there.
- Okay.
But I'm still putting Foreman
in charge of the case.
- That's the arrangement?
- Okay.
- You're okay
with Foreman in charge?
Who you calling?
Oh...right, you don't want
to look like a lunatic.
- Yeah, about that...
- You think we did
the wrong thing?
- I'm not sure.
I'm not even sure
why we did it.
- Well, that argument
you made to Cuddy
sounded pretty good.
- To you, maybe.
- Huh.
I figured by now
you'd be at the board
in your monocle
and jodhpurs.
- Yeah, you did
something stupid.
Quick, better mock someone.
- Why did you do it?
- Why did I give a human being
the power of hearing?
You ask God the same question,
he'll give you the same answer.
- Patient has a fever now too.
- Probably just a post-op
complication.
Arnold-Chiari?
- Not without muscle weakness.
- Pseudotumor cerebri?
- We checked his eyes
before the surgery.
No papilledema.
- Candy?
I'm pretty sure
Wilson's stripper's name
was something sweet.
- Maybe his fever is more than
the post-op reaction.
His girlfriend
was sick a few months ago.
Maybe her flu
was really Epstein-Barr.
- Lolli?
- They swap spit,
virus travels to his brain,
leads to meningitis,
leads to increased
intracranial pressure.
- I agree. Taffy?
- I agree.
- Go ahead, start him
on rivavirin for Epstein-Barr.
- Keep making
decisions like that.
It really bolsters the illusion
that you're in charge.
- Why aren't you
in my office?
- Because I know
what the word "my" means.
- I did something insane,
and you're not all over me
analyzing why.
- It was nice.
- I gave that idiot an implant
to prove to him
what an idiot he's been.
How is that nice?
- You didn't do it
to solve the case.
You didn't do it
to save his life.
You...did it
to make his life better.
It was a caring act.
Which you did in a way
that was...
immoral and illegal, but...
baby steps.
- Doesn't sound like us.
- You can't make me go
to the bachelor party.
- I know.
- And you're okay with that?
- What choice do I have?
Seth!
Please, God.
"Seth"?
Yes.
Seth.
Oh.
I think he just
wet the bed.
- The kid's dehydrated,
but stable.
Thankfully,
the fountain of whiz
seems to have stopped
for the moment.
- Not before hosing
Epstein-Barr off the table.
Now eat up.
We're gonna pick out
the ice cream flavors
for the bachelor party.
- Could be systemic
autoimmune disease.
Sarcoido--
This tastes like...Vodka.
- Well, it'd be stupid
if it tasted like bourbon.
That's the brown one.
- It is vodka?
- Flash frozen
in a secret process.
Guy figured it out
in his basement.
Lemoncello.
Genius.
- Symptoms came on
too hard and too fast.
Sarcoidosis is progressive.
- Remember in med school
when Donovan gave grand rounds?
There was that guy
who was peeing liters.
- Glomerulonephritis?
A wrestler--steroids could
have damaged the kidneys.
Hmm, the scotch is nice.
- His urine
would have been brown.
- Donovan ruled out
osmotic diuresis--
Kidney disease.
- Pheochromocytoma?
- No hypertension.
Plasma metanephrine's normal.
- Devic's?
- It happened at night.
That was the clue.
Night, recumbent body position,
changes in B.P.
- It's his heart.
Run a 12-lead EKG,
watch him for four hours.
Foreman concurs.
What the hell just happened?
Everything started to fade away.
- You're getting better
at focusing.
Ignoring everything
that doesn't matter.
Uh-oh.
He looks pissed.
I think he might hit us.
- Is your eyesight
better than mine?
- We need to talk about
the bachelor party.
- Excellent topic choice.
Surgery's so boring,
and my lying to you
is just so yesterday.
- It's my fault for letting you
talk me into the implant.
Cameron is not gonna be happy
about this party.
- But you, on the other hand...
- Plan on spending the rest
of my life with Cameron.
- So...I need to cancel
the fart band?
- So...I need you
to kidnap me.
- Spoken like a true Aussie.
By the way, if you know where
I can get me the sheet music
to Waltzing Matilda...
Hey...want some ice cream?
We're having a sundae bar.
- Sweet.
- That's her name.
- Sundae or bar?
- Karamel.
- With a "K."
Bathroom?
- Down the hall,
two doors on your right.
- Thank you.
- Do I...
sound like...
her?
I do.
- It takes time.
- You still haven't slept?
And then I have
a clever response.
- EKG, normal sinus,
normal intervals.
His heart's fine.
- His heart's not fine.
- The heart was fine
during this test.
The arrhythmia's hiding.
- Or we were wrong
about the heart.
- Could be the thyroid.
- Hashimodo's would explain
the kid's urine
and brain pressure.
- Treadmill.
- Or the arrhythmia is hiding.
We need to stress him.
Put the patient on a treadmill.
- The patient
just had brain surgery.
A stress test could cause
a brain bleed and kill him.
- I value your opinion.
I value rejecting your opinion.
- You're not doing this.
You haven't been sleeping.
- Cuddy doesn't actually
want you in charge.
She just wants
to avoid a lawsuit
and to win an NAACP award.
- And if I let you
risk our patient's life
testing an organ
we already tested,
we accomplish neither.
Run a thyroid panel.
How do we get him
into the stress lab
without Foreman's sign-off?
- We could kill Foreman.
Is she new?
- Focus.
The lab simulates stress.
What if it's not simulated?
- We could tell him
his girlfriend dumped him.
- That's a tough sell.
She never leaves the room
for more than five minutes.
We could kill her.
Or...asthma meds.
Force the heart
to beat faster.
- Revealing the arrhythmia.
Nice idea.
- It was yours.
- I just left the room
for a few minutes.
He ripped out his implant.
So much
for improving his life.
- Actually, I think
we just saved it.
- Look at that.
Arrhythmia.
- You were right
about the heart.
Should have listened to you.
- The correct phrasing
would be,
"I should always
listen to you."
- He's got problems everywhere.
What goes everywhere?
- Blood. Could be
thrombocythemia.
Excess platelets lead
to clotting throughout the body.
- Not with a normal
platelet count.
- So the clotting
doesn't start in the blood,
it starts in the lungs--
pulmonary embolism.
- Should do a VQ scan,
see if his lungs are clear.
- Go.
You sure I did this
at Wilson's party?
- The last time,
you used grain alcohol
instead of the sambuca.
- And it worked?
Explains my lack of eyebrows
by the end of the evening.
By the power of greyskull, I--
- This is why
we're rehearsing.
Ever wonder what's happening
every time our patient
gets sicker?
- Not right now!
- First symptom, wrestling.
Then, under the lights
of the seizure lab--
- Are you going somewhere
with this, because this feels--
- Just keep doing
what you're doing--it helps.
Then, under the stress
of blindness...
and post-op fever.
What do all the symptoms
have in common?
- Heat.
See, if you hadn't been here,
that would have just
popped into my head.
Which actually would have
been way cooler.
Foreman, kid's
got Uhthoff phenomenon.
Which means it's MS.
Start him on double-dose
interferon.
- Let's get our drink on.
- Not before I've added
"chemical burns"
to this guy's
cause of death.
- Well, the patient's
responding to interferon.
Looks like I can retire
as department figurehead.
- Dr. Robert Chase.
We're with the department
of citizenship
and immigration.
Did you recently apply
for a marriage license?
- Uh...Yes.
- According to our records,
your work permit is expired.
If you could come with us.
- Um, I'm his fiancee.
I can come along
and clear this--
- I'm sorry, ma'am.
Illegals only.
- I'm--I'm sure
it's a mistake.
I'll call you as soon
as I know what's going on.
- Don't let House get him
in too much trouble.
- Oh ho!
- Allow me to welcome you
to the best night
of your life.
- Ahem!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Now, aha, a few ground rules
for the evening.
Uh, safety is job one.
We've now gone 18 days without
an injury in the workplace.
Uh, yes, these girls are all
working their way
through law school.
Don't test them.
- House!
- I knew you couldn't
stay away.
- This is my apartment.
You can't do this.
- Clearly, reality
begs to differ.
- Where's my furniture?
- Out back somewhere.
- James!
- Karamel?
Hi.
- How's your wife?
- Uh...we--we got divorced.
- Ohh.
- How is your cat?
- Dead.
- Oh.
- How 'bout we go
have a drink?
- Oh...Okay.
- Yeah...yeah...
- All right!
- Yeah!
- You're okay with this?
- I paid 50 bucks for this.
- You guys are great together.
Trust is everything.
I gotta get some air.
Keep it real.
- You should be out there...
enjoying the lap dances
of your labors.
- Eh, I kind of like it
in here.
- Me too.
To us figuring out M.S.
- And the blindness
and neuropathy and arrhythmia
and anything else we did.
What exactly did my team do?
- Look good
in their lab coats.
Except for Taub.
- Some people just
work better alone...
so to speak.
- One more drink.
- No! I can't!
I need to take a break.
- Meet Karamel.
- Huh?
- Maybe one more drink.
- Ooh...
- What's that taste?
Is that--
is that strawberry?
- House, you in there?
- Use the other bathroom.
It's in the kitchen.
Looks like a sink.
- Chase went
into anaphylactic shock
from the stripper's body butter
or something.
- Is he okay?
- One of the residents
had an epipen, so he's fine.
We're taking him to the hospital
to be safe.
- Okay.
- I knew that Chase was
allergic to strawberries,
didn't I?
That's why you wanted Karamel
at this party.
- I suggested Karamel
'cause she was great
at Wilson's party.
- I knew about her body butter
and about
his strawberry allergy.
I tried to kill Chase.
Why would I do that?
I don't want Cameron.
- You're not a big fan of other
people's happiness, either.
Hello.
You confirm?
Thanks.
That kid we saved...
he's dying.
It's not M.S.
We were wrong.
- Thank God you're okay.
What happened?
- It was a good--
- Uh, long story.
- Your patient's lung failure
rules out M.S.
We put him on a ventilator.
- Uh, enlarged lymphs could--
- Are any of you sober?
- Turn around.
You need to go to the hospital.
- I need to sleep.
- I'm you.
You can't just shut a door.
- You tried to kill Chase.
I need to push you back down.
You're dangerous.
- That's the hospital.
- Not answering.
Hello.
- I'm here with your team,
trying to sober them up
so they can...help treat
your dying patient.
- Foreman's dying patient.
- What causes lung failure
plus your patient's
previous symptoms?
- Eosinophilic pneumonitis.
White blood cells accumulate,
clog up the lungs,
lead to heart problems.
It fits.
- House, are you there?
- It's not
eosinophilic pneumonitis.
I gotta crash.
- House, don't hang up.
We need your help.
- I can't.
- We can solve this.
- Good night.
- Eosinophilic pneumonitis
could actually make sense.
- No, House ruled it out
because it would
affect the larynx.
Patient would be...
Hoarse,
Which we wouldn't notice
in a deaf kid
who rarely speaks.
- Wait.
Everyone's getting
breath mints.
- We need to hear
Seth speak.
- But that means
taking out the tube.
Isn't that dangerous?
- It's the safest way to
confirm what's wrong with him.
- I need him to breathe out
as I pull on the tube.
- okay.
Breathe out.
- Say, "ah."
- Ahhhh.
- I'm sorry.
We were wrong.
I need to, uh,
suction out your throat
before we reintubate.
Your son smoke?
Smoke?
I don't think so.
- Tobacco stains
on his teeth.
- He says he used
to chew tobacco
to cut weight
for wrestling.
- Used to?
- Chewing tobacco wouldn't
explain his symptoms.
- But not chewing tobacco
might.
Taub was right.
It's sarcoidosis.
The tobacco releases toxins.
Those toxins suppressed
his immune system.
Once he quit chewing,
the absence of those toxins
kicked a dormant condition
into hyper-drive.
- Is it treatable?
- Usually responds
to corticosteroids
and methotrexate.
I'll start the meds.
- I need sleeping pills.
I was gonna hit up Wilson,
but he's not
answering his phone.
- He must have
left it in his pants.
Which he wasn't wearing
when the police found him
trying to walk home...
oddly, from his own apartment.
- Pills.
- Your patient's doing fine.
Thanks to your team.
- It wasn't eosinophilic
pneumonitis, was it?
- Sarcoidosis.
- Good.
- House, please talk to me.
- I haven't
slept through the night
since Kutner killed himself.
- The wrestling
might have to wait.
I'm gonna tell your doctors
to repair your implant.
- And then
you ripped it out
rather than live with it
for a few days, even.
I'm your mother.
This is my call.
I don't know if I'm
making the right one.
But it's mine to make.
- Sleep well?
Subtitles by LeapinLar