(LEE GRUNTING)
(WOMAN CHATTERING ON PA)
LEE: Hey!
How long have I...
Blunt force trauma
to the head did
the fatal damage.
Since the accident,
he's had a continuous...
LEE: Can't get up.
What's wrong with
my legs?
Hey, someone talk to me!
Hey, you don't hear me
talking to you?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(SIGHS)
Great heart
for transplant.
LEE: Who?
My heart? Oh, God.
They don't know
I'm in here.
HOUSE: Hey, genius.
I think it violates
certain ethical laws
to rip the organs
out of a guy
that's still alive.
Possibly certain
law laws, too.
LEE: Thank you. Thank you.
Could you get back
in your bed, please,
Mr. House?
HOUSE: It's actually
Dr. House.
LEE: This guy's a doctor?
There's also
a Navy SEAL House,
but you're gonna
have to save up
for that one.
Really? Well,
that's interesting,
but you're here because
you crashed your motorcycle,
not because I need
a consult, so get
back in bed.
HOUSE: Scraped my elbow.
Just need a truckload
of Vicodin.
Whereas this guy...
He's brain dead.
LEE: No, I'm not!
So drop it.
HOUSE: See that?
KURTZ: Minimal brain waves
don't mean he's alive.
LEE: I am alive. I'm here.
Isoelectric EEG
for several hours,
no EEG response
to painful stimuli,
hot or cold.
What you're seeing
is random, barely
discernable.
HOUSE: I discerned it.
LEE: Listen to him. Please.
No. That's just
the amplifier's
internal noise level.
It's on increased
sensitivity.
LEE: No, no, no,
it's not! It's me.
HOUSE: Then why is
his eye following you?
LEE: Exactly.
Following motion is
an involuntary reflex.
LEE: No.
You're a doctor,
you should know
these things.
LEE: No, no. I'm not dead.
I need help. I'm here.
I also know about
locked-in syndrome.
And things are either
involuntary or voluntary.
Blink if you
can hear me.
LEE: I hear you.
Oh. This is
gonna be fun.
Eye movement
is deliberate.
Can you blink once
for yes, twice for no?
LEE: I hope so.
HOUSE: Square
root of nine?
He got that faster
than you. Brain is
fully functional.
LEE: Where's Molly?
Lee, you were
in an accident.
Lee, hit the brake.
Hit the brake.
You sustained
a traumatic injury
to your brain stem,
which has cut off
your brain's ability
to communicate with
the rest of your body.
LEE: Can you fix me?
Where's Molly?
You still have
movement in your eyes,
so we can get you
to a rehab facility
where they can teach you
how to communicate.
LEE: No, I can't be
stuck like this.
HOUSE: Unless the
crash didn't cause
the brain damage.
Maybe the brain
damage caused
the crash.
LEE: Yeah. I couldn't stop.
Why couldn't I stop?
Look at his palms.
No scrapes.
He didn't even try
to protect himself.
Suggests slowed
reflexes or
no reflexes.
You're not a doctor
in this hospital,
you are a patient.
LEE: Yeah. And you're
the guy who wants to
cut out my organs
and he's the guy
who doesn't.
Get me the scans.
Stroke, cancer,
even a simple infection,
anything that insults the
central pons could do this.
LEE: Then that means
I could be fixed.
KURTZ: You're giving
him false hope.
He needs to accept
what's happened
and work on making
the most of it.
LEE: Molly.
Hey.
LEE: Don't look at me
like that. That's not
making me feel better.
(SNIFFLING)
I love you.
I don't know how God is
gonna get us through this,
but he will.
Stop it,
I'm blushing.
KURTZ: What are
you doing?
Just looking for
some reading material
for the crapper.
These CTs...
Get back in your
bed. Come on.
The children are
in the waiting area.
Can I bring them in?
LEE: No. No, don't.
You don't wanna
see them?
LEE: I don't want them
having nightmares. I don't
wanna scare them, Molly.
You don't want
them to see you?
It's okay.
I understand.
(SIGHS)
You're gonna be
better soon enough.
LEE: You really
that sure?
Why are you so sure,
babe? How do you
get so sure?
FOREMAN: Are you okay?
HOUSE: Never better.
Here's your burger.
If you can't bring
Mohammed to Princeton,
bring Princeton to Mohammed.
It's my diagnostics posse.
Hot, dark and darker.
LEE: Talk about getting
me better, please.
What are you doing
up in Middletown?
LEE: Who cares?
Buying a Gibson
'57 Goldtop.
It's the guitar Duane
Allman used to play.
FOREMAN: Next to
the trauma, the most
likely causes of
a sudden onset of
locked-in syndrome
are basilar artery stroke
and brain hemorrhage.
CT was clean.
LEE: Man, those
fries look good.
FOREMAN: Certain
circulatory diseases.
Guy's an active bike
rider, his heart's fine.
A well-placed tumor
could explain it.
LEE: Jeez, is the last
thing I ate gonna be
the last thing I ate?
It could evade the CT,
and still show up on
an MRI with contrast.
LEE: It was
a melted PowerBar.
She's the smart one.
I just keep dark
and darker to
fill out the quota.
If we find it,
treat it, you
can be fine.
LEE: I never thought
I'd be praying for
a brain tumor,
but please, dear God.
If you're praying
in there, stop it
right now.
We'll get his doctor
to order an MRI.
HOUSE: His doctor's busy
teaching him how to blink
out "kill me" in Morse code.
Luckily, I found some
forms under the mattress.
KUTNER: Check it out,
they have those MRI
video goggles.
I heard these were awesome.
THIRTEEN: What do you see?
KUTNER: It's a beach.
Oh, look. There's Taub.
Drinking a margarita and
mocking us for driving all
the way up here
because House said "jump."
LEE: Easy. I can
still feel in here.
Excuse Dr. Kutner.
He gets a little excited
about new technology.
It can get loud in there,
and a little closed off.
These will put you
in a quiet place.
You can create
a relaxing scenario
for yourself.
LEE: I hope they work.
Wow.
You're in my
relaxing scenario?
I guess you like me.
Either that or
you got sent here.
What, by God?
I'm not sure if
I believe in God.
You spend an awful
lot of time in church
for someone who doesn't.
I don't not
believe either.
It's either one
or the other.
I go to church
to mainly keep my
wife happy, but...
I don't know.
I've never actually
thought that
God could reach out
and affect my life.
But getting a brilliant
doctor in the bed next
to me...
God is also the guy
who opened his car
door in front of you.
I think
Molly was right.
I think you were
sent here to make
me get better.
I think so.
Hey.
Hey, Dad.
Making a volcano.
Yeah. You're making
a volcano. Looks like it.
What you doing, baby?
(DOOR OPENING)
LEE: What time is it?
Hope you don't mind.
My new roommate snores.
And my new room
doesn't have you.
Your MRI showed
a lesion in the
central pons.
LEE: What is that?
What does that mean?
See it there?
LEE: No.
Yeah, that's
what they said.
But it's there,
which means no way
head trauma did this.
It's cancer, causing a
paraneoplastic syndrome.
Unfortunately, your
current doctor thinks
its diffused nature
means an infection.
Now, the bad news
is the antivirals
he's got you on
might kill you.
LEE: I'm not gonna die.
The good news is,
if they just almost
kill you,
then Dr. Idiot will
realize that his name
is not a coincidence,
and he'll let me
do whatever I want.
LEE: Thank you.
See, the irony here is,
you're kind of fascinating.
So many questions.
But if you could
answer any of them,
then you wouldn't
be fascinating.
LEE: I get it.
You're a little
nuts, aren't you?
Your wife is the one
getting you through this.
Your wife and me.
Although, frankly, the MRI
was a lot more useful than
four hours of hand holding.
I think.
LEE: If he had a wife,
he'd know it matters.
You're a good guy.
Easy to talk to.
LEE: Wait, something's
happening. What's
happening to me?
HOUSE: Need some
help in here.
Your patient is seizing.
Why would
he have a seizure?
HOUSE: Because he has cancer.
His brain stem
is compromised.
LEE: Why are you still
arguing with this guy?
You thought I was dead.
Welcome back.
And nicely played.
You almost died,
exactly as we planned.
You knew this
was gonna happen?
Usually happens when you
treat cancer by pretending
it's not cancer.
Right, Doctor?
My turn?
It's cancer?
No, it isn't.
LEE: Yes.
Small tumor in his
brain stem causing
paraneoplastic syndrome.
He needs plasmapheresis.
Can you give that to him?
No, no, I'm sorry.
I completely disagree
with Dr. House.
LEE: Please shut up!
I don't.
Which means
I can treat him.
LEE: Let him. Let him.
Is that what you want?
LEE: Absolutely.
Could you send up
a couple of bellboys?
(WOMAN CHATTERING ON PA)
I got the transfer
papers, plasmapheresis
is all set up.
Are you okay?
Fresh infusion of
macho. You like?
LEE: I can't move,
and she's worried
about his boo-boo?
What were you
doing up there
anyway?
Antiquing.
Found you a late
Victorian corset.
Come by later.
I'll tie you up.
LEE: He hitting on her?
If she turns around,
she's into him, too.
And there you have it.
Sorry, I didn't show up
in Middletown. I didn't
get the message.
Probably 'cause
there was no message.
I decided to accept
your resignation.
Uh, I thought
we were past this.
I decided to stay.
HOUSE: No, you didn't,
you had it decided
for you.
So now you're
stuck here
with a boss
who knows that
you wanna be
somewhere else.
Which means you're
no longer motivated
to impress me.
Which means you're
no longer motivated to
come up with good ideas.
Unless I'm wrong.
Save the cheerleader,
save your world.
I got it from here.
LEE: I thought you
already solved this.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
You thinking you
might be wrong?
What's going on?
Hey, just curious.
What're you driving
up to Middletown for?
Why do you care?
LEE: Why does he care?
Because I'm your friend.
I was
buying a guitar.
Yeah. I heard that.
Used to belong to
a guitarist who died in
a motorcycle accident.
Just reeks of you
screwing with people.
Your crash was 10 miles
from the Orange County
Progressive Pain Clinic.
You live 10 miles
from Mary's Dress Shop.
And yet,
that's not even on
my list of reasons
that I think you're
secretly a transvestite.
If you're going
to another state
to get more narcotics...
LEE: He's on drugs?
I went to visit
your ex-ex-ex wife...
LEE: What?
...who lives in
Thompson Ridge.
Let her know about the
extra money you're making
on the lecture circuit,
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
So she'll be sure to
adjust your alimony.
You wouldn't do that.
Yeah, I wouldn't do that.
Would you?
LEE: You guys
are friends?
Shouldn't we be
entertaining
our patient?
I performed Euripides
with sock puppets,
you just missed it.
House said we should.
The mind is like a muscle.
If you don't exercise it,
it'll atrophy, just like
anything else.
Whoever's with him
needs to talk, keep
his mind active.
And it'll show
House you still care.
Not sure if I do.
LEE: Jeez,
you're my doctor.
KUTNER: Then why
don't you just quit?
Not sure I want
to do that, either.
Oh.
Maybe you should figure it
out before House figures it
out for you.
LEE: Dude, maybe you
should have your midlife
crisis after I'm better.
Kutner.
We'll be right back.
LEE: Wait. Wait,
what did you just see?
Do you drink?
He's a roofer,
alcohol hardly
proves your theory.
Marchiafava-Bignami
disease fits.
LFT's are normal.
LEE: Speak English.
Is it fixable?
What does that mean?
That hurts.
THIRTEEN: No tremors.
How much do you drink?
A six-pack a day?
LEE: I hate beer.
I don't even drink beer.
Could mean
he drinks
more or less,
or maybe something else.
KUTNER: It may not
be alcohol at all.
Street opiates could
also cause locked-in...
LEE: I don't get high.
...MPPP.
Either we play
20,000 questions
with every street drug,
or instead of talking
to him, we talk to
the lesion.
LEE: Talk to me.
TAUB: We're going to
biopsy the brain stem?
For the record,
that doesn't count
as your inspired idea.
It's sort of
where I was heading.
LEE: You're gonna cut
into my head? Why?
Stop treating me like
a piece of furniture!
I have a right to
know what's going on!
Where is that going?
Blood in your urine
clogged up
your old catheter.
LEE: Peeing blood?
That must be what the
insecure doctor saw.
(LEE GRO ANING)
Every clue gets us
closer to the answer.
LEE: Damn it!
The surgery will
get us more clues.
You have visitors.
LEE: No. No, Molly.
You can come in now.
Daddy.
LEE: I told you
not to bring them.
They wanted to
see their father.
LEE: I can't
even hug them.
They can handle it.
It's gonna be all right.
LEE: You're not so sure
any more, are you?
They must have told you
that it's dangerous,
that I could die.
And that's why you
brought them in here.
I got an A plus
on my test.
LEE: To see me
before I die.
I love you, Daddy.
LEE: Daddy loves you, too.
I want to show
my drawings.
LEE: Kids just want a dad.
Even if he's just a lump.
Maybe you should go now.
LEE: Oh no, they can stay.
Please, let them stay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Bye, Daddy.
Sorry. You were crying.
LEE: Damn.
We're going to put
you out, just so we
can drill the hole.
LEE: Oh, that's very
thoughtful of you.
Then we'll wake
you back up.
We need you to answer
some simple "yes"
or "no" questions
while we're cutting
to make sure
we're not cutting
where we shouldn't.
LEE: Seems to be working.
Deep breaths. In about
10 seconds, you will
feel light headed.
By now, you should
be floating high...
(ALL LAUGHING)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
How come I'm not better?
God's not supposed to
work in trial and error.
God's mistakes
are well documented.
If he'd done everything
right the first time,
there'd have been
one plague and
zero great floods.
Those were because
of human mistakes.
You think your doctor
has an apartment on
Mount Olympus?
God put me with
you for a reason.
I'm gonna be all
right still, right?
I don't know.
Lee?
You with me now?
Easy questions.
You'll be done
before you know it.
Is this equation correct?
LEE: What? So if
you make a mistake,
I'm not gonna
know that any more?
Are these lines
parallel?
Spatial relationship's
intact.
Take a look
at this circle.
Is more than
half of it shaded?
LEE: Of course.
Don't forget to blink.
Is more than half
of the circle shaded?
LEE: Sorry. Yes.
Look at me, Lee.
Again. Is more
than half of this
circle shaded?
Blink. Come on,
Lee. Blink.
Foreman, back out.
LEE: I can't blink.
Cannot blink.
MOLLY: Why aren't
his eyes moving?
HOUSE: Two options, my
neurologist screwed up,
or else something that
the hospital lawyer
is going to have
to come up with
when you sue us.
FOREMAN: Blinking and eye
movements are controlled by
a small cluster of nerves
just millimeters
from the biopsy site.
MOLLY: But he's still in
there, right? I mean, he
just can't communicate?
HOUSE: It's possible.
Also possible is that
the surgery caused so much
swelling in his brain stem
that he's just gone.
He had one way to
communicate and now
that's gone. Well played.
Brain biopsy revealed severe
damage to the myelin sheath.
The question is why.
Epstein Barr.
Picornaviruses.
Malaria.
He runs a business, meets
a lot of people, could have
picked up rotavirus.
Did he report
having bloody
diarrhea?
Wife's not sure.
Says he doesn't
complain.
Did you ask him?
THIRTEEN: We prioritized.
He can only blink,
a real history
would've taken weeks.
If he had Epstein-Barr,
he'd have belly pains.
If he had picornavirus,
he'd have headaches.
Five other
"yeslno" questions,
and maybe we'd know
what treatment to give,
and what treatment
would kill him.
Unless he's already dead.
Maybe there's another way.
Brain-computer interface,
better known as BCI.
The goal is to get you
to move that cursor
with your mind.
When you think "up",
the computer records
the pattern.
Think "up" enough times,
it eventually learns
what you're thinking.
So, start thinking "up."
You in there?
Are you trying?
(SIGHING)
I called the
ex-ex-ex-wife.
She was at a sweat lodge
in New Mexico last week.
What were you
really doing
in New York?
Know how you hate
it when I meddle
in your lies?
(EXCLAIMS)
I mean, your life?
Why are you
being so evasive?
Unless you have
something to evade.
Interesting.
So it's nothing to do
with you, your ex-wife,
or my pain.
I was heading to the
Downstate Correctional
Facility in Fishkill.
One of your hookers
arrange a conjugal visit?
It's where Foreman's
brother is being held.
(TAUB SIGHING)
This is gonna mean
months of sleepless
nights wondering
if I could've done
something differently.
Maybe it's not that
I'm sick of House,
it's that I'm sick
of being scared
out of my mind to
go to work every day.
Sorry.
(MACHINE BEEPS)
Did that just...
Was that you?
(MACHINE BEEPS)
(CRYING)
Are you really in there?
(LAUGHS)
I knew you were in there.
LEE: I was scared.
Thank God.
(SIGHING)
LEE: I am scared.
Molly, I love you so much.
Have you had any
bloody diarrhea in
the last two weeks?
(BEEPING "NO")
Rotavirus out.
Any recent joint pain?
(BEEPING "NO")
Epstein-Barr's out.
Have you traveled out
of the country lately?
What about inside
the country?
(CONTINUES BEEPING "NO")
He was in St. Louis.
Good.
Could be Missouri malaria.
We'll start treatment.
(BEEPS "NO")
(STAMMERS)
He was there.
The machine must
not be working.
Hmm.
Either that or
he lied to you
about it.
People do
that sometimes.
For example,
I just lied to him
about Missouri malaria.
Did you go
to St. Louis?
LEE: I should've told you.
Why didn't I just tell you?
Down.
(MACHINE BEEPS "NO")
When you weren't in
St. Louis for two days,
I assume you were
getting some strange
for two days.
LEE: So does she.
(MACHINE BEEPS "NO")
You have to tell
her I wasn't.
Amazing.
A man who only has two
blips at his disposal
can still lie.
LEE: I'm not lying.
If you were getting some
really strange strange,
you could have
contracted neurosyphilis.
Infection went to your
brain, froze you right up.
Good news is,
it's treatable.
You'll be up and moving
in time to sign
the divorce papers.
LEE: Why would I tell
you the truth about
being in St. Louis
(MACHINE BEEPS "NO")
And then not tell you
the truth about this?
TAUB: He just admitted
he wasn't in St. Louis
in front of his wife.
And you think he's lying
when she's not even in here?
LEE: I'm liking this
one more and more.
Don't fire him.
Were you out
of the state?
(MACHINE BEEPS "NO")
LEE: I never left.
Were you within 20
miles of your house?
(MACHINE BEEPS "YES")
LEE: Yes.
HOUSE: Were you
within five miles?
LEE: Yes.
Within two miles?
Yes.
Did you stay at a hotel?
No.
You had to sleep
somewhere. Your car?
No.
A friend's house?
Yes.
That narrows it down,
depending on how
popular you are.
Tell the wife to stop
crying, get in here.
He says that
when he was supposed
to be in St. Louis,
he was staying at
a friend's house.
Really?
Yes.
Let's assume that
you believe him
for the moment.
Name your friends
within two miles.
Martin and Kim's?
No.
Guess someone who
doesn't have a wife.
Dave?
Yes.
You got an address?
TAUB: If this is where he
got sick, someone else here
should have symptoms.
Not if Lee was the
only one coming down
to the basement.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Furnace is rusty
but no gas leaks.
R?sum?s and
cover letters here.
Some are weeks old,
he's been spending
time here for a while.
Business wasn't
going good.
I didn't want you
and the kids to worry.
I was trying
to protect you.
Molly...
I wish you
could hear me.
I wish I could make
all of this better.
Looks like he
temped a few times.
As a janitor.
Factory out on
Route 10.
(METALLIC CLANGING)
TAUB: The factory
foreman says they make
rechargeable batteries,
mostly for cell phones.
Big step down from
running your own business
to sweeping up.
Doing what
I had to do.
KUTNER: Metal filings.
Judging by the color,
I'd say cadmium.
Which he'd aerosolize
with the broom, then
right into his lungs.
Heavy metal poisoning
explains everything.
The chelation will
scrub the heavy metals
out of your blood.
If we're right
about the cause,
we should see some
movement in about
a day or so.
LEE: Can you put
this thing on turbo?
(EXHALING)
Getting a little
anxious in here.
Somebody will be
here at all times
to irrigate your eyes,
keep you company.
Hopefully help make
the time go quicker.
LEE: My eyes still
feel really dry.
Thank you for
thinking "up".
For helping me
find you in there.
Man, when you
moved that cursor...
(CHUCKLES)
Bought my first
girlfriend a necklace,
it was silver.
Cost 180 bucks.
Had to save for
six months.
She hated it.
LEE: Really, seriously,
would you tell this story
to someone who
could walk away?
Never bought
another girlfriend
jewelry again.
Until Dr. Hadley.
LEE: You're dating her?
You might want to start
all your stories with that.
Same thing.
She didn't
even wear it.
LEE: The diamond thing?
She was wearing it
the other day.
If she doesn't like it,
she doesn't like it.
Apparently, I suck at
picking out jewelry,
but at least have
the guts to tell me.
LEE: Okay, getting
boring again.
How long till we know
if this treatment is
working?
You lied to me.
LEE: I wasn't
having an affair!
So, we needed
money, who cares?
LEE: The last time business
was slow, you got migraines
every day.
Why would you
do that to me?
LEE: I'm sorry,
I was stupid, I was...
(SIGHS)
Don't go. Don't...
Damn it! Somebody put
"I'm sorry" on
this stupid computer.
My eye is killing me.
I want to keep my job.
Great. All you gotta
do is come up with
a good idea.
How about we hook the guy's
brain to a computer
so he can communicate?
That's a great idea.
For the guy who
invented the computer
that can read minds.
Your idea was
to use his idea.
You didn't come up
with it. No one else
came up with it.
If I didn't re-establish
communication, we never
would have found...
What's interesting is
why you're here now.
Not when I gave
you the ultimatum.
Was it something
the patient said?
I realized that what
we do here terrifies me.
And overcoming that
is the only way
I can matter.
Kutner found the battery
factory, Kutner came up
with cadmium.
Maybe you don't matter.
I'm gonna close your eyes
so you can get some sleep.
Hopefully, when you wake up,
we'll see some improvement.
LEE: Hope that includes
my eye feeling better.
Hand me the
fluorescein stain.
LEE: What does
that mean?
Epithelium looks torn.
These drops sting.
I'm going to close
your left eye to
keep it protected.
(LEE GRO ANING)
I'm gonna blink
your eye a few times
to distribute the dye.
Ulcerative keratitis.
It means it's not
cadmium poisoning.
LEE: Which means you
don't know what's wrong.
Again.
When was the last
time you changed
that dressing?
Judging by the smell
of it, I'd say never.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SIGHING)
He's locked-in,
his kidneys blew
a fuse,
and now his eye's
oozing pus.
I assume you went
over all that with
your team.
Also assume
they didn't have
any brilliant ideas
or you wouldn't
still be muttering
to yourself.
This is gonna hurt.
Ow!
The way he's
losing his myelin
makes an infection
most likely.
Could be varicella.
Road debris has come to
the surface. I'm gonna
have to scrub it out.
And the initial
acyclovir would've
treated that.
Which pushes me towards
an auto-immune disease.
Like Behcet's.
Here, this is gonna
hurt even more.
Take two now,
two later.
Oops.
(SIGHING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(EXHALING)
Of course, if
the varicella
was resistant,
it wouldn't matter
what they did
up in Middletown.
Do an LP.
You've been in
the ER too long.
When the patient
had a head trauma,
white blood cells only
indicate that he had
head trauma.
Or you could use the LP
for something useful.
If you find polys,
it's varicella,
lymph's, Behcet's.
Why did I fire
you again?
You didn't. I quit.
You weren't visiting
Foreman's brother either.
Busy. Kutner's doing
an LP so I have to focus.
I had prison security
check visitor logs,
phone records,
you've never had any
contact with anyone
at Fishkill.
(CHUCKLES)
So I ask again,
what were you
doing up in
Middletown?
You know what's more
interesting than
what I was doing?
The reason you are
so obsessed with
what I was doing.
Stop deflecting, House.
Says the deflector.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
The reason I was up there
is the reason you're scared
I was up there.
I was checking out
your dirty little secret.
How long have you
been sleeping with her?
(EXCLAIMS)
How did you know?
Your only secrets are
the girls you find
embarrassing.
And the only
embarrassing girl
you've met recently
is the one at
your brother's
cuckoo facility.
We've only been
out a few times.
She's a caregiver.
Like all your
other failed exes.
(SIGHING)
And someone who takes
care of your brother.
Say, who was the last
person that took care
of your brother?
(LAUGHING)
You think
this is oedipal?
Actually I was
thinking masturbatory,
but I guess your mom
took care of him first.
So the safe course
is to gouge
your eyes out.
(SIGHING)
LP stands for
lumbar puncture.
We use this needle
to collect fluid
from your spine.
LEE: That's
a really big needle.
You're going to
feel some extreme
pressure in your back.
I already feel
pressure in my front.
My chest hurts.
...sort of
a fetal position...
LEE: Something's wrong.
...the best angle
into your spine.
LEE: (SLURS)
No, my chest.
(MACHINE BEEPING CONTINUOUSLY)
Something's wrong.
I think I'm...
FOREMAN: Pull the needle out!
LEE: Oh, God, I'm flatlining.
Call a Code.
(DEFIBRILLATOR CHARGING)
There is no God.
You don't know
what's wrong with me.
Doesn't seem that way.
So am I dead?
Not yet.
(EKG ALARM BLARING)
But you're about to be.
LEE: Okay.
Charging. Clear.
Again. Clear.
He's back.
LEE: No. No. Let me go.
HOUSE: The arrest means
the demyelination
hit the area
in his brainstem
that controls heart rhythm.
LEE: You can't fix me.
I've been here
for three days.
We need answers fast,
'cause this is
going to happen again.
LEE: Everything hurts.
We need to get him
started on steroids.
LEE: It's okay.
Just stop fighting.
HOUSE: Not without
the results of the LP.
LEE: She's gotta go
on with her life.
The kids don't need this.
I can't do nothing for
them. I can't.
God, this foot. Oh,
that really, really itches.
So we put in a
temporary pacer,
it's not gonna...
Shut up! Shut up!
(MACHINE BEEPING)
He's trying to talk.
Something
bothering you?
If there's still
tightness in your
chest, it's expected.
Is it your eye?
(MACHINE BEEPS THREE TIMES)
Why's he saying "no"
three times? You only
asked one question.
Maybe he's not
saying "no".
Maybe he's
saying "down"?
Are you saying that
the pain is lower?
How low? Your leg?
(MACHINE BEEPS "NO")
Your foot?
Left foot?
(MACHINE BEEPS "NO")
Check his...
Let me see now.
Yeah. His right foot.
No bruises,
no rashes,
no cuts.
Then there should
be no pain.
Is it a tingling
sensation?
Is it itching?
(MACHINE BEEPS "YES")
Ltchy foot means
liver failure.
TAUB: The liver's fine,
his enzymes have been normal
since we admitted him.
I didn't say failing,
I said failure.
Just like you.
Liver's like a cruise
ship taking on water.
As it starts to sink,
it sends out an SOS.
Only instead of radio
waves, it uses enzymes.
The more enzymes in
the blood, the worse
the liver is.
But once the ship has sunk,
there's no more SOS.
You think the liver's fine,
but it's already at
the bottom of the sea.
So dying liver
released toxins,
damaged the nerves,
led to locked-in
syndrome.
Now we just need to
know what's causing
the liver failure.
Liver plus eye plus
kidney, most likely
sclerosing cholangitis.
Oh, God, if only
Taub had said that,
it would have
been a happy ending.
Do a biopsy to confirm.
I'm gonna numb up the
area where we'll go in
for the punch biopsy.
Where's the new bracelet?
She was wearing
the bracelet?
You didn't notice
that I was wearing it?
Because you weren't.
He noticed
and you didn't?
If you don't like it,
it's fine, it's not
a big deal.
THIRTEEN: I like it.
That's the point.
I'd rather have it at home
in the jewelry box than
getting peed on at work.
You got the patient's
urine on that arm?
When I was putting
in the catheter. Why?
You've got a rash.
The bracelet's real.
I figured.
So what if the rash
isn't just a rash,
what if it's an infection?
If there were rats
in that basement,
then the liver failure
could be caused by
leptospirosis.
Transfers through urine.
Rat pee to him.
His pee to you.
The infection would
need an entry point.
Look for any recent
scratches, cuts.
Look. Next to
his fingernail.
The infection
destroyed your liver,
which released toxins
that caused the
locked-in syndrome.
You were dying
of a paper cut.
LEE: I hope you're
right this time.
Let's start him on
high dose penicillin G.
We found rats in your
buddy, Dave's basement.
Tested positive
for leptospirosis.
Means we're on
the right treatment.
So try moving
a finger.
Your brain needs
to get used to
doing its job again.
Try harder.
I'm sure you've lost hope.
I know we've told you
several times that
we knew what this was,
but this time we're right.
Concentrate. Move
one finger for me.
Welcome back.
(LEE LAUGHS)
LEE: I did it.
Rat pee.
Very nice idea.
Who came up with it?
I did.
Good.
You okay with him
claiming the credit?
It was his idea,
he saw the rash, he...
If he did,
he would have hung
a "Mission Accomplished"
banner in my outer office.
Don't toy with him,
if you're going
to fire him...
Fact that he stole your
idea means that he cares
enough to lie.
That's all
I needed to know.
Rat pee.
It's a very nice idea.
House, you left
this in my office.
No, I didn't.
So either I have
a hole in my pocket...
No, that's right.
I remember now.
I stole it.
Because if you had
gone up there to check
out my girlfriend,
you wouldn't have come
back here and lied to
me about it.
You would have thrown
her right in my face.
You underestimate the
entertainment value of
your obsessions.
And then there were all
those calls you weren't
taking in front of me.
So I dialed the number
of the calls you
weren't taking.
You're seeing
a psychiatrist.
You had no right to
invade my privacy.
Is that?
Yeah, it's irony.
(TAPE WHIRRING)
Hey.
God sent you.
Suddenly, you're not
so fascinating.
WILSON: You're spying
on your team?
Prioritize, Wilson.
Is that really what
you want to torture me
about right now?
I don't want to torture
you at all. I think
this is a great thing,
not something you have
to drive an hour out of
town to shroud in mystery.
Yeah, whining on
someone's couch
is an excellent
use of my time.
Maybe I'll discover
that my childhood
wasn't perfect.
So your attitude
about therapy clearly
hasn't changed.
And yet you went.
Which leads me to believe
that maybe something else
has changed.
Maybe you think you
can change. Credit
Cuddy with that.
Not much credit to
take 'cause I'm not
going back.
Oh, House, please.
I assume you went
because you're tired
of screwing up
every chance you
get at happiness.
View contact.
Delete contact.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Do not let the fact
that I found out about it...
(SIGHS) Don't beat
yourself up.
I'm not going back
because it doesn't work.
You'll end up alone.