It's okay, Eileen.
I got this.
- Are you sure?
Yeah. You get home.
Thanks, Danny.
See you in the morning.
- I'll be here.
[sighs]
[knock at door]
[door rattling]
[knocking continues]
[sighs deeply]
Food's gone, Daryl.
We're closed.
You wouldn't happen to have an
extra coat in there, would you?
You're wearing a coat.
A winter coat, man.
It's cold.
Come on.
Here.
Rangers?
You expect me to
wear this in Jersey?
Come on, man,
where's your sense of humor?
Good night, Daryl.
[mellow rock music]
# #
[knock at door]
Go away.
[sniffs]
[knocking continues]
That's not funny, freak.
No one is laughing,
Daniel.
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
# #
You doing
anything Friday?
Taking a lovely young lady
to the philharmonic.
That your way of saying
you're having sex with a hooker?
Two. Can't create a harmonic
with just one.
Well, I was hoping
you might available
for Rachel's Simchat bat.
It's a...
Jewish baby-naming
ceremony,
a time-honored tradition dating
all the way back to the 1960s.
My house at 7:00.
It'll just be the Rabbi
and a few friends
and some family.
Nothing like welcoming a baby
into the world
with a completely naked display
of hypocrisy.
There'll be plenty
of wine
and nice people
you can quietly mock.
Wish I could, but I already
put down a deposit
on 16 crates of jell-o.
House...
It's one evening.
I'd like you to be there.
Religious hokum,
get sponge bath.
Can I get back to you?
Can I help you?
Just browsing.
Thanks.
Happy to be
underachieving again?
Running the E.R.
is slacker heaven.
Looking for anything
in particular?
Not anymore.
Where's this guy?
Why?
'Cause he's
my next patient.
It'd be rude of me
not to introduce myself.
He's a drunk priest
who hallucinated Jesus.
Afraid you might have
missed something?
Afraid you're
everyone's time?
It's obviously either alcohol
or exhaustion.
So you admit
you have no idea which?
I admit that I'm too busy to
care who you're screwing with.
Don't thank me.
Just knowing I can be
of assistance
is thanks enough.
(Taub) You went out of your way
to pick him?
This is nothing.
There are no small cases.
Any guesses
where this joke is going?
Could be
psychomotor epilepsy...
(Taub)
Could be alcohol.
Shouldn't we let the E.R.
rule the obvious out--
Could be atropine toxicity,
occipital lobe tumor.
You know something about this
case you're not telling us?
Why would you think that?
'Cause you want to screw
with us.
Or screw
with a hallucinating priest.
Both are possible.
There's only one way
to find out.
Run an E.E.G.
for epilepsy.
C.T. his brain for tumors.
And go check
his House of God
for toxins.
Fourteen, hold up.
[cane thuds]
This department is broken,
And I'm not gonna take
a real case
until it's fixed.
Job or relationship--
your choice.
What?
- To put it in terms
you might better understand,
If you don't split,
you must quit.
The drug trial is over.
I'm out, she's out.
Don't care.
- We're adults. We can handle this.
You just have to give us a chance.
- No, you're not.
No, you can't.
And no, I don't.
Mull it over.
You got until the end
of this fake case
to decide.
I wasn't drunk.
I had one or two drinks.
People often underestimate
alcohol's effect on their--
I was on my way to six.
I know how alcohol affects me.
This wasn't the alcohol.
(Kutner) You lived in Manhattan
for three years.
Then a year in Oregon,
18 months
in new Mexico,
less than a year
in Wisconsin,
and now you've been living
in Trenton
for the last six months.
Yep.
The more we know about you,
the more likely
it is we can help you.
Mm, it's not
medically relevant, so--
No way to know unless you went
to medical school.
[sighs deeply]
Four years ago, a teen
in a youth group at my church
accused me of inappropriate contact.
I was innocent,
but the church decided
to transfer me.
Said it would be easier
for all involved.
When the parishioners
at the new church
got wind
of why I'd been transferred,
they were unhappy.
I was sent off again and again,
and how is any of that
medically relevant?
So the kid lied?
He was confused.
Confused whether
you molested him or not?
Okay, you wanted to know
why I moved around so much
and I told you.
How about telling me
why I was hallucinating?
Syphilis
could explain
the hallucination.
I'm not sexually active.
You don't have to admit
you did anything with the kid.
You weren't always a priest.
I wanted to be since I was 12.
I entered the seminary
when I was 17.
Maybe it wasn't
a hallucination.
Maybe it really was Jesus.
I'm not insane.
(Kutner) Seeing Jesus
makes you insane?
A bit of an odd attitude
coming from a priest.
Well, it's just a job now.
The fairy tale
ended a long time ago.
You're a wuss--
part wimp, part puss.
I have no choice.
I'm part of the ceremony.
I thought you were already
circumcised.
It's one night for a friend.
What about the friend
who has two tickets
to see Brubeck at the blue note?
I thought you had an orgy planned.
I lied.
Are you lying
about the Brubeck tickets?
Yes, but only to save you
from yourself.
I'll be fine and so will Cuddy
if you don't show up.
I'm surprised she even invited you.
It is oddly flattering.
God, I'm so sick
of his stupid stunts.
Everybody has to put up
with their boss's stupid stunts.
No, they don't.
There's H.R. there're Cuddy.
- There's other jobs.
House doesn't listen to H.R.
Cuddy will let him fire us
before she fires him,
and I don't want another job.
Why do you cling to him?
Why do you defend him?
Just because I don't want
to be unemployed
doesn't mean I'm codependent.
I'm not saying
you're codependent.
I'm saying you're scared.
[sighs]
You know what?
You're right.
So you want to quit?
No, I want to stop
a stupid stunt.
House doesn't want
either one of us to quit.
He wants this.
He's got two lab rats in a maze
and thrown in one piece of cheese.
[chuckles]
S--so what do we do?
Nothing.
(House)
Cool.
It's cool he's a child molester?
It's cool the priest
doesn't believe in God.
It's cool that God did to him
what he did to the kid.
Allegedly.
You think he's innocent?
- He had honest eyes?
And you think he's guilty,
Which explains why you're dying
to discharge him.
I'm dying to discharge him
because he's not sick,
not because he's a pedophile.
- Allegedly.
You actually believe
the kid got confused?
If everybody lies,
that includes teenage boys.
(House) Aren't we lucky to have
such an interesting patient?
Had--there's nothing wrong
with him.
The world's most boring case
just became a page turner.
You want to tear out
the last chapter?
You want to examine
his character,
go to a soup kitchen.
We are done testing him
for things he doesn't have.
[elevator bell dings]
Bad news
for Foreman and Thirteen.
(House)
Case is over.
We're not splitting up.
So which one of you
is taking a hike?
- And neither of us is quitting.
Interesting.
You were fine
with Chase and Cameron dating.
You obviously don't
actually have an issue--
You're fired.
How long are you
gonna keep this up?
We know you're not--
Wrong...
Again.
In fact,
in the last few weeks,
it's hard to remember
a correct call you made.
If Chase had compromised
his professional judgment
to help Cameron,
I'd have fired his ass, too.
When my mistake
blew up,
you did everything to keep me
from contacting
the drug company.
To save your license,
not your job
and definitely not your relationship.
So, badge.
Fine.
[drawer closes]
Why don't you see
if you can find us a real case?
How can you discharge me when
you have no idea what's wrong?
We know what's wrong,
and now that
you've slept it off...
[sighs]
It's not just a hallucination.
I feel nauseous.
My foot feels numb
like it's fallen asleep.
You didn't mention that before.
I didn't notice it before.
Are you hiding from someone?
Why are you so intent
on staying here?
I don't feel well.
I know there's
something wrong with me.
Which foot?
My left.
Oh, God.
What the hell is that?
What is that?
Your toe just fell off.
Must be my lucky day.
New symptom means the old
symptom was a real symptom,
and I get to keep
our pederast priest after all.
Where are Foreman and Thirteen?
They left.
Leprosy can cause necrosis
and hallucination.
Why would they leave?
Because Foreman
doesn't work here anymore,
and Thirteen is mad
that I fired him.
Don't worry.
She'll be back.
She'll be pissed off.
She'll want to take a stand.
And then Foreman
will convince her
that there's no reason both
of them should be out of a job.
Leprosy's a bad fit.
Why'd you fire Foreman?
- I gave him a choice--
split or quit.
He chose neither.
What about ergotism?
He's giving up his career
for her?
He's giving up
this career for her.
No, normal
white blood count.
Carbon monoxide poisoning?
They're good doctors.
Separately, they're great doctors,
better than you.
Together,
they're morons.
Go check out the house
that they would've checked
had this been a real case.
And page Thirteen.
Tell her to run the blood
for C-O.
And get the priest
in a hyperbaric chamber
before anything else
falls off.
So what are we gonna do now?
I get a letter
of recommendation from Cuddy
and find a new job.
Oh, that's it?
You're just gonna give up?
House is right.
Our relationship
did affect my judgment.
Then I should quit.
It'll be easier for me
to find another job.
Not like this one.
[sighs]
We should both quit.
What's that gonna accomplish?
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
We'll be fine.
[pager beeping]
Go ahead.
I'll see you tonight?
I'll be home early.
[chuckles]
(Kutner) You really think House
is done with Foreman?
(Taub) If you ask me, Foreman
should be done with Thirteen.
He's not gonna get a better job,
Which means
he'll end up resenting her
for losing this one,
which she'll end up resenting.
Or the hardship'll bring 'em
closer together.
She'll invite friends over
for Foreman to share.
No leaks in the heater.
(Taub)
She's not a nympho.
She's bisexual,
which, by the way,
means she's accustomed to
partners who don't need a map
to find the treasure.
C-O poisoning might have come
from these cigarettes.
Not unless he was smoking them
in a bell jar.
And even if you know
where the treasure is,
it can still be pretty hard
to dig it up without a shovel.
You can buy a shovel.
[clears throat]
Let's see...
how do I keep House
from ruining my precious display
of religious hypocrisy?
I know, I'll pressure him
to attend,
knowing that he'll never agree
to anything
I actually want him to do.
I didn't pressure you.
I invited you.
And there's nothing hypocritical
about recognizing your heritage.
So you keeping Kosher now,
Wearing four-cornered garments,
Slaughtering heifers to the God Ra?
Wait, is that one your people?
Do it all, do nothing,
or option "c"--
you're a liar and a hypocrite.
House...
for better or for worse,
you are a part of my life.
It isn't a ploy.
It's a sincere invitation.
I honestly want you to come.
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
I'm glad.
You idiot.
I was free and clear.
Now he's coming,
and it's your fault.
Since when have
your failed attempts
at communication through lies
become my fault?
Since you forgot
how to keep your mouth shut.
You messed it up,
and now you're gonna fix it.
And you're gonna keep
my name out of it.
(Kutner)
How is he?
Stable. Necrosis doesn't look
to be spreading.
I was talking about Foreman.
(Kutner)
Is he really gonna leave?
That's usually what people do
when they get fired.
Why are you biting my head off?
I was just wondering
what he was gonna do.
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's not
House's fault either.
He gave you guys a chance,
you blew it.
Uh, he didn't give us a chance,
he gave us an ultimatum.
I would've thought five years
here would buy a mistake or two.
[banging on glass]
Help me!
[motors whirring]
I can't breathe!
Feels like
something's on my chest!
Looks like a heart attack.
[gasping]
[knock at door]
I assume you've heard.
I can't override him.
I'm not asking you
to override him.
I'm asking for a letter
of recommendation.
Eric,
House should've fired you.
You falsified medical records,
Put this hospital's reputation
in jeopardy.
You're lucky
you still have a license.
I can't get a decent position
at another hospital
without a recommendation.
I'm sorry.
Chest pain wasn't angina.
EKG ruled out heart attack.
So the good news is,
he didn't have a heart attack.
The bad news is,
I apparently fired the only guy
who actually knows
what a heart attack looks like.
[mug thuds]
So the man of God
who doesn't believe in God
had a heart attack
that isn't a heart attack.
Do I know how to pick
awesome cases or what?
(House)
Could be a clotting disorder.
Three different symptoms,
three different clots?
I know.
How cool is that?
You two do an angio.
You don't want to work,
so why don't you
just go get me
A lottery ticket?
The sicker he gets,
the luckier I feel.
Where are you going?
I've been wanting
to introduce myself.
Are you really a virgin?
You have to treat me.
You don't have to believe me.
And before we treat you,
we have to diagnose you.
Not knowing
whether we can believe you
is making that difficult.
Everything I've told you is true.
You lost your faith
because a teenager
got confused?
And the church abandoned me,
and my God forsook me,
and I couldn't come up
with a reason
why God would do that.
(Kutner) God gave the church
and the kid free will.
Their exercise
of that free will hurt you.
Means you're just a victim
of God's gift to mankind.
- Oh, yeah.
God wants life to have meaning.
Life's meaningless
without free will.
With free will,
there's always suffering.
So God wants suffering.
I got tired of that argument
before I even finished
saying it.
And even
if I bought that,
what the hell is God doing?
Just the big stuff?
The acts of God, the hurricanes,
the earthquakes,
the random killings of millions
of innocent people.
Then we better damn pray.
God, I wish you weren't
a pedophile.
(Taub)
Lungs are clean.
No embolism.
No pleurisy,
no pneumonia.
I'm sorry.
This is gonna hurt.
No, it's fine.
(Kutner)
No pain at all?
No.
Why?
Because there should be.
You feel that?
No.
Regional anesthesia
is a new symptom.
Not if the chest pain
is related to the numbness.
It's not circulatory.
It's neurological.
Run a nerve-conduction study.
And be careful.
If you kill him, he'll be
dancing with the dark one.
(Wilson)
Why the hell are you going
to Cuddy's baby naming?
It's a religious ceremony.
It's boring.
Why waste a good evening
that could be much better spent
in a drunken stupor
feeling sorry for yourself?
Okay.
Okay?
Okay, you won't go?
Okay, your obligation
to Cuddy is fulfilled.
[groans]
Why are you doing this?
Why did Hillary conquer Everest?
You always have a reason.
It's usually a bad one,
but a reason.
She's being childish.
See, that's an example
from the bad category.
Is it resentment?
The stork brought home
a new baby,
and you don't want
to share mommy?
Or you just can't stand
to see others happy?
She's trying to play me.
If I let her succeed,
the terrorists win.
[sighs]
[both talking indistinctly]
I heard there might be
an opening in the E.R.
Foreman's a neurologist.
That's not where he--
I did an E.R. rotation
in Miami.
If I can find another position,
I figure House
will rehire Foreman.
Don't quit.
Cuddy wouldn't give Foreman
a recommendation.
He's not gonna
be able to find
a decent job.
Foreman shouldn't leave either.
You think they should split up?
Office romances
are a bad idea.
We beat some very long odds.
Wow, why don't you save
the gushy stuff for the wedding?
House is playing with you.
If you let him get away
with it,
he's not gonna respect
you anyway.
Or House is helping you.
He knows it probably
won't work out.
And he's actually
doing you a favor.
Yeah, that sounds
a lot more like House.
I know they're looking
for someone at Mercy.
I'll make a call.
(Bresson)
Your boss always like that?
Usually worse.
Finding a fellow atheist
always makes his day.
[chuckles] Think it's possible
maybe God's testing your faith?
No, I already failed.
There'd be no point
in what he's doing to me now.
[machine beeping]
Got something.
Looks like intercostal neuralgia.
(Bresson)
What's that?
Something's traumatizing
one of the nerves
that runs along your ribs.
Explains the chest pain
and numbness.
Could also cause
muscle atrophy.
Does it do
anything to the eyes?
Why?
What's wrong?
Are you seeing Jesus again?
I'm seeing nothing.
My right eye went blind.
(Taub)
Ophthalmological exam's normal.
Nothing structurally wrong
with the eye.
(Kutner)
His heart rate's down.
Sensory loss is becoming
more diffuse,
progressive muscle weakness--
he's shutting down.
It's got to be
something systemic,
like autoimmune.
CSF was clear
for Guillain-Barre.
Cancer?
(Taub)
Imaging studies
Have been clear
for tumors.
Then that leaves infection.
He'd be brimming
with white blood cells.
(House) Or we are
at the backstage door
of a Duran Duran concert.
Hundreds of screaming girls
clustered around.
What does that mean?
That girls like rock bands.
The presence of the fans
indicates the presence
of the band.
Different night--
same band, same door.
Now there's not a girl in sight.
What does that mean?
Sorry, I don't speak hair band.
They weren't a hair band.
They were new romantics.
The band already left?
Nope, the band's still there,
still rocking out.
The absence of the fans
not indicate the absence of the band?
When it's 2009.
There aren't
any Duran Duran fans.
They don't make them anymore.
If there's
it's because there aren't
any fans, no white cells.
You think his spleen?
Why do I bother
with these great metaphors
if i still have
to spell it out?
Yes, I think it's his spleen.
Go get a biopsy.
I'll try to get
New Moon on Monday
out of my head.
Why are you talking this time?
If I quit,
will you rehire Foreman?
Why?
He can't find another job.
I can.
And you're willing to make
that sacrifice for him?
Yes.
Does Foreman know about this plan?
Well, if he's okay with it,
who am I to say no?
(Kutner)
Hold still.
Mm.
You think it's my spleen?
That's what they're testing.
So if I happen to cure you,
what happens then?
You start thinking that God
was working through me?
This is some sort of miracle?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
That's what I'm testing.
Losing my faith
wasn't a choice I made.
It happened.
It's gone for good.
(House) But if it can
magically disappear,
it can magically reappear,
And that's what you're hoping.
Your job...
- Sucks.
That's my point.
You can make more money
frapping decafs,
and yet you're still ministering
to the meek.
Why do the Lord's work if
the Lord has left the building?
I've been with the church
my entire adult life.
It's my only marketable skill.
I detect the stink
of leftover faith.
You want to talk hypocrisy,
what about you?
You act like you don't care
about anyone,
but here you are
Saving lives.
Solving puzzles.
Saving lives
is just collateral damage.
Yeah, nice try.
I don't think you're looking
for somebody
to prove you right.
I think you're looking
for somebody to prove you wrong,
to give you hope.
You want to believe,
don't you?
Yeah, I want to walk out
and find myself
in a forest of whore trees,
but I don't think
it's a good idea
to tell people
to go fornicate with fruit.
Hey, I was just talking
about you...
not you specifically--
whores and hypocrisy.
[sighs]
You were right.
I don't want you there.
It's a special occasion
filled with love and acceptance,
and the last thing I need
is someone there who's filled
with loathing and contempt.
Okay.
That's it?
You're really not coming?
I'm really not coming.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Gosh, I feel so grown up.
He's obviously
just jerking you around,
wants to see
if you're serious.
If you just
stick it out,
I think he'll bring
Foreman back.
I don't,
and even if I'm wrong,
I think you
should still split up.
It's just a matter of time
before one of you
finds the other in bed
with another woman.
This coming
from the relationship expert.
12 years and counting.
Hey, if you can make it
that long, then anyone can.
Funny how the two people
in the room
Who think relationships are easy
are both single.
I don't think they're easy.
That's why I think if you find
something that could be good,
you should hang on to it.
Everything could be good.
Very little ever is.
His spleen is fine,
just some
insignificant traces
of minor bugs.
Nothing
that'd make him sick.
Which minor bugs?
Why do people suddenly find
religion when they have kids?
Fear of the unknown.
Cornerstone of faith.
I think it makes perfect sense.
So it makes sense
because it doesn't make sense.
The fact that you're railing
about it
doesn't make a lot of sense.
You really got a thing
for your boss, huh?
I've got a thing
for my boss's thing.
She doesn't have
a thing...
per se.
I'm big on metaphors.
What about you?
29 years of celibacy.
What's holding
you back now?
Who wants a relationship
with a priest?
Who wants a relationship?
House?
It's the holy water.
We assumed
if it was an infection,
it had to be
something big and nasty.
But he has pneumocystis,
a harmless bug that's everywhere
and never makes anyone sick,
unless they have
a compromised immune system.
So father Nietzsche
has AIDS.
Impossible.
I've never had
a blood transfusion.
I've never done I.V. drugs.
I've never had sex.
So prove it.
Have an AIDS test.
No.
I know I don't have AIDS.
We can't treat you
until we know what it is.
A negative result proves nothing.
On the off chance
it's a false positive,
I permanently lose
any credibility
I have left.
- I'd say you just lost that.
I'd say I lost that
with you a long time ago.
(Taub)
We should start
Treatment for AIDS.
(Kutner) We need to be sure.
The antiretrovirals
could fry his heart,
his liver, his kidneys.
I'm willing to take that chance.
- Big of you.
I'm more worried
about the kid he molested.
We should be finding him
and getting him tested.
You don't think he already got tested?
- Maybe he did, maybe he didn't,
but that's a chance
I'm not willing to take.
Legally, we can't inform
sexual partners about STDs.
This isn't some middle-aged
barfly who likes it bareback.
This is an innocent kid
who was molested.
You just want to rub
the priest's face in it,
get him transferred again.
Yeah, heaven forbid
a diddler has job issues.
And you get brought up
on charges.
I've lost enough doctors
this week.
Treat him for AIDS.
I found a job.
I didn't know you were looking.
Eggers at Mercy
says I can start Monday.
Why would you--
House says if I go,
you can come back.
[scoffs]
It's been less than two days.
Give up on me that fast?
You get a job behind my back?
You're acting
like I'm cheating on you.
I said I would handle this.
House knew you'd be like this.
[chuckles]
Wow.
I guess House knows me
better than you do.
Too bad I don't go both ways.
[silverware clanking]
Good night.
Don't you hate when they
Put the mushrooms
underneath the cheese?
Your attendance
is validating her hypocrisy.
If she invited you
to a ceremonial lynching,
would you go?
It would depend
on what she was serving.
Everyone's a hypocrite.
Why are you suddenly so obsessed
with Cuddy's particular brand?
Just making conversation.
Would you rather
we go back to talking
about mushrooms and cheese?
You're the hypocrite!
You want to go!
You don't resent this baby.
You want to be a part of it.
Yes, but not
until her 16th birthday...
in some states.
This is ridiculous.
You two deserve each other.
If you want to go,
Just go and act
like a human being.
Wow, solid advice,
except for two things.
I'm acting
like I don't want to go
because I don't want
to go, and...
I am incapable
of acting like a human being.
Ryan?
Yeah.
I'm Dr. Chris Taub.
Can we talk?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Uh, in private?
Nobody's listening to us here.
Um, I work at
Princeton Plainsboro Hospital.
I have some news
about Father Daniel Bresson.
What about him?
Uh, we believe he has AIDS.
Okay, so?
Well...
Uh, given the incident
four years ago,
I think you should be tested,
Unless you've already done so.
How sick is he?
Very.
Okay.
Well, um, thanks.
Have you been tested?
Uh, yeah.
And?
And it really isn't any
of your business.
I want my job back.
Love,
sacrifice, deception,
and now betrayal.
This is better
than a telenovela.
What's going on?
Well...
Either Foreman is here,
as the two of you discussed,
to beg for his job back
in exchange for me dumping you,
or...
nothing.
You're trying to get me fired?
I'm suggesting you quit
and I stay, which is exactly
what you suggested last night.
I told Eggers I didn't want the job.
Find another one.
Only took you eight hours
to find that one.
The point is,
why didn't you tell me
you were doing this?
Why are you here without me?
You're overreacting.
We'll talk about this later.
- Oh, that's what this is about.
It's about you taking control.
It's about you not being able
to handle me saving your ass.
And you're not
being controlling right now?
(House)
Yeah!
Who's the controlling bitch now?
House, shut up.
You never wanted to take
that other job.
You never wanted to save me.
You wanted to offer to save me
so you wouldn't feel guilty.
You knew I'd say no.
That's why you're so mad
right now.
You're an idiot.
Well, either you can go after
her and try and patch things up,
or you blow her off
and take your old job back.
[sighs]
Welcome back.
AIDS meds aren't gonna work.
If you'd let us do a test,
we could stop treating you,
or you could stop lying.
[breathes deeply]
I know the feeling.
[monitor beeping] BP's climbing.
You feeling okay?
No, I feel flushed.
Ah, I'm burning
all over.
Ah, my chest.
Ah.
(Taub)
It's not a new symptom.
It's just a reaction
to the AIDS meds.
He reacted by getting worse.
Means it's not AIDS.
So went Satan forth
from the presence of the Lord
and smote Job sore with boils.
You think it's hyper-IGE syndrome?
I prefer the colloquial term
"Job syndrome."
Explains the symptom and my quote.
That's the first thing I checked.
VELs are normal.
Could be some other genetic disorder.
Cerebral microtumors
could explain the blindness
and the hallucinations.
We didn't find any tumors.
That's why
I didn't say "tumors."
I said "microtumors."
So your explanation
doesn't depend
on us being major morons,
just morons?
We should start genetic testing.
It takes too long.
So we start treatment.
Treatment is surgery.
We can't open him up
without confirmation.
So your position is we can't
test and we can't treat?
My position is you're wrong.
This isn't gonna work.
Are you kidding?
I've never felt more alive.
Conflict breeds creativity.
Go run the genetic tests.
On it.
So now you don't think
I have AIDS?
I still think it's AIDS.
On the off chance it isn't,
we're pursuing other avenues.
[doors sliding open]
Ryan.
He's, um...
He's dying?
Uh, we don't know
what's wrong with him.
Can I speak to him?
- I don't think that's a good idea.
Ryan?
Uh...
Um, why don't I get you--
Come on, Ryan, now's not a good ti--
I'm sorry...
For everything.
I'm sorry.
I know.
[door opens]
Any second thoughts about Cuddy?
Nope.
But please, feel free
to blather on.
Raising a child
on her own is scary.
She's just doing
what you do,
what everyone does--
trying to avoid pain.
Religion is not the opiate
of the masses.
Religion is the placebo
If you're saying
she's not a hypocrite--
I'm not.
I'm trying to give you
a rational reason
to overlook her hypocrisy
so you don't feel
like a hypocrite for going.
Oh, sorry.
Continue.
Okay, even if
an absolute truth exists,
we can't know all of it,
and you can't condemn her
for recognizing that.
Are you eliminating symptoms?
We can know everything.
This is medicine,
not metaphysics.
Truth is truth.
It fits.
It doesn't fit.
You can't eliminate a symptom.
I can if it's not a symptom.
Well, what is it?
Not a symptom.
You're not gonna die.
You have Wiskott-Aldrich syndrome.
It impairs your immune system,
Makes you susceptible
to all the AIDS stuff
Without actually having AIDS.
And you didn't catch it.
You were born with it.
Another gift from God.
You sure?
Genetic test
should confirm it, but it
explains all your symptoms--
toe, chest, eyes, skin.
What about my hallucination?
Scotch explains that.
But that was just a coincidence.
Coincidences do happen.
That coincidence is what brought
me to you in the first place.
You promised
you wouldn't go there.
Einstein said,
"coincidence is God's way
of remaining anonymous."
A woman in Florida said,
"Look, Jesus
is on my cheese sandwich."
You didn't even want
to take my case.
You didn't even think
I was sick.
The fact that I was wrong
is not a proof of God.
I'm just trying to understand
how my life could completely
turn around in a single day.
Don't worry.
Your life will go
back to sucking soon enough.
Everything that happened to you
can be rationally explained.
I know.
It's just...
That's a lot of coincidences.
[sighs]
House was right about the priest.
Genetic test confirmed
it was Wiskott-Aldrich.
And I would've discharged him.
Everybody would've
discharged him, House included.
He only took that case
as a stall.
And yet it was a real case,
and he solved it.
But by violating
his own principles
and ignoring the admitting symptoms.
Still he somehow got away with it.
Saved another life.
You want him there tonight.
You should tell him.
[clears throat]
It's--it's cold out there.
At least you have shoes
that cover your toes.
So it's tonight?
Yep.
Bad weather for it, huh?
Maybe you'll get lucky.
Maybe your sister will decide
The roads are too dangerous
to drive on.
Fingers crossed.
Have fun.
[slow piano music]
# #
[Hugh Laurie's
Cuddy's Serenade]
# #
[Rolling Stones' You Can't
Always Get What You Want]
# #
[Cuddy's Serenade continues]
Subtitles by LeapinLar