Prosciutto's not bad, but it's not
what you're saying about the fortunato.
....out of a can
[object thuds lightly]
My fish isn't bad.
But it's not great either,
I'm sure.
I warned you against the snapper.
[light thud]
Do you think it'll calm down?
- God, I hope so.
That guy is a bit
of a blowhard, though, isn't he?
The food's not spicy at all.
You can barely taste it.
Mine's pretty spicy.
Try it.
Mm...I don't taste anything.
[chuckles]
You been throwing rolls
at me?
[clears throat]
Uh...it wasn't me.
Uh, really...
he didn't.
I'm so sorry someone
would choose to behave that way.
Really, I...yeah.
I'm...so sorry!
Really, really, really
sorry!
No, no, no, I swear, I--
it's...not...me.
[Massive Attack's Teardrop]
# #
[somber music]
Bloody tear could just mean
subconjunctival hemorrhage.
He sneezed too hard from a cold,
which caused his lack of taste.
House isn't gonna care.
Does black tie optional
really mean black tie?
'Cause I don't wanna rent--
There's been a glitch
with the wedding.
And House will be interested.
A glitch?
Patient had
his corpus callosum cut
to correct a seizure issue.
A glitch?
The seizures stopped
after the surgery,
but he's having trouble
adjusting to a split brain.
A glitch?
This is Dr. Taub.
Tell him about shopping.
Uh...I go into
a grocery store.
Everything seems normal.
I get to the checkout,
and there's all these
extra items in my cart,
stuff I didn't put there,
stuff I hate.
My left hand hates me.
Yeah.
I think House'll be interested.
# clang, clang, clang
went the trolley #
# ding ding ding
hmm hmm hmm #
Just warning you--
I'm in a good mood.
And largely pain-free,
so I have no idea
how things are going--
Alien hand syndrome.
Set off by a stroke,
or is there
a pony in the backyard?
Split brain.
Right hemisphere
controls the left and--
Is making life miserable.
Nonlogical thinkers often do.
Current issue
isn't the split brain.
The surgery corrected--
You're dissing
the right hemisphere?
Most people who have
this operation
don't even notice
they're missing anything.
Left brain has language,
arithmetic, rationality.
Right brain is a mute loser.
Right brain is more
aesthetically oriented,
has greater facial
recognition.
I couldn't have been
a plastic surgeon without it.
Yes. And where would
junior high be
without our ability
to judge people on aesthetics?
Right brain's also more
aware of the present moment,
our place in the universe.
Mm-hmm. It's a universal
daisy chain of peace and love
that throws buns at people.
His present symptoms
could mean autoimmune disease,
nasolacrimal tumor,
an infection, or just a cold.
Good morning, sunshine.
We got a brand-new toy.
You wanna play?
We need to talk.
Great. I love euphemisms.
By euphemism I mean
when you say something,
and it means something else.
Begin eliminating.
Search the home.
The, uh...
isn't that like
locking the barn door
after the horse has put his face
between your breasts
for an hour and a half?
I'm your boss.
You're an employee.
Well, I'm not normally
into role-playing,
but if you wanna...
People who get close to you
get hurt.
That's a fact.
You're also a valued doctor
in this hospital.
That's another fact.
From now on, we're gonna
focus on the second fact.
So this isn't you
freaking out over last night.
This isn't
an emotional decision.
I'm just giving you
the rules.
You can either accept them
or leave.
[somber piano music]
# #
[door slams]
I slept with Cuddy.
After she helped me
detox from Vicodin.
I've been clean for
almost 24 hours now.
Okay.
Thought I'd mention it.
Wow.
Wow!
One for each.
That's what she said. Ha...
- How's the pain?
She's probably got
some bruising...
Yeah, I get it.
You're a stud.
This is serious, House.
I feel better than I did
four hours ago.
Four hours from now,
I'll feel better than this.
The other wow...
you were sober.
She was sober?
Clean and sober and hot.
Wow!
This is fantastic.
How are you gonna
screw it up?
Several good options.
Unfortunately, I don't think
she's gonna
give me the pleasure.
She left before I woke up,
and five minutes ago
she told me that
I'm just an employee.
Ha.
- Yes.
Well, either she's actually
in love with you and scared,
or she realized last night
was a gigantic mistake...
you were needy and vulnerable,
she was maternal...
You think she jumped me
out of pity?
No. I'm saying
whatever's going on,
you...need to talk to her.
Absolutely.
Does our patient
freak you out a little?
No.
If he's two people,
then we're all two people,
and we just don't know it.
What does that say
about identity?
It says...we're making it up
as we go along,
which I find freeing.
Wow, I haven't been
in a bathroom this size
since my dorm in med school.
Is that fungus?
- It's from the steam buildup.
What do you think
of this glitch
with Chase and Cameron's
wedding?
It's always a sad thing
when sperm comes between people.
I hear the sperm
is very good today.
I mean the salmon.
Go away.
- No other tables.
You'd let your wife
keep another man's offspring
on ice next to the frozen peas
just in case?
That's what this is about.
She's not ready
to commit to me.
She's planning for failure.
Did you know that male
fruit flies
have toxic chemicals
in their seminal fluid
that inhibit the sperm
of other males?
Wilson says we need to talk.
We talked.
- I agree.
This has clearly gotten past
the talking stage.
What?
Hey.
Great. Did you find my MP3?
Uh, not yet.
But I got your shaving stuff,
toothpaste, deodorant,
some magazines...
and this cactus
from your window.
You didn't have to do that,
really.
The hospital supplies
all that stuff.
I'm still trying
too hard, huh?
Trying to get
your other half to like me.
Don't say that, okay?
I like you.
Which means that--
we shouldn't read into that.
- Anti-fungal meds.
Ordinarily, we'd put them
in your IV,
but since your right brain
doesn't seem too fond of IVs...
You should be feeling
better in a few days.
I have to get back
to work.
Rick says your shift
will be waiting for you
when you get back.
- Thanks.
Oh! Oh, my God!
God! I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
I'm sorry.
- I have to--
I have to get back to work.
- Babe, wait, hold on!
No, it wasn't me!
I can't walk.
Well, obviously,
it wasn't the fungus.
And it's not
a coordination issues.
Dehydration can cause
loss of balance.
We haven't had him on IV.
- No, good skin turgor.
Not orthostatic.
Could be
our tax dollars at work.
Constantly building
new roadways and bridges.
A meningioma.
Slow growing.
Could extend along
the subosteal layer
of the cranial cavity
and be hidden by the bone.
The cancer cells are
actually re-growing a connection
between the left
and right hemispheres.
If you're right,
the two halves have begun
sending messages again,
but it's too early
in the process for him
to pick up on it.
But...we can test for it.
Proof.
You didn't talk to her,
did you?
If I talked, she'd have lied,
I'd have lied.
And though two negatives
make a positive,
I thought thermal imaging photos
seemed simpler.
Note how many more
heated areas appear
after less than
a minute with me.
So it's either love
or possibly rage.
Don't talk to her.
I have no plans
to talk to her.
Manipulation
is in your genetic Code.
You think I'm making a mistake,
you move in to correct.
You are making a mistake.
- She lied to me.
Either last night or today.
I need to find out which
and why.
And clearly,
thermal imaging is the way.
This isn't a case.
You're not looking for
a diagnosis.
If this matters at all to you,
please, for once in your life,
be an adult.
Keep your eyes focused
on the plus sign.
Any image that appears
on your far right
will only be seen
by your left brain.
And any image on your far left
will only be seen
by your right brain.
Okay.
Just start by saying
the words.
Book.
Giraffe.
Willow.
Fortunate.
You're not saying the word.
I didn't see a word.
Could you draw a picture
of what you think
the word might be?
Uh, look, I-I didn't see...
Candle.
This is so cool.
Yeah, that's not freaky
at all.
No communication.
So far.
Scott, why are you
standing?
Uh...
I'm a little chilly.
I thought I'd get a sweater
or something from my room.
Is that okay?
- A few more minutes.
And that,
ladies and gentlemen,
is the left hemisphere...
the side that's obsessed
with finding answers,
the one that needs things
to make sense, the interpreter.
That's where we tell the story
of who we are
and why we do things.
That's also the side
that was wrong.
Right brain's advantage
is that it isn't logical,
doesn't choose which details
to look at,
makes connections
you could never see.
You owe your insight
to the "mute loser."
I'll send it tickets
to a Phillies game.
Confabulation
means no communication.
Means your theory's wrong.
But he is cold.
Why are you scratching?
It itches.
- Ammonia breath.
Your liver is failing.
I know for them
to approve this price,
they'll need statistical
documentation.
What?
Why are you looking at me?
When you first walked in,
I was under the impression
you wanted to...
say something else.
Nope.
About House and me.
There's nothing
to talk about.
[door clicks open]
I want permission
to do a liver biopsy.
We're looking for sarcoidosis.
Fine.
- What do you mean, fine?
What do you mean
what do I mean?
Do you mean because
a liver biopsy
is not a test that, by any
stretch of the imagination,
can be considered risky,
so asking my permission
is essentially wasting my time,
and you're wondering what
my reaction to that will be?
Yes.
Are you trying
to make me angry?
Yes.
- Do your biopsy.
And also do your clinic hours.
I'm blowing off
my clinic hours.
Really?
Let's see how that goes.
Still not angry.
Try again later.
Ah...sorry.
I know I'm a little ripe.
Just a sweaty guy.
- Recently?
Always.
Uh, with a crazy left hand.
Sometimes I fantasize
about cutting it off.
Just a fantasy.
It's the hand that's crazy,
not me.
What? If it doesn't like
an ultrasound wand,
how's it gonna react
to a needle?
Can you get music
into this room?
I think you're using
your relationship with Cuddy
as a replacement for drugs.
You should be in more pain
so soon into detoxing,
but your body's
full of romantic endorphins.
And on top of that,
you create this distraction
of looking for proof.
Think I should stop
and let the pain flood back?
Cuddy is not
a Vicodin substitute.
Quite the opposite.
You have to wait
for her to be ready.
Great advice.
You pretend
that I'm gonna do that.
You've made two major
changes in your life.
Not a time anyone's
judgment is at its best.
Didn't you use to argue
that my judgment
would be better off drugs?
Admit it--you're curious
why I wanna make her angry.
I'm sure it's convoluted,
wrong, and stupid.
You're dying to know what
I found on her coffee cup.
No. Because--
- Oxytocin.
Oxytocin...
The chemical involved
in emotional bonding?
Her lips say no...
her hormones say,
"oh, my God, yes, more!"
No. For you to know
her levels were elevated
you'd need a base line
to compare them with.
I paid the guy in the gym
to retrieve one of her
water bottles from the trash.
Love inspires us
to greatness.
So I need to make her
lose her temper...
which breaks her delusion,
which demonstrates to me
and to her
that there is something
underneath this facade.
And then what happens?
She admits everything
and falls into your arms?
That's outcome one.
Outcome two...is she kills me.
I think it's 50/50 right now.
Great.
I thought you'd say that!
You're committing
yourself to something--
Someone.
I mean, it's childish
in a way,
but ultimately great.
Assuming...
are you absolutely sure
you want this to succeed?
Why is an old guy
standing in my doorway?
Eugene Schwartz.
Dr. Cuddy asked me to come
up here from the clinic.
She says you're seeing patients
in your office.
It's still free, though,
isn't it?
She sent him.
That's gotta mean something.
I'll go get my decoder ring.
I squawk.
Like a parrot.
Aaww!
No, that's not it.
It started a few months ago.
I was doing some woodworking
in my garage.
I was trying to make a chair.
Was it the chair?
Anyway, all of a sudden,
from nowhere,
this strange noise comes
bursting out of my mouth--
Caaaww!
Tough to fake that.
Nice pants.
My wife Mona thinks
I'm bustin' her chops.
It's ruining my marriage.
Where are we going?
[Doobie Brother's
China Grove plays]
So your left hand
would rather play air guitar
than give me a hard time?
It'd rather play air guitar
than tie shoes, eat dinner...
Your right hand's
playing too.
I don't wanna
discourage it.
# #
Splinter hemorrhages
under his fingernails.
What's that?
What--
BP and 02 sats are dropping!
Need a bag of B-negative
in here!
So much for sarcoidosis.
Points to
a clotting issue.
Clots would explain
all his symptoms.
Why aren't we
in the office?
I'm tired of clinic duty.
There's only one thing that
could cause squawking, right?
Yeah. We gave him heparin
and did an echo of his heart
to see if it was
throwing clots, but--
More air guitar?
- The heart's fine.
We wanted to test
for factor V leiden,
Protein C, protein S,
but the hand got tired
of cooperating.
We finally knocked him out.
And all those tests
came up negative anyway,
or you would have opened
by telling me
your brilliant diagnosis.
He apologized
for being sweaty,
said it had always
been an issue,
but what if it's a symptom?
There are cancers
that cause night sweats
and can lead to clots--
Lymphoma...
Or pancreatic cancer.
Go scan his pancreas.
And...
try Led Zeppelin.
We've always remembered
what this hospital did for Leo
when his appendix burst.
Still, a check this size...
Sorry to interrupt.
Here's my poo.
[chuckles]
Dr. House said to bring it
over and leave it with you
as soon as I could.
I don't know if you people
have an official term for it--
Stool sample.
- Ah, yes.
Thank you.
I'll take care of it.
It's hard to rush
these things.
Even if you've eaten
a lot of broccoli.
Where you goin'?
- Annie called.
She's not coming back.
This is not the best time.
You said the heparin would
keep new clots from forming.
Maybe. But something's
obviously causing the clots.
If you have
pancreatic cancer--
We're not trying
to scare you,
but even in its early stages,
the fatality rate--
You walk out of here--
- Stop!
Look, I'd ask you to put
yourself in my place,
but nobody can put themselves
in my place.
Did she find somebody new?
Was I not being
attentive enough?
No.
She's just tired of being
insulted by a limb.
She said that my feelings
toward her were mixed.
Well, my feelings
aren't mixed.
You're not goin' anywhere
unless you wanna go naked.
Your right brain
knows you need to stay.
My right brain's an ass.
[sighs]
Got a minute?
There's something wrong
with this cup.
I need someone
to bounce ideas off of,
someone to be my whiteboard.
That's how
you taught me to work.
I have three choices:
First--I can accept it's over,
pretend we don't work
in the same hospital,
have selective visual impairment
when we pass each other
in the hall.
Second--I can accept
it's over and leave--
Or you could try
making him angry.
Standard choice number three.
Third...I can talk to him,
but it's not like I have
any new facts I can present.
And Chase has this
romantic view of love
that reality
can't compete with.
I know how you could succeed.
- How?
Just say the magic words--
"I will destroy
my husband's sperm."
Oh, you mean succeed
without doing that.
Probably not.
I have doubts.
Normal doubts.
It's not wrong to prepare
for bad things to happen
even if you don't
expect them to.
I don't expect my condo
to burn down,
but I have fire insurance.
Patient's girlfriend
left him.
Now he wants to leave us.
If your condo rules
don't let you buy insurance,
would you go homeless?
His room is this way.
What, do you think
I can fix this?
We need to offer this guy
something he can only get
if he stays in the hospital--
relationship counseling.
I don't know
if his girlfriend's--
I mean
his two hemispheres.
That's the breakfast
of relationships--
The most important one
of the day.
We need your special skills.
Is the guy out there?
The guy that's gonna
make my right brain work?
Oh, for...
[click] What do you think
your right brain wants?
How should I know?
It's crazy.
It does things
I would never do.
Duct of Wirsung's
slightly enlarged
but within normal parameters.
Say something.
It's mute.
It can't communicate with you.
Maybe you should try
communicating with it.
"Talk to her."
the well isn't deep, is it?
You're the dominant half.
You make all the decisions.
The right side
has no control over anything.
It must be...frustrating.
No masses in body
or tail segments.
I can't communicate with it.
That's the whole--
When you decide to go and get
groceries, what do you do?
What do you mean?
I put on my jacket,
and I go to the store.
Your right brain
has no idea
why you're suddenly getting up
and putting on your jacket.
It just gets dragged along.
Next time,
try saying it out loud.
Just say to the empty air,
"Hey, I think
I'll go to the store
because we're out of
peanut butter"?
How much did they teach you
about people like me
when you were learning
to be a therapist?
I'm an oncologist.
The right brain
likes what he's saying.
Hasn't moved
the entire scan.
Hasn't gotten us
anything, though.
Scan's clean.
It's not pancreatic cancer.
Clotting could be a problem
well before a solid tumor forms.
It can still be pancreatic.
Yes, but if you want
a diagnosis
backed by actual evidence,
we should probably
look at other cancers.
House.
I just squawked!
- What?
Eugene Schwartz,
your patient from yesterday.
I just squawked!
I was buying some flowers
for Mona.
It happened
when I was paying the clerk!
I assume Dr. Cuddy
gave you this number.
Yes! She told me to call you
any time I squawked
day or night!
I'm sorry,
but I'm about to lose you
because I'm about to drive
into a tunnel
in a canyon on an airplane
while hanging up the phone.
I might be getting
some more phone calls,
so let's make it fast.
Lymphoma--
- That's right, pancreatic.
I know it's pancreatic.
I know there's evidence.
I know we've seen it.
I just can't--
Right brain,
left brain issues?
If the cancer's
too small to find,
let's make it easier.
Let's open him up and paint it.
There's a new procedure
using scorpion toxin
and infrared paint.
Paint only works
on the cancer cells,
makes 'em easier to spot.
Just agitating the pancreas
can cause clotting,
and you wanna do it to a guy
whose problem is clotting.
If I'm right about
pancreatic cancer,
The only chance he's got
is finding and removing
those cancer cells now.
His brain MRI showed
narrowing in the blood vessels
leading up from the neck.
If we do shake something loose,
we could kill him.
Clot in his brain
could kill one of them
without affecting the other.
He might actually
be okay with that.
How long's it gonna take?
Assuming he doesn't crash...
A few minutes.
[click, beep]
Hey...you and Cameron.
I'm sorry.
I'll be right back.
I don't wanna be homeless.
Okay. You can stay
in the condo.
I'll find some other--
- That's not what I mean.
I wanna marry you.
I got the forms
to destroy the sperm.
You sure?
Yeah.
[laughs]
I wanna hug you,
but then I'd have to rescrub.
I know.
BP's dropping.
Go.
No sign of cancer.
BP's 90 over 60.
[footsteps approach]
You never answered
my question.
Relax.
Our friendship
is not doomed.
Thank God.
But my question was
do you really want Cuddy,
or is this just another
challenge?
You're worried that once
I'm in a relationship
you and me'll be over.
Hey! I'm actually for this.
I think this is great.
But if you're serious and
you don't treat it seriously,
then you will get hurt.
And if you don't accept that,
then accept
that she will get hurt.
She look angry?
If you're standing there
when she looks up here--
Oh, no.
Systolic's 80.
Gotta finish this suture
before I can get out.
Give him a dopamine drip.
We weren't looking up
at the right time.
Get to your point.
We're a little busy here.
The clots aren't from cancer.
They're coming from his heart.
We echoed the heart.
No clots.
Not while we were looking.
Didn't I open with that?
The clots were caused
by an arrhythmia.
No arrhythmia.
- Not while we were looking!
Intermittent arrhythmia.
This guy pulls our equipment off
at the slightest provocation.
We'd have to be watching
at the exact moment it happened,
which I'm guessing,
given the way you two are
scrambling around like idiots,
is right now!
Yes, I'm saying
do a transesophageal echo.
We have to get his BP stable.
Absolutely.
Right after the echo.
[alarm beeping]
Systolic 70.
The heart looked healthy
at the last echo.
And an arrhythmia wouldn't cause
clots in a healthy ventricle.
So start with the left
atrial appendage.
[alarm beeping]
[beeping stops]
Wow.
- Yep.
I did it again.
Now get this poor guy's
BP under control
And seal off the appendage.
Then all we have to do
is find out what damaged
his heart
before it goes after
something he really needs.
So what damages
a healthy 20-year-old heart
enough to make it send out clots
like it's bombing Dresden?
Rhabdo?
Would have fried
his kidneys too.
What about Graves?
Thyroid function tests
were normal.
Cushing's.
Cortisol overproduction could
interfere with heart rhythm.
Run a dexamethasone
suppression test.
Annie.
You hit me.
I know.
I'm so sorry, but...
It wasn't me.
I know you would never
have done that
if you were in control
of yourself, but...
But you came back.
To talk with your doctors.
I've been going over
and over what happened,
and I had this thought
out of nowhere.
Ever since I've known Scott,
I've seen his left hand
throw things
but always sort of playfully,
thinking it's fun.
But when he threw this...
it was angry,
and that's when
his hand slapped me, too,
when I brought it to him.
Could it mean something?
Deodorant shouldn't--
How often do you use it?
Uh, a few times a day.
It's special heavy duty stuff.
I have to send away for it.
Sprayed around a bathroom
the size of a shoebox.
I'll check the ingredients
from the manufacturer.
I'll check for any references
associated with health issues.
Somebody's grateful.
We'll just leave the...
three of you alone.
[door thuds]
Why is there
no lipstick on this cup?
Cuddy was wearing lipstick
when she drank from it.
It was on my face.
Why isn't it on the cup?
Why is it always reasonable
in Houseland
to take an emotional problem
and sidestep it by turning it
into a mechanical problem?
Because in Houseland--
and the rest of the universe,
by the way--
when a question presents itself,
it calls for an answer.
If the left brain
is the interpreter of reality
and the one that tells us
the story of who we are,
then what is your story?
Do you wanna be
the man with the answers,
or do you wanna be
the man with Cuddy?
What do I do?
You make her angry.
You really think that was
the best time to mock me?
I'm as surprised as you,
but I think I'm serious.
Communication can't start
unless you're--
I've been trying
to make her angry for--
No, you haven't.
Come on!
Poo, strippers?
It's routine stuff.
You've been pulling
your punches.
You're scared.
You should be.
Now...go terrorize her.
You don't wanna
destroy it, do you?
I said I was gonna do it.
I'll do it.
But you don't want to.
I wanna be with you.
Maybe I'm not
comfortable with it--
Let's say it's our fifth
anniversary.
Are you ready
to destroy it now?
Tenth.
Three kids.
They spend their summers
in Melbourne
And have annoying accents.
It's disgusting
how happy we are.
You ready now?
You don't have doubts.
You just don't wanna kill
the only thing left
of someone you loved.
Don't do it.
I do have trouble
giving things up.
For example...
I never cancelled
any of our wedding plans.
[laughing]
[bang bang]
Attention!
I have an announcement.
As you go about your day,
I would like you
to be aware of the fact
that I slept with Lisa Cuddy!
[murmuring]
This is beyond ass-hood!
You have the luxury
of not caring about your image.
I do not!
I can permit a lot of crap,
but an employee
shouting about
his sexual
exploits with me--no!
That is zero tolerance!
So congratulations, House.
I am angry.
I was wondering
if we should move in together.
[laughing]
You're fired.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I think she likes you.
If I'm fired,
I think that probably means
I don't have to see patients.
I'm here as a squeaky wheel.
I know how you doctors are.
You're busy,
you get distracted.
My lab results could be
sitting in your in-box.
I don't need your labs.
You have acid reflux.
Well, how could you--
Acid splashes
on the vocal chords.
They tense,
make that squawking sound.
It's completely harmless.
I'm gonna give you
a prescription,
and you are gonna go away.
You are a great doctor.
Ha.
Why'd you move your belt?
I always move my belt.
Makes me sore.
You didn't tell me that.
At 86, what isn't sore?
Soreness is less important
than squawking.
It's the squawking that was
bothering my wife. [grunts]
That's not a potbelly.
It's a tumor.
That's why pancreatic cancer
was on my mind.
My brain was trying
to tell me.
This isn't sounding good.
Pancreatic cancer?
It can cause acid reflux.
We should scope you.
So it's not good.
Even for cancer it's not good.
No, it's not.
[elevator bell dings]
The deodorant has a high
proportion of propylene glycol.
Same stuff made a kid
in Singapore
develop a heart condition,
and--get this--seizures.
Our patient may never have
needed split-brain surgery.
I'm sure he will
half-appreciate the irony.
Take this man to radiology.
Pancreatic scan.
And stay with him.
Eugene Schwartz.
[blows nose]
[door clicks open]
[brads clattering]
Whatever it is,
just say it quickly.
Do you have more than one
lipstick in the same shade?
Maybe one that has a sealing
agent and one that doesn't?
How could that possibly
be relevant to anything?
You really don't think
you're just...
overreacting
to the other night?
Fine. I am overreacting.
You've said plenty of lousy
things to me before.
But...
reaching the final straw
has been a good thing
because it made me realize
we not only don't have
a personal relationship,
we never could.
You--you're--
you've been overreacting...
to something I said?
You insulted me.
I walked out.
It's nothing that hasn't
happened a hundred times before.
[exhales]
I quit.
Great.
My Nanny is off the clock
at 7:30,
so...
you're a week off.
You can go suckle
the little bastard child
if it makes you feel good
about yourself.
Screw you.
No, no, that--
that's not what happened.
I told you that I needed you.
You--you helped me.
Are you okay?
[pills clicking]
[top pops]
So...this is the story
you made up about who you are.
It's a nice one.
Too bad it isn't true.
No.
I'm not okay.
[door clicks open]
[Vitamin String Quartet's
As Tears Go By]
# #
[fading into the rolling stones'
As Tears Go By]
# it is the evening
of the day #
# I sit and watch
the children play #
# smiling faces I can see #
# but not for me #
# I sit and watch
as tears go by #
[instrumental break]
# #
# it is the evening
of the day #
# I sit and watch
the children play #
# doing things I used to do #
# they think are new #
# I sit and watch
as tears go by # #
Subtitles by LeapinLar