(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WRITING)
(EXHALES)
Damn it, Zach.
This is the last time
I'm turning around.
The next time you
forget something, you're
gonna be on your own.
I can't play
without a stick.
Then I guess
you won't play.
I don't care.
I suck anyway.
Don't say that.
I'm the worst guy
on the whole team.
No, you're not.
Then who's worse?
Don't worry about
anyone else,
just do your best.
See? You can't
name anyone.
Zach, stop it.
Then name someone.
You can't, can you?
Donny, Mark, Navid...
You really think
I'm better than those guys?
Yes.
Hurry up and
get your stick.
Zach, get back
in the car.
I need an ambulance
at 860 Oakwood Avenue.
Why is Dad's car on?
Get back in
the car, Zach!
(GRUNTING)
Come on.
(PANTING)
Don't do this to me,
Jeff. Don't do this!
(COUGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I'm sorry. I just...
I couldn't take
the pain any more.
(PANTING)
(WOMAN CHATTERING ON PA)
Either I need a new watch
or Mowgli is cutting into
your beauty sleep.
I was up all night
looking at finance reports,
and Rachel is
doing great,
thanks for asking.
Proving that you're
a better foster mom than
a homeless drug addict.
Departmental budgets
are due this week.
I'm gonna need
an extension.
I've got some
time next decade...
Cameron already
turned yours in.
That's nice of her.
Two questions, why did she,
and why are you telling me?
Same answer.
Now you owe her a favor.
I'm gonna need an extension.
I've got some time...
House, I've got a DYFS
home visit on Friday.
And I've got
a W-H-O-R-E visit on...
Mama's busy. You two are
gonna have to go play
outside for a while.
32-year-old male
with chronic pain all over.
This is the favor?
I was expecting something
involving whipped cream
and tongue depressors.
He's seen seven different
specialists over three years,
no diagnosis and no relief.
Oh, I am fascinated
already. It's like
I'm treating myself.
He gets cured,
and I get to learn
a valuable lesson
about the milk of
human kindness.
If I thought you
learned lessons,
I never would have quit.
So you're wasting
a favor because...
I think you can
help this guy.
Drug-seeking patients...
Don't attempt suicide
with medicine cabinets
full of narcotics.
Sounds like fibromyalgia.
Sounds like you
don't work for House.
A diagnosis that provides
neither an explanation
nor a cure
is, by definition,
not a diagnosis.
The American College
of Rheumatology
would disagree.
There're specific
diagnostic criteria...
Which this guy
doesn't meet.
Putting pressure
on his pain helps,
doesn't make it worse.
He's got abdominal pain,
severe headaches, muscle
cramps that come and go.
And he tried
to off himself.
He's, obviously, mentally
ill. The pain's probably
psychological.
It's not a sign
of mental illness to
wanna be pain-free.
It is if your solution is
sucking on a tailpipe. Sane
people don't attempt suicide.
Not ever?
So, if you were being burnt
at the stake and someone
handed you a gun...
I'd shoot the guys
with the torches.
Not one doctor
this guy's seen in
the past three years
has been able to
find a single thing
wrong with him.
What does that tell you?
It means they're idiots.
It means we got to
start from the beginning.
And do a pain profile to
rule out psychosomatic pain.
Search the home. Go home.
Get a refill. And a donut.
I'll help with the home.
"Choose the statement
in each group
"that best describes how
you've been feeling lately,
including today."
I'm not depressed.
I know what I did
was stupid.
"I usually sleep well.
I have some trouble
with sleep.
"I have a lot of
trouble with sleep."
I have a lot of trouble.
It's up and down.
Between the pain and
the meds, his sleep
pattern's pretty erratic.
"He's a calm person.
He's more nervous
than most people.
"He's so nervous
he's miserable."
He's definitely calm.
Sometimes calmer
the worse the pain gets.
I think talking,
interacting with other people,
actually makes it worse.
Interesting.
Why, does that
mean something?
No, it's just...
We've seen that
in other patients.
TAUB: "He can do chores
around the house.
"With help he can do chores.
He no longer can do chores."
ZACH: He helps all the time.
He's really strong.
He used to play hockey.
He was really good, too.
"I believe there's hope.
Hoping for things to get
better is a struggle for me.
"Most of the time
I feel completely
hopeless."
He still laughs,
all the time.
LYNNE: He was always
optimistic. Still is.
It's just, it's harder now.
I guess I pray for
strength more than hope.
There's nothing in there
but a pharmacy's worth of
pain meds.
This guy makes House look
like a Christian Scientist.
He's also more
compliant than House.
Kept all the inserts.
Had daily pill dispensers
to make sure
he didn't mix them up.
Guess if you're gonna
go out in a car, this
ain't a bad one to choose.
If I ever did it,
it definitely wouldn't
be like that.
Don't worry,
I'm not making any plans.
I certainly wouldn't know.
Ever since we kissed,
you've been avoiding me.
No, I haven't.
I've just been busy.
Metal polish could
cause nerve damage,
if he inhaled enough of it.
And judging by
the shine on that car,
he used a fair amount.
And judging by the fact
that he owns a body shop,
and one of these,
I'd say he knew
not to inhale.
Busy tonight?
We could get some dinner.
I don't think so.
So, making out, okay,
meals, too intimate?
I don't wanna kiss
you again, either.
Why? Because
we work together?
No. Because I like you.
That makes a lot of sense.
What doesn't make sense
is me getting involved
with anyone.
I thought you'd gotten
past that. That's why you
agreed to the drug trial.
You can't give up
on life because...
I'm not giving up on life,
I'm just giving up on you.
I finally feel like
I have a grip on things,
I can handle this.
What I can't handle
is dragging anyone
else down with me.
Does this look like
quail to you?
TAUB: You think he's had
food poisoning every day
for the last three years?
THIRTEEN:
Wild quail can be toxic,
cause rhabdomyolysis,
which would explain
his pain as well as
the elevated CK levels.
So would the carbon monoxide
he sucked out of his car.
It's not a toxic reaction,
it's a psychosomatic reaction.
The pain profile showed
an excessive concern about
his physical health,
difficulty sleeping,
getting out of bed...
He's not in pain
because he's depressed,
he's depressed
because he's in pain.
Not according to the
pain profile you ordered.
It's not a diet issue.
We should start him on
antidepressants, for his
sake as well as his family's.
We're not diagnosing
his family.
you, either.
It's rhabdo.
Push IV fluids,
check his urine,
do a muscle biopsy.
What muscle?
He says it hurts
all over.
Then she'll
biopsy all over.
Where are you going?
If Cuddy can come in late,
I can leave early.
If you need anything
while I'm gone, just
ask Cameron to do it.
So if he just
stops eating quail,
the pain will go away?
If we're right,
it's definitely treatable.
(JEFF BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING) My arm,
it's starting to...
He needs more medicine.
KUTNER: BP's down.
We need to get him
in Trendelenburg position.
Jeff, can you hear me?
KUTNER: He's arresting.
THIRTEEN: We need
a crash cart in here!
(ALARMS BEEPING)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(SIGHS)
He's not answering
his cell, either.
V-Q scan showed
a pulmonary embolism.
Means the pain's
not psychosomatic.
Also means it's
not rhabdomyolysis.
Up till now his heart
and lungs were the only
places he didn't have pain.
Means it's getting worse.
(PHONE RINGING)
You gotta let the phone ring
more than four times when
you're calling a cripple.
Chronic pain and
pulmonary embolism, go.
How'd you know he had a...
Call after midnight,
it's gotta be a heart
problem. Heart only would
be consistent with rhabdo,
which means Thirteen
and Foreman would be
singing in the rain,
which means it has
to be lungs as well.
Hypercoagulable state
could cause pain and a PE.
You think the blood clot
was caused by a clotting
problem. That's helpful.
What if it's
a cancer syndrome,
like Trousseau's?
Explains blood clots,
multi-focal pain, lack of
obvious physical signs...
And why he's gone
three years without
anyone seeing it.
Check his chest, abdomen,
and pelvis for tumors.
Why did he think
only you two would be
singing in the rain?
(WATER RUNNING)
Bone windows are normal.
Checking for cancerous
masses in the lungs.
So, who do you know
who committed suicide?
Hemingway, Goebbels,
Romeo and Juliet...
Your mom, dad?
Saying I wouldn't do it
under any circumstances
means my whole
family was suicidal?
No. But categorically
insisting there are
no circumstances
means you've got baggage,
personal betrayal,
abandonment...
Just because you grew up
in a Charles Dickens novel...
It's people like me
who don't do it.
When your life sucks
from the beginning,
nowhere to go but up.
Thorax is clear,
no tumors
in the lungs.
The only betrayal comes from
father of the year in there.
He has a wife, a kid,
people who count on
him to have a pulse.
Okay.
Switching to high-res
cuts of the abdomen.
My parents live
very happily in Queens.
They never attempted,
thought about, or attempted to
think about committing...
What?
There, along his diaphragm.
That's not cancer.
No hurry. I already bathed
once this week. I wouldn't
want to look elitist.
Can't do anything till
I write up an estimate.
Fine. Pad it all you want.
Here's a check for
the deductible.
Don't touch the piano,
and lock up when you leave.
Sorry, deductible
doesn't apply here.
I'm no architect,
but I'm pretty sure
the master bedroom
is part of the home,
which means the
home warranty...
Doesn't cover negligence.
This pipe goes through
the ceiling, over that wall
and into your shower.
It didn't burst,
it was pulled apart.
Yeah, 'cause I'm clearly
a guy who likes to knock
out a few naked pull-ups
before I greet the day.
You hang laundry in there?
I'm about to hang
a plumber in there.
Look, there's no rust,
there's no corrosion.
I don't know how it happened,
but I know what happened,
and it's not covered.
So, whenever you're ready
to spend the $2,200,
give somebody else a call.
I promise, I'm only holding
your hand to check for
choreiform movement.
I'm getting absolutely
no intimacy from it.
I told you, it has
nothing to do with you.
I know.
That's the problem.
There's 80 reasons we
shouldn't date. But you
can't shut everyone out.
You're gonna
need help, support.
Look at our patient.
Thirty-two years old,
not dead yet,
and already
he's traumatized
his wife, his son...
And I'll bet they're
cherishing every traumatic
minute he has left,
wouldn't trade him
for the healthiest
guy in the world.
True. And they're
stuck suffering with him,
hating every day,
only their pain has
no prospect of relief.
This a bad time?
No.
Yes.
No trace of cancer
in the patient.
But we did find edema
in his intestines,
air in the intestinal
blood vessels, and House
won't answer his phone.
His intestine must be
damaged, the air's
leaking into his body.
If there's a blockage
in the superior
mesenteric artery,
it could be
choking off blood flow
to his intestine.
Blockages all over his body
would explain his pain,
why the cramps come and go.
Do an angioplasty
on the superior
mesenteric,
and find the other
blockages, before he has
another cardiac arrest.
I'll help.
Good thing we don't
have a suicidal patient
with a horrific,
undiagnosed pain disorder.
We did,
till we diagnosed it.
We found intestinal edema
and air in the blood vessels.
The pain was vascular.
If it was vascular,
we would've seen
uneven pulses.
His blood pressure was uneven.
Thirteen and Kutner
are doing an angio.
He'd have hemorrhages
in his fingers.
There's air in the intestine,
it has to have come
from somewhere.
Yes, it does.
After we thread the
catheter through his
groin and into position,
the blood will start
flowing freely again.
Will that take
away the pain?
It will be completely
ineffective, and the pain
will completely go away.
Cancel the angio.
He has air in
his blood vessels.
If we don't open
the artery to his intestine...
Where can air come from?
Hmm.
Air can either come from
a breach of the lumen
in the small intestine,
or, in rare instances,
air can come from the air.
Teeth marks.
I'm guessing from
when he blew
into his IV tube.
Air bubble caused
the PE and cardiac arrest.
You tried to finish the job
that you started at home.
Jeff, why?
You said that...
I lied.
I want to die.
Please just let me die.
No.
KUTNER: He's in
a hyperbaric chamber.
A dose of high pressure
ought to chase the air
out of his blood.
CUDDY: Is anyone
keeping an eye on him?
You know, because
the whole idea of
suicide watch
was specifically created
for suicidal patients.
I realize how you might
have thought the name was
just a coincidence...
Are there any
visuals in this room
that are key to us
learning our lesson?
Because the telephone...
I'm inconveniencing you
because you inconvenienced me.
(BABY GURGLING)
When was the last
time you showered?
Scent of a man.
I realize you haven't
experienced it sober.
If anyone should be
able to handle a
depressed pain patient...
He insisted
he was no longer...
Apparently,
he lied.
Didn't think I'd have to
remind you of that
remote possibility.
I have a DYFS inspection
in less than 24 hours,
so if you can't control...
Non-motor seizures.
Sorry, I was thinking
about the patient.
What were you saying?
Go on.
The pain started
in his abdomen,
near his intestine.
The first symptom's
got to be key.
HOUSE: He's had
multiple EEGs,
all of them cleaner
and squeakier than
Cuddy's rubber nipples.
What about a glycogen-storage
disease, like McArdle's.
Explains the pain, plus
there's plenty of muscle cells
in the wall of the intestine.
Foreteen is right.
Go run an ischemic
forearm test.
Take the garbage
out on your way out.
If you want a man
to take your crap,
you have to marry him first.
Or employ him.
Good girl.
I don't think I'm ready
to run a decathlon yet.
If we can get you
managing your life a bit
better, that'll be plenty.
Dr. Hadley,
whenever you're ready.
Janice.
(CHUCKLES)
You look better.
Yeah, they said
my basal ganglian
volume's improved.
All I know is,
for the first time
in two years,
I can drink a cup of water
without spilling it
all over myself.
Thank you for getting me
back in the study.
I haven't even
seen you in weeks,
I didn't even know
our appointments were
back-to-back again.
Well, they weren't.
Mine got switched
this morning.
We're gonna take
your blood repeatedly.
If the increased strain
makes your arm hurt more,
you have a muscle abnormality.
If you're right about
this McArdle's disease,
can you take away the pain?
With gene replacement
therapy, with lifestyle
changes, we can reduce it.
Keep squeezing
the ball.
(GRUNTS)
How long does he have to...
Maybe you and Zach
should eat something.
LYNNE: Honey,
don't worry about us.
I'm not.
Please, get out of here.
These tests are
all I can handle.
TAUB: They're trying
to help you.
They can't.
Then how about helping them?
You know, by not being...
An ass?
You have no idea
what I'm going through.
I know it's better
than what you
tried to go through.
Sure, no baggage at all.
Where's the pain
worst right now?
In my left arm.
Does it hurt more?
Couldn't.
And lactate level's steady.
It's not any kind of
glycogen...
(SCREAMING) Oh, God!
Pain jumped to my leg.
This never happened before.
Your chest, your abdomen,
you feel anything there?
My leg feels like
it's being sawed off.
Nice.
What?
Switching Janice's
appointment time, so I can
see the skies brighten
like a Lifetime TV movie.
I don't know what you're...
Sticking your
most improved study
participant in my face.
Is that your way of
getting into my pants?
I don't make the schedule,
and if I did, I wouldn't
use it as a social lubricant.
And this is the first
I've heard of Janice
improving at all.
So, hey, thanks
for the good news.
Pain started
in his abdomen.
Now it's hopped from his
left arm to his left leg,
skipping the trunk entirely.
I need the name
of a good lawyer.
We're getting sued?
Probably.
That's Cuddy's problem.
Hopping pain.
Means it's something
in his brain, not his body.
Except the pain's in two
places that connect two
separate regions of the brain,
which means you're
not using yours.
Come on,
you're from one
of the Twelve Tribes,
you must know
a ton of shysters.
What type of lawyer
do you need?
I'll bring it up at
the next world domination
subcommittee meeting.
I didn't say I needed
a lawyer, I said I needed
the name of a lawyer.
Pain hopped to another
limb on the same side,
it's gotta be central...
Could still be peripheral.
If multiple areas of
disc disease...
Were consistent with
a completely spotless MRI.
Who represented
the hospital when you
set that patient on fire?
Chris Carrick.
Chris.
That doesn't sound like
a very good lawyer.
If we can't even resolve
body versus brain, we're
never gonna diagnose the guy.
What was the
name of the firm?
Caddell and Carrick.
It's not like we can
chop off his head to see
if the pain goes away.
Why not?
(DOOR OPENS)
Need to cut off
a guy's head.
Gotta figure out if
his pain's coming from
his brain or his body.
Stiff shot of Lidocaine
below the brain stem
should numb him
all the way down
to his tippy-toes.
And hearing me say
"no" over the phone
wasn't good enough?
I'm inconveniencing
you because you
inconvenienced me.
You know that
foster care official is
coming in the morning...
If they weren't
there'd be no
inconvenience.
Do not try and force me
to choose between
my child and this...
I'm forcing you
to do your job.
If you can't also...
Fine.
You want to separate
a patient's central
nervous system
from the rest
of his body.
If the pain stays,
it's in his brain.
If it vanishes...
What about options three,
four and five?
His respiratory
system freezes,
or he dies of infection,
or he leaks CNS fluid like
a fire hydrant, which would
make him wish he were dead.
Scratch option five,
he's already there.
You preach objectivity,
but as soon as a patient
comes in, in pain,
all you want to do is
look under the hood.
You don't care if
there's a one-in-three
chance you'll kill him.
If I don't diagnose him,
there's a one-in-one
chance he'll kill himself.
(PAGER BEEPING)
I gotta go.
Do whatever it is
you think is right.
(BABY CRYING)
Tammy. You said
you were gonna
be a little late.
DYFS is gonna be here
in an hour, and this
place is a disaster.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Never mind.
This should numb
everything from
your shoulders down.
Any pain
that's peripheral
should be gone.
What are you doing here?
Just stretching my leg.
Carry on.
Bad pain day today?
About to get better.
Don't worry, he's
making yours a double.
(SCOFFS)
I remember when
the drugs still made
things tolerable,
when I still thought
I had good days left.
Turns out you have
to live to find out.
JEFF: You don't have
a family, do you?
Left them all back
on Krypton.
You're alone.
That's why you can
handle your pain.
No need to put up a front,
to be what anyone else
wants you to be.
You're having more
bad days lately,
aren't you?
Yes.
Take a look at your future.
Let's hope the drugs work
this time.
(GROANING)
I really wasn't
expecting you till later.
Had a cancellation,
so I thought I'd knock
you off the docket.
Well, I'm sorry this place is
such a mess, it's been a bit
of a difficult work week.
Any guns in the house?
No.
Pets? Besides the ants?
Nice bag. Pricey way
to ditch the diapers.
That's not what I usually...
I sort of panicked.
Mr. Carlton,
if you'll just give me
a minute to explain...
Everything looks fine.
Really?
Dr. Cuddy, you've got
sufficient income,
a high degree of personal
and professional stability,
and you care enough
to be embarrassed by
what a mess this place is.
Believe me,
that puts you
head and shoulders
above most of
the foster moms
I visit.
See you next year,
if you haven't
adopted her by then.
(SIGHS)
My legs, they're
different, better.
No pain at all?
No, but less.
Four out of 10,
maybe five.
Can't be.
If whatever's causing
the pain's in your brain,
it's still a 10.
In your periphery, a zero.
It is. Some of the pain
is gone, but not all of it.
What does this mean?
Maybe Taub was right,
it's psychosomatic after all.
Which one of
you is House?
The big black guy.
Chris Carrick. Next time
you use my name in
a threatening e-mail,
it won't be just a bill,
it'll be a lawsuit.
Can you blame me?
Last time that happened,
the guy shot me.
What if the spinal block
triggered some sort of
placebo effect?
Guy's taken
the finest opiates
Blue Cross can buy,
how come they didn't
trigger a placebo effect?
(PAGERS BEEPING)
(SCREAMING)
What happened?
LYNNE: He just started
screaming. Do something!
Please, God,
do not let it be
what his father has.
I think he's faking.
How dare you?
What makes you think...
House, the kid's
in excruciating...
Where is it?
Where's what?
His idiot son
distracted the orderlies
so that Daddy Deathwish
here could down
a bottle of isopropyl.
Put him on dialysis
or in half an hour
he'll be a corpse.
You're hurting me.
Remember the feeling.
Maybe next time you
wanna help Pops, you'll
do a better acting job.
You can't help him.
Zach, why did
you do this?
Because he's
not Dad any more.
He just wants it
to be over with.
(CRYING)
Please, please,
just let him die.
FOREMAN: Fabry disease
might be able to cause
central and peripheral pain.
No angiokeratomata.
Lightning pain
from syphilis.
All the syph tests
were negative.
Why aren't you
guys still talking?
Because we ran
out of ideas.
Nothing explains this.
Something has to.
Unless nothing does.
So now you think it's...
Mine's a more interesting
version of nothing.
It used to be something.
We can't find anything
because whatever injury
caused the original pain
healed a long time ago.
The only thing left
is the drugs.
Opioid-induced pain.
Pain and the drugs
that treat pain work by
changing brain chemistry.
Sometimes to the point
where pain receptors read
painkillers as killer pain.
Take him off the drugs.
We can't cure him,
so we're gonna
torture him?
Torture is the cure.
Eventually his body
will recalibrate itself.
Assuming you're right.
Yes, I find it confusing
to assume otherwise.
How would you like
to stop taking Vicodin?
Good thing I'm
not the patient.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
It's open.
(CHUCKLING)
Thank you.
Is it too big?
She'll grow into it.
Put it there.
I take it
the home inspection
was pushed back?
I passed.
You do realize
that's a good thing?
This place was a disaster.
I had to stash a dirty
diaper in my briefcase.
So you buy another briefcase.
I let House supervise
himself. That's like
handing a 12-year-old
the keys to the liquor
cabinet and the car.
You passed the inspection.
The patient lived.
The car is still
in the driveway.
And the next time my
nanny gets sick? When House
wants to saw someone in half?
Did I mention you
passed the inspection?
I passed by their
meager standard,
I failed by mine.
Why do women
always do that?
Fail?
Create ridiculous standards
that no human could meet.
With your careers,
with your kids.
You gotta be more
like us men.
Be lazy? Blame others?
Get help. Most men in your
position have a deputy and
two assistants at work,
and a wife and two nannies
at home. You're not
Superwoman, don't be a martyr.
We'll be injecting
you with naloxone,
which will knock the opioids
out of your pain receptors.
If we're right,
your system will recalibrate
within a few hours,
and most of the pain
will be gone.
Hours?
I need those drugs.
Not if they're
causing your pain.
Then knock me out,
sedate me while you...
That takes drugs, too.
We need to clear everything
out of your system.
Please, I'll try
anything else.
TAUB: That's what
we're trying to stop.
So it's not your parents,
then it's your wife,
someone you were close...
A colleague.
We were
residents together.
I should've done more
to stop it. He had the
mother of all God complexes.
So busy treating
everyone's problems,
he was blind to his own.
Helped himself to
a vial of insulin.
It's a miracle he survived.
His friends
and family almost didn't.
He was a selfish ass.
It'll be over soon.
(JEFF GROANING)
This is lunacy.
You're torturing
this guy on a hunch.
It's the only
hunch we've got.
If I really wanted
to torture him, I'd
manipulate a clinical trial
in the hopes that
he'd sleep with you.
Are you suggesting I got
Thirteen in that trial
because of some personal...
I think you got her in
because of your usual
messiah complex.
I think you messed
with the appointment
schedule
because of your
l-like-to-have-sex complex.
I checked the logs.
You moved your most
promising patient
right before her.
False hope being
quite the aphrodisiac.
How's it false
if the trials are
showing results?
If it were that promising,
you wouldn't have to
change the schedule.
But, hey,
hope springs eternal.
(JEFF CONTINUES GROANING)
This was
a cooking accident?
First time making
Cherries Jubilee.
Awfully big fire.
If you ask me,
some of the portions
in that recipe were off.
I sure hope it happens
to be covered, under,
say, section three,
subsection 2.2,
paragraph one.
"Accidental fire damage."
In which case you'd have to
replace the entire water line
to fix the sagging pipe.
I guess so.
(PAGER BEEPING)
I'd hate to have your
next-door neighbors
end up with no hot water.
Lucky the fire skipped
your pipes entirely.
(JEFF GROANING)
(CONTINUES GROANING)
It's not working.
I know. I've started him
back on the pain meds.
Which means you can leave.
My son was right.
I've tried for so long
to protect him from...
But I'm the one
who's been selfish.
This is no way
for him to live.
Until we get an answer,
it's the only way.
There is no answer.
There's always an answer.
Then what is it?
He's been here
for four days.
Three suicide attempts.
You don't have an answer.
When I saw you,
when I saw the cane,
I thought, "Thank God,
a doctor who
will understand."
Because I sure
as hell don't.
My husband
thinks it's over.
So look me in the eye,
tell me you'd want to
live like that.
Then stabilize him,
get him in decent enough
shape for the drive home,
so he can finally...
(CRYING)
Okay.
There's gotta be something
we can do. We can't just
let the patient leave.
We didn't,
House did.
TAUB: Because he realized
there's nothing he could do.
THIRTEEN: There's always
something we can do,
something else we can try.
You're insane.
You know that, right?
Because I have principles?
Because you paid
more to bribe me
to lie on your claim
than the entire cost
of the repair.
I don't care if I pay,
as long as the people
who pocketed my premiums
for the last nine
years also pay.
I didn't break the pipe.
Whatever.
You wanna stick
it to the man,
that's fine by me.
You happy?
No. But I'm right.
(LAUGHS)
Lock up on your way out,
and don't touch the piano.
Testicles. What do
they make you think of?
STDs, testosterone issues,
that summer on Fire Island.
Oh, so close.
The correct answer
is epilepsy.
Epilepsy doesn't
cause chronic pain.
It does if it spreads
to the sensory region
of the brain,
then rewires
the pain neurons.
Would've shown up
on an EEG.
Not if the seizures
are in a place you
can't see on an EEG,
a place too deep
in the brain,
like the area that
controls the muscles
supporting the...
Testicles.
Feels like you got kicked
in the nads, doesn't it?
The abdominal pain, how it
all started. It wasn't the
stomach. It was lower, right?
It's everywhere.
But when it first started.
It started in the
stomach, cramps.
Like bad gas or
a permeating pain?
Like your kidneys were
being pulled out through
your scrotum?
Why?
Because epilepsy
is treatable.
Looks like we shot
the guys with the torches.
Yeah. Pays to hang around.
That selfish ass
with the God complex
who almost made
the stupidest decision
of his life,
it wasn't your colleague,
was it? It was you.
No.
See you tomorrow.
You're here early.
I'm feeling better.
What's wrong?
IV's leaking a little.
It's no big deal.
I'll be right back.
Foreman.
You busy tonight?
No.
Rita, the spike on
Dr. Hadley's IV bag
wasn't pushed in all the way.
I don't want
any dosing errors.
Sorry. It won't
happen again.
Stinks, doesn't it?
What?
The medication. When we
switch out the bags you
can smell it. It's disgusting.
I didn't smell anything.
She must be on
the placebo, then.
You offered to do House's
budget because you
wanted him to owe you,
wanted him to take
that case. Why?
I thought it would help
House, seeing someone
worse off than him,
possibly curing a guy
with even less to
look forward to.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Can I ask you something?
How would you
like my job?