[Sniffs]
What time?
4:30.
Why so late?
Make-up test
in social studies.
Did you invite Shelby for Saturday?
- No.
Do you want me to call her?
Yeah, that'd be great,
you calling a 12-year-old girl
for a sleepover.
It'll be fine.
- Make you a deal.
I'll call a friend
when you call a friend.
[Exhales]
It's your birthday,
do what you want.
Thank you.
Bye.
[Door closes]
Heh.
What did you forget?
Nothing.
Then why'd you come back?
'Cause I live here.
Come on, Samantha,
you're gonna be late
for school.
What are you talking about?
It's 4:30.
Are you okay?
I, uh...
[sets down coffee can]
Tired, I guess.
(Samantha)
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Great.
That's all I need to know.
You're late!
Okay, bye.
37-year-old male
with recurring blackouts.
Tell him to switch
from tequila to bourbon.
Worked for me.
The three doctors
he's already seen
already ruled out
drugs and alcohol.
Well, then it's epilepsy.
Tell him to buy
a hockey helmet--
EEG's clean.
So is the CT.
Relax.
Just because you got approved
by an adoption agency
doesn't mean you'll get approved
by the birth mother.
You're a single mom.
That puts you somewhere
below couples acquitted
in daycare scandals.
You're welcome, Dr. House.
It is an interesting case.
What time are you
seeing the mom?
Are you having
your guy follow me?
I just trashed
your social value as a mother,
and all I got was
a little sarcasm.
It means you don't feel
the need to defend yourself,
which means you're not worried
about getting a kid,
which means you've
already got one.
We're meeting at 11:00.
She's due to deliver
a baby girl in two weeks.
I'm sure
the mom'll be thrilled
to hand her crack baby
off to a doctor.
She's not a crack baby.
No, mother's
perfectly healthy.
She just had
to give up the baby
in order
to continue her work
on the human genome.
She confessed
to some past meth use.
What they don't confess to
is almost always
more interesting.
This is a mistake.
Because a kid you don't know
may have some problems
you don't know about
that she may have
passed on to a kid?
Because you're
a control seeking narcissist.
Which is fine,
good even, in some jobs.
But you're not equipped
to handle a real kid,
never mind
a factory second.
Where are you meeting her?
In a little place called
"follow me
and your urologist
will be buying himself
a new yacht."
They explained
the returns policy, right?
It's worse than video games.
I'm not changing my mind.
(Thirteen)
Could be post concussion syndrome.
Not without
a pre-concussion.
Pick a number.
For what?
Cuddy pool.
She got the nod.
Little tweaker's
due in 14 days.
That's great news...
I think.
It's good news.
The great news is
she insisted that she's
not gonna change her mind,
which means she's
actually thought
about changing her mind,
which means she's not sure
she's ready to be a mom,
which means she's
not ready to be a mom,
which means she's gonna
change her mind.
The only question is when.
$100 buy in.
Less than seven means
the next seven days.
But she's been dying
for a kid for three years.
No way she's gonna
back out now.
Not one of the options.
Mini strokes can cause
blackouts and memory loss.
Nine hours is a lot of time
to be out for a mini stroke.
And there'd be
residual damage on the ct.
(Thirteen) Guy works at home
as a consumer product tester.
He could've been exposed
to a toxin
that caused short term
memory loss.
Wouldn't show up
on imaging.
Cavernous Sinus Thrombosis
could absence seizures
and memory loss.
I'll take 7 to 14.
We have a player.
You just said it was
great news.
Now you want to bet
against her?
It's only great news
if she wants it
to be great news.
House knows her better
than any of us.
I'd rather use
pseudonym.
Good thinking.
I say she's gonna meet
the mom and bolt.
I'm going
for the early fold.
Check his home
for toxins
and his sinuses
for thrombosises.
Maybe he ODed on caffeine.
Apparently he didn't drink
the coffee.
He just smelled it.
Wow.
Did they just move here?
(Thirteen)
Six years ago.
This is no way
to raise a kid.
He's a single dad.
I'm sure
he's doing his best.
Which is why single people
shouldn't have kids.
You got a problem
with what Cuddy's doing?
You think
single mothers can't--
I think the traditional
family is a fraud.
Even married moms
are single moms.
Daddy just pays
some bills
and reads just enough
bedtime stories
to not kill himself
t of guilt.
My dad was great.
After my mom died--
he might be the exception.
On the other hand,
you are fairly screwed up.
No booze, no meds,
no drugs.
And no view.
Building's half-empty.
He'd rather have a view
of the turnpike than the park.
Park views are probably
50% more.
You're the surprised
the guy's a pragmatist
after looking
this place?
Guy's not a pragmatist.
He's a flagellant.
Oh. Looks like mold.
[Grunts]
[Baseboard peels off]
Mom would've cleaned better.
(Thirteen)
Exposure to certain types of mold
can cause short term
memory loss.
We're testing both of you.
I feel fine.
I'm sure you are.
We're just
being cautious.
So where do you guys go
other than home and school?
Nowhere.
Dad works at home,
and I go to school.
What about sports,
friends, travel?
Like I said, dad works at home,
and I go to school.
Must be hard not having
your mom around, huh?
I was only four
when the accident happened.
Still, I'm sure you both
miss her sometimes.
Not really.
You're strong.
No, I just don't get
what the big deal
about death is, you know?
Yeah.
How is she?
Physically, she's fine.
Mentally, she's weird.
I'm sure she's just
freaked out about her dad.
Mr. Harmon?
Mr. Harmon.
Where are you going?
[Elevator pings]
I have an appointment.
I have to go.
We haven't finished
with your treatment.
We're still waiting
on some test results.
I have an appointment.
Sorry, you're gonna have
to reschedule.
I really have to go.
Mr. Harmon, do you know
where you are?
Why are you
trying to stop me?
His eyes.
(Thirteen)
Is he having a seizure?
His pupils are responsive.
I think he's...asleep.
(Taub) He was just asleep.
Means no memory loss.
And sleepwalking
doesn't kill.
Unless he walks out
a window.
Sleepwalking's
not a diagnosis.
It's a symptom.
As long as we
can't figure out why--
stress-induced insomnia.
Lots of people sleepwalk.
Not in the middle
of the day
before they've even put
their head on a pillow.
Could be some sort
of narcolepsy.
Which is caused by--
there's usually
genetic history.
Or?
If you know the answer,
can you tell us the answer?
I don't know the answer.
Which brings us back to--or?
Some sort
of environmental trigger.
Which means?
It's a toxin.
So we are?
Being lead down
an annoying path.
I honestly don't know
where this is going.
Just following the clues.
We're right back
where we started.
The mold we found
doesn't cause these symptoms.
And there's nothing else
at his home.
And?
And you're obnoxious.
He never goes
anywhere else.
Which we know because?
Because he says so.
Because his daughter says so.
Cause they have
no reason to lie.
Which proves he never
goes anywhere else...
when...
he's...
conscious.
Oh, my god,
you're right.
He said he had
an appointment.
Next time,
let him keep it.
Send him home.
See where his dreams
take him.
[Soft music
plays over P.A.]
Becca?
Dr. Cuddy?
Lisa.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, you want one?
(Cuddy)
No thanks.
I can't stop eating them.
I guess it's, like, a craving.
I must have, like,
a dozen a day.
Oh, and this is decaf.
How have you
been feeling?
Oh, you know, tired,
fat, nervous.
Is there, um, anything
you want to ask me?
Uh, yeah, actually,
I just have one question.
Um, what are you
gonna call her?
Ah, I'm not sure.
It's all been
rather sudden, you know?
I like joy.
But as I said,
I haven't really decided yet.
Well, is there anything
you want to ask me?
It's okay.
The agency web site is filled
with prospective parents.
Their photos,
their biographies.
There's so many wonderful people
out there.
Wonderful couples.
Why did I choose
a single mom?
My grandmother was married
for 37 years
to a man that treated her
like garbage.
And my mom
would've stayed married
to my dad that long,
but he dumped her.
You know, I never understood
how you could fall
for the same crap
as your mother.
Then I met Tony.
When I read your bio,
a doctor,
a head of a hospital,
I saw your picture...
I don't want her
raised by a loser.
How long have you had
that rash?
I don't know.
A few days?
Have you had
any joint pain?
Yeah, I'm pregnant.
All my joints hurt.
They shouldn't all hurt.
Have you been using?
Not in seven months.
Not since I found out
I was pregnant.
That needs
to be checked out.
You sure
you don't want children?
You know, just because
we're stuck here
and I'm lying down
doesn't mean
we need to get deep.
You're afraid you'll make
the same mistake
you made with your wife.
Get caught taking some
other kid to a ball game.
I like my life as it is.
Alpha waves increasing.
(Taub)
Any change in demeanor?
No, nothing.
He just got up.
Maybe it's a result
of the blood pressure change.
Delta waves out of nowhere.
He's now asleep.
Brain's supposed
to turn off motor function.
If the brain was doing what
it was supposed to be doing,
we wouldn't be here.
He's leaving.
Come on.
(Cameron) She's 38 weeks.
You think it's fifth disease?
What's that?
It's a viral infection.
It can infect the fetus.
Usually in the first
20 weeks of pregnancy,
and in women who have trouble
with their immune system.
History of drug abuse could've
compromised her immune system.
I told you I haven't used
anything in seven months.
It does look more
like a heat rash to me.
Yes, well,
maybe we want to look
at the actual blood tests.
Of course.
She work for you?
Yeah.
Everybody here
works for you.
When this happens for real,
are you okay
to deliver here?
Yeah, sure.
Good.
Blood work's normal.
Test it again.
Tested it twice.
I'll get you some topical cream
for that rash.
I'm admitting her.
There's nothing
wrong with her.
There are dozens
of other things
this rash could indicate.
I want
a full fetal work up.
(House)
You're losing it.
That's what happens
when you have kids.
Ceaseless crying and nagging
leads to irrational fears.
It's impressive
that you didn't wait
for the actual crying
and nagging.
She had a lace pattern rash,
joint pain,
and a history
of drug abuse.
You would've done
exactly the same thing.
Uh-huh, and I'd be an excellent father.
- Oh!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Baby barf.
Maternity ward was handing out
free samples.
Well played, sir.
You leave me no choice
but to change.
My clothes,
not my mind.
That's exactly my point.
It's not gonna be me
and a cup.
It's gonna be
eight times a day.
If you can't handle wearing
that stain,
you can't handle a baby.
Why do you even care?
It's not like I'm ever gonna ask
you to babysit.
I'm a humanitarian.
We should stop him.
(Thirteen)
The whole point was to--
let him plow
into some innocent bystander?
His legs are working.
Obviously, his eyes
are working too.
His reaction time
could be slower.
He stopping.
Yeah, I see.
He's having sleep sex.
Maybe.
Pull up to her.
I know.
What'd that guy want?
Piss off.
Go after him. She's not a hooker.
- How do you know?
(Thirteen) Do you want me
to describe the clues,
or do you want to stop him
before he finishes off
the drugs he just bought?
Apparently,
Rip's a coke fiend.
Snow white.
(Taub)
Coke explains the narcolepsy.
Narcolepsy explains
the sleepwalking.
But it doesn't explain the rip
in the space time continuum.
Coke leads to sleepwalking,
which leads to coke,
which leads
to sleepwalking.
What caused
the first sleepwalking?
The coke he took
while he was wide awake.
Says he didn't.
Wouldn't be the first time
somebody lied about drug use.
(Kutner)
He has no reason to lie.
He knows he's sick.
His job doesn't drug test.
No relationship.
His daughter wouldn't find out.
Maybe he just forgot.
Forgot he did cocaine?
You're going with forgot
over lying?
Fits.
Cocaine explains
the narcolepsy.
Narcolepsy explains
the sleepwalking.
Whatever is in the cocaine
other than the cocaine
explains the memory loss.
Dealers cut this stuff
with all kinds of garbage.
Great, we'll start him
on immediate treatment
for all kinds of garbage.
You can narrow it down
in the lab.
Not without a sample.
So get a sample.
You want us to score cocaine
from a drug dealer?
It's exciting.
It's a fony.
It's necessary.
(Cameron)
There she is.
Amniotic fluid
looks good.
Good fetal movement.
Heart's beating nicely.
Heh.
What?
It looks like
pulmonary hypoplasia.
What's that?
The baby's lungs
are underdeveloped.
She won't be able
to breath on her own.
She might die?
I don't know.
If she was born today,
she'd be in trouble,
but we're not gonna let
that happen.
We'll put you on magnesium
to prevent labor
and steroids
to grow the lungs.
It's a good thing
Dr. Cuddy brought you in.
(Taub) How do you know
what a drug dealer looks like?
I'm not doing drugs,
if that's what you're asking.
I just noticed
that she had cash in her hand.
Obviously came from him.
Obviously didn't have
enough time
to perform
any other services.
I didn't notice
her holding--
there she is.
Uh, we're not cops.
Cops aren't allowed to say that,
right?
Yeah, they can say it.
Oh.
But if you were a cop,
you'd know that.
What do you want?
Um--ahem.
I would like to buy
some cocaine, please.
Oh, definitely
not a cop.
Thank you.
Wait.
It's good.
Glad you like it, Pablo.
Now can we go?
No.
You gave us the wrong stuff.
What are you talking about?
You got my best.
I know.
I don't want the good
"get your new customer
hooked" stuff.
I want the stepped on
"keep the old customer coming
back for more" stuff.
Are you crazy, bitch?
No, I'm a just a bitch
who knows what she wants.
[Squeaks]
Looks like this kid thing
is really working out
for you.
All of the shopping,
none of the stretch marks.
Not a good time.
Right, kid's
getting worse.
Blessing in disguise.
Although a completely
predictable one.
You take in strays,
don't be surprised
by the worms.
Still wearing
the sweater.
I didn't say
you weren't stubborn.
I said
you weren't maternal.
Thank you.
Go away.
You're getting crankier.
- Baby's sick.
Sorry m not finding
the fun in that.
Is it really worth it?
Just for the pursuit
of unconditional love?
Only you could see that
as a bad thing.
It's a fake thing.
There's no unconditional love.
It's just unconditional need.
Don't make this child
a victim
of your biological clock.
Victim?
You think she's
better off staying--
Yes!
Because at least she knows
she's not qualified
for the job.
Let me guess.
I'm gonna tell her not
to play ball in the house,
but she's not gonna listen.
No, actually,
I was going for
she sneaks her boyfriend in
while you're sleeping,
and he wants to do it
on the desk.
And at first she says no,
but she has issues
with self-esteem.
You know
you're gonna pay for that.
I'm paying for it
right now.
With wisdom.
Get out.
We found lactose.
The coke was cut
with milk powder.
Makes it nutritious.
Not much of a toxin.
It is if he's
allergic to milk.
He's not.
He has milk in his fridge.
How does
he like his coffee?
I don't know.
What does that--
what type of cereal's
in the cabinet?
Cocoa-something.
Why, what does it matter?
He likes his coffee black.
Milk's for the kid.
How can you be sure?
Because if he drank
the milk,
he'd know
that he's lactose intolerant.
Ask him, then treat him
for allergic reaction.
If he gets better,
we all get
to go home early.
Steroids make you
more prone to infection.
You'll have to stay here
for the new two weeks
so we can monitor you.
The baby's lungs, is that
because of...the meth?
Could be.
You must hate me.
If you'd done everything
right in your life,
I wouldn't be getting
a baby.
You're not scared?
I am scared.
You got, like,
this perfect life.
Not yet.
[Beeping]
What's that?
Heart rate's climbing.
What's wrong with her?
It's not the baby.
It's you.
I need two units
of O-negative, stat!
[Door opens]
The mother had stage two
placental abruption.
She's losing blood.
So deliver the baby.
The lungs are
ten weeks premature.
So deliver now,
risk the baby.
Deliver later,
risk the mom.
It's not your baby yet.
It's not your call.
She'll do whatever
I tell her to do.
Self-worth issues.
That's genetic, you know.
You should deliver now.
Right.
Are you serious?
You're not?
You just told me--
the wrong answer.
You can give the mom
more blood.
You can't give
the fetus more lungs.
The lungs might work.
It's the right
decision medically.
And yet you're here.
To get your opinion,
not to get jerked around.
See, this is what's
screwed up here.
You're not sure that this
is the right call,
but you are sure that this
is what you want to tell her.
And that scares you
because your motives
aren't medical.
Some part of you
doesn't want this baby,
and that part
wants to tell her to kill it.
This is
an impossible situation.
I'm advising her to take
the safest route.
Right.
Doesn't explain why
you changed your sweater.
I need your advice.
It's not cancer.
Wow!
Can you remove spleens
with your mind too?
You're here to talk
about Cuddy.
The file is a pretext.
Why the hell haven't you come
to talk to me about Cuddy?
I've been doing all sorts
of insane stuff.
If she can't handle
your insanity,
she can't handle a baby.
That's exactly
my point.
No, it isn't.
You're feeling threatened
because she's going on
to high school
and leaving you behind
to repeat the eighth grade.
She's sleeping
with the math teacher
to get a diploma.
Adoption is cheating?
Are they giving her
a fake kid?
That's the problem.
She gets to have
a relationship with a kid,
but she can't handle one
with an adult.
So she's gonna kill it.
Well, it does seem cleaner.
I've seen the file.
She's making a judgment call.
Decisions are never made
in a vacuum.
Just like your decision
to make her miserable.
You're doing this
because we no longer
have inkwells and Cuddy
doesn't have pigtails.
Why do you think
I did that?
How you doing?
Not sure.
Been keeping an eye
on the clock like you said.
I don't think I lost
any time.
The machinery
agrees with you.
That means your problems
were caused by the coke.
Can't believe
I did coke.
You were asleep.
I chose to do coke.
In your sleep.
You weren't responsible.
Something inside me
wanted to do it.
Something inside of me
didn't think it was wrong.
It's like a dream.
We all do stuff
in our dreams
we wouldn't do
when we're awake.
I don't.
What's that?
Did I fall asleep
and hurt myself?
I don't see any cuts.
Because there aren't any.
I think...
you're sweating blood.
Guy's bleeding
out of his pores.
What does that tell us?
Other than you don't want
to play basketball against him
and he's dying?
(Foreman) And neither cocaine
or allergies are the answer.
(Kutner) It's gotta be systemic.
Hemorrhagic virus, maybe?
(Thirteen)
You think it's Ebola?
His white blood cell count
would be through the roof.
It's not an infection.
D.I.C.?
Coags are normal.
It's cancer.
Leukemia explains everything.
(Kutner)
No fever. The bleeding.
No weight loss.
The rash.
No headache.
the fatigue.
Leukemia'd be obvious
from the CBC.
Leukemia has false negatives
all the time.
So we have four reasons
for leukemia,
four reasons against.
Only need one against.
Yeah, if we had one reason
for anything else.
Go do a bone marrow
biopsy.
What would you do?
I think...
I think you should wait.
But if I wait...
I could die.
There would be
more danger for you, but--
is this your opinion
as a doctor or as a mother?
It's my medical opinion.
It's my personal opinion--
[sobbing]
I don't want to wait.
It might only be one week.
We will keep you on plasma.
This is not my baby.
I have already sacrificed
nine months
for this stupid mistake.
I don't--I don't want
to sacrifice any more.
Becca, you asked my opinion
because you wanted to do
the right thing.
You are giving up this baby
because you don't want
to make the mistakes
your mom made,
her mom made.
You have a chance
to break this cycle
to do something great
for this baby.
No.
I need you
to hold still.
Unh.
Wait.
Have you been testing
any tanning creams or sprays?
No.
It's not a tan.
Means it's not leukemia.
(Kutner) Chem panel confirms
kidney failure, end stage.
Got him on dialysis?
BP's too low.
Too bad.
It would've been nice
to have more than an hour
or two to solve this thing
hemachromatosis?
He have tiny testes?
No. Scleroderma.
His skin's darker,
not lighter.
As much fun as 20 questions
tends to be,
he's blowing blood
out of every orifice,
you think it just
might be vascular?
Vasculitis?
If I had said it might be
"vitas gerular,"
would you have said
"vitas gerulaitis?"
Test him for vasculitis,
angio and blood.
Even if we're right,
he's gonna need
a kidney transplant.
Test the daughter.
She's 12.
Small kidney.
It just means he won't pee
as much.
Great for road trips.
I meant she's a minor
and daddy has a conflict,
so we're gonna need
Cuddy's signoff.
So get it.
She's...kind of busy.
(chase)
Clamp.
Suction.
Entering
the abdominal cavity.
There's the head.
(House)
Got a minute?
Get out of here.
Who's that?
(Chase)- Dr. Gregory House.
He's the one you'll be suing
when you develop sepsis.
Well, why is he here?
Better question is
why is she here?
You're an administrator.
Administrate.
I have a patient's daughter
needs a guardian ad litem.
That's it.
Tests are inconclusive.
But either way
he's gonna need--
House, get out!
This doesn't need you.
I do.
Head's out.
Later.
Later's too late.
And there she is.
(Cuddy)
Come on, cry.
Come on.
Joy, cry.
Cry, joy.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
[Baby crying]
(Chase)
That's the sound we like to hear
Blood count's
nine out of ten.
You hear that?
You just got
your first "A."
[Cuddy laughs]
She's...yours now.
Mazel Tov.
Now it's time
to say those magic words
you'll be telling her
for the rest of her life.
Mommy's gotta go to work.
(Cuddy) Have the risks
of the transplant procedure
been explained to you?
Damn it.
I was hoping you
weren't going to ask her that.
Of course she knows.
Can you just sign
the paperwork?
Dr. House explained to you
that all surgeries carry risk?
You could die.
And if you don't do it,
Daddy will die.
Stop pressuring her.
Sorry.
Daddy's perfectly healthy.
But we want you
to give him a kidney anyway
because it'd be cool
if he had three.
Shut up.
Do you understand the risks
of living with one kidney?
Yeah.
And you still want to proceed
with the transplant?
Yeah.
Okay, go ahead.
No.
I'm saying
you can proceed.
I'm saying I can't.
Whatever he has,
she has too.
She's sleepwalking.
(Kutner)
If we don't give him a new kidney,
he's dead in a week.
We have to transplant.
When your remote
has a dead battery,
you don't replace it
with another dead battery.
Whatever's killing
the dad's kidneys
is gonna kill
the kid's too.
It is possible the sleep issues
aren't medically related.
Maybe they're both insomniacs
due to the turnpike noise.
Maybe they both drink
too much coffee, maybe--
House is right.
How do you know?
Because the daughter's
sweating blood.
If they have the same thing,
it means there has to be
a common cause.
Which means it has to be
a toxin, infection,
or genetic.
And since we've ruled out
infections and toxins--
it narrows it down to any one
of a dozen genetic disorders,
each of which takes more
than a week to run.
Call Foreman.
Get to work.
(Wilson)
Cuddy is positively aglow.
What's your theory?
She's only acting happy
to make you miserable?
I need a genetic disease.
I'm sure
you're carrying a few.
Symptoms are kidney failure,
bleeding, and insomnia.
You paid off the pool?
Technically, anyone
who didn't enter is a winner.
It's not over yet.
Everyone's happy until they
unwrap that pretty present
and find they got a wall clock
in the shape of Africa.
Adoption's a cheat,
remember?
There's no real pregnancy,
so there's no stranded
dopamine receptors,
so there's
no postpartum depression.
Cuddy will be the happiest
new mother you've ever seen.
I've just given you
the answer, haven't I?
And now you're going
to walk out of here
without saying a word.
Nope!
(House)
Good news.
I know what you have,
and you're both
gonna be fine.
What?
Are you serious?
Yes and no.
So you do know what they have?
Yeah.
(Foreman)
But they aren't gonna be fine?
No idea.
They might be.
Why the hell would you
say they were?
To make them happy.
(Foreman)
For two seconds?
Technically, to see
if they can be happy.
We should've seen
a grin, a twinkle,
a sigh of relief,
something.
They're sick.
They're tired.
They're anhedonic,
incapable of experiencing
pleasure.
Something's bushwhacked
their dopamine receptors.
They're depressed.
Mom's dead.
Dad's dying.
You should know
that being bummed
isn't necessarily
a pathology.
Being bummed doesn't explain
their lack of friends
or their indifference
to each other.
Why their place
had no music,
no view, no decor.
But if you can't feel pleasure,
what's with the cocaine?
Really?
Is that why you do drugs?
Because you're happy?
Most people do 'em
because they want to be happy.
His subconscious craved it,
needed it.
Most common cause
of anhedonia is schizophrenia.
Sure, in white folk.
They're black?
They're liars.
What's your name?
Jerry Harmon.
Your real name.
Hosarian?
Herzog?
H'ali-baba?
Hammoud.
Jamal Hammoud.
Changed it
when we invaded Iraq
the first time.
How'd you know?
You and your daughter
have familial
Mediterranean fever.
It's a genetic disease
contracted by people
of Mediterranean descent.
Sephardic Jews,
Armenians, Arabs.
Causes anhedonia,
seizures, kidney failure,
even lactose intolerance.
Symptoms are set off
by age and stress.
Kid couldn't get happy,
but she could get stressed
by daddy dying.
You don't know
if we'll get better?
Treatment tends to be
hit and miss
once you reach
the sweating blood stage.
Start them on colchicine
and melphalan.
His kidneys
are fried.
If he doesn't have FMF,
the colchicine will kill him.
Boy, sure hope I'm right.
Mr. Harmon?
Mr. Harmon, I need you
to open your eyes.
Feeling better?
How's Samantha?
Healthy enough
to toss you a kidney.
Dad?
Sammy.
[Laughter]
The baby's doing great.
I...
I can't imagine how hard
this must be for you.
I was--I was stupid
and selfish.
You were scared.
Yeah, but you
wouldn't have been.
That's not true.
Well, I mean,
you would've been scared,
but...you would've done
the right thing anyway.
And I want to be like that.
I don't--I don't want to be
a loser.
You're not a loser.
When I saw you hold her
and the look
on your face,
it was the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
And that's
when I realized...
I can't.
Becca.
My life, it's always been
about pain, and anger,
and disappointment,
never about love.
And that's when I realized,
you know, it could be.
And I can't give
that away.
Becca, don't do this.
Uh...
what you're feeling
is natural.
But you're filled
with hormones,
and emotion, and fear,
and...
you just can't make a huge
decision like this right now.
You have to give it
some time.
I am...I'm so sorry.
It's a decision
that changes everything.
Changes the rest
of your life.
I hope so.
[Knock on front door]
It's really not
the greatest time for gloating.
There's more
than one baby in the sea.
The world is full
of teenage boys
riding bareback.
No.
I'm done.
I can't go through
that again.
You're quitting.
Just like you quit IVF.
Yeah, just like that.
There, you just
did it again.
It's too bad.
You would've made
a great mother.
You son of a bitch.
When I was getting
a baby,
you told me
I'd suck as a mother.
Now that I've lost it,
you tell me I'd be great
as a mother.
Why do you need to
negate everything?
[Softly]
I don't know.
Good night.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
Subtitles by LeapinLar