(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
You made your point,
now how about letting us
do our job?
Our point will be made
when your company stops
tearing down this mountain.
Then who's gonna
feed our kids? You?
If you really cared
about your kids,
you'd want them to
have air to breathe
when they grow up.
What did you say,
you son of a bitch?
You guys aren't
the problem.
You're being hurt
more than anyone.
You breathe in
that coal dust...
Coal is the dirtiest
energy on Earth.
Gonna need some backup.
Not enough for
you thugs to assault
the environment?
Doug, please, don't.
Susan? Susan, you okay?
She needs to get
to a hospital.
She's just dehydrated.
We have medics here.
Let them give her fluids.
She has no pulse.
Either unhook your arm
or I'm gonna break it off.
Either way,
this protest is over.
The protest is over,
come on!
(MINERS SHOUTING)
All right.
(MINERS CHEERING)
What happened?
You passed out.
It's okay.
Just dehydrated.
You know we'll be back.
We'll be back!
Hey, stop screwing around.
I'm not screwing around.
I just can't...
I can't stand up.
(GRUNTS)
I need to push back
our getaway.
No, you don't.
I found you a board,
perfect size to learn on.
I'm just postponing.
O'Neil, from Philly General,
wants me to get a patient
in to see House.
So?
I owe him a favor.
He's taken about
a dozen of my referrals
over the last year.
I meant, so,
that's five seconds
to hand House the file,
30 for him to question
your real motives,
a minute for
witty comments
comparing the length
of your legs
to Thirteen's...
Plenty of time left over
for the shore.
I need to make sure
he doesn't toss
the file in the trash
as soon as
I'm out of sight.
Babe, can't you
repay the favor
on another case?
After last week,
I could really use
a break from this place.
We both could.
Once I'm sure
he's really on the case,
then we're out of here.
And these legs, and
every other part of me,
will be all yours.
He's seen three
different specialists.
Interesting.
Almost as interesting
as you trying to step
into Kutner's shoes
just days after
he stepped out of them.
CAMERON: I am not
shoe shopping,
I'm just trying
to repay a favor to
his referring doctor.
What's the mystery?
The nutcase spends all his
free time wreaking havoc
at toxic waste dumps.
Tox screen's negative.
No neurological, muscular
or cardiovascular
abnormalities.
The guy cares
about the environment,
that makes him a nutcase?
TAUB: He's a single guy
in his 20s,
he cares about getting
his hybrid waxed by girls
who care about
the environment.
See? Not a nutcase.
He's probably just faking
so he can sue the cops
and get a six-figure
settlement.
If he was trying
to fake an illness,
why would he consent
to be seen by the best
diagnostician in the country?
Now look who's trying
to get her hybrid waxed.
We need to do
a vestibular
caloric test,
see if the balance
problem starts above
or below the neck.
And when I say "we,"
I mean you.
You're the one
with a favor to
repay, not them.
I'm going to be
injecting ice-water
in your ear canal.
If the resulting
eye movements
are at all erratic,
then the balance problem's
in your inner ear.
Those in every room?
I think so.
Can you get rid of them?
Preferably from every room?
They use over 30 pesticides
to grow commercial flowers.
You'd think
the medical industry
would be a lot more...
Concerned with medicine?
Let's fix your body,
then you can go back
to fixing the Earth.
This is gonna get
a little uncomfortable.
I just spent 14 hours
chained to a tire.
Most doctors
would recommend...
Our planet's headed
for destruction.
Coastlines underwater,
a million species extinct.
Whoa! Feels like
I'm tumbling
head over heels.
It's normal. Sometimes
this test causes vertigo
and nausea.
Cameron just
brought me a case.
Cameron is happy
in the ER.
There's no way
she wants her nose
back on your grindstone.
Egg-white omelet,
no bacon,
whole-wheat toast.
I say it's not
my grindstone
she's after,
and not her nose
she wants on it.
She and Chase
are practically
living together.
What did you just order?
An omelet.
Since when do you
pass on the swine?
And wheat toast?
Might as well eat
a sheet of sandpaper.
Yes, but I don't like
eating the same thing
two days in a row.
Your bro's nurse
not loving
the love handles?
I'm just not
in the mood
for bacon,
and you are obviously
trying to avoid
talking about Kutner,
which is odd because
you spent a whole week
obsessing about why...
He's no longer
on my team.
I'm sorry he's
no longer on my team.
There's nothing else
to talk about.
You're wearing the
watch he gave you
for Secret Santa.
Five functions,
including a stopwatch
to time how long
it takes you to
ask me if I'm okay.
You gonna order?
Not hungry.
It's just weird.
She's brought cases before,
but he's never made her
run the tests.
Maybe he's looking for
someone to mother him
after what happened.
The only kind of
mothering House wants
involves a bullwhip,
leather diapers
and a credit card.
Mommy's home.
Test made the patient lose
his lunch, but his calorics
are normal,
his inner ear is fine
and he still can't
balance himself.
How many normal test
results do we need
to know the patient's
a granola-filled phony?
He's not lying
about his symptoms.
And you know this
because...
She changed her shoes.
If he was faking,
he'd have vomited on
the other side of the bed.
Sparring with the police
and chaining yourself up
for days can cause stress.
Stress screws with
the heart and arteries.
Carotid atherosclerosis
could cause a loss
of balance.
Wouldn't show up
on CT or MRI.
It could also be our
only warning before
a massive stroke.
(SIGHS) Do a Holter
and a carotid doppler,
see if his heart skips
for more than
the Spotted Owl.
Although I didn't
say "we," if I had...
(HICCUPPING)
Sorry if this is
screwing up the test.
Been hiccupping
a lot lately, but
not as bad as this.
How much is a lot?
And how long is lately?
It's been on and off
for about a week.
Maybe a few hours a day.
Did you tell the doctors
in Philly about it?
They didn't seem to think
it was any big deal.
Hey, so we're still
leaving tomorrow,
aren't we?
I'm not sure.
The referring doctors
didn't realize that
his hiccups were...
Hiccups?
With this
duration and intensity,
most likely pathological,
and it could mean
it's serious.
Are you avoiding me?
No.
So, I shouldn't be
at all concerned
that you're treating another
doctor's patient for hiccups
instead of going on
the vacation I spent
a week planning?
There is a reason I need
to stay with this case
a while longer,
but I can't tell you
what it is.
So, you admit you
lied to me, now you're
asking me to trust you.
Yes.
Okay.
No sign of heart
or arterial problems,
but he's been hiccupping
on and off for over a week.
Nice. I'm hooked.
You can get back to
your shift at the ER,
except, as far as
the ER is concerned,
you're on vacation, right?
I postponed a trip
because I'm concerned
about the patient.
Explains why
you ditched Chase and
came to the differentials,
not why you ran
the tests.
You told me to.
Well, I'm not your boss,
something you usually
take great pleasure
in pointing out.
Hey, you don't still
have the hots for me,
do you?
I care about the patient
and I care about the people
who work on your team,
they've been through
a lot lately.
I just thought I...
Was Florence Nightingale
and you're gonna nurse us
back to spiritual
and mental oneness.
That would make sense
if we were having this
conversation a week ago.
Think what you want,
that I'm here to
get a job,
that I'm here
to wrap you in
swaddling clothes.
Problem is, I think neither.
Because neither makes sense.
The only thing
that does, doesn't.
Pathological hiccups
plus inability
to balance, go.
What she said.
Brain would connect the two.
It could if Cameron
hadn't already CT'd
his head.
Empty as her
boyfriend's calendar.
What does this have
to do with Chase?
Nothing.
Not sure yet.
Patient is
on a jihad against
commercial flowers,
he's picketed
several nurseries.
Organophosphate poisoning
can cause both hiccups and...
No GI problems,
no hypersalivation.
It's possible it's not
connected to a protest.
MS wouldn't show on the CT,
and his name is Swenson.
Scandinavians
have an increased
susceptibility to MS.
Better theory than,
"He's faking it."
The clogs have it.
Do a lumbar puncture
to confirm MS.
I guess we'll just
continue to twiddle
our thumbs.
God, I hope
that's a euphemism.
How am I supposed to
do a lumbar puncture
on a patient with
intractable hiccups?
I'm trying to figure out
what that could be
a euphemism for.
You'll find a way.
(SIGHS)
(DOUG HICCUPPING)
You're not worried House
is gonna be pissed you're
helping me do the test?
He said find a way,
and you did.
How do you think
House is doing?
That why you're here?
Yeah.
No, it isn't.
Even if House was messed up
by Kutner's suicide,
it wouldn't matter.
He already thinks
life is nasty,
brutish and long,
and misery helps
his diagnostic skills.
All of which you know,
so, why are you here?
Which answer
would you believe?
If you want Kutner's place,
it's fine by me.
I could use someone else
with the stones to
stand up to House.
But you've got to know
that's gonna blow up your
relationship with Chase.
All I did was postpone
a three-day trip.
With Chase,
to be with House.
(HICCUPS)
What are you doing?
Ordering IV chlorpromazine.
This could still be
neurological.
You can cloud
his mental status.
You wanna get the
needle in his spine
or you wanna talk?
You and House
been talking about
filling Kutner's slot?
Yeah, we went straight
from the funeral
to Human Resources.
You interested
in getting back
on the team?
I'm interested in knowing
if Cameron's interested.
She's been running
all the tests
for House's case.
Well, she hasn't said
anything to me.
But I guess the referring
doctor might have asked her
to keep an eye on him.
Do you think Cameron's
in love with House?
That is a ridiculous question.
She's in love with you.
Are you in love
with House?
That is an even more
ridiculous question.
Two questions,
zero answers.
I think I can
extrapolate from there.
FRANNI: Dr. House?
Sorry, I'm just
the zone delivery guy.
I'm Doug Swenson's wife.
His history said
the environmental
kamikaze was single.
He probably didn't
want me to worry.
He told me he was
in jail with some of
the other protesters.
Yeah, well,
no worries there.
He's in jail a lot.
Not so often in
the hospital.
I searched his e-mail,
and I found the referral
to you yesterday.
You must really
love your husband,
and travel by rickshaw.
Only took you 18 hours
to get here.
Who eats kale?
It's so bland it doesn't
even taste like kale.
I had to find somebody
to take care of
our 4-year-old son.
Doug's all right,
isn't he?
I have no idea.
I know he's an idiot,
and now I've learned
that he's a liar,
so we're making...
Who told you
that I was in here?
The doctor in the office
next to yours said that
you might be here.
I got it figured out.
That mean we don't
need to do the LP?
I was talking to her.
You're not even
supposed to be here.
You want us to stop or not?
What? I don't care
what you do with him.
You're not doing a favor
for a doctor in Philly,
you're doing a favor
for an oncologist
in North Jersey.
I'm spying on you
for Wilson?
Spying, pre-emptive
grief counseling...
Wilson sees you
10 times more than I do,
he's a better liar,
and he wouldn't have
to cancel a vacation
to do it.
Good points. Also doesn't
explain the diet.
What does any of this
have to do with my husband?
Nothing.
Meet Mrs. Environmental
Nutbag, or did you keep
your maiden name?
He's married?
Yep. Got a kid, too.
Double threat,
eco-freak and
deadbeat dad.
House!
Sorry, parentally
challenged.
No, his neck.
It's torticollis,
reaction to
the chlorpromazine.
That's not just a spasm,
it's swollen.
Crunchy.
FOREMAN: It's definitely
not MS.
Crunching sounds were
caused by an air leak
between his lungs.
CAMERON: The leak in his
mediastinum could've been
caused by prolonged hiccups.
More likely it was
the neck spasm.
CAMERON: Most likely
it was there all along.
We just didn't notice
until the other symptoms
made it worse.
So, what causes
loss of balance,
pathological hiccups,
and a hole in
his Gloria Steinem?
He was protesting
a lumber mill last fall.
Sarcoid's been linked
to pine forests.
No, his AC levels
are normal.
THIRTEEN: Progressive
systemic sclerosis?
Guy practically lives
in industrial waste sites.
If a solvent got absorbed
through his lungs, caused
an autoimmune firestorm...
Start him on
IV methylprednisolone
for systemic sclerosis.
Do a full work-up
to confirm.
By myself?
Without yourself.
Grab a bat.
Grab some pine.
Time to bring in
the first string.
Why?
You obviously
want to be here.
I can't figure out why.
So I want to see
where you go when
you can't be here.
You know what vacation
means, right?
You here because of House,
Chase, or overtime issues?
He's very concerned.
Chase, not House.
If it's all right
with you,
I'd rather communicate
with Chase by communicating
with Chase.
Are you in love
with House?
You are not
concerned about me.
You're marking
your territory.
You shouldn't be
involved with House,
neither should I,
neither should anyone.
You and Chase
are good together.
Don't screw it up.
FRANNI: When are you
gonna stop this?
How can you
ask me to stop?
You're in a hospital.
You have a son.
The steroids ought to get him
breathing normally again.
But autoimmune diseases
are serious.
Might not be a bad idea
to take some time at home,
rest up.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I can't just quit.
Do you hate us
that much?
I love you,
and I love our son.
But why should he
matter more than
everyone else's?
He does.
Why?
Because he's biologically
connected to me?
There's no rational reason.
He's our son.
And he's going to need
to drink clean water
and breathe clean air.
I'm doing this
for him, too.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Come on in, House.
Because who else
is it going to be
at 10:30 at night?
And, no, thanks,
I already ate.
I didn't ask you
to dinner.
But you were going to.
And when I explained
that I'd eaten hours ago,
you were going to move on
to your real entree,
rifling through
my kitchen.
Hmm.
Inviting me to
search your kitchen.
Means you know
that I'd find nothing,
or you know that
I'd find something,
so you're hoping that
I'm gonna assume the former
and I won't bother to look.
Or it means it's late,
I'm tired,
I know you're here
to advance some
paranoid theory
based on a single
egg-white omelet, and I'd
like to get it over with
so we can both
go to sleep.
Your single-omelet theory
conveniently overlooks
the grassy knoll you had
for lunch today,
a vegetable
and grain gag-a-thon.
The Warren Commission
found no evidence of
a second lunch,
possibly because
it was stolen from
the doctors' lounge.
You're not getting
any fatter,
your medical records
were clean.
You checked my...
You're alone tonight,
so it's Kutner.
How could Kutner
have any conceivable...
Your patients live,
your patients die,
you float above it all
like a medical colossus.
But a fellow doctor dies...
That's brilliant.
Kutner was a wake-up call
that if I didn't eat
healthier,
I might kill myself.
Mortality is mortality.
And ice cream
is ice cream.
Full-fat content.
Quadruple-fat content.
Stuff you haven't eaten
just proves you haven't
eaten it.
You were hoping
for evidence of
stuff I have eaten?
First door on the right.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(DOUG SCREAMING)
Excruciating pain
in his left leg.
Acute onset,
about 10 minutes ago.
What are you
doing to him?
I assume they were checking
for vascular pulsation.
Either it's negative
or he's a big wuss.
It's not a tumor
or an aneurysm.
Metabolic bone disease?
Bone density's normal.
But the bone covering
might not be.
If it's osteomyelitis,
an infection eating away
at his periosteum...
Explains the pain.
Odds are it's
a subclinical infection
that we made worse
with the steroids
we gave him.
Start him on IV antibiotics,
x-ray his legs to confirm
osteomyelitis.
Cameron's already
done a full set of
lower body x-rays.
Infection obviously flared,
do them again.
Even if I had
changed my diet,
what possible reason
could I have for
hiding it from you?
Ankle, tibia, fibula,
all look normal.
No inflammation,
no signs of osteo.
(GROANS)
Hang in there,
we're almost done.
You and your wife,
you talk about stuff?
Sex.
No. Anything else.
Money.
I'm gonna go way out
on a limb here.
Foreman not
a Chatty Cathy?
Normally, it doesn't matter.
Last week, it did.
You want to date men,
good chance talking
won't be...
His femur's fractured.
That's impossible.
It's the hardest bone
in the body.
And he broke it
lying in bed.
How can you have
a broken femur without
so much as a bruise?
Whatever broke it
had to do it
from within.
Osteogenesis imperfecta?
Brittle bones
wouldn't cause hiccups,
plus we'd have seen
abnormal coloring
in the sclerae.
Which leaves cancer.
Since when does
bone cancer
cause hiccups?
Which means it's
a bone cancer.
Or it's not cancer.
House is right.
It'd be hard to find
a guy outside Chernobyl
who'd been exposed
to more carcinogens,
pesticide plants,
nuclear waste sites.
Tell Chase to
repair the break.
You two prep him
for chemo.
You want to blast him
with chemo for a cancer
we don't even know he has?
No. I want to blast him
with chemo for a cancer
that explains the symptoms.
CHASE: Intramedullary nail.
FOREMAN: Hold on.
That your House imitation?
Some late-breaking epiphany?
Just need you to get
a bone biopsy before
you insert the pin.
For a broken leg?
House is prepping him
for chemo.
Thought it might be worth
checking for cancer before
pumping him full of poison.
Does Cameron agree
with House?
Cameron's not on
the case anymore.
Oh.
Still enjoying your
day off, I see.
Why are you
prepping him
for chemo?
The more interesting
question is,
why do you care?
You're not even sure
that it's...
What I mean is,
why do you care
from here?
You can monitor
the patient from home.
What's the difference
between here and home?
You're not at my home.
This has nothing
to do with...
Any other differences?
Hmm.
There's less
medical equipment,
more training bras,
and more
Vegemite sandwiches.
Actually, technically,
right now Chase is here,
but that's because
I called him and
you didn't know that,
and it's irrelevant
to my point, which is
you and Chase are over.
You are wrong.
You decided that his
single drawer of clothes
is one drawer too many.
But you don't have
the guts to tell him,
so you're emotionally
walking away instead of
actually walking away,
which is stupid because
only one of those is
good for your heart.
He's gonna ask me
to marry him.
I was looking for
some thick socks,
found the ring.
And you want to say no.
So I circle right back
to his single drawer
of clothes...
I don't want to say anything.
I don't want him to ask.
Not now.
Kutner... We're all
a little freaked out.
We go home,
we just want
to hug someone.
We just want to know
everything's gonna be okay.
I don't want him to propose
just because he's scared.
Oh.
She's got a headache, fever,
she's completely exhausted.
Tell him about
your chest, honey.
Her breasts
are really tender.
You guys have a hot tub?
No.
So you must go
to the gym a lot?
Not in years.
But maybe when you
travel on business,
you zip on down
to that complimentary
hotel spa.
No.
Sorry, did you
just say yes?
What the hell is
wrong with her?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Got a minute?
He doesn't.
What's wrong
with her?
Sorry, I'm sure she's
got a medical crisis,
and I need more time to
figure out some leading
questions for your wife.
What's going on
with Cameron?
She doesn't want back on
my team, and she doesn't
want to jump me.
Okay.
What?
You ask a question,
I rule out two possibilities,
and you're satisfied?
That means you don't
want an answer,
you just wanted
to know there wasn't
a particular answer.
Either you were worried
that she wanted back
on my team
or you were worried
she wanted back on me.
This isn't
a medical crisis,
is it?
Could be. A lot of STDs
hang in the balance.
I give up.
Vinegar compresses
four times a day.
Any chance I could
just leave it at that?
No. Pseudomonas folliculitis.
It's a skin infection
from crowded and
contaminated hot tubs,
which you obviously use,
but not with your husband.
Tried to help
a sister out.
The nuclei were
all normal-sized,
bone cells are
well-differentiated.
No dysplasia means
no cancer.
That's good, isn't it?
We hope so, although it also
means we still have no idea
what caused the break.
How does it feel?
It hurts.
Is it supposed
to look like that?
No, but it's probably
just residual bleeding
from the surgery.
We should be able to...
Need two units of FFP,
right away.
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
He's bleeding out.
Means it's gotta
be cancer.
It's gotta be,
except it's not.
The biopsy was negative.
Biopsies can be wrong,
symptoms can't.
All signs point to cancer,
but you can't blast a cancer
you can't find.
Sure you can.
Prep him for
total-body irradiation.
You do realize
that's insane.
Not unless you think
the cancer's cleverly
hiding outside his body.
Steroids already weakened
his immune system.
That much radiation
will kill him before
it kills the cancer.
And if he doesn't have cancer,
we could cause one,
or destroy his
immune system altogether.
The guy could die
from an infected toenail.
So you'd rather do nothing,
just let him die on his own?
I'd rather make
his cancer worse.
Give him insulin-like
growth factor, make any
tumor or malignancy grow.
Grows big enough,
we can find it.
That's like pouring
gasoline on a fire.
At least total-body
irradiation is
an actual treatment.
His idea is better.
Pour away.
I've lost my mojo.
Have you retraced
your steps?
Does your cleaning lady
check your pockets before...
I was clueless about Kutner,
I was wrong about Cameron,
Taub just came up
with an idea that I should
have seen long before he did.
No one saw anything
coming with Kutner,
you hardly ever see
Cameron anymore,
and you hired Taub to
come up with ideas that you
wouldn't have come up with.
And I have no idea
why you're eating carrots.
Good.
I'm losing my mind,
all you got to say
is, "Good"?
House, a guy you worked
with for two years,
who you mentored,
and, yes,
possibly even cared about,
just blew his brains out.
You can't find the
reason, can't find
the meaning in it,
because sometimes
there isn't any.
Sometimes
this is all there is.
You should be losing it.
You'd be crazy
not to be off your game.
But your mojo's
right where
you left it.
Just keep playing with it.
I gotta go.
Help yourself.
I know this is
a tough process.
At the first sign
of any tumors
or masses we can...
Start saying prayers?
It's gonna be okay.
Once we can...
No, it is not gonna be okay.
You're growing
his cancer.
This isn't
the doctors' fault.
I've exposed myself
to a lot of bad stuff.
I knew the risks.
(WHEEZING)
I want my life
to mean something,
and if that means
I'm destined to...
(EKG ALARM BLARING)
He's in V-tach,
and no pulse.
Grab the paddles.
Oh, God.
Charging. Clear.
I've been looking for you.
And I've been
thinking about you.
Just hadn't reached
the looking stage yet.
Which is the problem.
You asked for a day,
I gave you two.
You told me you had
a secret you couldn't
share, I respected that.
Now I don't know
what's worse,
blowing off our vacation
to hang around House,
or continuing to
blow it off when
he won't hang around you.
If you think I'm the
least bit interested
in House...
I don't know what
I'm supposed to think.
I know this looks bad
and...
I don't care how it looks,
I care what it is.
And you're not
telling me what it is.
I'm trying to
trust you, but...
I just...
I need a little more time.
No.
This has nothing
to do with House.
Yeah, well, it has
nothing to do with me
either, not anymore.
Let me know
when I can come
pick up my things.
TAUB: Nothing on the echo.
We drew a troponin level,
no signs of
myocardial ischemia.
All the tests were normal.
Loss of balance,
pathological hiccups,
air leak between the lungs,
broken femur,
now tachycardia. Go.
Come on, give me something.
Give me a bad idea,
maybe I can turn it
into a good one.
Fine. Open him up,
put in a defibrillator.
FOREMAN: That's permanent
and risky.
We don't even know what,
if anything, is wrong
with his heart.
Redo all the tests.
In the meantime,
open him up,
put in a defibrillator,
so he can live long enough
for you to finish the tests.
Balance organs, nerves,
lungs, bones, heart.
Things you use
to make bratwurst?
There's no sign
of infection,
it's not a metabolic
or autoimmune disease.
It's definitely not cancer.
I think.
Definitely not cancer.
Aren't you gonna pick?
I'm thinking.
Is there
a ticking clock?
You already
put your money in.
You never do that
until you decide.
That's very observant of you.
Too bad you distracted me.
Now I'm thinking I might
change my mind.
There's nothing healthy
in that machine.
No, there's not.
Gummi Bears.
You hate Gummi Bears.
People can change.
No.
And more importantly,
I hate them.
Oh, fine.
Then I won't
offer you any.
You manipulative bitch.
You're not suddenly
eating healthy because
you want to.
You're eating healthy
because you know
I don't want to.
I've been mooching food
for 10 years,
so either something
started bothering you
this week or you're...
Screwing with you.
It needed to be done.
After Amber died, I withdrew,
tried to change everything,
hoping I'd sort it out,
find some deeper truth.
It was a mistake.
I should have gone back
to normal, to here and now.
Because that's all
we can ever really
count on.
Things need to get back
to normal in your life.
And what could be more normal
than me screwing with you,
and you figuring it out?
You manipulative bitch.
TAUB: We need to put in
a cardioverter defibrillator.
It'll keep your heart beating
while we keep looking.
What does that mean?
It means, even if
we figure this out,
you'll have to stop
protesting anywhere
not near a hospital.
Hi. Got a few questions.
We're about to
start doing...
A hopefully pointless
medical procedure.
Your life and my mojo
hang in the balance.
Pesticides are evil,
which means that commercial
flowers are doused in evil,
but plant life is
nature's answer to evil.
So you have a garden.
No. We live in
an apartment.
A window box then?
No.
Potted plants?
Nothing.
The commercial
growers...
Yeah, they're evil.
Yeah, got it.
House, I really don't think
we have time for this.
Your marriage sucks.
Thank you.
All marriages suck.
Your marriage sucks.
No.
I love her.
He loves a tree in Oregon
more than he loves you,
but he can't have
sex with it.
Unless it's
that slutty oak
outside Portland.
You want to get
to your point?
She's had enough.
She's gonna leave,
maybe she's just not
putting out, whatever.
You gotta make it right.
Right away.
You gotta compromise
that precious flower
principle.
Never.
Once.
Three weeks ago.
Our anniversary.
I missed the dinner
to be at that rally.
You planned it for months.
You were mad, really mad.
I bought you flowers.
I brought them home.
You were gone,
so was your suitcase.
I tossed them,
bought you the earrings.
Roses?
Yes.
You have sporotrichosis.
It's an infection from
the thorn of the rose,
which by any other name
is still a cheap marital aid.
The flowers are
what gave me...
Lesion on your eighth
cranial nerve knocks out
your balance,
another on your phrenic nerve
gives you serial hiccups.
We then spread it
to your bones and heart
with steroids
and insulin-like
growth factor.
Please tell us that
this is good news.
It's good news for him,
it's good news for
future generations.
It's crappy news for you.
He's gonna be fine.
And he'll never
doubt himself again.
There you go.
Damn. I was hoping
to interrupt something.
Your favor's repaid,
patient's cured.
He's already packing
for another Earth Day
extravaganza next week.
He almost died.
He can't take a few days
at home with his family?
People only change after
a trauma if they wanted
to change before the trauma.
Or if they've watched too many
After School Specials.
You talking about Chase?
I'm talking about you.
You lost husband number one,
no surprise that the death
of a colleague
would make you question
another long-term lease.
You teaching
commitment classes?
'Cause I thought
you were too busy
with your lecture...
I'm sure that was
going to be hysterical.
Let me just give you
the Cliff Notes.
Don't try to dump him
by dumping cases on me.
I told you, I never
wanted to dump Chase.
Absolutely.
You wanted him
to dump you.
It's totally different,
much less guilt.
Either way, you're out
of reasons to avoid him.
Kutner was a pretty
dumb one to begin with.
I should never have
postponed our vacation.
I should never
have planned it.
I found the ring
in your sock.
I didn't want you
to propose out of some
sort of knee-jerk reaction
to what happened
to Kutner.
Well, I guess you don't have
to worry about that anymore.
I'm not. I...
I don't care how it happens,
I just want it to happen.
Are you proposing to me?
I'm proposing that
you propose to me.
After I broke up with you?
After you ruined my
planned proposal?
You expect me to...
I'm not expecting.
I'm hoping.
(SIGHS)
Yes.
(HOUSE PLAYING JAZZ ON PIANO)
Solved another case,
busted Wilson.
Looks like you're not
losing it after all.