(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PEOPLE SNIFFLING)
(STABILIZED MONITOR BEEP)
CHARLOTTE: Bye.
I want to be
alone with my wife.
I'm a selfish SOB.
I never got you to Rio.
There was always
one more problem
at the stores.
You deserved
better than that.
I love you.
I always have.
I'm ready.
CHARLOTTE: It's okay.
(SNIFFLING)
I know...
(GASPING)
(WHEEZING)
(GRUNTING)
(WEAKLY) Somebody
help her.
Help her!
Fifty-four-year-old
woman with acute
respiratory failure.
No anaphylaxis,
lung issues
or tracheal lesions.
Tox screen
was clean for coke
and amphetamines.
I will give you 30 reasons,
one for each pound
that caused the apnea,
which inflamed
the epiglottis.
Why's our rainbow coalition
missing Brown and Bi?
Thirteen's with the patient,
and Kutner's dog's sick.
He should be in
by lunch.
No apnea because
no sleeping problems
when she's sleeping.
She's spent
the last six months
caring for
her husband who's dying
of heart failure.
Reason 31,
whatever whacked
the husband's heart
is also
whacking her airway.
And, oh, good, I thought
maybe Kutner was home
nursing the rib you broke
when you elbowed your way
in for credit
on the last patient.
I contributed.
And the patient's illness
wasn't caused by her husband,
unless lung cancer
is contagious.
Interesting.
Not about the patient,
that was kind of dull.
I thought maybe you were lying
to cover for Kutner,
which sounds noble,
except you're doing it
out of guilt,
instead of love.
She visited her sister
in Hawaii
about six months ago,
just before
her husband got sick.
Could've picked up
melioidosis from
one of the islands.
Would have jumped
to the husband,
finished off him
and his lame
immune system.
TAUB: No tumors,
no drugs, no bacteria...
Leaves viral.
Varicella zoster.
Start her on IV fluids
and acyclovir.
Can't. She's demanding
to be released
so she can get
home to her husband.
How sweet.
They can die together,
instead of separately,
40 years apart.
She claims he got stronger
as soon as
she stopped breathing.
The mind
can heal the body.
Seeing his wife in distress
might have actually
slowed down his death.
Or he just had
an adrenaline surge
when he saw his chance
to hit the singles market.
Send her home.
We don't need to.
I had an idea,
all by myself.
CHARLOTTE: Eddie?
Found him loitering
in the lobby.
You're still with me.
Where the hell else
am I gonna go?
TAUB: And now,
with your permission,
we'd like to try
to make you better.
KATHERINE: The pageant
starts in an hour.
You have to do something.
There's something wrong
inside her head.
It's like she has no idea
what's going on around her.
I thought she was just
flirting with me.
I could fix it,
but it's gonna
cost you $3.75.
Well, I'm not
just gonna give you
my coffee.
Think of it
as Costa Rican
sober juice.
She's drunk?
That little minty scent
hiding beneath
the rose petal perfume,
and the cherry blossom
moisturizer,
and the morning dew
hairspray...
You sneak into
Mommy's bathroom
and gulp some
of her mouthwash?
Gotta be perfect.
You spit it out?
Mommy doesn't.
Treatment worked.
Charlotte's breathing's
back to normal.
She's being discharged.
She can resume her vigil
over her husband.
He's started fading again.
Win some, lose some.
And, strictly speaking,
since he's not my patient,
win some.
Oh, look at the time.
It's half past Taub
was lying about Kutner.
He probably went to
a comic book fest,
spent the night
at some Wonder Woman's lair.
I'm sure he'll...
Find out what,
or who, he's doing.
Either way, Cuddy's gonna
want me to write it under
"Reason for Termination."
(PAGER BEEPING)
Is that Kutner?
Charlotte.
O2 sat and S-T are normal.
It's not her airway.
(CHARLOTTE GASPING)
You're okay.
Yeah, don't worry about me,
she's in pain.
Pulse is rapid and regular,
no fluid in her lungs.
What's happening?
I don't know.
(KNOCKING)
Kutner.
It's Foreman and 13.
Where are you going?
House didn't ask us
to find out
where he wasn't.
If you wanna climb
a fifth-floor
fire escape...
(KEYS RATTLING)
This might be faster.
Kutner!
Man-boy heaven.
Surprised
he ever leaves.
There's nothing
on his calendar.
His pager's still here.
Oh, God.
(DIALING)
Need an ambulance
at 410 Willis,
apartment 5C.
Twenty-eight-year-old male,
single gunshot wound
to the right temple.
THIRTEEN:
No pulse.
FOREMAN:
Alert Princeton-Plainsboro,
have a trauma unit ready.
(THIRTEEN PANTING)
His pupils are dilated,
his head's swollen.
Still no pulse.
Come on, Kutner!
Let me try.
(FOREMAN PANTING)
He's cold.
(PANTING)
Eric.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
He didn't say anything
to any of you?
Family problems?
Bad relationship?
Financial pressures?
His parents were shot
right in front of him.
Parents are
ancient history.
Not to someone
who actually cares.
He didn't slit his wrists
and peacefully drift away,
he shot himself.
He didn't leave a note,
that means panic.
Which could've been pre-empted
if the idiots
who worked alongside him
for 80 hours a week
had seen this coming.
You're blaming us?
I'm just trying to
figure it out.
We would've helped him
if he'd reached out to us.
He didn't.
We should've
picked up on something.
This isn't our fault.
Something like 25%
of suicidal people
show no outward signs
of depression.
No, 25% of suicidal people
have friends
who didn't notice anything
and don't want
to feel guilty.
Killing yourself
also kills
all other options.
Makes Kutner an idiot.
So pity, yes,
but guilt, no.
If that's what
you want to
tell yourself.
We still have a patient.
Actually, two.
One worsening, one
who should be worsening.
You can't be in denial
about Kutner
and the husband.
It is possible Eddie's body
is willing itself to live.
Well, call the tabloids.
Tell them you just witnessed
the miracle of slightly
increased kidney function.
Maybe we should
pass this file off
to another doctor.
And the next one, too?
And the one after that?
How many files
till it's okay
that Kutner's dead?
Cardiac enzymes means
she didn't have
a heart attack.
No vision problems means
no mitochondrial disease.
Could be
a metabolic disorder.
Acidosis.
THIRTEEN:
Blood pH was normal.
Polyserositis would
inflame the membranes
near her epiglottis
and the heart's pericardium,
causing the chest pain.
I'm sorry.
I've hired a grief counselor,
who I'm sure
none of you will see.
And I'm offering time off,
which I'm sure
none of you will take.
But just know
it's available.
Polyserositis fits.
Start her on indomethacin.
CUDDY: If you'd rather
not deal with this case...
I'm fine, despite
what Wilson will say.
He hasn't come to you?
Pretty sure
he has Mah-jong
Tuesday mornings.
I assume he thinks
that I will work
through this better
if I don't have to keep
flicking his wings
off my shoulder.
You didn't even
have an inkling?
I know his fantasy
football team cratered,
figured he'd gotten over it.
Well...
Sorry for your loss.
Thanks.
It's not my loss.
Then I'm sorry
you don't think it is.
Patient's membranes
aren't going to
heal themselves.
Taub went
to run the treatment.
We'd like to go
see Kutner's parents.
I'll join you.
Polyserositis damages
the protective covering
around tissue and organs.
The indomethacin is simply
an anti-inflammatory,
but it should fix it.
Just make
the pain stop.
Charlotte.
Close your eyes.
Now.
Pretend you finally
made it down to Rio.
You're on
the balcony of
(CHUCKLES)
Some fancy hotel.
You never talk like this.
Yeah, just shut up
and let me do this.
And you're on
that balcony, and you are
watching the Mardi Gras.
It's called Carnival.
And I don't want
to go without you.
I want you to.
And I want it to be
everything
you've ever dreamed of.
Sorry to interrupt,
but I'd like to
run one more test.
On you.
JULIA: This is the
first day we got him.
He was six.
Sweetest little boy
you ever met.
FOREMAN:
Must have been scary,
going through a trauma,
and then being handed off
to a new family.
We kept telling him
to call us
Richard and Julia,
but it was always
Mr. And Mrs. Kutner.
Then, on his ninth birthday,
we gave him a chemistry set.
(CHUCKLES)
Lawrence always loved
blowing things up.
And he said,
"Thanks, Mom.
Thanks, Dad."
That's who we were
from then on.
He was pretty special.
We were lucky to have him.
You spent the most time
with him.
He spoke so highly
of all of you.
Do you have any idea...
I wish we did.
We all...
HOUSE: It was his name.
He was conflicted.
Didn't know
where he fit in.
Being ripped out of his world
and stuck into yours.
We encouraged him
to hold on
to his heritage.
HOUSE: It's hard
to still be
Lawrence Choudhary
when everyone sees you
as Lawrence Kutner.
It was his idea
to take our name.
You should have said no.
House.
All his Anglo name gave him
was the illusion that
he was someone he wasn't.
You were being emotional,
not rational.
You didn't understand him.
We loved that boy,
you son of a bitch.
You wanted to make him happy
by shutting out his pain.
When he looked happy,
you assumed
the pain had gone,
but it just
got buried deeper,
leaving him tormented
about who he was, until
finally he put a bullet...
House.
Go back
to the hospital.
I'm sorry
about your son.
Indomethacin had no effect,
she's still in pain.
Rules out polyserositis.
I ran a hormone panel
on Eddie.
His prolactin's
above normal.
Means
he's actually improving.
Body chemistry changes
for all sorts of reasons.
Stress, fear,
why not love?
Maybe he's going into
some sort of remission.
You haven't asked
if I learned anything
relevant from the Kutners.
If you had, I'm sure
you'd have mentioned it.
Or you're just afraid
there is something relevant,
which would mean
you could have saved him.
I don't buy that suicide
is always a cry for help.
Sometimes you just
don't want help.
Good thing
you got some,
or you'd have tried again
and gotten it right.
She doesn't have
Wegener's.
Kidney function's normal.
It's not byssinosis,
it's not
mitral valve stenosis.
Nothing fits.
If it doesn't fit
any diagnosis,
that just leaves
one diagnosis.
I'm Dr. House.
You have hypertrophic
cardiomyopathy.
His heart is too weak,
yours is too strong.
Good news is
it's fixable.
We induce a massive
heart attack and
kill off the extra muscle.
You want to give me
a heart attack?
It's only dangerous
if your heart
is normal-sized.
But since all the...
Are you serious?
No.
This is actually
very annoying,
and I'm getting really bored
of lying to patients
to scare them
into telling me the truth.
She's faking.
And, yes,
if she keeps faking,
I'm going to eventually
do something
that will kill her.
How could she be...
The windpipe thing?
That was real.
The treatment
made her better.
But good for her
was bad for you,
which was bad for her,
so she made herself bad.
It's all so simple.
She figured
that the sicker she was,
the longer you'd hang on.
Charlotte?
We haven't been
this close for years.
I wanted to
hang on to that.
(EXCLAIMS)
HOUSE: Oh, please.
People hate reruns.
It's my leg.
I swear, this is real.
Do you pinky swear
or you just
plain swear, because...
How can she fake that?
She can't.
(CHARLOTTE GROANING)
So, what can shred
an epiglottis and
make muscle disappear?
Mr. And Mrs. Kutner.
They caused Kutner's death,
why not Charlotte's?
Mourning period's over.
Foreman's sense of irony
is back.
I was wrong
about the ethnic reason.
Step one,
change your name back.
Step two,
if step one fails,
move to Bangalore.
Step 14,
if step 13 doesn't work,
kill yourself.
So, what now?
You gonna insult your way
through his rolodex
till you find someone
with an answer?
I've been polite
to the friends I've called,
all of whom were useless.
They weren't useless,
they just didn't know
anything more than we did.
Tomato, tomato.
MS. Weakens myelin sheath,
compromises nerve conduction.
I'm talking about Charlotte,
the one who's still alive.
You two,
stick her in an MRI,
confirm MS,
and you,
run the echo on Eddie
that you're planning
to do behind my back
to see if
his heart's improving.
Did you let me
hire a pervert?
Well, it'd be hypocritical
of me not to.
Kutner's police
background check
from when he started.
He was charged with
indecent exposure.
Kutner streaked
at the Penn-Dartmouth
football game.
Precisely the kind of thing
you'd expect him to do.
It's okay.
You should be upset.
He thought like you,
pushed boundaries
like you.
If he thought like me,
he'd have known that
living in misery
sucks marginally less
than dying in it.
Just a few more minutes,
then we'll get
you back to Eddie.
What's it like,
30 years
with the same man?
Great for me,
good for him, I hope.
What, you don't think
he loves you?
I think he always
loved me, in his way.
(ON SPEAKER) Just not
in a "spend time with me"
or "show emotion"
or "any affection
for me" sort of way.
Why did you stay?
I didn't need him
to feel about me
the way I did about him.
(FAINTLY) Love doesn't...
Charlotte?
(MACHINE BEEPING)
I've heard stories
of cancer patients
going into
spontaneous remission.
You think this might be
that sort of thing?
It's unlikely,
but you never know.
If I just had
a little more time
to be with Charlotte.
Try and do better
by her.
Yeah, maybe.
You don't think
I mean it.
I think
you mean it now.
I think it's much easier
to mean it than
to do anything about it.
(LAUGHS)
(HEART BEATING)
Chamber walls
are barely moving.
I'm sorry.
(DOOR OPENING)
He needs a friend.
I can't deal with this
and House.
You need a friend, too.
You couldn't give
a crap what I need,
you just want someone
to take care of him.
He told Kutner's parents
it was their fault.
(DOOR CLOSES)
CHASE: Ruptured spleen.
Means it's not MS.
What are you
doing here?
Waiting for you to fix her
spleen, so we can biopsy it
for rheumatoid arthritis.
I'll do it. Go home.
She's not your patient.
And Kutner
wasn't my friend.
Kutner wanted to die,
Charlotte doesn't,
so in a contest
for my concern and interests,
she wins.
Okay, either you're
a cold-hearted bastard,
or you're too miserable
to face it.
Go home and cry.
It's not
rheumatoid arthritis,
her liver's scarred.
Whatever she's got,
it's spreading.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
For the record,
I'm uncomfortable
violating a dead
colleague's dignity.
It's only violating
if we find something.
Good to see you.
What are
we looking for?
He was hiding.
Why?
Shame? Fear?
Are you okay?
It's okay
not to be okay.
"Colonial Warrior Blaster.
Number 101."
He spent months
tracking this down.
He had passions.
He was obviously in pain.
Does it really
matter why?
He hung the bad
with the good.
His loss beside a reminder
of what he'd gained.
Means he was open
about the pain.
Should mean that
if it got worse, he had
no reason to hide it.
Here's how we're gonna
handle this, House.
We're going to leave here
and go to
the closest bar and drink,
tell stories about
the time Kutner
almost blew up an OR,
and pass out
in our own sick.
Sound like a plan?
(SWITCH CLICKING)
(SIGHS)
What am I missing?
You've got that look.
You figured this out.
You're not here because
you care about Kutner.
You're here
because it's a mystery.
for the puzzle.
What if I didn't
miss anything because
there's nothing to miss?
He didn't kill himself.
He was murdered.
TAUB: Epiglottis, muscle,
spleen, and now her liver,
which is operating at 20%
and deteriorating fast.
Autoimmune hepatitis?
Did you page Foreman?
He took up Cuddy's offer
of time off.
Normal thyroid
means no hepatitis.
Could be amyloidosis.
Amyloid build-up
hits the organs, tissue...
HOUSE: Her muscles
wouldn't have atrophied.
You run the echo
on the husband?
Heart's still failing.
The improvement
was only temporary.
I prefer the
less subtle answer.
"You were right, House."
So, less time proving
why hubby isn't dead,
more time proving
why Kutner is.
Motives for murder.
House, it was a suicide.
The police have
already investigated.
They investigated
what they saw,
not what they didn't saw.
Talk to friends, classmates,
pizza delivery guy.
Draft Foreman.
He can make calls
through his tears.
No.
Is that, "No,
I'm not calling
my boyfriend
"who apparently called my boss
instead of me to say
he wasn't coming in"?
'Cause it's really not fair
to have that much subtext
in one syllable.
We all want to know
why Kutner did it,
but we're not
gonna waste time
chasing ghosts.
You're not
remotely curious?
Only why a man
who embraces the rational
is suddenly pursuing
the irrational.
She could have
Alpha 1-antitrypsin
deficiency.
Run her AAT proteins.
I'd like to be
with Eddie.
It's too soon
after your surgery.
You can ask if someone
gets your organs
if you die, right?
Even if
the donor bank
turned them down?
Individual donors
can bypass
the registry,
but there are
a lot of
other factors.
Blood type...
I've given him blood.
It's not just...
Please.
If I go before him,
I want you to
give him my heart.
This isn't over yet.
For me.
But it is for him,
isn't it?
Yes.
(DOOR OPENING)
Remy Hadley.
I also answer to 13.
I sometimes
sleep with you.
I know
I should have called.
I just need some time.
Alone?
I've worked through
a lot of
bad stuff in my life,
always done it solo.
So I should go?
I'm sorry.
Okay.
(DOOR OPENS)
(CUDDY CLEARS THROAT)
IT's been trying
to close out
Kutner's email account.
Apparently, someone's
still logged on to it.
Wasn't hard to figure out
that his password
was "Kutner."
He did what
they tell you not to.
He wasn't murdered.
But his parents were.
And the guy who
killed them
is coming up for parole.
He's coming up for parole,
he's not out on parole.
Kutner testified at
every one of his hearings.
Guy wouldn't be the first
to see the clock ticking...
He was killed
by his own gun.
Which he bought years ago,
obviously for self-defense.
In the temple,
cops found residue.
Right.
A murderer would never try
to make it look like suicide,
that'd be unethical.
You haven't asked
about my patient.
You're waiting on
AAT protein results.
Means you checked up
to see that
I'm still on it.
You want to
transfer the case,
but you won't because you
think it's the only thing
that's holding me together.
Well, relax.
Either I'm right
or I'm wrong.
We'll know soon enough.
Find what's
killing your patient,
and then I'll find you
another patient.
TAUB: What happened?
Nurses found her like this.
She broke into the cart,
injected whatever
she could grab.
Dumb way to look
worse for Eddie.
She wasn't trying
to look worse.
(CHARLOTTE GASPING)
She was trying
to kill herself.
TAUB: She's stable,
but whatever
was left of her liver
is definitely shot now,
and there's no change
in Eddie.
HOUSE: So, thanks
to her idiotic move,
she's dead in 24 hours
if she doesn't
get a new liver.
It was selfless.
She loves him.
How does that disagree
with what I just said?
Test was negative
for AAT deficiency.
Myelofibrosis fits,
but testing
takes at least 48 hours.
TAUB: We should try
a partial donation
from a live donor.
Damage is too severe.
She needs
a whole new liver.
No diagnosis, no liver.
No liver, no living.
What do you know?
It is myelofibrosis.
Says so right here.
Who wants to tell Cuddy?
How many times have
you lied to
the transplant committee?
Just twice.
How many times
has it worked?
I don't quite see
how that's relevant.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Cheese it,
it's the coppers.
We're not just gonna
leave them to die
while you fixate on Kutner.
Technically,
he's not our patient,
so I'm really only
leaving her to die.
We've already explored
the usual options,
shouldn't we at least
explore unusual ones?
Absolutely.
Don't worry, this is why
God gave me two ears.
Kutner would say
we should just
come clean with Cuddy.
Wow, if only
he were here to say that.
I'm sure Cuddy would be
bound to fall for the old,
"Hey, the dead guy
won't mind
that we're wasting..."
I need an incurable romantic
to talk to
an incurable romantic.
Kutner wasn't murdered.
You deduce that by removing
your sunglasses to
the strains of a Who song?
Suicide means
you could have helped him,
murder lets you off the hook.
Needs a liver.
Has a liver.
He can make
a partial donation.
The faster he agrees,
the faster
she gets to not die.
Partial won't be enough,
she needs a whole liver.
And he'd never
survive the procedure.
Nice symmetry, huh?
He dies on the table,
you give her
his whole liver.
If he's gonna do this,
he's gonna
do this for love.
Thought he should talk
to someone
who spoke the language.
You want me to
die on the table?
We don't want you to.
Your wife needs you to.
My heart?
Is still dying.
You have
a couple days at most.
But this could buy us
enough time to save her.
When can I say goodbye?
You can't.
If she knew
what we were planning,
would she be okay?
She'll resent me.
She'll be alive.
Nothing else matters.
CAMERON: You can't
do the transplant.
Only if he said no,
but your urgent hovering
means he said yes.
His fingers have nodules.
I think his doctors
misdiagnosed him.
Or you sprinkled
too much wishful thinking
in your tea.
Obese man with lung cancer.
Two easy explanations
for his heart failure.
Nodules could mean
something else,
something curable.
Go back to the ER.
My thanks to you
and your cold feet.
What's going on?
I'm giving you a shot
at a cool result.
Better yet, a chance
to prove
other doctors idiotic.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Except you're wrong.
You figure that out
by taking off
your sunglasses
to the strains
of a Who song?
The guy who killed
Kutner's parents
died of an aneurysm
two months ago.
Kutner hid
from everyone.
You didn't get a chance
to save him. No one did.
Run the test.
Find out if you have
a chance to save Eddie.
Bad news.
Love can't save you.
(DOOR CLOSING)
On the other hand,
mold can.
Your heart failure
was caused by
a fungal infection
called cardiac blastomycosis.
Started as nodules
in your lungs,
which every doc,
except one,
mistook for cancer.
It's very rare,
very curable.
I'm starting you
on itraconazole.
But how come
I was getting better
without the medicine?
Your emotional state
bumps your catecholamines,
which help raise
your prolactin...
My emotional state?
Three months of treatment,
you'll be back to
your buff, chiseled self.
I don't want
the treatment.
Do the transplant.
You'd be trading
the certainty
that you'll live
for the uncertainty
that she'll live.
I was ready
to die anyway.
Now you get to be nicer
to your next wife.
If you won't do it,
release me.
And when I get hit
by a car and show up
in your morgue,
you can give her
my liver then.
You're basically
asking us
to commit murder.
I was yesterday, too.
There's a difference
when he has 20 years to live
instead of two days.
Not really,
not legally.
That's your way
of convincing us
to do this,
by saying
it's no more immoral?
The idiot is gonna do this
with or without us.
This way, we can
protect the organ.
We should be
protecting him.
So we strap him to the bed,
wait till his wife dies?
I'm not doing this.
TAUB: I will.
We've already had
one pointless death.
Eddie?
What's going on?
I don't know.
He just came and got me.
(MOANING)
Your husband
has a curable disease,
but he wants to die
so he can
give you his liver.
Are you okay with that,
or would you rather
he take the treatment?
You son of a bitch.
Eddie, don't.
You have to
let me do this.
Charlotte,
can you hear me?
(SHIVERING)
She spiked a fever.
LP shows her white cells
through the roof.
She's infected
everywhere.
I should fire you.
I just did
what you failed to do.
Convince Eddie to live
and let his wife die.
THIRTEEN: Infection means
we have a new clue.
And a full
two or three hours
to figure it out.
Sarcoidosis.
Hits the spleen
and the liver.
She'd have lung issues.
Scleroderma
inflames the tissue.
HOUSE: No skin
or GI problems.
(SIGHS)
What is she hiding?
You don't know that...
Either we have all the clues
and we're idiots
or we don't have
all the clues.
Possible exposure.
People, places.
Both.
Bad lie.
Did you really think
the beaches in Hawaii
were just like
the beaches in Rio?
The disease-bearing
sand flies
are completely different.
She's never
been to Rio.
Who'd you go with?
Why are you doing this?
I don't actually
need to know who it was,
I just need to know
that you went,
so we can know
that you have
visceral leishmaniasis.
But since Lancelot there
was ready to die for you,
he might want
the answer to both.
(SIGHS)
Last year.
It was nobody you knew.
Rio was supposed
to be ours.
I got tired
of waiting.
I'm so sorry.
Start her on antimony.
Have Cuddy
find her a liver.
They were all
ready to die.
But for guilt, not love.
You can't feel
that much guilt
without love.
New York Mercy's
medevacing a liver.
It should be here...
Tell them to turn around.
Charlotte's treatment
isn't taking.
We diagnosed it too late.
(CUDDY SIGHS)
Everyone's heading over
to Kutner's funeral.
You're welcome
to ride with me.
I'm going to
stay with Charlotte.
She bought you some time
to save Eddie,
it'll give her death
some meaning.
No, it won't.
(DOOR OPENING)
I was wrong about you.
No, you weren't.
You're in pain.
And you're romanticizing.
Again.
You worked with him
every day for two years,
and you never
saw this coming.
No one saw it coming.
But you see
everything coming.
This has never been
about what you missed,
this is about
why you missed it.
You're terrified that
you're losing your gift,
losing who you are.
And I'm terrified
of what you'd do then.
Unless you feel
there's more to do here
to cure me,
don't you have
the funeral to go to?
(DOOR CLOSING)
I'm taking a ride
Off to one side
It is a personal thing
Where?
When I can't stand
Up in this cage
I'm not regretting
I don't need a better thing
I'll settle for less
It's another thing for me
I just have to wander
Through this world alone
(INAUDIBLE)
Stop before you fall
Into the hole
that I have dug here
Rest even as you
Are starting to feel
the way I used to
I don't need a better thing
Just to sound confused
Don't talk about everyone
I am not amused by you
'Cause I'm gonna lose you
Yes, I'm gonna lose you
If I'm gonna lose you
'Cause I'm gonna lose you
Yes, I'm gonna lose you
If I'm gonna lose you
I'll lose you now for good