# Joy to the world #
# the lord has come #
# let earth
receive her king #
# let every heart
prepare him room #
# and heaven
and nature sing #
# and heaven and
nature sing #
# and heaven,
heaven and nature sing #
This sucks.
This is why we need
to make a statement.
You know?
I don't think that--
What? You afraid we'll
end up in detention?
Well, yeah, that's--
that's what teachers do.
They're not going to send
all of us to detention.
Mr. Henderson is totally lame,
and this is our best chance
to inform him
of that fact.
You don't
think he's lame?
Well...
Yeah, but--
- Then what's the problem?
Okay.
The Camden Hills local jazz ensemble.
# chestnuts roasting
on an open fire #
# Jack Frost
nipping at your nose #
# yuletide carols
being sung by a choir #
# and folks
dressed up like Eskimos #
# everybody knows #
# Mr. Henderson's
a stupid-- #
I can't believe
she fell for that.
Loser.
Why--why'd you do that?
I--I don't feel so g--
So good.
16-year-old female
gets pranked, also
gets visual hallucinations
and vomiting.
Turns out
to be a failing liver.
Why have Foreman's breasts
suddenly started to droop?
Large breasts
are a classic symptom
of you letting Foreman
take vacation days so he
can finish his F.D.A. reports
before
the end of the year.
When are
you taking vacation?
Hepatic and neurological
involvement--
so I understand
Foreman's absence.
Your presence,
not so much.
I'm bringing in a case.
You may have noticed
me doing that before.
I've noticed you
a lot recently.
It's almost as if
you have a sexual interest
in someone here--
Like, say...Taub.
Well, Taub might
think I like him
if I stayed,
which is why
I'm gonna do this.
Somehow I don't think
that was really about me.
Uh, Wilson's Disease.
Ceruloplasmin's normal.
You've got
a Christmas present.
"Greg--made me think of you."
That's funny.
Usually explodes
after I do that.
Alcohol abuse?
- She's 16.
The kind of boozing that
destroys your liver that early,
parents or teachers
would notice.
Wow, Manual of
the Operations of Surgery
by Joseph Bell.
You're throwing that away?
Twice.
Someone's screwing with me.
- Forget it.
Yeah, gifting
antique medical texts.
Oldest gag in the book.
Handwriting's kinda girly.
You got an admirer, House?
I said forget the book!
Why'd they pick on her?
She's an overachiever.
High grades. She volunteers.
She's a big target.
I'm assuming literally.
Depending on where
this school falls
on the Heathers scale.
Do you think the kids
slipped her something?
Their teachers
grilled them.
When do teachers ever know
how to motivate their students?
What did you do to Natalie?
It's all my fault.
I didn't stop her
from being a total pig.
What are you--
your friend's liver
is failing.
We're doing what we can,
but she still might
need a transplant.
She could die unless you
tell us what you gave her.
Just tell him.
- Shut up.
We gave her some 'shrooms.
We took some ourselves,
we just--
Wanted to make her
loosen up a little.
How thoughtful of you.
You got any left?
They're in Simon's locker.
This was your idea?
No way.
I didn't give her anything.
Right, you
just knew about it
And let them do it.
poisonous mushrooms
And hallucinogenic ones
are different.
Not if they
don't dry correctly.
Get back to school.
You better hope
we got to her in time.
What?
Am I going
to get in trouble?
Should we apologize
or something?
Yes, you should.
Natalie's
on the third floor.
Who's down there?
Where's the woman
I spoke to last week?
The trial patient, um,
with the advanced symptoms.
She dropped out.
Is she okay?
Not health-related.
She just wants
to drop out.
Why?
- She didn't say.
And I only break
into the houses
of very special patients
to understand them better.
I do good today, boss?
No rigidity,
no cog wheeling.
So, absolutely
I'd call that good.
Great. Thanks.
Your clipboard.
Keep it.
This place actually smells of evil.
Where do you work, again?
Why would House
throw out
a book worth
hundreds of dollars?
To make you
ask that question.
Can you really put a price tag
on screwing with people?
Can you get us into
Natalie Soellner's locker
While we're here?
House always
has an agenda.
Just screwing
with us isn't--
Yeah, he'd never do that.
Oh, wait--
he already did last year.
Remember the Secret Santa gift
he got himself?
He was making us fight
over who could get him
the best present.
This time he's
just making us wonder.
No animosity,
no ugly competition.
I think it's
a real present.
If it's real, then House
really was freaked.
And if it affects him,
eventually
it'll affect us.
Uh-oh.
Maybe it wasn't those kids
who poisoned Natalie.
Maybe it was
Natalie herself.
I didn't try to kill myself.
Then why'd you have
all those painkillers?
In case
I get a headache.
Well, maybe you
took a few too many.
Do you have any kids?
No.
But high school
wasn't all that different
when I was your age.
Teenagers can be
incredibly mean.
I know what you're
going through.
I bet you were cool.
You're pretty.
You're pretty, too.
I'm fat.
I'm a loser.
They all hate me.
You know what
they did last year?
They took these photos of me
for the yearbook...
but it wasn't.
It was for this website.
Making fun of me...
calling me a pig.
Forget about them.
Let's just
make you better.
What's the point?
Acetylcysteine
could save her liver.
But we have to act fast.
If there's any chance that
she took all those pills--
There's no chance.
Okay.
She was the happiest,
sweetest little girl and--
and a year ago
she hits puberty,
and it's like this
secretive little stranger
moved into her room.
I try to talk to her about
what she's going through.
Give her the treatment.
You can't really think
that she tried--
I don't know
what to think.
If it's a subpoena,
he's gotten that
kind of present before.
It was a book.
That narrows it down.
Just look for someone
who knows how to read
or has been to a bookstore.
Most bookstores don't carry
Joseph Bell on surgery.
Did it have a note?
"Greg--made me
think of you."
Green wrapping paper?
How did you know that?
What is it?
It's nothing.
Yes--when something's
nothing,
the natural response
is to guess
the color of the paper
it's wrapped in
and then descend
into stunned silence?
Irene Adler.
Christmas, 2001.
Sarcoid symptoms,
But she didn't respond
to methotrexate.
I've never seen him
so obsessed.
He saved her with a last
minute Wegener's diagnosis,
but the hours he put in--
I thought
it would kill him.
And then...
well, he fell for her.
But it was too soon
after Stacy and--
It sounds silly,
but Irene was
the one who got away.
Really?
No, you idiots.
House is just
screwing with you.
You think
there's some woman
with a mysterious green
wrapping paper trademark?
Then how did you guess--
I could be wrong.
It's possible
a secret admirer gave House
the same book
I gave him last Christmas.
And the same paper
I wrapped it in
and the note I wrote.
We gotta go.
Heartbeat?
150.
B.P. 180 over 110.
Crackling 3/4
of the way up.
Guess this means she didn't
try to kill herself.
Well, scratch
the hallucinations.
That's from the mushrooms.
Leaves liver failure
and now pulmonary edema.
And you--
Standing there,
beseechingly.
Yes, I was going
to stalk you at home,
but it was a busy week
and your office is closer.
Thirteen and Foreman
were busy drug trialing
and we needed an answer
on the overdose,
so we called her in.
She's just updating us.
- Convenient.
Update's done.
This is a good
experience for me,
as my parents
never got divorced.
Theories?
- Glue sniffing.
Effects on the lungs
would have been immediate.
House, we all know
what's going on here.
Cuddy gave you
that present.
No.
Infections?
No fever, no polys
in the sputum.
I think--
I think she loves you.
I told you to lay off the present.
And the L.S.D.
We got distracted
by the painkillers.
Toxins are still
the most likely--
Just tell her
how you feel.
If you won't,
then I will.
I'll walk
right down there.
Damn it.
Love like this
needs to fly free.
You talked to Wilson.
He has very girly
handwriting, by the way.
I knew I should have
just wrapped a new present.
You said the patient
volunteered. Where?
Uh, Pleasant Valley.
Soup kitchen in Trenton.
Thirteen and Kutner,
search the home and the school.
Taub...
You take
the anal swabbing
of the fragrant and
contagious homeless man.
Why don't you hang out
in the video store
and tell everyone
Kevin Spacey's keyser soze?
And by the way,
that ending really
made no sense at all.
You had my present
for a year
and didn't even
open it?
I had no way of knowing
there was an expensive
book inside.
Completely
meaningless prank,
even for you.
Stealing your ice cream
is a completely
meaningless,
albeit delicious,
prank.
Observing
my team's reactions
to unexplained
phenomena
could have been
pretty useful.
Of all the ways
to mess with people,
why give yourself
an imaginary present?
Have you checked
the prices
for fireman strippers
recently?
Yes.
The holidays--
they're hard for you.
I get it.
You see the people
around you
giving and receiving gifts,
having sustained,
meaningful relationships,
and since you can't,
something deep
in your subconscious
makes you create
the appearance of a gift.
Sad.
You really passed
your psych rotation?
It's too bad you can't
just be nice to people.
You could get
a real present that way.
If I wanted gifts,
I would just look deep
into my patients' eyes
and act like you.
"Oh, I'm so sorry
you're dying,
"Mrs. Moron.
"Of course
I'll sleep with you.
What I lack in skill
I can make up for in--"
You'd just wind up
insulting her,
perhaps calling her
Mrs. Moron.
Right, 'cause
I'm physically incapable
of being polite.
Being kind in a sustained,
meaningful way?
No.
Oh, I get it.
You're trying to get me
to prove you wrong,
then I'm gonna be
nice to all my patients
all through
the holiday season,
and then Mr. Potter won't
steal Tiny Tim's porridge.
I'm totally on it.
Yeah, that actually
is what I'm trying to do.
And the pathetic part is,
it's not gonna work.
You're right.
I gotta stop
being such a jerk.
Oops.
Just kind of
undercut myself, there.
Across the country.
Be paying attention.
Well, people should pay attention
because they could
expect up to 23...
Janice?
I'm Remy.
I'm--
yeah, I remember you.
I heard you
left the trial.
Yeah.
If there's some way
I could help--
Um, it--
it was that doctor.
He--the one that
was runnin' the tests.
Dr. Foreman.
Yeah.
He's a great neurologist.
He's a great guy.
You--you like him?
Why don't you?
I told him
that those injections
were making me sick
in my stomach,
and he just
gave me antacid.
We were warned that
nausea's a side effect,
and giving you antacids
is all he really could do.
No, he told me,
"get over it."
With or without
the use of drugs,
I don't have a long time.
I'm not gonna spend it
bein' his guinea pig.
House.
It's tuberculosis.
You got that
from an anal swab?
Man, you're good.
There was
a more subtle clue.
Homeless guy,
uncontrollably
hacking up blood.
Cough's lasted two months,
he was cachectic.
Unless you can
tie him to the patient--
Yes, again, if only
there was some subtle clue,
like the fact that he
was standing next to her
in the soup line
for a week.
I hate spunk.
T.B. can cause
liver failure,
lung symptoms--
fits.
Start her on
the standard regimen.
Uh--you don't have
clinic duty today.
Who says it's a duty?
Hi. I'm Greg.
Hi, I'm Whitney.
Hi, Whitney.
How can I help you?
I have a--
a terrible headache.
Oh, sorry
to hear that.
I'll get you fixed up.
Is there anything else
you need?
Bottle of water?
Coffee?
Mint tea?
No, but that's so nice.
Usually the clinic doctors
are kind of rushed.
If you can't be nice,
why be a doctor?
So where do you
feel the pain?
In the back
of my head here.
Uh-huh.
That's beccaria's sign.
That'll be gone by
your third trimester.
Oh, I'm not in school.
Neither is your fetus.
Oh, God.
You didn't know
you were pregnant?
How do--you know that
just from the headache?
How do I know?
I missed my period,
I got fat,
threw up,
oh, no, wait--
that's how you know.
What?
I know because
of the tight shirt
stretched over
the swollen boobs,
the salt craving you've
imported into the clinic,
the motion sickness patch
that doesn't do anything
for the kind of sickness
that you feel in the morning.
Yeah, I'm a virgin.
So is my fianc?.
I believe him.
Aren't there other ways
I could get pregnant,
like...sitting
on a toilet seat?
Absolutely--there
would need to be a guy
sitting between
you and the toilet seat,
but yes, absolutely.
I was doing so well.
Natalie?
Oh, God. Natalie.
She's having a seizure.
Put her on her side.
Nurse!
- Is this from the T.B.?
Not with
the supple neck.
I don't know
what this is.
Four milligrams
lorazepam.
Liver, lungs, and now brain...
which has mysteriously
reappeared.
Speaking of mysteriously
Her A.L.T.
is 20 times normal.
Transaminases
and P.T.'s way up.
She's gonna lose
her liver.
We gotta get her
on the transplant list.
You keep showing up.
You also keep leaving.
It's possible that you
have the hots for me,
but really,
really hate this kid.
It's also
remotely possible
that I have that reversed.
She's a nice kid.
I wanna make sure she's okay.
Hepatic fibrosis?
Normal complement level,
normal-sized liver.
She remind you of...
You?
Nah, you weren't a loser
in high school.
You had every Tom,
Dick, and Hershel
wet-dreaming about you.
But she could
be making you
think of another helpless,
chubby little girl
you recently met.
You are not
really making this
about the baby
I tried to adopt.
It's been a few weeks.
Just enough time
to get over hurt feelings.
Natalie's 16.
I think you're confusing
being maternal
with being human.
If we hadn't
ruled out the mushrooms--
Maybe we shouldn't have.
Forget toxic--
think allergic.
Severe mold allergy
could cause,
uh, liver failure,
respiratory arrest,
and encephalopathy.
She ate the 'shrooms
days ago.
There's no way
she'd still be sick.
Unless it also gave her
a fungal infection.
Give her a prick test in antifungals.
Hey.
Thank you
for the gift.
I really appreciate it.
I spoke to Janice.
She okay?
Yeah.
Her nausea--
she said you
told her to, like,
get over it?
And?
Nausea isn't something
you can overcome
with sheer willpower.
Which is why I didn't
prescribe willpower.
I prescribed antacids.
If she
can't handle that,
she'd have to leave
the trial anyway.
Just call her,
say you're sorry.
She'll come back.
No.
God, you're acting
like House now.
No, I'm not acting
like House,
Which is exactly why
I don't need to apologize.
I'm not being cruel.
I'm not being manipulative.
You said
the same thing to me
when I told you
I was having a hard time.
And it worked.
She's a 40-year-old woman
who's falling apart
physically
and emotionally.
She's dying.
Look, I know seeing
the ghost of your
Christmas future is tough.
But the only way
I can help her
is to make sure
she follows her regimen,
not by becoming
her life coach.
You're not acting
like House.
You are like him.
Dr. House?
This is my fianc? Geoff.
She says you told her
you can get pregnant
from sitting
on a toilet seat.
I said those words,
but with a particular
inflection.
I knew it was untrue.
Well, is there
any other way?
Isn't it possible?
There was
a reported case
of a civil war soldier
who was shot
in the testicles,
and the musket ball
carried the non-musket ball
into the uterus
of a woman working
in a neighboring field.
Nine months later,
a miracle child was born.
Also, maybe she
cheated on you.
We made a promise.
We d--we do
other stuff in bed.
Couldn't
some of his sperm
have made it
up there somehow?
More likely,
it came from the guy
whose penis
made it up there somehow.
But...
sure, anything's possible.
I want a paternity test.
Tell him that amnios
are dangerous this early on
in the pregnancy.
Are they?
- Well, who cares?
He doesn't know.
Well, we'll--we'll
do the paternity test.
No reaction.
- That's bad?
If you had
a mold allergy,
it would explain
your symptoms.
We'll find out what's wrong,
don't worry.
And, uh,
I know some things
are hard to talk about
with your parents around,
but kids
can be really mean.
There are people
you can talk to--
programs--
I'll--I'll be okay.
You're in good spirits.
You feeling better?
No.
I was just
doing my homework.
I'm such a dork,
I guess that cheers me up.
Parents brought it?
No, Simon did.
The jocky kid
in your class?
Yeah. He just left.
Security.
I was just bringing her
her homework.
You helped bully
this little girl
and completely refuse
to accept responsibility.
No way you came here
out of compassion.
That only leaves guilt.
What'd you do to her?
Nothing.
- Stop lying.
Or I'll take the drugs
I found in your locker
down to the cops,
you slimy little jerk.
This kid didn't do
anything to you.
This isn't about me.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. I get it.
You were bullied yourself
when you were in school.
Take it easy.
I wasn't bullied.
Right--
the Indian foster kid
whose parents were shot
in front of him.
You were clearly
Homecoming King.
Let's try this again.
Just tell me--
Honestly,
you don't understand.
We used to be friends.
And I'd be friends
with her now
if, you know, people
wouldn't make fun of me.
There's nothing you could
tell us that'll help?
Did she mention
she used to drink a lot?
No.
How do you know that?
Look, don't tell anyone,
all right?
I had my brother's I.D.
and I kind of supplied people.
I used to get her
a few bottles of vodka
each week.
Why'd you stop?
She got her own I.D.
Said it was cheaper
buying it herself.
You can go.
I think we got
our diagnosis.
Our little girl's
a drunk.
I don't drink.
I did back then, but--
you could die.
We can't get you
on the transplant list
until we know why
your liver is failing.
Alcohol abuse
would explain that.
The seizures could be
from withdrawal.
I haven't drunk
in six months.
I didn't even drink
that much back then.
A couple
of vodka bottles a week?
I didn't open
half of them.
I just bought them
because--
you know, 'cause Simon
was selling them.
We used to be friends.
And that's, like,
the only way
I could get him
to even talk to me.
Then why did you
stop buying from him?
He said
you got your own I.D.
I don't know.
See, that's
not a good answer.
Remember when you asked me
if I had any kids?
I don't.
I don't know, maybe it
has nothing to do with it,
but I was good at school,
good at work,
lousy at life.
I screwed up every
relationship I ever had.
And I thought,
"why would I
want to bring a child
into this?"
But then I got older.
And...
How you feel now
will pass.
Don't let it screw up
your whole life.
It's already screwed up.
My asthma.
They said they'd fix it,
but it didn't make
any difference at all.
Well, sometimes
doctors make mistakes...
Anna,
and then you have to try
twice as hard to fix them.
Are you using your inhaler?
- All the time.
Go through one a week.
You sure
you're using it right?
Do I look like an idiot?
No.
Why don't you show me
how your inhaler works?
Jerk.
Uh, what was
that all about?
Jamaican chicken recipes.
The parents said
no to the benzos,
but I still think Natalie's
not being honest with me.
So she's willing to die
to cover up some boozing.
She's very depressed.
She feels
like she deserves
what the other kids
are dishing out on her.
I think she
either wants to die
or she wants the attention
that dying gives her.
I have no idea
why you care so much.
Tell Kutner
to start her on benzos.
House, the parents just--
- Uh-uh.
Not the alcoholism.
Seizures.
Totally different.
Don't need
their approval for that.
You sure
you want to know?
If it makes it
any easier,
I'm gonna
tell you anyway.
We want to know.
What does it say?
Don't leave.
You go home last night?
I meant to.
Started
reading this file,
just couldn't
put it down.
Let me ask you--
That patient
that dropped out,
the one I told you about--
Yeah.
You think I
should pursue it more?
No, patients drop out.
That's why we
start with hundreds.
Well, I just thought if
there's an easy way to make
the people who drop off
come back, then why not--
They're not people.
Really?
I thought
the zombie trials
were all completed
during phase two.
You can't see
the patients as people.
You can't even
see them as patients.
They're numbers.
Look...
a friend of mine
has this disease.
I don't wanna know.
There's a reason
this is double-blind--
Any personal stake
we have skews the studies.
Science is not about
human relationships.
It's about results.
Now, you know that.
You work for House.
Why do you think I
brought you on as my partner?
Dr. Taub!
She was talking to me
and then she just passed out.
Her heart's slowing down.
Can you fix it?
- I'm trying.
Pushing one amp atropine.
We've been waiting here for six hours.
Am I the father or not?
No.
But...
She also didn't
cheat on you.
Normally,
sperm meets egg,
D.N.A. meets D.N.A.,
goes back to her place,
cells divide,
nine months later,
joy is bundled.
That's normally.
Abnormally,
An egg could have
two naturally occurring
gene mutations
that don't naturally
occur together.
A spontaneous calcium spike
could prep the egg
for fertilization
without sperm,
and a division mistake
could let the egg split up
without ever needing
male D.N.A. at all.
Parthenogenesis.
A baby without a daddy.
In humans, it's only
ever been theorized,
but it was never proved.
Until now.
Mommy.
Baby.
Your daughter has
only maternal D.N.A.
I personally
checked this five times.
In seven months,
you will have...
a virgin birth.
Merry Christmas.
Gotta tell you about
this clinic patient.
Natalie's liver is
continuing to fail.
And now bradycardia.
Atropine isn't keeping
the heart rate up.
We're gonna have to
put her on a pacemaker.
Alcohol withdrawal
would cause her heart
to race, not crawl.
There's nothing structurally
wrong with her heart.
E.K.G., echo, electrolyte
panel are all normal.
Multiple
endocrine syndrome?
Free T-4's normal.
Hypothalamic brain tumor?
Didn't come up
on the C.T. scan.
It's hitting
all her organs.
Could be the blood.
What's her alk phos?
300.
It can't be leukemia.
High alk phos could
also be from liver failure.
She's a teenager--
means bone growth
and destruction
could throw it off.
Maybe, but it's higher
than you'd expect.
Start her on chemo.
We'll do a bone marrow
biopsy to confirm.
Why are you ordering
tests instead of treatment?
Her heart and liver
are about to give up.
Do whatever you need to.
Why are you
so attached to this girl?
It's your call.
He doesn't want us
to treat her.
If it's leukemia,
even if we kill
every cancer cell,
her heart and liver
are too far gone.
A double transplant--
With brain involvement?
The committee
won't even open the file.
There's no reason
to put a dying girl
through
a painful treatment
if it can't save her.
He's being kind.
I'll arrange a biopsy.
Mrs. Burke?
We are conducting
another trial
in tandem with yours.
Same drug, lower dose.
The nausea will be less.
I did some checking.
I can switch you.
Here's the forms
if you want back in.
What if we're wrong?
Maybe we shouldn't
have overlooked autoimmunes.
High sed rate--
We went over this.
Normal complement level.
So it isn't
hepatic fibrosis.
Could still be
Microangiopathic
vasculitis.
With high-dose steroids,
we might be
able to reverse--
You run a hospital
That treats thousands
of patients every day.
Some of them die.
Every day.
If you're gonna
get this worked up
over every one of them--
Yes!
B.R.B.
What is it?
Thank you from a patient.
For you?
I saved her marriage
by showing
that her pregnancy
was the result
of parthenogenesis.
Human parthenogenesis?
You proved--
- Yep.
It's unbelievable.
But I personally
checked it five times.
How did you
check it five times?
The cycler's broken,
you would have
had to send it out.
It would have taken--
- Oh, yeah.
That does sound impossible,
now that I think of it.
I guess
the better explanation
is that the paternity test
showed she cheated
so I faked the whole
parthenogenesis thingy.
What?
Why?
I win.
You faked
a scientific miracle
just to win
a bet with Wilson?
Mmm, more an argument.
I realize it
would have been simpler
to just fake
the paternity test,
but hey--Christmas
spirit and all that.
I think you're confusing
nice and evil again.
Letting a woman
deceive her husband
by inventing a virgin birth
just so you can--
And it obviously
would have been more fitting
if the baby had
been born on Christmas,
not just invented then.
It's not leukemia.
Seizures,
liver failure--
It's eclampsia.
This means we don't
have one dead patient.
We have two.
Um...
You have a disease
called eclampsia.
It causes liver failure,
pulmonary edema,
and seizures.
It's also associated
with cardiomyopathy.
That's a pregnancy disease.
You tested her
when she came in.
Uh, you can get eclampsia
up to a month
after giving birth.
That's ridiculous.
How could she hide a pregnancy?
- Loose clothes.
She's heavy
to begin with.
It was probably premature.
If it was
three weeks ago,
They could have missed it
on a physical exam.
The baby's why
you quit drinking,
isn't it?
Why you asked me
if I had kids.
Why you feel guilty.
I'm sorry.
Oh--
who did this to you?
Simon.
It wasn't bad.
We were like boyfriend/
girlfriend for a while,
We just
didn't tell anyone.
He doesn't
even know about--
What happened
to the baby?
I was gonna give it away.
If they found out
at school--
I was at
the soup kitchen
And she started coming.
There was this empty house
down the street,
But then
she wasn't breathing.
I tried so hard,
but I couldn't do anything.
I'm...so sorry.
If I had her
in a hospital,
maybe she'd be alive.
Can you cure this?
The damage to the heart
and liver are permanent.
I'm gonna die?
I'm sorry.
I didn't even bury her.
I just
put my coat over her.
Get out of my house.
I'm a doctor.
I don't care
who you are.
Did you, uh...
Find the body
of a baby?
I said get out.
Michael?
Who are you?
That's not your baby.
You're tiny.
There's no way you gave
birth three weeks ago.
She's my sister's.
That baby is sick.
She needs clean water.
She needs real heat.
She was probably born
with a partially blocked
airway and--
might even have brain damage.
You can't take care of her
in a place like this.
Shut up.
I took care of her--
I know.
You found her.
You saved her life.
Now you have
to let her go.
Who is that?
It's your daughter.
She was alive.
People found her
and took care of her.
# runnin' the race
like a mouse in a Cage #
# gettin' nowhere. #
She's beautiful.
# but I'm trying #
# forgin' ahead #
# but I'm stuck
in the bed that I made #
# so I'm lying #
# but if you keep real #
# close #
# yeah, you stay real #
# I will reach you #
# I'm down #
# to a whisper #
# in a daydream #
# on a hill #
# shut down to a whisper... #
Kutner.
No transplant?
We appealed.
Too sick.
How much time
does she have left?
A couple of days
at most.
What about the baby?
Seems healthy,
But it's
too early to tell.
She's in the hospital
for observation
For a few days,
but after that--
Best case, winds up
with her teenage father
who just got voted
captain of the varsity
bullying team.
He's just a kid.
You all right?
I gotta go.
# and I've stopped
trying to find #
# any peace in my mind #
# 'cause it
tangles the wires #
# but if you keep real #
# close #
# yeah, you stay real #
Jonathan.
Yeah?
It--it's, uh...
It's Lawrence Kutner.
Wh-why are you here?
I wanted to apologize.
For all of
the horrible stuff
I did to you
in high school.
I'm sorry.
# shut down
to a whisper #
# can you hear me? #
# still? #
# the sound #
# tires on my lips... #
What's gonna happen to her?
I spoke to both sets
of grandparents.
It's too painful.
They're putting her
up for adoption.
What are you gonna do?
I already spoke
to a lawyer.
I become a foster parent
and then I adopt.
# shut down
to a whisper #
# can you hear me? #
# I'm down
to a whisper... #
Merry Christmas,
Cuddy.
Hey.
# can you hear me? # #
Where is everybody?
Down at the party.
I heard Janice is back
on the trial.
My Christmas gift
to you.
I was wrong.
You're not House.
Yeah, well, that's
my Christmas gift to myself.
We should
go to the party.
We should.
# chestnuts
roasting on an open fire #
# Jack frost nippin'
at your nose #
# yuletide carols #
# being sung by a choir... # #
Subtitles by LeapinLar