I still can't believe
you talked me into this.
(CHUCKLING) Come on,
honey, you're gonna
throw him off.
It's okay,
I'm almost done.
(SIGHS)
A little more light
on your hips.
God.
Why couldn't you
have come up with this
before I had two kids?
(CHUCKLING)
You look amazing.
Okay, I think...
Yeah, I'm done. Want
to come take a look?
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS) I can't.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You first.
No, we'll look together.
I don't understand.
I thought...
What the hell is that?
Honey, it's okay.
This is not
what we discussed,
or what I paid for.
I don't understand.
I think this is one of
the best I've ever done.
I want my money back.
I'm sorry, but this is
not some department
store photo studio.
And this is
not my wife.
Yes, it is.
You asked me to paint
her exactly as she looks.
That's exactly what I did.
Honey! Stop it!
What's going on?
Brandon.
That check better
be in my mailbox by
Friday, or I'll be back.
Come on.
What happened?
I don't know.
They saw the painting,
and they just freaked out.
Brandon, what is this?
What do you mean?
It's her portrait.
What's wrong with it?
Why is this in here?
First column,
last entry.
Today is going
to be a good day.
This him?
No.
Yes.
She means, are you the
private investigator
whose bills I've
tried to slip through
as medical expenses?
Oh. Hi.
I'm Lucas Douglas, PI.
This hospital is
not putting a private
investigator on retainer,
nor is it going
to pay any more
phony repairs on
vending machines,
cryostats, or elevators.
Information saves lives.
Saving lives saves money.
No, saving lives
costs money,
which is why I'm
trying to make sure
there's still some left.
You want your
own personal PI,
you're gonna have to
pay for him yourself.
Sorry.
No, I understand.
Hey, I like the
shoes, by the way.
Oh.
Thank you.
You don't
like her shoes,
you like her legs.
It sounds less creepy
if you say shoes.
Less creepy, more gay.
That's my firm's motto.
What is a cryostat?
No idea.
Whoever fixed ours is
about to get stiffed.
There's no distorted
perspective in any of
his other recent works.
Not much talent
either.
It's like the symptom
just came on.
Acute onset visual agnosia
points to a stroke
or brain tumor.
TAUB: MRI revealed no
stroke or brain tumor.
We should do another
with contrast.
If he's like the other
struggling artists
I've known,
he's also into drugs.
We should...
What are you looking at?
Apparently a moron.
One, ER routinely
tests for drugs.
If it was positive,
we wouldn't be
looking at this file.
Two, who pays 12%
interest on a car loan?
How did you...
Did you run a
credit check on me?
No, that would
be illegal.
Interestingly enough,
paying someone to run
it for me, though...
(SCOFFS)
What?
It's part of my job.
Your job is to
diagnose patients.
Which I do
with a team.
How am I supposed
to know how best
to utilize that team
if I don't know
everything about them?
Say that
Van Gogh turns out
to have neurosyphilis,
and our last
vial of penicillin
is in a storeroom
at the end of
a 20-mile hallway with
a two-foot-high ceiling.
You've discovered that
one of us has been
hiding the ability
to stretch or
shrink themselves?
No, I would never out
someone's superpowers.
This, on the other hand...
You crawled 20 miles?
My name's in
the Guinness Book.
I'll bet that really
impresses the babes.
I didn't do it
to get the babes.
No, that would
cheapen the purity
of your achievement.
Sorry to interrupt, but
we have a patient with
a probable brain tumor.
Who needs
an MRI with contrast.
We've established that.
What do you
got on Taub?
I got nothing on Taub.
THIRTEEN: Could also
be environmental.
We should check his
studio for toxins,
mold, fungus...
Taub's wife,
on the other hand...
FOREMAN: House.
That's enough.
Dad's right. This is
no time for gossip.
Patient desperately
needs our help.
Check his head
and his house.
Can't Lucas...
No.
He's very busy.
FOREMAN: If there is a tumor,
this test will show us...
Is that stuff
dangerous?
This is just the
contrast material.
There is a small risk of
an anaphylactic reaction.
I could stop breathing?
Don't worry.
We're prepared to deal
with whatever happens.
You know, I did some
drawings this morning
and they seem fine.
So, maybe it
was just a reaction
to something I ate.
FOREMAN: How many people
you know have reactions
like that
to something they
ate for breakfast?
But if I'm
getting better...
You'll continue
to get better.
If you're not,
we need to
know why not,
so we can start
treatment immediately.
Baby, let them
do the test.
Can lead poisoning
cause visual agnosia?
TAUB: Not without
lead showing up
in the blood work.
Nothing in the medicine
cabinet except some
harmless toiletries.
No signs of mold
or fungus anywhere,
either.
You think House really
got something
on your wife?
No, not that
I care if he did.
Wait, your wife's
doing the doorman
in your bed,
and they're sweating
all over the sheets
that you paid for and...
My wife's not doing
the doorman.
How do you know?
We don't have
a doorman.
And I just do,
okay? Drop it.
In college, my friends
and I came up with an
Inverse-Square Law.
Sounds like
a real fun group.
The girls who you think
are the most inhibited,
straight arrows?
They're the ones
you hook up with.
Are you saying
my wife's a slut?
I'm saying if my
wife was a slut,
I'd want to know.
KUTNER:
His place was clean.
So is his head.
Even with contrast,
no masses, no lesions.
A neurological symptom
with no apparent
neurological cause.
Time course means
we can rule out
cancer and MS.
That just leaves
toxins or drugs.
You called Thirteen
a moron for thinking
it was drugs.
Yeah, when she said it,
she had other options.
And I really just wanted
a segue into her stupid
loan and your...
A cavernous angioma
in the brain could leak.
Once the blood
gets reabsorbed,
pressure goes down,
symptom goes away.
He'll never consent to
petrosal vein sampling.
Really?
He was nervous about
an injection of contrast.
Is his girlfriend hot?
I'm not talking
fever, here.
I mean, is she all
curvy and perky?
Very. And if he dies,
it's good news for
all of us, but...
That explains why all
his paintings suck.
And what's wrong
with him.
Where are you going?
To tell him he may
have a massive
brain tumor.
He doesn't.
I know. I'm not a
moron. It's drugs.
(DOOR OPENS)
You seem to have
a massive brain tumor.
Who are you?
He's Dr. House.
He's pleased
to meet you.
We've found no trace
on any of your imaging,
so we need to cut
your head open.
It's risky,
but it's the only way
to save your life.
No.
Wrong answer.
I'm not allowed
to say no?
You're not allowed
to not be terrified.
There's only two
good reasons not to be
terrified in a hospital.
You're delusional, but
then you're not afraid of
contrast material either,
or you know you're fine.
Since we haven't told
you you're fine,
you obviously
have information
that we don't have.
What drugs are you on?
His drug tests
were clean.
Drug tests only test
for drugs they've
made tests for.
What are you
talking about?
(SIGHS)
Hottie thinks that
he's a great artist,
selling art to the
rich and tasteful.
She's stupid enough
to be fooled by
the canvasses,
but bank accounts
don't lie.
He needed money.
There are not many
jobs you can do that
don't require time,
training and intelligence.
And I know you're not
a news anchor or supermodel
because those jobs
seldom cause agnosia.
He's a guinea pig.
Companies pay him to test
their untested drugs.
Did Hottie go for
a pee or coffee?
'Cause either way,
I don't think we should
waste any time on denials.
The clinical trials
were supposed
to be safe.
The drugs are about to
be approved by the FDA.
"Drugs"? How many
trials are you on?
Three.
Admirable. Not many
idiots have that
much ambition.
You've been symptom-free
since your admission,
so whatever you took
has probably cleared
your system now.
You'll be fine.
Keep him overnight
just to make sure,
and get the names
of all the trials
he's been in.
You gonna
tell Heather?
Couldn't,
even if I cared
enough to want to.
Not bad. You almost
made it the whole day.
What did you
find out?
The point is to see
how everyone reacts.
You may go get
the rest of the gang.
Cut the crap, House.
Your wife has
a separate
bank account
in her name only.
She's been making
weekly cash deposits
for about a year now.
No withdrawals yet.
That's it? A bank account?
A secret bank account.
What makes you think
it's a secret?
Because if it wasn't
you would call it
"the" bank account.
Damn, always forget
to use the right
article when lying.
It's not secret.
We're refurnishing.
We set the budget,
set up an account.
I just couldn't
make it to the bank
the day we opened it.
You're spending
almost $100,000
on furniture?
Yes.
(PAGERS BEEPING)
TAUB: What happened?
FOREMAN: I don't know.
He was fine,
then all of a sudden
he started seizing.
He said you told
him he was better.
What's happening?
What's wrong with him?
(CHOKING)
(MACHINES BEEPING)
She is hot.
Obviously,
the drugs weren't
out of his system.
None of these drugs,
nor the drugs
they're derived from,
are known for
causing seizures.
By themselves, no.
But three unproven,
untested drugs?
It's like The Mod Squad,
no one can stop them.
It's ridiculous that
they let people take
potentially dangerous
drugs for money.
Just to short circuit
that discussion,
people should not be
testing drugs because
they're desperate.
But people won't test
drugs unless they're
desperate.
We need drugs to save
children and puppies,
ergo we need
desperate people,
ergo welfare kills
sick children.
First drug...
Why don't we call
it Bisexidrene?
Clinical trials involve
experimental drugs.
Means they don't
have comforting,
catchy names yet,
just random,
unmemorable
trial numbers.
(BEEPING)
Go ahead.
Bisexidrene is
designed as an
anticoagulant.
Phase one indicated
some risk of nausea,
ED and insomnia.
Second drug...
Cuckoldisol.
She is having
an affair?
Worse.
Sex can be dismissed as
hormonal or emotional,
can be easily regretted.
Money is always
a calculated decision.
My wife has her
own bank account
that House doesn't
think I know about.
Shocking. Discuss.
Drug B is
an autoimmune treatment,
almost no side effects.
But even if it's doing
what it's supposed
to be doing,
it doesn't mix well
with anticoagulants
or anticonvulsants.
KUTNER: Which is
the third drug?
World's-sorest-knees-isil.
Cuddy used to have
that title,
by the way.
There's a million
ways these drugs
could interact,
if they're doing
what they're
supposed to.
If they're not,
two million.
And it'd be interesting
to know which of those
interactions
was causing the problem.
Unfortunately,
we don't have to.
We just have to stop
the interacting.
If we don't
know which...
We stop them all.
Put him on dialysis,
clear out his system.
Rapid detox
risks arrhythmia,
another seizure,
hepatic failure...
Difference is we know
what those risks are.
Put him on dialysis.
Dialysis. You use
that for kidney
failure, right?
Don't worry,
your kidneys are fine.
He's not worried
about his kidneys.
He's worried about
how he's going
to explain
the dialysis to
his girlfriend.
I just don't want
her to worry.
You mean you don't
want her to leave you.
What's wrong with
that? I love her.
It's not like I've
lied to her about
anything important.
I am an artist.
I've sold plenty of
paintings in the past,
I just hit a bit of
a dry spell lately, so...
So tell her that.
He can't.
He wants her to
be happy, too.
He's telling her
what she wants
to hear.
You didn't know.
No.
What are you gonna do?
She's not sleeping around,
she's not gambling it away,
she hasn't even
spent any of it,
so I don't see
a reason to
do anything.
You don't think
a conversation...
How many people
do you know
in completely happy
and fulfilled
relationships?
None.
I am.
Most people cling to
some storybook notion
of what a relationship is.
You can't have
an imperfect thought.
a private zone.
You can't...
Steal money and
hide it away in
a secret account?
She makes me happy.
I make her happy.
It works.
Because we
don't do storybook,
and I don't plan to
poke into her business.
You were right
about the dialysis.
He made it through
the night without
any more seizures
or visual symptoms.
And I'm gonna
be just as right
after breakfast
up in my office.
The only difference is
I'm gonna be right in
front of other people.
Which means you're
not here to talk
about the medicine.
You can screw with me
all you want at work,
but stay out of
my personal life.
What did she say?
Did you just hear
what I said?
I heard the part about
"You can screw
with me at work
all you want."
You want my advice?
Of course not.
Good, because
I have no idea
what you should do.
I only know what
you're going to do.
You're gonna...
I said I didn't
want your advice.
I said this is
not advice.
You are going
to forgive her for
opening that account,
and you're gonna confess
everything you've done
and then you're gonna
beg her to forgive you.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
What purpose could
that possibly serve?
None, which is why
I'm not saying you
should, but you will.
DOUGLAS ON EARPHONE:
What's your end game?
Where are you?
I'm at the track.
That's like six miles away.
How cool are these things?
I feel like an idiot.
I'm not giving you
any more of my stuff.
Do you have those
night vision goggles?
No.
You're lying.
You like making
him miserable.
You like driving
people away from you.
He deserved to
know the truth.
There was no truth
until you dug it up.
HOUSE ON EARPHONE: You do know
that stuff exists even when
you can't see it, right?
It was a truth that
mattered to him
and a truth that
mattered to her,
why did it matter to you?
First of all,
stop saying "a" truth.
There is only one truth.
That may be
true for you.
Miserable people
save more lives.
If your life has meaning,
your job doesn't have
to have meaning.
Screw-ups are
more palatable if you have
someone's arms to go cry in.
That makes sense.
Usually, I have more
of a fight on that one.
So why are you making
Taub miserable?
I just said...
He left his last job
to save his marriage.
If his marriage falls apart,
you think he'll be working
harder for you?
Or you think he won't be
working for you at all?
(BRANDON WHEEZING)
FOREMAN: His head and neck
are completely swollen.
I need a Trach kit.
His throat's closing.
(MACHINES BEEPING)
Can't find
any landmarks.
Just start cutting.
An exploratory trach?
We don't have a choice.
I got it.
Here.
KUTNER: His face is so
swollen it's squeezed
his tear ducts shut.
We've been lubricating
his eyes by hand.
We've started him
on steroids, IV,
and cream to reduce
the swelling,
but it's having
limited effect.
Negative for
thrombosis and Chagas.
Could be infection.
Cultures still
negative.
Could be his immune
system's on hyperdrive,
cytokine storm.
Why would you pay
for a three-year
gym membership
and only go twice?
Sorry. You guys
still diagnosing?
I thought
we finished hours ago.
You remember,
when we decided
it was the unproven,
unapproved cocktail of drugs
he's been downing like...
Like a cocktail.
He just completed
a total dialysis.
If it was the drugs,
he'd be better.
Or he'd be worse.
I take it none of you
saw Trainspotting.
You think swelling
is a symptom of
withdrawal?
You think it's
a coincidence that three
new symptoms cropped up
as soon as we took
him off the drugs?
It's possible some
of the symptoms...
Either the drugs
are the answer
or the drugs are
a coincidence.
If it's one, we have
to find a better way
to detox him.
If it's two, we have
to know which symptoms
are withdrawal related
before we can formulate
a diagnosis.
Which means we have
to find a better way
to detox him.
So how do we do it?
Hair of the drug
that bit him.
That's ridiculous.
If it is the drugs,
they're dangerous, and
they've already caused...
That's why we're
gonna put him back
on the drugs,
then wean him off again.
Just much slower.
Why are you
looking at him?
Try it out.
You heard the boss. Go!
Taub...
I didn't talk to her.
Why are you...
Excuse me.
Uh, sorry.
He does look like me,
doesn't he?
You gave him
your hat?
I needed you out of
here so I could go
through your desk.
Of course.
Nice blouse. I really
like that color on you.
Tell House that if
he wants to know
what I'm doing,
all he has to do...
It's not House. It's me.
I was... I don't know.
I was thinking maybe
we could get together
for a drink or something.
I wasn't sure exactly
what you like to do,
so I thought...
You'd spy on me?
No, no, not spying.
More like research.
I think it's a good
idea to get to know
a little bit more
about a woman before
you ask her out.
Show you care about
more than just what
she looks like.
As romantic as you
make that sound,
pretty sure that
what you're doing
is not so much
caring as creepy.
That's not fair.
You were scrounging
through my desk.
What the hell am
I going to find out?
You went to Michigan.
You like your sandwiches
a little light on mayo.
You stay in touch
with your mother.
You rented
The English Patient
and you gave money to
Amnesty International.
There's not one thing
I can find out in here
that you wouldn't tell
a co-worker while riding
in an elevator.
I'm not a creep.
I just thought you
seemed interesting.
I'll go now.
Yeah, these...
(SNAPS FINGERS)
I'll give you
embarrassing
info on House.
In exchange for...
No. No need
for a date.
You'd be employing me,
so I'd have all the
time in the world
to ask you all about
you and it would fall
under the category
of socializing,
instead of
creepy stalking.
And I'd be paying you?
I know it's weird.
But if you pay me
while I check you
out, it's all cool.
And you'd get value.
You'd get leverage
against him.
Help you keep
him in line.
You think I need help
keeping House in line?
No.
Nope. I'm sorry.
This hospital
can't afford...
Oh, whatever
you can afford.
How did you know
I liked roses?
I was in your house
last night.
(CHUCKLING)
No, I'm kidding.
Who the hell
doesn't like roses?
I forgot to tell you,
the Parker Quartet
is going to play at
the library fundraiser.
That's it?
It was your idea.
They'll be great.
Mmm-hmm.
You okay?
I couldn't find
the letter opener.
I went through some of
the drawers in your
desk, looking for it.
There were a bunch
of statements in there
from Jefferson Mutual.
I was so close.
To what?
You've got
$83,000 socked away
in a secret account.
Not anymore.
I wanted to keep it
a surprise,
but I bought you the car.
(LAUGHING)
Uh...
The one that I...
(CHUCKLES)
I knew you would
never buy it yourself,
so I've been saving.
And it's gonna be
delivered on Friday.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You are amazing.
Lucky you.
(LAUGHING)
We've gradually
reduced your dosage.
You're actually
drug-free now.
I feel great.
Thanks to you.
All part of the job.
Your blood
pressure is normal.
Can you sit up?
Hey!
What are you...
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
What happened
to his face?
Question is,
what happened
to his hormones?
We're gonna need
an ice pack in here.
KUTNER: We can rule
out the clinical trial
drugs at this point.
His system has been
completely cleaned twice.
So unless the drugs
found a hiding place
under the stairs...
Drugs could have set off
a dormant neurological
condition.
Good point.
Coming clean causes
a lot of damage.
Alienation, divorce...
My wife's
buying me a car.
I was talking
about the patient.
You were wrong.
The divorce was
metaphorical.
FOREMAN: What about
Kl?ver-Bucy Syndrome?
Bilateral lesions
in the temporal lobes.
Visual agnosia
and hyper-sexuality
are the key symptoms.
Good thing he's got
that girlfriend.
If it's Kl?ver-Bucy,
his brain will melt down,
he'll try to swallow
his own hands
and she can take care
of him for the rest
of his talentless life.
You owe me an apology.
Any rationalization
you had for meddling
in my private life
disappeared
when she had
good reason...
You're right.
Fact is,
nothing I said applies.
You had no reason
to forgive her,
therefore no reason
to seek forgiveness,
no reason to be an idiot.
Kl?ver-Bucy wouldn't
explain the seizure or
the cytokine storm.
Withdrawal complications.
Then again,
she is handing
you a giant gift
that you don't think
you deserve.
The fact that the MRI showed
no lesions on the temporal
lobe tends to rule out
your "lesions on the
temporal lobe" theory.
The damage can be
a circulatory issue,
rather than structural.
We wouldn't see
that on the MRI.
Foreman's right.
Go call your wife,
tell her you're
not coming home,
say you have to give
a patient a cranial
MR angiogram,
then say good night
and hang up.
Odd that a man who
can't run would own so
many pairs of sneakers.
You mind hanging this
up when you're done?
I have to find something
embarrassing about you.
No, you don't.
I ordered us Indian.
Not too embarrassing.
Just something credible.
Well, if you hand her that,
she's not gonna need you
anymore.
If I don't hand
her anything, she'll
think I'm incompetent.
I don't care if
she thinks you're
incompetent.
This isn't gonna work.
It's worked so far.
I'm not good at lying.
I know.
That's why your cover is
that you want to do her.
I like her.
I don't want to do her.
Then what's the point
of liking her?
I meant I don't
just want to do
her. I like her.
What do you think
you're gonna find
out about her?
Something personal,
something embarrassing.
I spend half my life
negotiating with
that woman.
Anything I can
use to scare her
into saying yes.
Okay.
"Okay"?
You're okay with
being paid twice to
facilitate blackmail?
I'm okay.
I don't believe
you. But I'm okay.
You're doing this
for the same reason
I'm doing this.
We'll see
who gets there first.
Here it is.
Circle of Willis,
the vessels are narrow.
Narrow for you,
normal for him.
If there were problems
with the vessels,
he would have had
symptoms long ago.
Not if something
else changed.
Like?
TAUB: His heart.
He could have
recently gotten an
intermittent arrhythmia.
I know "heart" and "head"
start with the same
three letters,
but you've got to read
all the way to the end.
The experimental drugs
cause an arrhythmia
which causes
low blood pressure.
Combine that with
those narrow vessels,
the brain doesn't
get enough blood.
That causes all
of his symptoms.
If we can trigger
the arrhythmia
and identify it,
we might be able
to stop it from
killing him.
Been home?
No.
Good. Do an EP study.
Find the arrhythmia.
We're gonna insert three
electrical catheters
into your heart.
Tell Dr. Hadley
I'm sorry.
She understands,
and you should
tell her yourself.
Maybe I should tell
Heather about it.
You're gonna be fine.
She's so supportive,
she's so great.
All I do is lie to her.
What happens if
you tell her?
I don't know.
You love her, right?
More than anything,
and she loves me.
If you open your mouth,
one of two things happens,
she either forgives
you or she leaves you.
At best, you wind
up exactly where
you are right now.
It's noble to want
to confess. Really,
it is.
But if the result's
just damage and pain,
that's not noble,
it's selfish.
TAUB: Stimulate right atrium.
Normal conduction.
How long you plan
on keeping me from
going home?
Until you're convinced
I'm a different person,
one who won't do
anything stupid?
Guilt fades quickly.
By Wednesday,
you'll be fine.
Right ventricle.
And why do you
want it to fade?
Why do you suddenly
care about my marriage?
Because if it
ain't broke...
You obviously think
it is broke.
And you obviously
think it ain't.
Your marriage is like
a broken toaster.
Bread keeps popping
out, and you keep
calling it toast,
which is weird because
you've put your bread
in a lot of toasters,
and apparently you don't
see any difference.
It's kind of fascinating.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
He's going
into V Tach.
What's wrong?
Good news,
test is working.
Your heart's freaking out,
but it's cool that you're
still conscious.
(WHEEZING)
Try to overdrive.
Didn't work.
(PANTING)
This might
burn a little bit.
Charging to 60. Clear.
Ow!
Going again.
Charging to 120.
Have you been
dyeing your hair?
No.
House. Clear.
Right.
(GROANS)
Your hair's growing in red.
(BRANDON PANTING)
TAUB: His heart rate
is stabilized.
Does your theory include
any genetic mutations
that could cause his
hair to change color?
Then either he's
lying about dyeing
or just dying.
Red hair means
it's not Kl?ver-Bucy.
Melanin affects hair
color. What affects
melanin?
Hormones.
Hormone panels
were all normal.
Age.
He's turning
prematurely crimson?
FOREMAN:
A genetic disorder.
Waardenburg Syndrome
causes arrhythmias and
can change hair color.
And make you deaf. Next.
I found a long QT interval.
I think it's Romano-Ward
Syndrome.
Explains the irregular
heart rhythms.
But not the ginger nut.
FOREMAN: If he's got Romano's,
he's got at least five
gene mutations.
It's not a big leap to
think he has others that
would give him the hair.
It also gives him the
likelihood of sudden
and unexpected death.
Beta blockers don't work.
His heart can't
handle an ICD.
Pete Best.
Good God, has none of you
ever read a history book?
The original
Beatles drummer.
A bunch of nerves
controls the tempo
of the heart.
They're all playing in time,
except one dude who
can't keep the beat,
wrecks the whole thing,
so we hire Ringo.
Pete Best was actually
a great drummer.
But I assume you
mean the patient needs
a cardiac sympathectomy?
I probably should
have just said
that, huh?
You start cutting nerves,
you risk his swallowing,
vocal cords, sweating...
So he saves a fortune
on karaoke machines
and deodorant.
You think he's stable
enough for surgery?
If he was,
he wouldn't need it.
CUDDY: Wow.
Wow.
Yeah.
Do you have
any brothers
and sisters?
One sister.
He told me he was
on the lacrosse team.
In high school.
In college he just
cheered the lacrosse
team on to victory.
Wow.
Yeah.
How was your
relationship
with your dad?
Fine. You have
three more questions.
How was your
relationship
with your mom?
Fine.
When did you lose
your virginity?
Not something I discuss
with co-workers
in an elevator.
And...
You know, don't you?
Bit of a wasted
third question
'cause the answer is
"Know what?"
Okay,
bear with me here,
because some people
sometimes consider
my thought processes
complicated.
I'm into you 'cause
you're hot and smart,
in that order,
but both are needed.
Photos can be retouched,
and House is an evil
genius, which makes
this photo suspicious.
And yet you're
not suspicious.
Which means either
you're not smart enough
to be suspicious,
in which case, I am
less interested in you.
Or you're
not suspicious
because you know
this is actually
a doctored photo
of House.
In which case, I am
more interested in you.
But I'm wasting my
time because you know
this is a game we
are playing on you
and I am busted
and I'm screwed.
I know the photo's a fake.
I know this is a game.
Sorry.
Too bad.
Goodbye.
So you knew that I
wasn't gonna give you
anything worthwhile?
And you were
never gonna give me
anything worthwhile?
Then why did you bother
coming out with me?
I wanted to
screw with House.
By wasting my time?
That doesn't make sense.
No. There must be
another reason.
Hmm.
Is it okay if I
sit back down here?
(CHUCKLES)
THIRTEEN:
Your heartbeat's
out of control.
We need to surgically sever
the connection between
your heart and brain.
We believe it's necessary,
but you need to know
the ramifications.
You'll never be able
to feel angina.
You may not know
if you have a
heart attack,
may not be able to
get help in time.
Where are my
regular doctors?
Regular doctors?
Dr. Taub and Dr. Hadley.
Why aren't they
telling me this?
Brandon, I am Dr. Hadley,
and this is Dr. Taub.
What are you talking
about? I've never seen
you before in my life.
TAUB: We can't
do the surgery.
We're back to
where we started,
visual agnosia.
We need to re-examine
neurological disorders,
something
slowly progressing.
This isn't progressing.
It's there,
then it's not,
then it is.
It's a new symptom,
intermittence.
It's irrelevant.
Since when is a new
symptom irrelevant?
Since it points
towards the same
disease.
Intermittence can fit
with Romano-Ward.
We still need to do
a sympathectomy.
Maybe we missed
something, toxins.
When?
When you checked
every bottle,
every can,
every tube of paint,
or when you
detoxed him twice?
Maybe there was
a batch of toxic paint
that he used up
a few months ago.
Then he would have
been sick months
ago, not now.
He's lost weight
since he got here.
That's a symptom of trying
to cram hospital food
down a throat he can
barely get air down.
It's not a symptom,
but what if the toxins
were stored in his fat
cells a year ago,
and now they're being
released into his
bloodstream?
So where are you gonna
get this old paint,
the city dump?
On his old paintings.
We know he hasn't
sold one in ages,
but there weren't
many in his studio.
He's hid them somewhere.
If you're wrong,
he could drop dead
from Romano-Ward
at any moment.
You okay with that?
Just give me a few hours.
You got one.
I need to talk
to him alone.
It's about your work.
Your paintings.
I need to look
at all the ones
you've sold recently.
Honey, can you
give us a minute?
To talk about
your paintings?
Brandon, please.
Tell me what's going on.
I've only sold two
paintings in the last
three years, since we met.
One was to my cousin.
I've been making money
enrolling in drug trials.
Two, three at a time.
Why did you lie to me?
I want to be...
The way you look
at me, the way it
makes me feel...
I want to be what
you see when you
look at me.
You think
I'm that shallow?
When I look at you,
I see you.
So,
where are the ones
you didn't sell?
(THUDDING)
(PHONE RINGING)
It's not the paint,
it's the drugs.
He's not on the drugs
I know it doesn't
make sense,
but I'm looking
at his paintings for
the last six months.
They're normal April,
June and August,
but they're distorted
May, July, September.
Every other month,
he was having
visual agnosia
because every other month,
he was on all three drugs
simultaneously.
The statin was
one month on,
one month off.
I don't know why
the symptoms keep
coming and going,
but it is the drugs.
They're hiding
under the stairs.
In the fat?
That doesn't make sense.
These drugs aren't
fat soluble.
I said stairs, not closet.
What was the last drug
he was on before the
drugs he was on
when the symptoms started?
I'm not sure, I think...
Antacid.
How do you know?
It makes sense.
Also, I'm looking
at the file.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yes.
It's Dr. House.
Wake him up.
We're done.
No, no, he says
he needs surgery,
but not this one.
Did he give
any specifics?
Abdominal surgery
to remove a bezoar.
It's like a hairball,
but it's made up of
undigested food.
You can get it if your
stomach acid's low,
which Brandon's
was because of an
experimental antacid.
The fruit and vegetable
fibers and skins
get stuck together
and form a ball.
It gets sticky,
ferments, grows.
It starts sucking up
some of the pills
he'd taken.
Some are never
heard from again,
but some get released.
For the last week,
it's basically
been giving him
massive doses of
all three at once.
That is why I won't
let Cameron buy a cat.
He should be fine.
(CHUCKLES)
Are you glad
he told you the truth?
Yes. Of course.
But were you happier
before you knew?
About 10 more feet.
I do know what it looks
like, so maybe this whole
blindfold thing...
Shh. My gift, my rules.
Bump!
All right, if you
don't like the color,
apparently we
can exchange it,
but I'm hoping...
You ready?
Ta-da!
(CHUCKLES)
Do you like it?
Baby, are you okay?
We need to talk.
(PIANO PLAYING)
She didn't buy it.
Damn.
(PIANO PLAYING)
So, you didn't
get anything?
Nothing.
We probably overstepped.
You're really not
the cheerleader type.
On the other hand,
I figured she probably
wouldn't figure me
as the "Photoshopping a photo
and planting it in an obscure
college paper" type either.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah. About that,
I took a little trip
to your alma mater.
You took a little
trip 150 miles?
Online, by phone.
I meant I did research.
That's a real photo,
isn't it?
(EXCLAIMS)
Wow, that is humiliating.
(PIANO PLAYING)
There was a girl.
Even more so.
That's too bad.
You wanted her to see
you in a different light,
and not only
didn't she see it,
but she didn't even
believe it was possible.
You know, people
hate people who have
theories about people.
You want me to back off?
Would you?
I barely know you.
(HARMONIZING)