(Woman)
you see them anywhere?
why don't we go back
to their house,
wait for them there.
Yeah, 'cause they'll
probably answer the door
the sixteenth time I knock.
There they are.
hi.
I'm sorry
I followed you here.
I just really wish
you could give me
a few minutes
of your time.
[speaking native language]
I know you would
never agree
to make it
an open adopon,
but I just figured maybe
you never had a choice.
[man translating]
I mean, it's china, right?
[translating]
[speing native language]
w-what did he say?
He wants you
to leave them alone.
Please...
[speaking native language]
I just want ten minutes.
Learn what you're li,
tell you about my life.
[spits]
[speaking native language]
he said they have
no daughter.
I am sorry
you wasted a trip.
I know that's them.
How does that work?
How do I pray?
You make a wish
and lift the buddha.
I wish they could understand
how badly I need this.
Now make the wish again.
If you cannot lift the buddha
this time,
your wish will bgranted.
[loudly]
oh!
are you okay?
unh!
[pained grunts and groans]
[speaking native language]
[massive attack's teardrop]
I picked cameron's pocket
down in e.r.
I came up  a doozy.
Your mother called--
twe.
She's still healthy.
This 25-year-old woman,
on the other hand...
Her messages sounded
kind of urgent.
Well, that's the way
women sound
when their spouse
of 50 years dies.
[cane whacks wall]
your dad died?
Are you--
Yep. Fine!
(House)
our patient,
who's been known to take
a few drinks
on non-occasions,
vomits blood and collapses
on a trip to china.
Chinese surgeons cut out
a foot of bowel,
but the pain is worse now
than it was before.
House, call your mom.
What are you, my mom?
We can continue
this differential
in five minutes.
Are those bags
under your eyes?
You were up all night.
You told her, didn't you
I don't know
what your daddy issues are,
but don't deflect them
on me.
Told his wife
he's been getting some strange.
She kicked his adulterous tuchus
to the curb.
Seriously, you told her?
Yes, I told her.
But no, she did not
kick me to the curb.
We stayed up late talking.
We're going to continue
taing.
Much like house
should be doing
with his mother right now.
(Foreman)
anybody read chinese?
otherwise, we have no idea
what these doctors did to her.
Kutner,
you're sort of asian, right?
Get it translated.
What about
meckel's diverticulum?
If the surgeons didn't remove
the diverticulum,
it can cause pain,
bleeding.
Too high up
for a colonoscopy.
Ct could Miss it.
Ultrasound's fastest.
And since I'm fastest
with theltrasound...
House, let me do
the ultrasound.
You need to deal with your dad
and stop--
I'm not deflecting because
i'm avoiding something deep.
I'm deflecting because
i'm avoiding something shallow.
Seriously, I'm fine.
I didn't even likehe man.
(House)
no meckel's.
Were you there for the rice
or the reeducation camps?
I was there to track down
my biological parents.
Like a salmon returning
to the stream where it was born.
Did you become whole again,
or did you get eaten by bears?
Eyenied my existence.
[coughing]
four parts,
and not one of them taught you
to cover your mouth.
Oh, my god!
Itooks like
they cut you in half.
Doctor, we're her parents.
I'm just a technician.
Her doctors will be by later.
You can schmooze then.
Can you let them kno
that we, uh,
we went by her apartment
and collected
all her mecation.
I'm a technician
and a doctor.
You went through
my apartment?
We found alcohol.
We thought you'd quit.
Did her drinking
cause this?
no.
Can you tell her it did?
Lirice root.
Uh, no, thanks
i'm good.
I threw it to you
for a reason.
That's what
the chinese doctors gave her.
It contains glycyrrhizin.
They were treating her
for sars?
Not very effectively.
But sars explains e cough,
causes hypoperfusion,
which explai
it's perfect.
Lung invvement
isn't very severe.
Okay, well,
so calit "ars."
Start her on ribavirin
and interferon.
Soy about your father.
I'm not.
Are we done emoting now?
If there's anything
I can do, just--
You know, you're right.
I don't think
I can sleep alone tonight.
And you can tell me that
that is liqu vicodin.
Wee giving i.g. Shots
to everyone
who came in contact
with your patient.
Shockingly, none
of the nurses volunteered
to ainister yours.
It goes better
in a large muscle.
Drop your pants.
You know, I usually pay
tens of dollars
to hear that.
[uips fly]
the funel's tomorrow.
My mom called you?
There is 3:40 flight
out of newark.
If you leave now, you can be
in lexington tonight.
Your mother wants you
to deliver a eulogy.
"eulogy."
From the greek for "good word."
Now, if she asked me
to deliver a bastardogy,
i'd be happy to--
Then be a grown-up.
Call your mother back
and tell her that
you're sick with grief,
but you're too busy
to be ther
she knows when I'm lying.
Then start writing
(nicole)
they yanked my brother
and sister o of college.
Can you please tell them
i'm not dying?
You have sars.
I'm wearing a mask.
It's a big deal.
Cut 'em some slack.
But I am gon be okay, right?
That's what
all this stuff is for.
We're gonna need the names
and numbs
of everyone
you came in contact with
here and in china.
Flight numbers, dates...
That doctor that
I coughed all over...
Is he gonna be all right?
So far he's fine.
Uh-unh! It's back.
This is where the pain
all started.
[Pained groans]
ow!
she's tachycardic.
Get a crash cart in here!
[nicole groaning in pain]
what's going on?
I need to know what's going on.
That's my daughter.
Unh! Aah!
[crying out]
her liver's failing.
It's not sars.
I am not doing this
because I care.
(house)
cuddy drugged me.
She...
My mom didn't call cuddy.
She called you.
I knew youcouldn't stay away
I knew you loved me
too much.
I'm doing this
for your mom.
I'm not doing this at all.
If there were something
to be done,
I would have done it
in the year he spent dying.
You took my vicodin?!
I'm in pain.
One?!
So the vicodin is my leash.
One'll take the edge off,
but it won't give me
enough relief
for an escape
back to plainsboro.
[Hanson's mmmbop playing
as ring tone]
where's my phone?
* *
That's the team.
It's their ring tone.
* *
Forget it.
The patient's ood is
on your has.
* *
[Ring tone stops]
[foreman over cell phone]
house? Youhere?
i'being held
against my will.
Call the police!
nicole had a clot
in theepatic vein.
Chase sucked it out,
saved her liver.
No signs of a tumor
or venous malformations.
Nothing that could cause--
She's an addict.
Drugs and alcohol wouldn't--
She's a smoker.
Combine smoking with any one
of a dozen genetic disorders,
and she's a clotting machine.
Multiple blood clotsould
tie together bowel ischemia,
lungs, and the liver.
(Foreman)
we need to pinpoint
which defect s has
so we can start her
on the right anticoagulant.
Draw her blood--let's find out
which genetic ft
her genetic parents
gave her.
Thanks for calling.
My ring tone for you
is dancing queen, by abba.
Nicole?
I need to pee.
Over at the next stop.
I'll just pee on the floor.
You bought used oomats?
th is brilliant.
There's a rest stop
in five miles.
Cane.
The restroom's right there.
You can make it
on your own.
I suppose I could talk
about the summer
he decided he wasn't speaking
to me.
Two months,
not one word.
Anything he wanted to say,
he typed up
and slipped under
my bedroom door.
You don't want to say anything,
don't say anything, but go.
Tell your mom you're sad
for her.
Just by being there,
i'd be lying.
She wants to think,
for a moment,
that she had a happy family.
So give her a gift--
lie!
Give me my cane...
I'll go to the damn funeral.
I said I'd go to the funeral.
I didn't say when.
We have these two categories:
inside and outside.
Patients stay inside.
Then, when they're better,
we let them go outside.
Thanks.
But they don't
let you smoke inside.
So why don't you
go back there
and give me five minutes
outside?
Make a fist.
It's such a beautiful day,
we thought we'd do
all our doctorg outside.
People stare at me any time
i'm out with my family.
It's like a puzzle.
"which one of these things
doesn't belong?"
belonging's overrated.
I was adopted by a white family
when I was nine.
I like being different.
The view's better
from the outside looking in.
Must be easier to be different
when you're a success.
Is that a problem?
This is why
we prefer inside.
You actually keep a flashlight
that doesn't need batteries
in the trunk?
Next to the jacket,
emergey water,
nail clippers,
tobrush,
space blanket--
When things go wrong,
I like to be rea.
Will you...please
hold the flashlight
for a minute?
[deep sigh]
you know,
those aren't just
my car keys.
My house keys are
on there too.
Amber gave me that key chain.
No, she didn't.
Not unless your pet name
for her was "volvo."
[whirring]
a man who would lie about a gift
from a dead girlfriend...
Is probably responding
to a childish,
pointless act of petulance.
The struggle to resist
one's capts
is never pointless.
[Heavy accent]
viva la resistance!
well, I hate to break it
to you, che,
but simple delay won't work.
Your mother will hold
the funeral till we get there.
My father was a punctual man,
beholden to time.
Two minutes late for dinner,
you didn't eat.
My mother would never
disresct him
by starting the funeral late.
Yeah, ye, u clearly have
no issues to work through.
Come on, forget the keys.
Call a lksmith.
We'll go inside and play
"guess that smell"
with the truckers
while we're waiting.
Join me on the dark side.
The dark side's done,
house.
I'm delivering you
to your mother,
and that's it.
I have moved on.
What do you think house
would send,
the "gentle comfort" arrangement
or the "warm thoughts" bouquet?
I mean,  he wasn't an ass.
Send one of those giant cookies
shaped like a coffin.
His mom would believe
it was from him.
I didn't tell yo
so you could send anything.
Just wanted you to know
the extent
to which the man
is disconnected
from the human race.
Took a six-pack of ffp
to stop the oozing.
She's bleeding and clotting?
Plus schistocytes
on her smear means it's dic,
which means she's got cancer.
She's young.
It could be leukemia.
Normal wbc makes tha
less likely.
The belly pain points
toward a g.i. Tumor.
House already did
an ultrasound.
He wasn't looking for a tumor.
Go run a ct.
(Chase)
I don't buy it.
Ct can find small
testinal cancers
that an ultrasound--
I don't buhouse.
When my father died,
I wound up killing a patient.
And I hated the man.
Whatever house says
or doesn't say,
i'm sure the guy's a mess.
Soe was a bastard.
He was still your father.
You're biologically programmed
to have feelings for him.
No, I'm not.
Feelings aren'rational.
I know you have trouble
with anything
that can't be antified
and counted.
He's not my biological father.
I figured it out
when I was 12.
Of course.
You were a brilliant,
socially isolated 12-year-old,
and you create
a parallel universe
in which your life
doesn't suck.
I lookt the facts.
First of all, he waseployed
on training exercises
off okinawa
ring the time
I had to be conceived.
Ansince
you're 150 years old,
air travel was impossible.
His second toe is longer
than his big toe.
Mine isn't.
This is sad.
You don't believe
your mother screwed around--
I have a distinctive
red birthmark on my scp
that matches a certain friend
of the family.
If you believed
this story,
you wouldn't be telling me
about his birthmarks.
You'd be telling me
out the genetic testing
you had done.
And since
you haven't mentioned it,
obviously,
you didn't do it.
Because you don't want to--
House, what are you doing?
Get your--get off the--
There's a cop!
[police siren wailing]
uh-oh.
Nicole, lie still.
This'll only take
a few seconds.
(Taub)
one millimeter cut
through upper abdomen.
She was adopted
when the parents thought
ey couldn't have kids.
She took the message
as "thanks for playing,
but we have
our real children now."
And the real children
probably think they're accidents
while she was hand-picked.
Everody's got problems
with their parts.
She's an addict.
Something went wrong.
And it has to be the parents?
Magnifying pancreas.
I'm not saying
the parents screwed up.
You're saying you like her.
So you don't want her faults
to be hefault.
But they're someone's fault,
and the only other people
you know are--
[machine beeping]
I think we may need
to call house again.
(House)
you lost track
ofour speed?
I think that was
hitler's excuse.
Lost track of e jews.
No one held him
responsible.
I'm not playing house.
You were protecting me.
Anybody in their right mind
would have ratted me out.
I'm just trying
to speed things along.
You are going
this funeral.
[Hanson's mmmbop playing
as ring tone]
* *
make it fast.
I don't want to miss
the anal cavity search.
Looks like a mass
in the pancreas.
[Hou over phone]
not to me. This is radio.
Ani want a full
play-by-play.
It's fluid-filled.
Would you get out
of the car, please, sir?
Offir, if you
want to give me a ticket,
I totally understand.
Just get out of the car, sir.
Cyst?
(foreman)
large cyst.
Something going on there?
Wilson's getting arrested.
(House)
how large?
(house)
suv sized,
or mid-rangeedan?
Seriously?
What'd you do?
I'm obviously joking.
If wilson was getting handcuffed
on the hood of his car,
would I be carrying on
a differential?
Diameter is at lea
eight centimeters.
[whistles]
ist in the tail
or in the head?
(Foreman)
the head.
You too, sir.
Out of the car.
We've got a construction site.
A steamroller is plowing--
Out now.
No can
(officer)
james evan wilson,
there's a warrant
r your arrest in louisiana.
What are the traits
of a steamroller?
Powerful.
Maybe pancreatic cancer.
Great idea,
except the only symptom
it mches up with
is being steamrollerish.
You don't think house
is onto something?
I think he thought
he had an idea.
I also think his metaphors
are tough enough to decipher
after he's said them.
We need to be focusing
on the medicine.
No answer.
There's not gonna be
an answer.
They've been arrested.
He was joking.
He reacted to the size
and location.
That's what we should be
focusing on.
Not playing mad libs
while our patient's
exploding noun destroys
her life-sustaining noun.
I'll try to get wilson
on the line.
What if it's not
how a steamroller works,
but what it does?
clears things.
This is a waste of time.
[Hanson's mmmbop playing
as ring tone]
* *
I need that phone call.
I'm a doctor,
and when someone tries
to call you three times,
it's code for
"pick up the damn phone
before someone dies."
I'm sure there's
other smart doctors.
You'd be surprised.
You told me
you'd taken care of this.
I did.
First words
you ever said to me.
I took care of it.
You must've screwed up someh.
sir?
Not to hurry you,
but we need to be
at a funeral--
Nobody is going anywhere
or taking any phone calls
till I hear back
from louisiana.
It's a really old warrant.
Isn't there a statute
of limitations
on this kind of thing?
It's suspended
when you flee the state.
I didn't flee the state.
I left the state.
Because I don't live
in the state.
And the charges were
just so minor...
"vandalism,
destruction of property,
assault."
there is
a simple explanation.
There was a medical convention
in new orleans...
You don't need
to explain to me.
I was fresh out of med school.
I dn't knoanybody
at the convention.
You heard the man,
wilson.
You don't have to explain.
I am not gonna sit here
wasting time
just so you can avoid
your father's funeral!
He's my father.
I have the right
to avoid his funeral.
Not if your mother's alive,
you don't.
Okay...
Explain.
(Chase)
did house react
to the eight centimeters?
he whistled.
It's huge.
Anyone would think so.
House doesn't whistle
because he's impressed.
It means he wasn't
expecting it.
It means he changed his mind
at that point.
(Chase)
a single super-sized cyst
ruled out a diffuse process
like scleroderma or lupus.
Rule out diffuse process, you're
stuck with single process
affecting just the pancreas.
Gallstones
or pancreatic divisum.
Whever he asked next
would have narrowed that down.
He asked about location.
Heads it's gallstones,
tails it's divisum.
It's at the head.
She's got gallstones.
The steamroller means
potholes--
Relax. We got it.
You figured out
she's got gallstones?
I was at the hotel bar
trying to unwind,
have a drink.
There was this guy
who kept playing
billy joel's
leave a tender moment alone
on the jukebox.
Leave a tender moment
is a good song.
It's a great song.
He was out of line.
Not as good as scenes
from an italian restaurant
or...
So I--I asked the man
to stop, polity.
Yeah, you yelled politely.
I was polite
the first couple of times,
but courtesy made no impression
on this ass.
So I threw a bottle
into the mirror,
which successfully conveyed
my message.
And smashed a ten-foot
antique mirror.
And set an emple
to two other patrons
who threw shot glasses.
I had nothing to do
with that fight.
The assault charge
was totally bogus.
And I paid
for the mirror.
I think I have
the picture.
I assume you're the guy
who was playing the song.
No, I was the guy
who bailed him out.
That's how we met.
I was in jail.
This guy was
a total stranger to you,
and you bailed him out?
It was a boring convention.
Had to have somebody
to drink with.
(Wilson)
and there's the foundation
of our entire friendship.
If you hadn't been bored
one weekend,
it wouldn't even exi.
Hey, there were 3,000 people
at that convention.
You were the one I thought
wasn't boring.
That says something.
It also says something
that you lied to me
about getting
the charges dropped!
I got a lawyer.
He cut a deal.
You didn't call the guy?
You ve to show up
at the arraignment.
Everybody knows that.
Everybody with
your misdemeanor experience.
You can go.
What?!
He--he's a fugitive
from justice.
That whole story was lies.
Stabbed a man.
Louisiana doesn't want to pay
to get you back.
Forget louisiana.
He was driving recklessly
through your comatose village.
Do theput lead
in the jelly doughnuts here?
Stop acting
like such an ingrate
and go pay your respects
to your father.
The ct confirmed
gallstones.
Normally not dangerous.
Almost everyone has them.
But sometimes...
They kill you?
yup.
Unless I take 'em out.
We do it laproscopically.
Um...
How long has her urine
been brown?
Kidney's were fine
this afternoon.
They're not now.
It's not the gallstones.
(house)
well, of course
it's not gallstones.
Who thought
it was gallstones?
You said "steamroller."
I also said
"construction site."
Gallstones could cause
a pancreatic cyst.
Just turn around.
The thing is
twhours over already,
and that's the third time
we passed that colonial
with the cross bni
out front.
I'm not lost.
I'm not talking
about what caused the cyst.
I'm talking
about what the cyst caused.
Everything.
Cysts are symptoms,
not diagnoses.
Unless it's a multiple ct,
with conctions
to other organs--
Like a steamroller.
That's a long road down
to the kidneys.
How do we prove it?
Won't be visible in a scan.
Chase isn't gonna go
groping around
when she's got kidney failure.
Bubbs.
Is that your new
stripper name?
Yes. And also,
we inject bubbles into the cys
and foll where ty drift.
If they end up
in the other organs,
we know you're right,
cut it out, she's fine.
Bubbles is right.
Go echo.
I'm not lost.
Nicole, you gotta stay still.
I'm--i'm nervous.
You'reot nervous.
It's the dts, isn't it?
I haven't had a drink
since I got here.
Good heavens,
we haven't missed it after all.
It's like the end
of christmas carol.
[sighs]
i'm so glad you're here.
Oh, it's a load
off of my mind
just to see you.
Thank you, james.
Mom, how could you delay
the funeral?
Honey, your dad is dead.
He's not going to care.
Do you know what
you're going to say?
I don't know.
Just let the minister
orne of his buddies
from the corps...
You're talking.
I don't care
that you didn't like him.
He was your father,
and he loved you.
The war is over, greg.
Please do this for me.
Stop looking so worried.
I know he's
gonna make me proud.
I'm sure you know him better
than I do.
Her liver's
been compromised.
And the dts will cause
her muscles
to continue to twitch,
even underedation.
We need to paralyze her
to do this procedure.
I wanted to stop.
A phenarbital coma
willot only low us
to inject the cyst,
'll treat the dts.
When she wakes up,
e won't be in withdrawal.
We've seen her
through withdrawal before.
through everything.
We've been supportive,
we've been combative.
We've picked her up from bars
in the middle of the night.
We've let her
spend the night in jail.
I used to say
it'd be okay.
That I'd get it together.
I don't say that anymore.
Let's make you healthy.
Then we'll worry
about making you sober.
The lord is my shepherd,
i shall not want...
I am not talking.
We were strangers
who shared some geography
30 years ago.
Right, he had no influence
on you at all.
The father who was compulsive
about punctuality.
His issue.
Which I deliberately made
not my issue.
Thereby making it your issue.
Compulsively showing up
four hours late,
ignoring discipline,
ignoring rules.
Oh, god, he's here.
Who's here?
The one you're pretending
is yr father?
Nice pick.
He looks like sean connery.
So back when you
were devising this fantasy,
did you tell your father:
"dad, I fuse to recognize
your existence because
I have chosen james bond
as my dad"?
(Minister)
let us pray.
I used different words.
What?!
Hearing your own son
hates you so much
he's replaced you
in his mind?
That's gotta suck.
How did he take it?
I already told you.
(Minister)
amen.
He didn't speak to me
for a summer.
It means more to me than--
An I can say
to have all of you
here today.
And w,h,
our son gregory
would ke to say
a few words.
Greg?
[sighs]
there's a lot of people
here today.
Inuding some
from the corps.
And I notice tha
every one of them is
either my father rank
or higher.
And that doesn't
surprise me.
Because if the test
of a man
is how he treats those
he has power over,
it was a test
my father failed.
This man you're eage
to pay homage to,
he was incapable of admitting
any int of view but his own.
He punished failure,
and he did not accept
anything lesthan--
He loved doing what he did.
He saw his work
as some kind of...
Sacred calling.
More important
than any personal relationship.
Maybe if he'd been
a better father,
i'd be a better son.
But I am what I am
because of him...
For better or foworse.
And I just--just wish--
[voice breaks]
[whispers]
put it back.
Well, he's
not gonna Miss it.
I'm done enablg.
You can't even let them
put him in the ground
without making it serve
your agenda?
(House)
you real want to do this
in front oeverybody?
you wanna punish me
or them?
How can I
still feel surprise?
You would take,
even this,
a moment of real
human grief,
and turn it into a farce.
Oh, cut the crap.
You enjoy what I do.
I never had to force you.
You like coming along
for the ride.
Yes, that's why
i'm cheering you on no
this is about you needing
to be prepared for the worst.
So you become
an oncologist.
No surprises there.
Worst happens all the time.
But amber, she was young
and healthy.
Her death came
out of nowhere.
Don't bring amber
into this.
And you weren't ready.
That makes you angry.
The world sucks, and y didn't
have time to brace youelf.
What happened out there
is your show!
You' scared to death
of losing anyone that matters.
So you dump the person
who matters the most to you!
I'm not scared to death.
I'm moving forward!
Because no one
can take away from you
what you no longer have.
[wilson gives derisive laugh]
your father's death is
about you.
Amber's death is
I can'imagine why someone
wouldn't want to be your friend!
Admit it, you're ary
and you're scared
of losing me.
I'm not angry, I'm not scared.
Admit it.
I'm not afraid.
I've lost people.
It happens.
Admit it. Admit it!
What are you, five?
Stop repeating--
Admit it. Admit it.
Admit it.
Come on, admit it.
Admit it!
unh!
Still not boring.
(wilson)
did u know
I was gonna do that?
Because I didn't know
I was gonna do that.
I know you have trouble
losing people.
In new orleans,
I saw you carrying
this express package
around the conference.
And you wouldn't let it go,
but you wouldn't open it.
So I peeked
at the return address.
Diamond, fairbairn.
Divorce attorneys.
Your first wife
had just served you with papers.
Did you know that
when you bailed me out?
Were you...
Doing something niceor me?
What did I say
about being boring?
Wewe your mom
an apology.
[ringing]
hello?
It's house.
Ouse over speakerphone]
how'd the bubble test go?
the problem wasn't
the cyst.
It's advanced dilated
cardiomyopathy.
We did a three-dimensial echo.
Showed a mass
in the left atrium.
(Kutner)
looks like an atrial moma,
but the ultrasound images
are a little grainy,
so it's hard to tell.
hous
The images aren't grainy.
They sure look grainy.
I've seen picturesf you
where you look tall.
It's iron overload.
Creates speckles on the image,
makes it look grainy.
Also makes her pancreas fa,
her blood clot,
and her intestine--
Atrial myxoma is more lily.
Mri for a better view.
And call me back
and tell me you're embarrassed
because my eyesight is better
500 miles away.
I need a phone number.
[telephone ringing]
[speaking native language]
i'm a doctor in new jersey,
treating one of your clients.
A young woman looking
for her biological parents.
You know, you could just wait
for the mri
to have your cursity
satisfied.
What person
who is nothing like me
are you saying that to?
Did the parents look tan?
The disease she has
is genetic,
which means
they shod have it too.
They don't look more tan
than anyone else.
Discolored teeth?
They're farmers--the village
doesn't even have a dentist.
Right. Thanks.
But if it matters,
i'm not convinced
they were her parents.
Why not?
Because they said
they have no daughter.
The man was adamant,
and the woman seemed confused
and frightened.
Thank you.
Differential.
Say you're a middle-aged
inese woman...
Fine.
Say it.
I'm a middle-aged
chinese woman.
Girl comes to you,
says that she's
your long-lost daughter.
Why would yo
be frightened?
i'm frightened
because she's a threat?
Maybe she knows something?
She hasn't seen you since
shwas an infant.
Maybe an inheritance issue.
They're peasants.
Her very presence is
a threat.
She--
What year was she born?
'83.
She's not supposed
be alive.
China introduced
the one-child policy in 1979.
Say they didn't want
a girl.
They tried to kill her.
Maybe the baby doesn't die.
Maybe the father panics
or regrets it.
Takes the baby
to an orphanage.
Maybe he doesn't tell
his wife.
Who freaks out
like she's seen a ghost
25 years later
when the girl shows up.
Why does attempted murder
om 25 years ago
suddenly become relevant
to her health now?
Maybe they gave her
something toxic.
It would have to be
fat soluble.
This is fun, isn't it?
Let me see the mri.
We don't have one.
She started vomiting
as soon as we started the scan.
Then let her vomit
through the mri.
That'shanurses are for.
Her parents
tried to kill her.
I don't know how,
but I know it caused her
to get sick 25 years later
trying to lift a buddha.
Explain.
I already had this conversation
with wilson--just go with it.
Poison?
Buddha
wouldn't make it worse.
Maybe the weight
stressed her back, which--
Makes sense if she's never
lifted anything in her life.
She actually didn't
get sick
till she tried lifting it
that second time.
I'm guessing
the weight changed.
Anybody have taub's
pager number?
What's up?
Maybe give him a call.
If he tosses that switch
on the mri, she's dead.
X-ray her brain.
(House)
pins.
Push them rough the soft
foanelle of an infant,
you skewer the bin,
and the hair hides
the entry wounds.
It's the perfect crime.
She's had them in her
all these years.
What changed
at the temple?
Same thing that changed
in the mri.
(house)
shockingly, not all
religious leaders are honest.
I'm guessing
these particular monks
are bilking the faithful
by pushing a magnet
up buddha's butt.
There's another one
under the table
that'll repel or attract,
depending on how youhift them.
When she picked up
that magnet,
it med one of the pins deeper
into the sympathetic
nervous center of her brain.
This sent a signal
through the nerves
to the blood vessels
in her small intestines,
whiccaused the symptoms
in china
and in the giant magnet
we call an m.
She'lucky.
We're all screwed up
by o parents.
She's got documentation.
The pins will be
removed surgically,
and she'll be fine.
We'll wake her from the coma
after the operation.
Is there any way
you could not tell her?
Please.
She's fragile.
She desperately wanted
to know her biological parents.
For her to find out
that they wanted her dead...
I don't know what
that'll do to he
she may not be as fragile
as you think.
We know our daughter.
See this pin here?
It's been pressing directly
on her addiction cter.
It's not her fault.
And it's definitely
not your fault.
She's not
who you think she is.
[knocking]
I hear your paent's
gonna be all right.
Is that why you're here?
A colleague checking up
on a patient?
Something in' on?
I'm celebrating.
My mom hated him too.
Your dna test showed no match?
That's incredible.
At the age of 12,
you actually figured out
your father wasn't
your birth fathe
that's what you wanted,
wasn't it?
Why should it depress you?
It doesn't depress me.
Doesn't make
any difference at all.
That's what depresses me.
Well, I gues
nobody gets to choose
who their parents are.
[inhales deeply]
i'm not even sure anymore
if we get to choose
who our friends are.
I spoke with cuddy.
She hasn't filled
my positioyet.
If you're coming back
just because you're attracted
to the shine of my neediness...
I'd be okay with that.
I'm coming back
because you're right.
That strge, annoying trip
we just took
was the most fun I've had
since amber died.
You hungry?
Wilson.
Yeah?
My dad's dead.
Yeah.
My sympathies.
Captioning by dave l
at captionmax
www.captionmax.com
(woman)
joseph!
Joe!
you're gonna be late!
, look at yourself.
Tuck in your shirt.
Put a comb through your hair,
for god's sake.
Dara's son,
always takes care
of his appearance.
[door slams]
meager.
It's mee-gar.
Late again and you're making
personal calls?
Oh, no, I'm--
Who's this?
Nobody.
She your girlfriend?
No, she came with the phone.
What are you stalking
this girl?
no.
[phone snaps shut]
[hissing sound
are you kidding me?
Aw, come on.
Unbelievable.
Two in one week.
Your sweep's leaving,
meager.
Get on it...
Or get another gig
[rock music]
* *
usic softens]
hi, how are you today?
And we're still on
for the regional manager's
meeting
oh.
tomorrow at 4:00?
Great.
Yeah, thank you.
Okay, great.